[
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$CLUP",
  "PROBLEM": "- CL$$CLUP WAS WAITING FOR THE IN CONDITION 'CTO-RUN-CL$$CLUP 0328' EVEN AFTER COMPLETION OF CL$$CLU1. PROCESS - JOB CL$$CLU1 RUNS CLU1 TRANSITION IN CICSD TO SWAP 24X7 FILES. AT THE COMPLETION OF THE CLU1 TRANSACTION, IT ADDS \"+**CLGOODP CLU3** SWAP SUCCESSFULLY COMPLETED\" MESSAGE IN THE CONSOLE (CAN BE CHECKED IN Q.LOG) CL$$CLUP WAITS FOR CL$$CLU1-ENDED-OK & CTO-RUN-CL$$CLUP BOTH, BECAUSE WE WANT TO MAKE SURE NOT ONLY CL$$CLU1 JOB RAN FINE BUT CLU1 TRANS ALSO RAN FINE IN CICSD. CONTROL-O RULE (CICSMSGS > CLGOODP CL) LOOK FOR THE STRING 'CLGOODP CLU3' IN THE CONSOLE AND ONCE FOUND, IT ADDS THE CONDITION 'CTO-RUN-CL$$CLUP ODAT+' IN THE DATABASE WHICH FINALLY TRIGGERS CL$$CLUP. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "- TODAY, CLU1 RAN AFTER 8 O'CLOCK AND CONTROL-O RULE RAN AROUND 09:02, THAT'S A NEW DAY MEANS ODATE IS CHANGED TO 0329 AND SO RULE ADDED THE COND CTO-RUN-CL$$CLUP FOR ODATE 0329 INSTEAD OF 0328. SO, CL$$CLUP FOR ODATE 0328 WAS STILL WAITING FOR THIS CONDITION WHEREAS THIS CONDITION GOT REMOVED FROM CL$$CLUP ODATE 0329. ",
  "SOLUTION": "ASKED PCD TO REMOVE IN CONDITION 'CTO-RUN-CL$$CLUP 0328' FROM CL$$CLUP 0328. AND, REMOVE THE CONDITION 'CTO-RUN-CL$$CLUP 0329' FROM DATABASE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0103",
  "PROBLEM": "- JOB CL$$0103 ABENDED WITH S01C AT STEP0020. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "-POLICY 0720782920 WAS RESTORED IN TODAY'S NIGHTLY CYCLE BUT DATA WAS NOT RESTORED CORRECTLY. DATA ON CL.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY HAD ALL ZEROS AFTER KEY ..$.07207829200000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000 TEMP WORK AROUND: - INFORMED OPS TO EXECUTE THE RESTORE JOBS CL$$R060 AND CL$$RCL4. - INFORMED OPS TO EXECUTE THE CL$$SEGD JOB TO RESTORE THE POLICY FROM SB BACKUP 0720782920. - INFORMED OPS TO RERUN THE ABENDED JOB CL$$0103 FROM TOP. - JOB ENDED OK. SUSPECT PROBLEM HAD TO DO WITH RECENT DB2 V12 UPGRADE AS OFFSHORE ALSO OBSERVED THAT CL$$POLX WAS ALSO ABENDING AFTER GOING INTO LOOP. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAWG RAN OPTIM BINDS AGAIN WITH UPDATED QUALIFIER (SYSOPT FOR DB2P) NEXT, OFFSHORE RERAN CL$$POLX TO RE-EXTRACT 0720782920 CL$$POLX ENDED OK THEN RAN CL$$POLR SUCCESSFUL,THEN CL$$0103 WAS ABLE TO END OK WITH THIS POLICY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "INC0529330",
  "PROBLEM": "OPERATIONS CHANGED THE MAINFRAME TIME FOR DAYLIGHT SAVINGS TIME 1 WEEK EARLY. EARLY RUNNING ABC JOBS WERE FIRST IMPACTED & OBSERVED. COGNIZANT MADE THE ON REQUEST TECH JOB TECHDSTS THAT UPDATED DAYLIGHT SAVINGS TIME TO SPRING AHEAD A SCHEDULED JOB AND HAD IT ON THE SCHEDULE FOR 3\/6\/21. SO JOB RAN ON 3\/6\/21 A WEEK TOO EARLY INSTEAD OF ON 3\/14\/21. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "- CURRENT TIME WAS 9AM, MAINFRAME TIME WAS 10AM NOTIFIED TRINA TO CALL A MIM WHICH WAS SET TO P2. ALTHOUGH AS OF MONDAY MORNING NO ONLINE FAILURES, THE RISK WAS TOO HIGH TO LET IT GO TILL THE NEXT WEEKEND AND HAVE PCD CORRECT WITH SATURDAY NIGT IPL. RISKS-UNKNOWN BATCH FAILURES SINCE WE HAVE NEVER ENCOUNTERED THIS BEFORE. RISKS-CYBERLIFE USES DATE\/TIME STAMP IN ITS DATA EXCHANGE TRANACTIONS AND NO WAY TO TELL IF REVERSALS WOULD HAVE ISSUE. RISKS-CL PROCESS TO AUTOMATICALLY ROLL TRADES TO THE NEXT DAY IF PROCESSED AFTER 4 PM. RISKS-THE APPLICATION FRAMEWORK, MQAF.AFAGCLG, HAS A KEY OF THE INSERT TIMESTAMP. THE APPLICATION FRAMEWORK IS USED BY REPS, COMP, ALS, EDS, AND OTHER APPLICATIONS. (CAN'T GO BACKWARDS IN TIME) RISKS-MANUAL INTERVENTION ON THE ABC JOBS THAT FEED INTO EAS. THEY RUN AT 5AM AND 10AM. BOTH RUNS COULD END UP MISSING PAYMENTS THAT THAT SHOULD BE GOING OUT BECAUSE THEY RAN EARLY. RISKS-ABC$0010 - SET TO RUN AT 5 AM, ABC$0011 - SET TO RUN AT 10 AM. THESE PICK UP FILES TO FEED EAS - WHICH IS HOW WE PAY FOLKS. THAT NEEDS TO CHANGE THIS WEEK IF WE DELAY THE FIX TILL THIS WEEKEND. CONSIDERATIONS FOR JOBS RUNNING DURING THE DAY CL$$0035 8AM,10AM,NOON,2PM,4PM,7PM CL$$RLPN 8AM,10AM,NOON,2PM,4PM,6PM CL$$0021 11AM,1PM,4PM (ASSESSED THEY WERE RUNNING 1 HOUR EARLIER BUT NOT DESIRED) TRINA RAN A FORECAST REPORT FOR 3\/8 AND 3\/9 OTHER TEAMS BROUGHT INTO MIM: ERIC MOODY-TURN OFF STP TO STOP INCOMING E-APP KIM CALVIN-FOR WEB, VINTAGE WOULD NOT BE UPDATED, NO POLICY WOULD BE IN OSO. KIM LOOKING AT PUTTING A MESSAGE OUT THROUGH MESSAGING APP. ACCOUNT SERVICES FOR RS ARE NOT IMPACTED -KIM ALSO ASKED ABOUT THE TIMING OF PLAN CHANGES IN CYBERLIFE. IF THEY OCCUR AFTER 4 PM DO THEY AUTOMATICALLY ROLL TO THE NEXT DAY? LINDA KIENTZ-DID NOT THINK TRADES WOULD BE AN ISSUE AS LONG AS WE MEET 4:45AM DEADLINE. SHANNON INGRAM-MQ IMPACT OF DOING NOTHING: -POSSIBLE BATCH FAILUES -UNKNOWN IMPACT TO TRADE TRX -THERE IS A TIMESTAMP MISMATCH ON THE MAINFRAME. -REPORTS AND FILES MAY BE RECEIVED 1 HOUR EARLIER THAN EXPECTED AND WITH INCORRECT TIMESTAMPS. IMPACT OF TAKING DOWN MF WHICH ALSO TAKES DOWN MQ: -ALL MAINFRAME APPLICATIONS DOWN. -ACCOUNT SERVICES INDIVIDUAL POLICIES WOULD NOT AVAILABLE -VINTAGE OSO POLICIES WOULD NOT BE AVAILABLE -GLIS WOULD BE UNAVAILABLE TO ELI LILLY -RLRP AND TDA LOANS WILL NOT BE AVAILABLE -CALL CENTER WILL NOT BE ABLE TO PULL UP CUSTOMER DATA WHILE THE SYSTEMS ARE DOWN BETWEEN 4:15PM AND 6PM. -EB FINANCE WOULD NOT BE IMPACTED -ACCOUNT SERVICES FOR RS WOULD NOT BE IMPACTED -SYSTEM ALERTS HAS BEEN SENT BY SERVICE DESK -SITESCOPE ALERTS WILL BE TRIGGERED BY PPLUS BEING DOWN (ASK FOR IT TO BE IN MAINTENANCE MODE FOR THE REST OF THE DAY) SIMON HAD TO TALK TO FINANCIAL JOAN GRAHAM, ILFS OPS AND CLAIMS MANAGER TO GET BUY IN TO TAKE DOWN APPLICATIONS AND THEY DID NOT WANT MAINFRAME BROUGHT DOWN NO SOONER THAN 4PM DUE TO HIGH VOLUME AT CALL CENTER ON MONDAYS. BASED ON ABOVE RISK\/ANALYSIS, IPL HAS TO BE DONE NOW AND CANNOT WAIT TILL SATURDAY AND CANNOT BE DONE DURING WORKING HOURS BECAUSE CALL CENTER HAS TO BE OPERATIONAL TILL 6PM. WHILE MAINFRAME IS DOWN, OPS WILL RUN A FALLBACK JOB CALL TECHDSTF TO CORRECT THE TIME. ",
  "SOLUTION": "AT 5PM, 1 HOUR BEFORE TAKEDOWN HAVE COGNIZANT START SETTING THE QR TO ZERO AND ONLY ALLOW JOBS THAT ARE QUICK AND CRITICAL TO RUN, SO ALL CURRENT RUNNING BATCH JOBS HAVE TIME TO COMPLETE AND NO NEW BATCH JOBS CAN START RUNNING. (THIS AFFECTS TEST AND PRODUCTION JOBS) HAVE PCD TAKE DOWN THE NON PRODUCTION CICS REGIONS. NOTIFY DEVELOPERS OF THIS OCCURING AT 5PM. M.AUL.SYS.AMS.CORE.MAINFRAME M.AUL.IND.SYSTEMSCYBERLIFEREGIONS M.AUL.SYS.CONTRACTOR_DEVELOPERS.CORE M.AUL.SYS.ENTERPRISEAPPS.CORE (NEED TO NOTIFY SQAS TOO-GET THEIR MAILING LIST) TRINA\/RAJ WILL MAKE SURE ANY REQUESTS TO RUN MAINFRAME JOBS (FROM SNOW FORMS) BE HELD BY PCD ONCE THIS PROCESS STARTS. HAVE COGNIZANT PUT THE MAINFRAME MONITORS INTO MAINTENANCE MODE TILL 8 PM OR WHEN TRINA ASKS THEM TO TURM THEM BACK ON. EXCEPTION-PPLUS MONITOR IS CONTROLLED BY DISTRIBUTED JOBS HAVING RUN (VCSXSTOP). SINCE NO ONE NEW HOW TO PUT THIS INTO MAINTENANCE MODE JUST IGNORE THE SITESCOPE EMAILS FOR PPLUS. IPL THE MAINFRAME AT 6PM THAT DAY. BECAUSE TIME IS ADVANCE 1 HOUR, AFTER THE MAINFRAME HAS BEEN TAKEN DOWN, WE HAVE TO WAIT AT 1 HOUR BEFORE BRINING MF BACK UP TO AVOIDE DUPLICATE TRXS. VALIDATION-MAINFRAME HAS CORRECT TIME. -ONLINE APPLICATIONS WERE UP. -BILL VALIDATED MIB CONNECTION WAS STILL IN TACT. -BILL RAN TEST.CL.JCLLIB(CL$$RESP) TO GET ACTIVITY REPORT STEP0080 SYSLST HAS A REPORT OF ALL TRX THEN PULL OFF JUST THE ONES WITH U1EX OR U1CA FOR THAT DAY SO TRX CAN BE REVIEWED FOR TIMING AND PROCESSING ACCURACY. QUESTIONS-SHOULD THE INCIDENT BE P1 OR P2 AND SHOULD THE P1 START IMMEDIATELY OR AR THE START OF THE TAKE DOWN. WHO REALLY MAKES THE FINAL CALL TO TAKE MF DOWN? CONSENSUS? MAJORITY? MANAGMENT? SUPPORT TEAMS? WHAT EMAIL TO NOTIFY SQAS REGIONS COMING DOWN? LESSONS LEARNED: 1)USERS RARELY SUBMIT EXCHANGES IN OSO. BY RUNNING CL$$RESP, WE FOUND 1 POLICY EXCHANGE BY DONE BY TIM SKINNER. PROGRAM THAT CONTROLS OSO 4PM CUTOFF IS ISPWP.CL.PRD.COB(D721TRDT). WHEN THE BUSINESS DOES AN EXCHANGE AFTER 4:00, THEY DO NOT AUTOMATICALLY MAKE IT EFFECTIVE THE NEXT DAY, BECAUSE THE REQUEST MAY HAVE ARRIVED AT NOON AND THEY DIDN'T PROCESS IT UNTIL AFTER 4:00. ELAINE CONFIRMED THIS MORNING THAT TIM DID THE TRANSACTION AS OF 3\/8 AND IT PROCESSED LAST NIGHT. NO CORRECTION IS NEEDED. WHEN TRANSACTIONS ARE SUBMITTED VIA OSO, AFTER 4:00, THE LOGIC IN D721TRDT IS USED. 2)ALS (APPLICATION LOGGING SERVICE) TRANSACTION FOR THE APPLICATION FRAMEWORK DID NOT GET ENABLED\/STARTED AFTER THE MID-WEEK IPL. USED MQAF9999 AND MANAGE TO ENABLE AND START THAT TRX. 3)REMINDER THAT AT 8 PM THE APPLICATION FRAMEWORK STILL STOP MOST OF ITS TRANSACTIONS TO DO A DB2 BACKUP. SO ANY IVP, OR VALIDATION WILL HAVE TO WAIT UNTIL THAT IS DONE(AND THE TRANSACTIONS ARE ENABLED). CAN TELL MY LOOKING AT MAINVIEW, OR CICSD MQAFMSGS. 4)TIMING OF CICS REGION START UP WAS JUST PRIOR TO 8PM AND CICS AUTOMATED CLOSE\/DEALLOCATE OF FILES\/TRANSACTIONS START JUST AFTER 8PM. -SCHEDULING HAS TAKEAWAY TO DEVELOP AUTOMATED STARTUP OF ALL REGIONS SO REDUCE TIME WINDOW FROM 30 MINUTES TO ABOUT 10 MINUTES. 5)ALIS CYCLE STUCK DUE TO FILE ALLOCATED TO CICSU. BRETT MANUALLY CLOSED FILE WITH CECI SET FI(ALISEMST) CLOSE. 6)TIMING OF WHEN CICS REGIONS ARE BROUGHT BACK UP IS VERY IMPORTANT. IN THIS SPECIFIC CASE, ALL PRODUCTION REGIONS AND MOST NON PRODUCTION REGIONS WERE UP BEFORE 8PM EST WHICH ALLOWED THE NORMAL PROCESS OF CLOSE\/DISABLED TO HAPPEN JUST AFTER 8PM AND BATCH CYCLES TO START. -IF THE CICS REGIONS HAD NOT BEEN BROUGHT UP UNTIL AFTER 8PM THEN THERE IS A HUGE UNKNOWN ABOUT OF FILES AND AND TRANSACTIONS THAT WOULD HAVE TO HAVE BEEN MANUALLY CLOSED BY PCD AND COGNIZANT INFRASTRUCTURE. THIS MANUAL PROCESS COULD HAVE CAUSED HOURS OF OF DELAY IN GETTING SOME CYCLES COMPLETED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0103",
  "PROBLEM": "(FROM JESMSGLG) - +PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C1 (OPERATION) AT LOCATION 00045A IN ELEMENT CKETRGET + PSW = 078D2400 90088D9C +CKSN01 PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. PSW=078D2400 90088D9C (OPERATION +CKUB03 CURRENT POLICY 3465022590 +CKSN02 ABENDING ELEMENT CKETRGET EPA=10088940 OFFSET 00045A +CKUB07 UNABLE TO CONTINUE PROCESSING - JOB ABORTING. FROM IDIREPRT - A USER ABEND 0010 OCCURRED IN MODULE CEEPLPKA AT OFFSET X'20A604' THE ABEND OCCURRED AFTER EXECUTING MACHINE INSTRUCTION 4DE03872 (BRANCH AND SAVE) IN MODULE CKAP01V CSECT CKUB01V AT OFFSET X'6CC'. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "- IN THE FIRST RUN, JOB FAILED ON POLICY# 3465022580 WITH CLIENT ERROR. THE PROBLEM COULD NOT BE RECREATED USING CISOFF LOADLIB & JOB ENDED FINE IN UNIT REGION. SO THE POLICY WAS BYPASSED USING CLMVSKIP CARD. HOWEVER, JOB ABENDED AGAIN AT ITS NEXT POLICY# 3465022590 IN 2ND RUN. ON ANALYZING MORE, FOUND -811 SQL ERROR IN IDIREPRT WHICH INDICATES - THE RESULT OF AN EMBEDDED SELECT STATEMENT OR A SUBSELECT IN THE SET CLAUSE OF AN UPDATE STATEMENT IS A TABLE OF MORE THAN ONE ROW, OR THE RESULT OF A SUBQUERY OF A BASIC PREDICATE IS MORE THAN ONE VALUE ON CHECKING, FOUND SQL CHANGES IN PROGRAM CKCSTGET WHICH MOVED LAST NIGHT SO THEIR DEVELOPERS WERE INFORMED AND IT WAS IDENTIFIED THAT PROGRAM CKCSTGET WAS TRYING TO FETCH UNIQUE ROW FROM CLIENT_PHONE TABLE BUT DUE TO MULTIPLE ROWS IN THE TABLE FOR A SINGLE CLIENT-ID, THE SQL QUERY WAS GETTING FAILED AND CAUSING THE ABEND. IT WAS RESOLVED BY EXPIRING ADDITIONAL ROWS FROM THE ABENDING CLIENTS ",
  "SOLUTION": "- -INFORMED OPS TO EXECUTE THE RESTORE JOBS CL$$R060 AND CL$$RCL4. -AS PER CTM DOC, RENAMED THE BAD RUN GDGS CREATED IN PRIOR RUN -EXPIRED ALL THE ADDITIONAL CLIENT ROWS FROM THE CLIENT IDS. -INFORMED OPS TO RERUN THE JOB FROM TOP. -JOB ENDED-OK WITH THE ABOVE RESOLUTION. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1170",
  "PROBLEM": "- MODULE M724NOTA, CSECT CKVSAMIO, OFFSET X'356': ABEND S0C1 (OPERATION EXCEPTION) ",
  "ANALYSIS": "- IF YOU RECEIVE SOC1 ABEND IN JOB CL$$1170 FOR PROGRAM M724NOTA DUE TO AN ERROR IN CKVSAMIO THEN IT MAY BE BECAUSE M724NOTA IS TRYING TO READ PDF AND ISSUE AGE FILE VSAM FILES. IN ORDER TO CALCULATE PREMIUM FOR PREMIUM CHANGE LETTER, ONE OF THE PROGRAM (CKULIART CALLED BY M724NOTA) TRIES TO ACCESS PLAN DESCRIPTION FILE AND ISSUE AGE FILE BUT BOTH OF THESE FILE ARE NOT PRESENT IN CL$$1170. THERE SHOULDN'T BE ANY NEED FOR ACCESSING THESE FILES IF POLICY HAD CORRECT PREMIUM ALREADY. INFORM THE BUSINESS THAT THIS POLICY HAS NOT CALCULATED ITS PREMIUM INCREASE, THE LETTER WAS NOT CREATED AND IT NEEDS TO BE RESEARCHED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "- BACKUP THE BELOW VSAM FILES : CL.ME.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY CL.ME.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG1 - DELETED THE RECORDS OF PROBLEM POLICY FROM THE BACKUP FILES. - PROVIDE OVERRIDE OF BACKUP FILES IN STEP0010 & STEP0020. - RERUN THE JOB FROM TOP. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "- CICSD REGION HAS GONE DOWN UNEXPECTEDLY WHENEVER CICSD GOES DOWN, FIRST STEP IS TO BRING THE CICSD REGION AND CYBERLIFE UP IMMEDIATELY. IF THIS HAPPENS IN EVENING, THEN ITS P3 INCIDENT - CTS MAINFRAME TEAM HAS THE INSTRUCTION TO RESTART CICSD AND CYBERLIFE IMMEDIATELY. - IF YOU ARE ONCALL AND GETTING A CALL AFTER HOURS THEN, OPEN A TECH BRIDGE AND ASK HELP DESK TO CONTACT CTS MAINFRAME <COG.INFRA.MAINFRAME@ONEAMERICA.COM> AND GET CICSD AND CYBERLIFE RESTARTED. - FOR SAFER SIDE SEND AN EMAIL TO CTS MAINFRAME FOR THE SAME. IF THIS HAPPENS DURING BUSINESS HOURS, THEN ITS P1 MIM - CONTACT HELP DESK TO INITIATE MIM AND ADD CTS MIANFRAME IN MIM - IF YOU FIND ZAKEER SYED OR ANTONY VIMALRAJ ONLINE THEN MESSAGE THEN TO RESTART CICSD AND BRING CL UP. - OR, SEND AN EMAIL TO CTS MAINFRAME FOR THE SAME. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "- 1. GO TO JESMSGLG AND MAX DOWN 2. ERRORS - 2.1 *# IEF450I CICSD CICSD CICSD - ABEND=S000 U1800 2.2 -IEFACTRT CICSD 3 ABENDED U800 0000 2.3 FIND 'DFHSR0606' ALL. YOU WILL SEE BELOW ERROR - +DFHSR0606 CICSD ABEND (CODE C78\/AKEB) HAS BEEN DETECTED. 2.4 FINALLY, FIND 'NOTFND' ALL. YOU WILL SEE BELOW ERROR - +CKSPSMIN: CICS ERR: NOTFND-80 ON READ TO FVDTRCK 3. IT'S A KNOWN ISSUE UNDER PROBLEM TICKET - PRB0066072 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0160",
  "PROBLEM": "- JOB ABENDED AT JSTEP060 WITH S04E - DSNU017I - DSNUGSAT - UTILITY DATA BASE SERVICES MEMORY EXECUTION ABENDED, REASON=X'00C9021B' DSNU016I - DSNUGBAC - UTILITY BATCH MEMORY EXECUTION ABENDED, REASON=X'00E40347' 00E40347 EXPLANATION: THIS UTILITY'S MAIN TASK IS ABENDING BECAUSE ONE OF ITS SUBTASKS TERMINATED ABNORMALLY. THE SUBTASK ITSELF ISSUES AN ABEND BEFORE THIS ONE IS ISSUED. THIS MEANS WE NEED TO CHECK PREVIOUS STEPS FOR EXACT ERROR. JSTEP0040 SYSPRINT - DSN1966I OUTPUT DATA SET CL.DSNDBD.CLRPT.TCLRPT.J0001.A002 NOT FOUND. DSN1993I DSN1COPY TERMINATED, 00523491 PAGES PROCESSED ",
  "ANALYSIS": "- CL.DSNDBD.CLRPT.TCLRPT.J0001.A002 IS A DB2 PRIMARY VSAM. DB2 CREATES 2ND DATASET BY ITSELF WHEN PRIMARY (1ST) DATASET RUNS OUT OF SPACE. INITIALLY WE HAD ONLY 1 DATASET FOR CLRPT TABLESPACE AS THE SECOND WAS NEVER NEEDED. CYBERLIFE USES DSN1COPY UTILITY TO LOAD THE DATA (FOR SNAP AFTER BACKUP). DSN1COPY IS A OFFLINE UTILITY AND IT CANNOT CREATE A NEW VSAM DATASET. ONLY DB2 OR DB2 LOAD\/UNLOAD UTILITY CAN CREATE DB2 PRIMARY VSAM DATASET. SO DSN1COPY FAILED. REFER - PRB0074778 FOR ADDTIONAL DETAILS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "- CL$$0160 FAILED IN JSTEP040 AS CL.DSNDBD.CLRPT.TCLRPT.J0001.A002 NOT FOUND\/EXISTING. - BASED ON THIS WE CONTACTED CTS MAINFRAME INFRA TEAM (DBA). -THEY SUGGESTED THAT IF DATASET 'CL.DSNDBD.CLRPT.TCLRPT.J0001.A002' DO NOT EXIST AND IT COULD NOT BE CREATED FROM THE BACK-END THROUGH A DSN1COPY. A DB2 LOAD OR SQL INSERT HAS TO BE RUN AGAINST THE TABLESPACE CLRPT.TCLRPT FOR THE A002 DATASET TO BE CREATED. - WE SUGGESTED TO TWEAK THE JOB CL$$1000 WHICH USES DSNLOAD UTILITY TO UNLOAD DATA FROM CISBMAIN AND LOAD DATA INTO TCLRPT. - AFTER MULTIPLE ATTEMPTS VIA CL$$SEGD JOB, ANTONY SUGGESTED TO HAVE - STOP UTILITY FROM CL$$0160 WAS CLEARED AND OBJECTS IN PENDING STATUS (TABLESPACE AND INDEX WERE NOT IN RW) WERE MADE TO RW. MODIFIED CL$$1000 FOR CLRPT DATABASE AND RUNNING IN CL$$SEGD CREATED THE CL.DSNDBD.CLRPT.TCLRPT.J0001.A002 DATASET. AN IMAGECOPY WAS TAKEN AFTER THE LOAD TO MAKE TCLRPT. - ASKED OPS TO RERUN THE JOB FROM JSTEP0030. JOB ENDED-OK WITH THE ABOVE RESOLUTION. IF YOU ARE GETTING THIS ERROR IN TEST\/CLT* DB WHILE LOADING PROD DATA THEN USE - TEST.CL.JCLLIB(DB2LOAD) TO CREATE 2ND VSAM. MODIFY CLT2 TO THE TABLE NAME IN STEP0080 PARM='DB2T,CLT2' MODIFY TABLE NAME IN TEST.CL.CARDLIB(DB2LOAD) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0021",
  "PROBLEM": "- NEW CHANGES MOVED IN FOR PORC CL$$EXT1 AND CL$$0021 IN 12\/12 RELEASE BUT SPECIAL INSTRUCTION IN RELEASE WAS MISSING CONDI TION TO NOT RUN CL$$0021 UNTIL CL$$EXT1 RAN FOR THAT NIGHT CYCLE AS A RESULT CL$$0021 FAILED WITH JCL ERROR LOOKING OUT FOR FILES THAT WERE GETTING CREATED IN CL$$EXT1. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CREATED BELOW MISSING FILES USING FIRE CALL ID 9461 CL.CL$$EXT1.DLS.CARECUST CL.CL$$EXT1.DLS.INSURED CL.CL$$EXT1.DLS.ADDLVAL CL.CL$$EXT1.DLS.WRITAGT THEN FOLLOWED SCHD.CTM.V9O.PROD.DOC(CL$$0020) INSTRUCTION TO FIRST DE DELETE FOLLOWING FILES CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR(0) CL.DLS.CUSTFILE(0) CL.DLS.ACCTING(0) CL.DLS.COIPREM(0) CL.DLS.INSURED(0) CL.DLS.OWNER(0) CL.DLS.PENDREQ(0) CL.DLS.RIDER(0) CL.DLS.ADDLVAL(0) CL.DLS.SURRCHG(0) CL.DLS.WRITAGT(0) CL.DLS.TRMPREM(0) CL.DLS.POLSUMM(0) CL.DLS.SLTCUST(0) CL.DLS.BENE(0) CL.DLS.ANNCUST(0) CL.DLS.INVACCT(0) CL.DLS.LIFECUST(0) CL.DLS.CARECUST(0) CL.DLS.RELPOL(0) CL.NAIC.ILLUS(0) CL.IPIPELNE.ILLUS(0) - ADDED RESTART=JSTEP010.STEP0030 IN JOB CARD - ADDED FOLLOWING OVERRIDES - - \/\/STEP0030.SEQUEN DD DSN=CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT(0) - \/\/STEP0045.SORTIN DD DSN=CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT(0) AND TOLD PCD TO RUN JOB FROM LIBRARY TEST.CL.PROD.CALLOUT.JCLLIB(CL$$0021). "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0021",
  "PROBLEM": "- USER REQUESTED POLICY PAGES INCORRECTLY . SHE FORGOT TO REQUEST PAGES FOR 5201428630 AND 5201428640 AND JUST REQUESTED FOR 5820653090. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "-WENT INTO IDIREPRT AND SEARCH FOR KEYWORD S0025.SORTOUT TO FOUND OUT THE CURRENT RECORD GETTING PROCESSED IN THE FILE CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G1780V00. FOUND THE RECORD GETTING PROCESED WAS 5820653090 . ",
  "SOLUTION": "REMOVED OUT FROM FILE CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G1780V00 USING FIRECALL AND COPIED PRODUCTION JOB IN LIBRARY TEST.CL.PROD.CALL OUT.JCLLIB AND MADE FOLLOWING CHANGES IN IT - ADDED RESTART=JSTEP010.STEP0030 IN JOB CARD - ADDED FOLLOWING OVERRIDES - - \/\/STEP0030.SEQUEN DD DSN=CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT(0) - \/\/STEP0045.SORTIN DD DSN=CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT(0) AND TOLD PCD TO RUN JOB FROM LIBRARY TEST.CL.PROD.CALLOUT.JCLLIB(CL$$0021). "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1000",
  "PROBLEM": "- DELETE FROM CLS1.CLT_ADD_ADR_TEXT SQL ERROR DURING EXECUTE IMMEDIATE SQLCODE = -904, ERROR: UNSUCCESSFUL EXECUTION CAUSED BY AN UNAVAILABLE RESOURCE. REASON 00C90083, TYPE OF RESOURCE 00000200, AND RESOURCE NAME CLS1 .TCLS1 SIMILAR ERROR AS ABOVE IS SEEN FOR ALL THE DELETE QUERIES IN STEP0070. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "- JOB FAILED TO DELETE ALL THE ROWS OF CLIENT DATABASE TABLES BECAUSE OF UNAVAILABLE RESOURCE. AND BECAUSE OF CONDITION CODE SET IN STEP0080, THIS STEP WAS FLUSHED - JCL WAS NOT ABLE TO LOAD DB2 TABLES FROM SEQUENTIAL FILES. ",
  "SOLUTION": "- REFER SCHD.CTM.DOC CALLED THE DB2 ONCALL (ANTONY), AND HE HAD TO RESET THE DB2 RESOURCES. WE RESTARTED AGAIN IN STEP0065 SUCCESSFULLY. JOB "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "- FILE AGCY.PROC0265.STEP0010.OLONESTR MISSING. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "-AGCY0265 HAD BEEN RERAN THE PREVIOUS DAY BY MISTAKE. IT CREATED DATA IN THIS FILE. DID NOT WANT THIS DATA TO BE REPROCESSED SO RENAMED THE PROD FILE TO TEST NAME. WHAT I SHOUDL HAVE DONE WAS LEAVE FILE NAME ALONE AND DELETE ALL THE DATA LINES IN IT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "FILE BACK TO PROD NAME AND DELETED ALL DATA. HAD ABENDED JOB RERAN FROM TOP. ENDED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1000",
  "PROBLEM": "- DELETE FROM CLS1.CLT_ADD_ADR_TEXT SQL ERROR DURING EXECUTE IMMEDIATE SQLCODE = -904, ERROR: UNSUCCESSFUL EXECUTION CAUSED BY AN UNAVAILABLE RESOURCE. REASON 00C90083, TYPE OF RESOURCE 00000200, AND RESOURCE NAME CLS1 .TCLS1 SIMILAR ERROR AS ABOVE IS SEEN FOR ALL THE DELETE QUERIES IN STEP0070. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "- JOB FAILED TO DELETE ALL THE ROWS OF CLIENT DATABASE TABLES BECAUSE OF UNAVAILABLE RESOURCE. AND BECAUSE OF CONDITION CODE SET IN STEP0080, THIS STEP WAS FLUSHED - JCL WAS NOT ABLE TO LOAD DB2 TABLES FROM SEQUENTIAL FILES. ",
  "SOLUTION": "- REFER SCHD.CTM.DOC CALLED THE DB2 ONCALL (ANTONY), AND HE HAD TO RESET THE DB2 RESOURCES. WE RESTARTED AGAIN IN STEP0065 SUCCESSFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$2060",
  "PROBLEM": "- A SYSTEM ABEND 0C1 OCCURRED IN MODULE ULTTGPOL CSECT CKETRGET AT OFFSET X'45A'. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "- ALL THE OTHER STEPS WERE EXECUTED SUCCESSFULLY. ON QUICK ANALYSIS, WE FOUND THAT THE JSTEP010 FAILED DUE TO POLICY 0710019210 FOR ULTIM WLTAX001. ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. COPIED : CL.MENC.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY INTO TEST.CL.MENC.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY.D032919 2. DELETED THE RECORD OF ABENDING POLICY FROM BACKUP. 3. ASKED OPS TO RUN THE FAILED STEP JSTEP010 OF JOB CL$$2060 FROM THE LIBRARY 'PROD.SCHD.IND.CALLOUT' AND PROVIDED BELOW OVERRIDES IN JSTEP010 :- \/\/STEP0010.CLPND DD DSN=TEST.CL.MENC.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY.D032919, \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) THE JOB ENDED-OK WITH ABOVE RESOLUTION. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$2100",
  "PROBLEM": "- A USER ABEND 0999 OCCURRED IN MODULE CEEPLPKA AT OFFSET X'1FF594' +PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) AT LOCATION 000C1E IN ELEMENT CKULLPLP ",
  "ANALYSIS": "- FIND THE ABENDING POLICY. LOOK FOR POLICY EITHER BY FINDING 'VSAM1' IN THE IDIREPRT OR LOOK IN THE JES OF THE CL$$0103 RUN WHICH WILL SHOW THE SAME ABEND AND THE POLICY NUMBER. NEED TO SKIP POLICY 1000776950 USING CARD TEST.CL.TOOLS(CLIVBYPS) NOTE - SIMILAR ISSUE FACED IN PROD CYCLE JOBS CL$$0420 AND CL$$EXT1 WHICH FAILED FOR THE PROGRAM CEEPLPKA AND SAME POLICY. RCA IS CURRENTLY IN PROGRESS FOR THIS ONE. THE CARD CONTAINED ANOTHER POLICY 1000783512 WHICH WE KNEW WOULD ABEND WITH THE SAME REASON SO WE BYPASSED THAT AS WELL. ",
  "SOLUTION": "- SEE SCHD.CTM.DOC 1. BYPASSED THE ABENDING POLICY USING CARD TEST.CL.TOOLS(CLIVBYPS) 2. OVERRIDE WAS GIVEN AT STEP0002 - \/\/STEP0002.SYSIN DD DSN=TEST.CL.TOOLS(CLIVBYPS), \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) 3. ASKED OPS TO RERUN THE FAILED JOB FROM TOP. JOB ENDED-OK WITH THE ABOVE RESOLUTION. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$DW49",
  "PROBLEM": "- AS PER SYSOUT OF STEP0011 - 2019-03-23@03.30.52 CDCXCLPF: *WARNING* EXCESSIVE SEGMENT LENGTH, RECORD#:+22417 SEG-ID:80 SEQ-CTR:+13. 2019-03-23@03.30.52 CDCXCLPF: *WARNING* LOGICAL TRUNCATION. 2019-03-23@03.30.52 CDCXCLPF: *WARNING* SEG-LEN:+341 DEFINED:+340 MAXIMUM:+340(SO FAR) EXTRACT-MAX-REC-LEN:+30 ON LOOKING AT THE 22417 RECORD IN PENDING MASTER FILE, THE POLICY# CAME OUT TO BE - 0620909910 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "- AS INDICATED IN SYSOUT OF STEP0011, THE 13TH SEQUENCE OF POLICY 0620909910 (HAS RECORD LENGTH 341) . RECORD LENGTH OF SPECIFIED SEQUENCE NUMBER EXCEEDS THE EXISTING PRODUCTION COPYBOOK CKFRECPR RECORD LENGTH (FPRLNGTH-SEGMENT-LENGTH) WHICH IS DEFINED 340. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CHANGED THE DISPOSITION OF INFILE CREATED IN STEP0011 AS - (NEW,CATLG,CATLG). \/\/STEP0011.INFFILE DD DSN=CL.CL$$DW49.CDCXCLPF.CDCOINS.PNTEMP, \/\/ DISP=(NEW,CATLG,CATLG), \/\/ UNIT=&DISK, \/\/ SPACE=(TRK,(14000,7000),RLSE), \/\/ DCB=(MODELDCB,RECFM=VB,LRECL=3000,BLKSIZE=0,BUFNO=50) \/\/* THE JOB ABENDED IN SECOND RUN AS WELL BUT THIS TIME THE FILE WAS CATALOGED. WE CREATED A SORT CARD TO VALIDATE THE ENTRIES OF ALL PENDING POLICIES RECORD BEING INCLUDED IN INFILE INCLUDING THE PROBLEM POLICY WITH ONE TRUNCATED DATA TOO. ASKED OPS TO RERUN THE JOB FROM NEXT STEP-STEP0030 AFTER RESTART STEP- \/\/ RESTART=CL$$DW49.STEP0030 JOB ENDED OK WITH ABOVE RESOLUTION. FIRECALL USAGE# 9215 INCIDENT RESOLVED - INC0354587 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$RLPN",
  "PROBLEM": "- JOB WAS IN WAIT STATE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "- JOBS SCHEDULE TO RUN AT 8:00 AM, 10:00 AM, 12:00... EVERY 2 HRS THRU DAY. JOB WAITS ON INFORMATICA JOB CLIPLPSEND WHICH ALSO HAD NOT RAN. ",
  "SOLUTION": "ERIC TRIED FORCING CLIPLPSEND TO RUN BUT IT ABENDED AND DID NOT RESOLVE PROBLEM. FINAL SOLUTION WAS TO RUN INFA JOB CLIPLPEMPTY FOR CURRENT ODATE. THIS RESET FILES AND ALLOWED INFA AND MAINFRAME JOBS TO SUCCESSFULLY EXECUTE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$EXT1",
  "PROBLEM": "- CEE3207S THE SYSTEM DETECTED A DATA EXCEPTION (SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=0C7). FROM COMPILE UNIT CKULLPLP AT ENTRY POINT CKULLPLP AT COMPILE UNIT OFFSET +00000C1E AT ENTRY OFFSET +00000C1E AT ADDRESS 0ECD9F96. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "- FIND THE ABENDING POLICY - 1000776950 NEED TO SKIP THE BAD POLICY, REFER TO SCHD.CTM.DOC FOR INSTRUCTIONS. *ANALYSIS - FIND THE ABENDING POLICY - 1000783512 NEED TO SKIP THE BAD POLICY, REFER TO SCHD.CTM.DOC FOR INSTRUCTIONS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "AS PER SCHD.CTM.DOC WE EDITED THE JOB WITH BELOW OVERRIDE FOR SKIP CARD - PARMSKIP TO BYPASS THE BAD POLICY AND ASKED OPS TO RE RUN THE JOB FROM TOP. \/\/STEP0100.PARMSKIP DD * 101000776950******** \/* *SOLUTION- AS PER SCHD.CTM.DOC WE EDITED THE JOB WITH BELOW OVERRIDE FOR SKIP CARD - PARMSKIP TO BYPASS THE BAD POLICY AND ASKED OPS TO RE RUN THE JOB FROM TOP. \/\/STEP0100.PARMSKIP DD * 101000776950******** 101000783512******** \/* NOTE- THE JOB CL$$0420 ABENDED FOR THE SAME POLICY AND SAME ELEMENT - CKULLPLP IN THIS CYCLE. THE VALUE OF VARIABLE WS-FUND-TABLE HAS EXCEEDED ITS VALUE OF +262 AND CAUSED THE ABEND. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0017",
  "PROBLEM": "- JOB CL$$0017 FAILED AT STEP0010 WITH COND CODE 0012 AND SINCE, STEP0020 HAD A RETURN CODE = 0004 CONTROLO CANCELLED THE JOB WITH ABEND=S222. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "- CHECKED SYSLST FOR FAILURE MESSAGE AT STEP0010 O I121M JB 121MB 000 X I121R JT 121RT 000 ERROR IN INPUT STREAM CHECKED INPUT CARD IN STEP0010 SYSFILEW AND FOUND RECENT CHANGES MADE TO THE CARD WITH AN INCORRECT TRMTRBT1-TRAN-FIRST-CHAR 'X' INSTEAD OF 'O'. ",
  "SOLUTION": "- COPIED CARD IN STAGE LIBRARY AND CORRECTED THE CARD SYSFILEW BY REMOVING THE ENTRY FOR ID I121RJT WHICH WAS ALREADY THERE WITH 'O' TRMTRBT1-TRAN-FIRST-CHAR. 1) ASKED OPS TO RUN RESTORE JOB CL$$R017. 2) COPIED JOB IN PROD.SCHD.IND.CALLOUT AND PROVIDED BELOW OVERRIDE - \/\/STEP0010.SYSIPT DD DSN=TEST.CL.PROD.CARDLIB(SYSFILEW), \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) THE SAME CARD WAS GETTING USED IN CL$$USYS AND CL$$0150 JOBS, SO TO AVOID ANY INCONSISTENCY, WE PROVIDED OVERRIDE FOR CORRECT CARDS THERE AS WELL. 4)ASKED OPS TO RERUN THE JOB CL$$0017 FROM THE LIBRARY 'PROD.SCHD.IND.CALLOUT'. JOB GOT EXECUTED SUCCESSFULLY WITH ABOVE RESOLUTION. NOTE - ASKED THE PROGRAMMER TO CORRECT THE CARD - PROD.CL.CARDLIB(SYSFILEW) TO AVOID ANY ABEND IN THE NEXT CYCLE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "INC0345727",
  "PROBLEM": "-62D1 WAS TRUNCATING NAME ",
  "ANALYSIS": "-REVIEWED CLIENT AND FOUND A X'05' VALUE IN THE CICL_FST_NM AND CICL_LNG_NM FIELD ",
  "SOLUTION": "FIRECALL AND UPDATE THE FIELDS IN THE CLADMIN.CLIENT_TAB TABLE. TYPE 'HEX ON' ON COMMAND PROMPT WHEN READY TO EDIT. FIELDS 20 BYTES OR LARGER HAVE TO BE EDITED USING THE EXPAND COMMAND. CICL_LNG_NM FIELD IS ONE OF THOSE FIELDS. -TYPE 'EXPAND' ON COMMAND PROMPT THEN, -PUT YOUR CURSOR'S FOCUS ON THE FIELD TO BE EDITED, -THEN HIT [ENTER] -A POP UP BOX WILL APPEAR AND YOU CAN EDIT THE FIELD. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "- BUSINESS REPORTED THAT VUL POLICIES W\/LTC RIDER DID NOT GENERATE A 1099-R TAX FORM. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "-FOUND THAT CL$$4900 RAN BEFORE CL$$2070 AT YEAR END AND SHOULD HAVE BEEN RAN AFTER CL$$2070. THE DEPENDENCY WAS MISSING AND HAS BEEN FOR YEARS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "LUCKILY A BACKUP OF CL.CL$$0870.LTCGAIN.ANNUAL(0) IS MADE TO CL.YE.LTCGAIN.ANNUAL(+1) IN CL$$4900. SHORT TERM-RESTORED MENC VSAMS FROM YEAR END AND RAN WITH THIS OVERRIDE A UNIT TEST VERSION \/\/STEP0060.IINPUT DD DSN=CL.YE.LTCGAIN.ANNUAL(0) \/\/ DISP=SHR THE FOLLOWING STEPS: \/\/STEP0010 \/\/STEP0060 \/\/STEP0070 \/\/STEP0080 \/\/STEP0090 \/\/STEP0120 \/\/STEP0130 THEN SENT PRODUCTION FILE TEST.CL.WET.TAX.MEC.LTC TO REX SO HE COULD RUN THAT FILE THROUGH TAX$0329. LONG TERM-CREATED REQ0118655 TO MAKE CL$$4900 RUN AFTER CL$$2070. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0015",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED IN IDIREPRT AND SAW... EBCDIC ------------------ *12\/03\/2018 A* *DDRESS * * D5ADDRSS 2019-0* *1-29-19.52.58.01* *7124+000000000SL* I THEN WENT INTO THE INPUT FILE CL.CL$$0015.REPS.SORTED(&GENOT) AND DID A SEARCH FOR \/ THOUGHOUT THE FILE TO SEE IF ANYTHING LOOKS SUSPICIOUS. FORTUNATELY I FOUND IN THE FIRST COLUMN WHERE THE AGENT NUMBER RESIDES RECORDS THAT HAD 12\/03\/2018. THIS OBVIOUSLY WAS INCORRECT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. COPIED - CL.CL$$0015.REPS.SORTED.G3118V00 TO TEST.CL.CL$$0015.REPS.SORTED.PROD.D012919 AND DELETED CORRUPT DATA RECORDS FROM USER FILE.PROVIDED OVERRIDE IN STEP0040,0050,0060. 2. RENAMED THE BELOW FILES USING FIRE CALL. CL.CL$$0015.STEP0040.ERR.G3120V00 TO TEST.CL.CL$$0015.STEP0040.ERR.PROD.D012919 CL.CL$$0015.STEP0040.CHG.G3120V00 TO TEST.CL.CL$$0015.STEP0040.CHG.PROD.D012919 3. INFORMED OPS TO EXECUTE A RESTORE JOB CL$$R015. 4. COPIED JOB IN PROD.SCHD.IND.CALLOUT AND PROVIDED OVERRIDE - RESTART=JSTEP010.STEP0040 THIS IS ALSO NECESSARY FOR JOBS CL$BACF AND CL$MACF AS THEY WENT DOWN ALSO. NOTE: INFORMED JAMI AFTER THE JOB ENDED-OK FOR THE CORRUPT RECORDS "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "- BANK GOT AN ERROR: BATCH HEADER EFFECTIVE DATE MORE THAN 30 DAYS IN PAST -PIONEER MUTUAL LIFE - 1015507 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "- THERE WAS A INVALID DATE IN THE EXTRACT TO THE BANK. CL.FIN.BANK.PML.EXTS.G3698V00 THE RECORD IN ERROR WAS CREATED FROM A MANUAL DRAFT. MANUAL DRAFTS ARE AUTOMATED TO BUILD MOST OF THE FIELDS IN THE MANUAL DRAFT RECORD EXCEPT PRIOR DATE. OFFSHORE HAS TO PHYSICALLY TYPE IN THE PRIOR DATE. THE PRIOR DATE FIELD HAD 010618 AND SHOULD HAVE BEEN 010619. ",
  "SOLUTION": "NO ACTION ON OUR SIDE. SHANTE BENNETT ASKED THE BANK TO PROCESS THE BATCH WITH CURRENT DATE SO WE DIDN'T HAVE TO RESUBMIT. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1000",
  "PROBLEM": "- PROBLEM WHILE COPYING POLICY AND AUXSEG1 SANC FILE TO MENC FILE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "- JOB CL$$EXT1 WAS USING THE FILES AND THUS WAS UNABLE TO TO TAKE EXCLUSIVE HOLD WHILE RUNNING FLASH COPY OF THESE FILES. RESOLUTION - 1. WE RAN FLASH COPY FOR THE FILES : 'CL.SANC.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY' INTO 'CL.MENC.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY' 'CL.SANC.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG1' INTO 'CL.MENC.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG1' 2. ASKED OPS TO FORCE COMPLETE THE JOB. NOTE - TO SOLVE THIS ISSUE IN PROD, A FIX IS PLANNED TO MOVED ON 01\/24\/19. IN WHICH THE FLASH COPY STEP FOR THESE FILES IS REPLACED WITH IDCAMS UTILITY. FIRECALL USAGE - 9122 INCIDENT NUMBER - INC0330616 --------------------------------------------------------------------- JOB "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0035",
  "PROBLEM": "- ABEND=S04C ON 5201464150 OR SYSTEM ABEND: 0C1 OR OFFSET X'45A' 60XX WOULD PRODUCE CKPNQCN PROGRAM CHECK 60D1 WOULD PRODUCE CKFMTC62 PROGRAM CHECK ",
  "ANALYSIS": "- FOUND THE POLICY NUMBER IN THE CL$$0035 DISPLAY RAN CKAP34V ON THE PENDING FILE. FOUND 5 89 SEGMENTS IN THE DUMP (20,10,30,01,00). FOUND 4 ROWS IN THE CLIENT DATABASE (20,10,01,00). OR GO TO IDIREPRT AND - 1. FIND: \"F SQLCA\" > IF YOU SEE - 'SQLCODE 100 EXPLANATION', IT MEANS CLIENT RECORD IS MISSING. AND FOLLOW BELOW INSTRUCTIONS (FROM #2) > IF YOU SEE - 'SQLCODE -811 EXPLANATION' THEN SEARCH MORE IN BOMBLOG FOR CORRECT ",
  "SOLUTION": "OF SQLCODE -811. 2. FIND: \"F 'INPUT HOST' PREV\" > YOU WILL FIND POLICY NUMBER WITH COMPANY CODE AND > SYSID, RELATIONSHIP CODE ETC.. EXAMPLE - DATA VALUE. . . . . . . : 055201566870 DATA VALUE. . . . . . . : CK4P DATA VALUE. . . . . . . : 3001 3. IT MEANS A ROW IN CLT_OBJ_RELATION IS MISSING FOR ABOVE DATA VALU SOLUTION - USED FIRECALL. IN THE CLT_OBJ_RELATION TABLE: 1. DUPLICATED THE LAST (4TH) ROW WITH AN R COMMAND 2. CHANGED THE SEQ_NBR FROM 4 TO 5 ON THE NEW ROW 3. CHANGED RLT_TYP_CD FROM 0001 TO 3001 ON THE NEW ROW 4. ELAINE STIFFLER INFORMED THE BUSINESS THAT WE ADDED A BENEFICIARY TO THE RECORD AND TOLD THEM TO CALL US BEFORE THEY CHANGE THE RECORD. SEND AN EMAIL TO NEW BUSINESS FOR PERMANENT FIX - TO: ANNA DELOACH, LO WEBB CC: M.AUL.SYS.AMS.CORE.MAINFRAME SUBJECT: CLIENT ISSUE IN PENDING POLICY 5201566870 BODY: WE HAD AN ABEND IN CL JOB CL$$0035 @ 02:00 PM TODAY DUE TO A MISSING BENEFICIARY IN PENDING POLICY 5201566870. TO FIX THE ABEND, I CREATED A BENEFICIARY RECORD IN CLIENT DATABASE USING PRIMARY INSURED RECORD. NOW, THE POLICY# 5201566870 IS NO LONGER ABENDING IN CYBERLIFE. PLEASE FIX THE BENEFICIARY RECORD WITH CORRECT DETAILS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0035",
  "PROBLEM": "- ABEND=S04C ON 0720123210 OR SYSTEM ABEND: 0C1 OR OFFSET X'45A' 60XX WOULD PRODUCE CKPNQCN PROGRAM CHECK 60D1 WOULD PRODUCE CKFMTC62 PROGRAM CHECK ",
  "ANALYSIS": "- GO TO IDIREPRT AND - 1. FIND: \"F SQLCA\" > IF YOU SEE - 'SQLCODE -811 EXPLANATION', IT MEANS DUPLICATE ROW FOUND IN CLT_OBJ_RELATION. 2. FIND: \"F 'INPUT HOST' PREV\" > YOU WILL FIND POLICY NUMBER WITH COMPANY CODE AND > SYSID, RELATIONSHIP CODE ETC.. EXAMPLE - DATA VALUE. . . . . . . : 000720123210 DATA VALUE. . . . . . . : CK4P DATA VALUE. . . . . . . : 0001 3. GO TO PST AND PULL UP THE POLICY IN CLT_OBJ_RELATION TABLE. YOU WILL FIND DUPLICATE ROWS THERE - TCH_OBJECT_KEY HIST_VLD_NBR CIOR_EFF_DT RLT_TYP CIOR_EXP_DT -------------- ------------ ----------- ------- ----------- ---- 000720123210 0 2010-11-15 3001 9999-12-31 CK4P 000720123210 0 2010-11-15 2001 9999-12-31 CK4P 000720123210 0 2010-11-15 1001 9999-12-31 CK4P 000720123210 0 2010-11-15 0001 9999-12-31 CK4P 000720123210 0 2019-05-22 2001 9999-12-31 CK4P 000720123210 0 2019-05-22 1001 9999-12-31 CK4P 000720123210 0 2019-05-22 0001 9999-12-31 CK4P 000720123210 0 2019-05-22 3001 9999-12-31 CK4P ************************* BOTTOM ******************************* 4. YOU NEED TO EXPIRE THE DUPLICATE ROWS - > USE FIRE CALL ID TO MAKE BELOW MENTIONED CHANGES > CHNAGE CIOR_EFF_DT OF OLDEST ROW(S) WITH THE EFFECTIVE DATE OF THE NEWEST ROW(S) > CHANGE HISTORY_VLD_NBR OF OLDEST ROW(S) TO '1'. TCH_OBJECT_KEY HIST_VLD_NBR CIOR_EFF_DT RLT_TYP CIOR_EXP_DT -------------- ----------- ----------- ------- ----------- ---- 000720123210 1 2010-11-15 3001 2019-05-22 CK4P 000720123210 1 2010-11-15 2001 2019-05-22 CK4P 000720123210 1 2010-11-15 1001 2019-05-22 CK4P 000720123210 1 2010-11-15 0001 2019-05-22 CK4P 000720123210 0 2019-05-22 2001 9999-12-31 CK4P 000720123210 0 2019-05-22 1001 9999-12-31 CK4P 000720123210 0 2019-05-22 0001 9999-12-31 CK4P 000720123210 0 2019-05-22 3001 9999-12-31 CK4P ************************* BOTTOM ******************************** "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "JOBS CAME TO DAILY SCHEDULE. THIS INCLUDES CL$$, CL$T, CL$M, ACTS JOBS, CK4 JOBS & MTAS JOBS. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB WAS CHANGED TO REMOVE CL$T CYCLE DUE TO THE REGION REFRESH; HOWEVER, WHEN PCD COMMENTED OUT CL$TJOBS THEY MISSED COMMENTING OUT THE DISP=SHR LINE UNDERNEATH IT SO JOB GOT A JCL ERROR. PCD DID NOT RESOLVE THIS ERROR. USER NOTIFIED MAINFRAME TEAM THAT THE CL$$0035 JOB HAD NOT RAN AT 8:00AM AND MAINFRAME TEAM SAW NO JOBS WERE ON CURRENT SCHEDULE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "INC0300168 TO HAVE PCD FIX JCL ERROR AND RERUN JOB. JOB WAS RERAN AT 10:55 AND NOW DAILY JOBS ARE ON THE SCHEDULE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$S247",
  "PROBLEM": "THE DATA-SETS CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN, CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH, CL.VSAM.BASEOL.FUNDVAL WERE ATTACHED TO THE CICSD REGION RESULTING IN FAILING OF THE 24X7 BACKUP FOR THE DATSETS. THIS MESSAGE DISPLAYED IN THE JOB: ADR801I (005)-DDDS (01), 2018.234 22:52:34 DATA SET FILTERING IS COMPLETE. 0 OF 1 DATA SETS WERE SELECTED: 1 FAILED SERIALIZATION AND 0 FAILED FOR OTHER REASONS ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE CL.VSAM.BASEOL.* FILES WERE STILL ATTACHED TO THE CICSD REGION. RESULTING IN UNABLE TO COPY THE DATA-SETS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "1.AS PER THE SCHD.CTM.DOC , RERAN THE JOB FROM TOP, BUT IT FAILED AGAIN. 2.ASKED OPS TO CLOSE THE VSAM FILES FVDSEGH, FVDFNDD, FVDAFAD. 3.RAN THE FLASHCOPY FOR THE DATASETS USING FIRECALL ID: CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN INTO CL.S24X7.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH INTO CL.S24X7.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH CL.VSAM.BASEOL.FUNDVAL INTO CL.S24X7.VSAM.BASEOL.FUNDVAL 4.PROVIDED THE RESTART INSTRUCTION IN THE JOB : \/\/CL$$S247 JOB (P,712W),'24X7 BACKUPS',CLASS=P, \/\/ RESTART=CL$$S247.STEP0030, 5.THE JOB RAN FINE WITH ABOVE INSTRUCTIONS. 6.ASKED OPS TO AGAIN ATTACHED THE FILES FVDSEGH, FVDFNDD, FVDAFAD, POINTING THE S24X7 VERSION OF THE DATA-SETS TO CICSD PROD REGION . "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "INCORRECT DATE AND FUND PRICES PRESENT FOR SPFUND IN THE PRICES FILE ",
  "ANALYSIS": "IF THE CLIPSP500 JOB FAILS, YOU MAY HAVE TO CREATE THE S&P 500 FUND INPUT CARD MANUALLY. 1.DO NOT FORCE COMPLETE CLIPSP500 AND PUT CONDITION 'WAIT-FOR-CSC' ON THE JOB CL$$0012. USE FIRECALL ID TO UPDATE 'CL.FUND.PRICES.INDEXES' WITH CORRECT DATE AND PRICES - TO GET S&P 500 FUND VALUE: SEE THE PROCEDURE WRITTEN TO GET THE PRICES ONLINE IN TEST.CL.BOMBLOG(SPFUNDS). ASK OPS TO RUN THE JOB CL$$0010, ONCE CL$$0010 IS ENDED-OK, CHECK THE LATEST VERSION OF GDG CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES.G* TO HAVE CORRECT DATE AND SPFUND PRICES. ASK OPS TO REMOVE 'WAIT-FOR-CSC' FROM CL$$0012. 2.IF CL$$0010 IS EXECUTED AND CL$$0012 FAILS DUE TO INCORRECT DATES AND FUND PRICES THEN, TO CORRECT CL$$0012 - TAKE BACKUP OF THE LATEST VERSION OF THE GDG - CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES.G* USE FIRECALL ID TO UPDATE THE LATEST VERSION OF THE GDG 'CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES.G*' WITH THE CORRECT DATE AND SPFUND PRICES - TO GET S&P 500 FUND VALUE: SEE THE PROCEDURE WRITTEN TO GET THE PRICES ONLINE IN TEST.CL.BOMBLOG(SPFUNDS). ASK OPS TO RUN THE RESTORE JOB - CL$$R012 ONCE THE RESTORE JOB ENDS OK, ASK OPS TO RE-RUN THE JOB CL$$0012 FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$IIAM",
  "PROBLEM": "CL.VSAM.BASER.DATECNTL FDRR47** DEFINE ERROR -- RETURN CODE 042, DSN=CL.VSAM.BASER.DATECNTL FDRR32** RELOAD PROCESSING TERMINATED FDRR33** RELOAD FAILED - CODE=U0999,DSN=CL.VSAM.BASER.DATECNTL ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CL.VSAM.BASER.DATECNTL WAS NOT ALLOCATED BECAUSE THE FILE WAS IN USE. -LATER ON, WE DISCOVERED THAT THE FILE CL.VSAM.BASER.DATECNTL GOT DELETED WHILE BACKING UP. AS PER SCHD.CTM.DOC WE RERUN THE JOB FROM TOP WHICH WAS NOT SUFFICIENT. -FOR CL.VSAM.BASER.DATECNTL, LATEST AVAILABLE BACKUP IS - CL.VSAM.BASER.DATECNTL.BACKUP WHICH STAYS ONLY TILL THE FDR REORG IS NOT SUCCESSFUL. IF ITS A SUCCESSFUL REORG IT GETS DELETED. RESOLUTION- IF THE JOB FAILS, CHECK TO SEE IF SOURCE FILE IS MISSING, IF IT IS MISSING THE SOURCE FILE SHOULD BE AND RESTORED FROM EITHER IAM BACKUP OR MOST PREVIOUS APPLICATION BACKUP. **IMPORTANT** IN CASE OF DATECNTL FILE, THERE IS NO SA BACKUP AVAILABLE, SO THE FILE NEEDS TO BE RESTORED FROM .BACKUP FILE BEFORE THE JOB RESTARTS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1940",
  "PROBLEM": "A SYSTEM ABEND 0C1 OCCURRED IN MODULE M7240CCR CSECT CKVSAMIO AT OFFSET X'356'. A PROGRAM-INTERRUPTION CODE 0001 (OPERATION EXCEPTION) IS ASSOCIATED WITH THIS ABEND AND INDICATES THAT: AN ATTEMPT WAS MADE TO EXECUTE AN INSTRUCTION WITH AN INVALID OPERATION CODE. THE ABEND WAS CAUSED BY AN UNDETERMINED INSTRUCTION. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS WAS REQUESTED JOB. WHILE TESTING THE UNIT RUN FOR THE JOB, WE FOUND THE JOB WAS ABENDING DUE TO AGENT ID PROVIDED IN THE OVERRIDE OF THE JOB. AGENT ID- 0046829 ",
  "SOLUTION": "WE MAILED THE REQUESTER SHARING THE DETAILS. AFTER HIS APPROVAL TO DELETE THE ABENDING AGENT IN THE JOB, ASKED OPS TO RERUN THE JOB FROM TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$IIAM",
  "PROBLEM": "TO REORG THE CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH THE REORG OF AUXSEGH SHOULD ALWAYS BE DONE ON A FRIDAY NIGHT WITH CTS MAINFRAME INFRA STORAGE TEAM ONCALL AVAILABLE. MAY 2018 WE REORGED THE AUXSEGH. REORG BACKUPUNIT=TAPE WOULD NOT WORK, FAILED WITH ERROR. SO WE HAD TO PUT THE IAM BACKUP ON DISK. THE BEST CANDIDATE TO FREE UP DISK SPACE WAS CL.ME.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH. MADE SURE NO OTHER JOB WAS USING THAT FILE(MAKE SURE ITS NOT MONTH END WD99,WD01, OR WHEN CL$$1180 IS ON SCHEDULE). IF CL.ME.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH IS NOT BEING USED IN CYCLE, DELETE CL.ME.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH USING FIRECALL. NEXT, FIND OUT WHAT MONTH THE CURRENT ME'S ARE SET TO. IN THIS CASE COL 45 SHOWS 218C059C OR 02\/28\/18 FMV\/L02-BROWSE-ACHERROR-CL.ME.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY --------------- COMMAND "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0035",
  "PROBLEM": "A SYSTEM ABEND 0C1 OCCURRED IN MODULE D7245000 CSECT CKETRGET AT OFFSET X'45A'. SQLCODE = -911. SQLSTATE = 40001. DEADLOCK OR TIMEOUT WITH AUTOMATIC ROLLBACK OCCURRED. THIS OCCURS WHEN ANOTHER ACTIVITY IS HITTING CLIENT AT THE SAME TIME YOUR JOB IS RUNNING. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB HAS BEEN RESTARTED FROM TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0690",
  "PROBLEM": "IN TRADE FILE SUBMISSION THE NIGHT OF 4\/16\/18. OMNI CYCLE WILL NOT COMPLETE IN TIME FOR TRADE FILE SUBMISSION. THIS IMPACTS BOTH OMNI TRADES AND ILFS TRADES. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CPU UTILIZATION ON ONE OF THE OMNI SERVER AND THERE IS SLOWNESS IN THE OMNNI JOBS. THERE WAS A BAD TEST TRX IN OMNI CAUSING DELAY AND LOOPING. SINCE DEADLINE WAS MISSED, CYBERLIFE TRADES ARE IMPACTED BECAUSE OMNI TRADE NEEDS A VALUE FROM OMNI TO FINISH THE TRADE CALCULATION FOR CYBERLIFE. ALTHOUGH UNIT PRICES WERE CORRECT, THE TRADE VALUE COULD NOT BE CALCLUATED IN TIME. ",
  "SOLUTION": "TO DOUBLE UP ON TRADES IN TONIGHT'S CYCLE. BELOW ARE THE 3 CYBERLIFE FTP JOBS FOR OMNI TRADE. 0 FTPICL1100 - CL$$0690 - CL FILE FTPICL1066 - CL$$0700 - CLTRD FILE FTPICL1130 - CL$$8002 - CLPOS FILE THAT FILES THAT WERE NOT TRADED NEED TO HAVE TODAY'S DATE. USED FIRECALL AND EDITED 3 FILES TO HAVE 04172018. CL.CL$$0690.OMNIMAN.G2365V00 CL.CL$$0700.FUNDS.SUMMARY.G2360V00 CL.CL$$8002.FUND.UNITS.SORT.G3753V00 CL.CL$$0690.OMNIMAN.G2365V00 COL 39-41 20180416 TO 20180417 CL.CL$$8002.FUND.UNITS.SORT.G3753V00 COL 18-25 20180416 TO 20180417 CL.CL$$0700.FUNDS.SUMMARY.G2360V00 COL 82-89 20180416 TO 20180417 TRADE DATE IS OT-STD-CURRENT-DATE, THAT IS THE DATE WE CHANGED AS OF DATE IS OT-STD-ACTIVITY-ASOF-DATE AND WE LEFT AS IS. PROD.CL.COPYLIB(OMNISTD) 05 OT-STD-ACTIVITY-ASOF-DATE. 10 OT-STD-ACT-ASOF-YYYY PIC 9(4). 10 OT-STD-ACT-ASOF-MM PIC 99. 10 OT-STD-ACT-ASOF-DD PIC 99. 05 OT-STD-ACTIVITY-ASOF-PRICE PIC 9(5)V9(6). = SPACES 05 OT-STD-CURRENT-DATE. 10 OT-STD-CURRENT-YYYY PIC 9(4). 10 OT-STD-CURRENT-MM PIC 99. 10 OT-STD-CURRENT-DD PIC 99. 05 OT-STD-CURRENT-PRICE PIC 9(5)V9(6). = SPACES 05 OT-STD-REQUESTED-SHARES PIC 9(11)V9(4). POPULATED 05 OT-STD-REQUESTED-CASH PIC 9(13)V99. POPULDATED 05 OT-STD-LOSSGAIN-CASH PIC 9(13)V99. POPULATED CREATED 2 JOBS TEST.CL.TOOLS(COPYFILE) TEST.CL.TOOLS(COPYFILX) ADDED WAIT-4-DXC TO FTPICL1100, FTPICL1066 AND FTPICL1130 INSTRUCTED DXC THE FOLLOWING: AFTER CL$$0690 AND CL$$0700 END OK (BOTH JOBS NEEDS TO COMPLETE) THEN RUN TEST.CL.TOOLS(COPYFILE). MAKE SURE IT ENDS OK. THEN REMOVE THE WAIT-4-DXC HOLDS OFF OF FTPICL1100 AND FTPICL1066. AFTER CL$$8002 ENDS OK , THEN RUN TEST.CL.TOOLS(COPYFILX). MAKE SURE IT ENDS OK. THEN REMOVE THE WAIT-4-DXC HOLD FROM FTPICL1130. NOTE-SEE ALSO FOLDER K:\\IT-RUN\\AMS\\CORE\\AMS CORE - MAINFRAME\\CYBRLIFE\\ OMNI TRADE FILES 2018-04-16 "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "- THE SYSSTAT FILE CONTAINED ZEROES INSTEAD OF VALID DATES. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SIGN ON TO CICS IN APPROPRIATE REGION (EX. TEST, MODL) & DO 'SSDS, ' COMMAND TO BRING UP LIST OF DPFS EXTENTS. IF ALL EXTENTS LISTED AS EMPTY AND NONE ARE ON-LINE THEN.... ",
  "SOLUTION": "- FOR TEST AND MODEL - DO AN E03 TRANSACTION IN THAT REGION TO FLIP DPFS EXTENTS AND IT WILL POPULATE 1ST RECORD IN SYSSTAT FILE WITH VALID DATES. FOR PRODUCTION - AS YOU WILL NOT HAVE ACCESS TO DO E03, ASK PCD TO BRING CICSCL1X IN AJF & RUN IT. THIS JOB RUNS 0003 TRANSACION ONLY. TO VALIDATE DO ANOTHER SSDS, COMAND AND SHOULD SEE 1 OF THE DPFS EXTENTS ACTIVE, ONLINE. (E03 IS SAME AS 003 TRANSACTION) RELATED INCIDENT AND PROBLEM # INC0571384 \/ PRB0091664. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$SYSD",
  "PROBLEM": "ABENDS ON SUNDAY MORNING THESE MULTIPLE DUMPS WERE DUE TO PROBLEM DOCUMENTED IN INC0233637. PROBLEM HAS BEEN FIXED BY DB2 TEAM, THEREFORE THE MULTIPLE DUMPS HAVE STOPPED. SEE INC0233632 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WAS A RARE PROBLEM CAUSED BY DB2 PROBLEMS, BUT NO ONE COULD WORK IN CYBERLIFE REGIONS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CICSD TO SEE IF CYBERLIFE HAS COME UP 'CYBERLIFE INITIALIZATION TRANSACTION STARTED ' IF NOT, MIGHT NEED TO CONTACT MGR ONCALL TO GET RESOLVED. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "THE TEST.CK4.BOMBLOG FOR S128 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE TEST.CK4.BOMBLOG FOR S128 ",
  "SOLUTION": "THE TEST.CK4.BOMBLOG FOR S128 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$IIAM",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB ENDED WITH A COND CODE = 0008 STOR27 FDRR30 RELOAD STARTED DSN=CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG1 STOR27 FDRR33** RELOAD FAILED - CODE=SB37 ,DSN=CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "& ",
  "SOLUTION": "- PER THE BOMBLOG - NOTIFY THE DASD ON-CALL PERSON,SIREESHA FROM STORAGE TEAM. - SINCE THE JOB WAS REORGANIZING FILES AND FAILED FOR ONLY ONE FILE AUXSEG1, WHICH WAS DELETED IN FAILED INSTANCE. - WE COPIED THE SNAP AFTER (SA) AUXSEG1 FILE TO THE CURRENT AUXSEG1 FILE USING FIRE CALL ID. - AND ASKED OPS TO FORCE COMPLETE CL$$IIAM. SO WE COULD CONTINUE ON WITH CYCLE. MEANWHILE IN THE BACKGROUND THE STORAGE TEAM WAS ASKED TO LOOK FOR THE ISSUE AND PROVIDE A RESOLUTION. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0130",
  "PROBLEM": "S2F3 AND SOC4 ABEND +CKAB01 IGZ SUBROUTINE FAILURE... + TOKEN = 0003032D 59C3C5C5 00000000 + CEE0813S INSUFFICIENT STORAGE WAS AVAILABLE TO SATISFY A GET STORAGE (CEECZST) + REQUEST. +PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0CX IGZ LOGIC ABEND AT LOCATION 001ABA IN ELEMENT CKULIV00 + PSW = 00080000 8EB4BC0A ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WE LOOKED AT THE ISSUE AND SEEMED SOME MEMORY LEAKAGE ISSUE AT FIRST WE CREATED A UNIT SET UP OF ONLY STEP0020 AND STEP0030. WE TRIED TO INCREASE THE SPACE BUT IT DIDN'T WORKED. SO WE FOUND POLICIES AFTER EACH RUN AND AND BYPASSED THE POLICIES FOUND IN THE SYSOUT. AFTER SEVERAL RUNS IN THE UNIT REGION, WE CAME UP WITH - ABENDING POLICIES - 2650056110 2650057120 5200181760 ",
  "SOLUTION": "- SKIP CL$$0130 SO ON-LINE WOULD COME UP ON TIME. 1) THIS IS A STAND ALONE JOB & ONLY CORRES FILE GETS UPDATED IN IT. SO IT IS VERY IMP TO RELEASE CYCLE AND REMOVE COND FROM CL$$0150 JOB 2) WE CHECKED THAT THE FILE CL.VSAM.BASEOL.CORRES WAS NOT UPDATED VIA CICS. 3) COPIED CL.BASEB.AP.COR.EXT1.G4990V00 INTO USER FILE AND BYPASSED ABENDING POLICIES FROM USER FILE :TEST.CL.BASEB.AP.COR.EXT1.G4990 4) SINCE ONLINES WERE UP BY THAT TIME, WE USED COPIED PROD CORRES FILE IN USER FILE - TEST.CL.VSAM.BASEOL.CORRES.PROD.D011518 AND RAN CL$$0130 USING THIS FILE. 5) PROVIDED OVERRIDES FOR USER FILE IN STEP0030 AND STEP0050. 6) NEXT DAY THE USER FILE WAS RENAMED TO ORIGINAL CORRES FILE - CL.VSAM.BASEOL.CORRES USING CL$$SEGD BEFORE THE CYCLE STARTED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$8502",
  "PROBLEM": "CEE3250C THE SYSTEM OR USER ABEND U 001 R=NULL ",
  "ANALYSIS": "REQUEST JOB BE RESTARTED FROM TOP ",
  "SOLUTION": "INCTASK IN SNOW TO HAVE PCD RESTART FROM TOP. ENDED SUCCESSFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1180",
  "PROBLEM": "D724ABS1 WAS ABENDING MODULE PROGRAM EP NAME NAME NAME EVENT LOCATION (*) DESCRIPTION -------- -------- -------- ------------------ -------------------------- DSNECP10 DSNECP10 N\/A P+20A FROM DB2.V101.SDSNLOAD DSNECP10 DSNECP19 N\/A P+1BEC FROM DB2.V101.SDSNLOAD DSNECP10 DSNECP16 N\/A P+554 FROM DB2.V101.SDSNLOAD D724ABS1 D724ABS1 D724ABS1 E+2938 FROM PROD.CL.LOADLIB D724ABS1 CKSDTXIO CKSDTXIO E+1F6 FROM PROD.CL.LOADLIB D724ABS1 CKVSAMIO CKVSAMIO E+1270 FROM PROD.CL.LOADLIB 9 PIC 0004 (ABEND S0C4) ***** IAMAVSOC IAMAVSOC N\/A P+61D6 FROM IAM.V9300.SPIN01.LOAD ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WAS GETTING IAM ERROR ON AUXSEGH +IAMW73 IAMAVSOC ESTAE ENTERED FOR ABEND U4036 +IAMW73 PSW AT TIME OF ERROR: 078D1F00 856167C8 ILC: 02 +IAMW73 FAILING PGM: CEEPLPKA 0559C000 OFFSET: 0007A7C8 +IAMW73 GPR 00 - 03: FFFFFFFF_00000000 00000000_84000FC4 +IAMW73 GPR 04 - 07: 00000000_00093340 00000000_00000000 +IAMW73 GPR 08 - 11: FFFFFFFF_0EDB23EC 00000000_00000000 +IAMW73 GPR 12 - 15: 00000000_00094BD8 00000000_0EDB2558 +IAMW73 AR 00 - 03: 00000000 00000000 01010037 01010037 +IAMW73 AR 04 - 07: 00000000 00000000 00000000 00000000 +IAMW73 AR 08 - 11: 00000000 00000000 00000000 00000000 +IAMW73 AR 12 - 15: 00000000 00000000 00000000 00000000 ",
  "SOLUTION": "DELETE THE CL.ME.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH FILE THEN RERUN THE JOB. JOB ENDED OK. PERM: ADD A DELETE STEP AT TOP OF CL$$1180 TO DELETE THE CL.ME.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH FILE. REASON: SINCE FILE IS MULTI VOLUME, IF THE SIZE OF THE FILE OR EXTENTS IN BETWEEN THE TIME IT IS BACKED UP AND RESTORED, IT CAN LEAD TO THESE PROBLEMS. BEST SOLUTION IS TO DELETE THE FILE BEFORE RESTORING. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0120",
  "PROBLEM": "ABENDED WITH ABEND U4087 +PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0CX IGZ LOGIC ABEND TYPE = 0CX IGZ LOGIC ABEND AT LOCATION 0013FA IN ELEMENT CKBSDPCT A USER ABEND 4038 OCCURRED IN MODULE CEEPLPKA AT OFFSET X'CBE78'. +CKAB01 IGZ SUBROUTINE FAILURE... + TOKEN = 00040322 61C3C5C5 00000000 + CEE0802C HEAP STORAGE CONTROL INFORMATION WAS DAMAGED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "208 RECORDS PROCESS OK. RAN UNIT TEST RUNS TO NARROW DOWN THE OFFENDING RECORD. THE OFFENDING RECORD WAS NOT IN THE DUMP, WHICH MADE THIS HARDER TO SOLVE. ABENDING POLICY WAS - 3465066850 REVIEW OF RECORD SHOWS THAT CLIENT NAME HAD SEVERAL COMMAS AND PERIODS THAT DID NOT LOOK RIGHT. ,P.MURPHY,JOINTLY,T. MC RAE,P. WE THINK THE CORRUPTED NAME CAUSED THE PROGRAMS TO CORRUPT MEMORY WHICH AFFECT POLICIES FURTHER DOWN THE RECORD. ",
  "SOLUTION": "PART 1: EARLIER AS THE POLICY COULD NOT BE IDENTIFIED, SO DECIDED TO SKIP STEP0040,STEP0050, STEP0060 AND STEP0070 AND EXECUTE REST OF OF THE JOB. REASON WAS THESE STEPS DID NOT UPDATE MASTER FILES. ABOVE STEP WAS COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY AND THE CYCLE WAS RESUMED TO MEET THE ONLINE DEADLINE. PART 2: ONCE THE ABENDING POLICY WAS IDENTIFIED, IT WAS DELETED FROM A COPY OF THE INPUT GDG AND GOT THE JOB RE-EXECUTED FROM TOP TO STEP0070 ONLY. WITH THIS ACTION, ALL THE REMAINING STEPS STEPS (THAT WERE SKIPPED IN PART I OF RESOLUTION) WERE COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. NEXT DAY: HAD BUSINESS FIX THE CLIENT NAME. THIS POLICY HAD BEEN SUSPENDED AND NOT BILLED IN A LONG TIME. THE CLIENT NAME HAD BEEN IN THIS STATE FOR A LONG TIME, BUT ONCE IT TRIED TO BILL, IT ABENDED ON THIS ODD NAME. ALSO DETERMINED THAT THE CAUSE OF THE ABEND WAS THE EXISTENCE OF A ',' COMMA IN THE FIRST POSITION OF THE CLIENT NAME. IF THIS OCCURS AGAIN, CATALOG DP1SDP02 FROM STEP0040, REVIEW FILE FOR EXISTENCE OF ',' IN FIRST POSITION OF NAME FIELD. IF YOU GET A HIT, DROP THIS RECORD FROM COPY OF CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.BILLEXTS(-0) AND RERUN THE JOB. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "IN THE EVENT THAT THERE ARE PROBLEMS WITH THESE JOBS, YOU MAY HAVE TO CREATE THE S&P 500 FUND INPUT CARD MANUALLY. SEE TEST.CL.BOMBLOG(SPFUNDS). "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0160",
  "PROBLEM": "-STEP=STEP0010 PGM=ADRDSSU EXECUTED - COND CODE 0008 TASK 051 TASK 052 ADR412E (051)-DYNA (02), DATA SET CL.VSAM.BASEOL.DXREGSRV COMPONENT CL.VSAM.BASEOL.DXREGSRV.DATA STOR2C FAILED SERIALIZATION ADR801I (051)-DDDS (01), 2016.226 01:39:08 DATA SET FILTERING IS COMPLET AND 0 FAILED FOR OTHER REASONS ADR455W (051)-DDDS (01), THE FOLLOWING DATA SETS WERE NOT SUCCESSFULLY P CL.VSAM.BASEOL.DXREGSRV ADR006I (051)-STEND(02), 2016.226 01:39:08 EXECUTION ENDS PAGE 0023 5695-DF175 DFSMSDSS V1R13.0 DATA SET SERVICES 2016.22 ADR013I (051)-CLTSK(01), 2016.226 01:39:08 TASK COMPLETED WITH RETURN CO ADR016I (052)-PRIME(01), RACF LOGGING OPTION IN EFFECT FOR THIS TASK ADR006I (052)-STEND(01), 2016.226 01:39:08 EXECUTION BEGINS ADR412E (052)-DYNA (02), DATA SET CL.VSAM.BASEOL.DXSTART COMPONENT CL.VSAM.BASEOL.DXSTART.DATA STOR8A FAILED SERIALIZATION ",
  "ANALYSIS": "AND CL.VSAM.BASEOL.DXSTART FAILED SERIALIZATION ON NIGHT OF AUXSEGH CONVERSION TO SMS. FAILED SERIALIATION MEANS FILES IN USE. SOME SORT OF TIMING ISSUE? DXREGSRV AND DXSTART WERE IN USE BY CICSD DXREGSRV AND DXSTART ARE NOT A PART OF 24X7 SO NOT SURE WHY THESE FILES HAD A PROBLEM THIS NIGHT. THESE FILES HAVE HAD A SIMILAR ISSUE UNDER SNAP. ",
  "SOLUTION": "JOB OK SINCE WE DON'T HAVE TO HAVE A SA BACKUP OF THE GUI FILES. IF IT HAPPENS AGAIN, WE WILL INVESTIGATE FURTHER. UPDATE-JOB KEPT FAILING AFTER 8\/12\/16 EVERY DAY. JP RECPOMMENDED ADDING TOLERATE ENQ FAILRE TO CARD TOLERATE(ENQF) - JOB NO LONGER ABENDS ON THESE FILES. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "TRYING TO FLASH COPY A CK4 ALTERNATE INDEX FILE COPY DATASET(INCL(CK4.VSAM.BASEOL.ULIFINQ$)) - RENAMEU((CK4.VSAM.BASEOL.ULIFINQ$, - TEST.CK4.WET.VSAM.SHK.ULIFINQ$), - (CK4.VSAM.BASEOL.ULIFINDX, - TEST.CK4.WET.VSAM.SHK.ULIFINDX)) - REPLACEU - SHARE SPHERE ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ADR412E (030)-DYNA (02), DATA SET CK4.VSAM.BASEOL.ULIFINQ$ COMPONENT CK4 VOLUME STOR9B FAILED SERIALIZATION ADR412E (030)-DDFLT(02), DATA SET CK4.VSAM.BASEOL.ULIFINDX IN CATALOG CA ADR801I (030)-DDDS (01), 2016.125 14:08:09 DATA SET FILTERING IS COMPLET AND 0 FAILED FOR OTHER REASONS ADR455W (030)-DDDS (01), THE FOLLOWING DATA SETS WERE NOT SUCCESSFULLY P CK4.VSAM.BASEOL.ULIFINQ$ AIX: CK4.VSAM.BASEOL.ULIFINDX ADR006I (030)-STEND(02), 2016.125 14:08:09 EXECUTION ENDS ADR013I (030)-CLTSK(01), 2016.125 14:08:09 TASK COMPLETED WITH RETURN CODE 8 ",
  "SOLUTION": "THE INPUT TO CK4.SB BECAUSE THE FILE IS IN USE. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "ERROR WHILE TRYING TO USE FLASH COPY FOR RESTORE JOB CL$$R127 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "IEW4000I FETCH FOR MODULE ADRDSSU FROM DDNAME -LNKLST- FAILED BECAUSE INSUFFICIENT STORAGE WAS AVAILABLE. CSV031I LIBRARY ACCESS FAILED FOR MODULE ADRDSSU , RETURN CODE 24, REASON CODE 26080021, DDNAME *LNKLST* CSV028I ABEND106-0C JOBNAME=P1T9TR27 STEPNAME=STEP0010 IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 867 SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=106 REASON CODE=0000000C ",
  "SOLUTION": "EXECUTE THE JOB BY GIVING REGION=0M PARAMETER IN JOBCARD "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "RIMMELE CALLED AND SAID THAT THE EDRB RELEASE INSTALL NIGHT(WHICH INCLUDED CHANGES TO EDRM) WAS SUCCESSFUL AND THAT RUNSTATS WAS RAN, BUT SINCE CL$$BIND WAS NOT RAN, CYBERLIFE WAS PRODUCING A -904 ERROR. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS PARTICULAR -904 ERROR, THE REASON CODE WAS INDICATING THE CODE PACKAGE WAS NOT VALID. THAT TRANSLATES TO THE MOST EFFICIENT ACCESS PATH WAS NOT BEING USED AND WOULD RESULT IN EXTREME SLOWED PERFORMANCE ISSUES. USERS THEN REPORTED SLOWNESS WHILE SUBMITTING APPS AND ALSO RECIEVED A 904 MESSAGE IN THE GUI MESSAGE BOX: OVERRIDE: 03\/24\/2016 115 362 OPN REQ EDU DB ERR 904-AGT SOE35 BATCH WAS OK, SINCE IT HAS CAPABILITY TO RESESTABLISH THE THE BEST ACCESS PATH. ONLINE CAN'T DO THAT WITHOUT BIND. ",
  "SOLUTION": "FIX. NOTIFIED NEW BUSINESS TO GET OUT OF CYBERLIFE TO STOP ANY ADDITIONAL ACTIVITY. WE RAN CL$$BIND. BUT BEFORE WE RAN BIND, MARCIE SAID WE HAD TO KILL ANY ACTIVE CICS THREADS IN THE DB2 EDRM DATABASE BEFORE WE DO THE PACKAGE REBINDS. MARCIE SENT LIST OF ACTIVE THREADS AND WE SENT LIST TO COGNIZANT CICS, PAUL CASA, TO LOOK AT BUT HE DOESN'T HAVE HAVE THE AUTHORITY TO KILL DB2 THREADS. POOLAE460001 POOLAE460003 POOLAE460006 POOLAE460013 POOLAE270002 THE ONLY THING PAUL SAW WAS TRX AE46. PAUL SAIS THAT TRX AE46 CKCI0022 WILL PREVENT ANY MORE THREADS FROM BEING OUT THERE BUT HE IS NOT SURE IS THIS WILL KILL THE CURRENT THREADS OR AFFECT ANYONE ELSE. MARCIE WAS CONCERNED THAT KILLING THE POOL THREADS WOULD AFFECT ANYTHING DOWNSTREAM. BOTH PAUL AND MARCIE WERE CONCERNED OF THE AFFECT OF ANY DOWNSTREAM PROCESSES IF THESE THREADS WERE KILLED. RATHER THAN HAVE PAUL BRING IN COGNIZANT DB2 RESOURCE, WE INSTRUCTED MARCIE TO KILL THOSE CICS POOL THREADS, THEN WE WERE ABLE TO RUN BIND. SINCE PAUL COULD NOT SEE THOSE THREADS, MARCIE WAS MORE COMFORTABLE THAT THEY WERE ISOLATED TO DB2 AND WENT AHEAD AND KILLED THEM. CL$$BIND WAS THEN RAN AND THE 904 MESSAGE WENT AWAY AND NORMAL RESPONSE TIME RESUMED. LONG TERM FIX -MARCIE HAS ADDED A STEP TO ALWAYS RUN BIND IN THEIR DB2 RUNBOOKS FOR EDRM. -IF WE GET A 904 AGAIN, THE NOTIFY THE DB2 ADMINSTRATOR TO REVIEW THE ERROR(NOT ALL 904 HAVE THE SAME PROBLEM). -IF THE DB2 ADMINSTRATOR INDICATES BIND NEEDS TO BE RAN DURING THE DAY, WE NEED TO NOTIFY THESE GROUPS TO EXIT CYBERLIFE UNTIL WE CAN GET CL$$BIND RAN. M.AUL.IND.LIFENEWBUSINESS <IND.LIFENEWBUSINESS@ONEAMERICA.COM> M.AUL.IND.ANNUITYNEWBUSINESS <IND.ANNUITYNEWBUSINESS@ONEAMERICA.COM> M.AUL.IND.UNDERWRITING <M.AUL.IND.UNDERWRITING@ONEAMERICA.COM> -THE ABOVE LIST SHOULD INCLUDE LIFE AND NEW BUSINESS, UNDERWRITERS AND CASE MANAGERS. -MARCIE CAN RUN BIND OR THE CYBERLIFE PRODUCTION SUPPORT TEAM WILL NEED TO HAVE PCD RUN IT. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$8003",
  "PROBLEM": "837-08,IFG0554A,CL$$8003,STEP0010,OUTFILE,2070,STOR5 CL.CL$$8003.UNIT.VALUES IT WAS TRYING TO PROCESS UNITS FROM 2\/27 TO 02\/29. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "REASON CL$$8003 ABENDED IS DUE TO THE FACT THE FILE WAS LARGE. THE FILE WAS LARGE DUE TO A LOOP. THE LOOP WAS DUE TO THE FACT THAT CKDCARTH DOES NOT HANDLE LEAP LEAP DAY OR DO ITS MLV ALIGNMENT CORRECTLY. HERE IS WHAT HAPPENS: ADD +1 TO 02\/28\/2016, CKDCARTH RETURNS 03\/01\/2016 ADD +1 TO 02\/29\/2016, CKDCARTH RETURNS 03\/01\/2016 THE PROBLEM IS NOT WITH 2\/29 BUT WITH 2\/28. IT JUMPS FROM 02\/28 TO 3\/1 AND THEN THE DATES ARE OUT OF SYNC WITH THE LOGIC. ",
  "SOLUTION": "UNITVAL TO UNITVAL3 AND MADE 2 LINE TEMP CHANGE BELOW. EDIT TEST.CL.WET.JCL(UNITVAL3) - 01.08 COLUMNS 00001 COMMAND "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0106",
  "PROBLEM": "+UNABLE TO RETRIEVE STUB POOL RECORD +IDI0002I MODULE D724ANNV, CSECT CKETRINV, OFFSET X'B90': ABEND U0001 USER COMPLETION CODE=4039 REASON CODE=00000000 IEF450I CL$$0106 STEP0440 CL$$0106 - ABEND=S04C U0000 REASON=00000000 802 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB WAS DELAYED AND RUNNING IN THE EARLY MORNING BUSINESS HOURS. IT LIKELY RAN INTO A POLICY THAT HAD BEEN UPDATED THIS MORNING CAUSING A CLIENT DISCREPANCY ",
  "SOLUTION": "WAITED FOR THE PARMDATE TO FLIP TO TODAY'S DATE AT 8:00 AND RESTARTED THE JOB IN STEP0440. THERE WERE FOUR STEPS TO COMPLETE WHICH INCLUDED TWO ULTIM REPORTS AND AN EMAIL STEP. THE DATES IN THESE REPORTS WILL BE ONE DAY OFF. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0690",
  "PROBLEM": "THE DAY AFTER NON-PRICING CYCLE OVERRIDES WERE NOT SET UP FOR THAT CYCLE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE SORT IN DATA MUST GO BACK ONE MORE GENERATION IN ORDER TO GET THE VALUES IT SHOULD HAVE GOTTEN YESTERDAY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "INSTEAD OF THIS OVERRIDE: \/\/JSTEP010 EXEC PROC=CL$$0690, \/\/ GEN01='-2' USE THIS OVERRIDE: \/\/JSTEP010 EXEC PROC=CL$$0690, \/\/ GEN01='-3' RUN THE JOB IN THE MORNING. UPLOAD THE FOUR OUTPUT FILES TO TEXT FILES. RENAME THE CL.CL$$0690.OMNIMAN(+0) FILE TO OTIMPORT.CL.YYYYMMDD.DAT WHERE YYYYMMDD IS THE CURRENT DATE (TWO DAYS AFTER THE NON-PRICING CYCLE). CHANGE THE DATES WITHIN THE FILE TO THE CURRENT DATE. SEND THESE FILES TO LINDA KIENTZ, MATTHEW HOBSON AND KEN MEYER TO LOAD INTO OMNITRADE. SEND THE TEXT FILES TO HEATHER HINOJOSA TO LOAD INTO ACCOUTING. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0600",
  "PROBLEM": "THE DAY AFTER NON-PRICING CYCLE OVERRIDES WERE NOT SET UP FOR THAT CYCLE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE SORT IN DATA MUST GO BACK ONE MORE GENERATION IN ORDER TO GET THE VALUES IT SHOULD HAVE GOTTEN YESTERDAY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "INSTEAD OF THIS OVERRIDE: \/\/STEP0210.SORTIN DD DSN=CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT(-1), \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) \/\/ DD DSN=CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT(-0), \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) USE THIS OVERRIDE: \/\/STEP0210.SORTIN DD DSN=CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT(-2), \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) \/\/ DD DSN=CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT(-0), \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0501",
  "PROBLEM": "CKETRGET, OFFSET X'45A': ABEND S0C1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS WAS A CLIENT ERROR DUE TO PARMDATE SINCE THE JOB RAN AFTER 8:00 WHEN THE PARMDATE SHOULD CHANGE. TRIED USING 12\/11 AND THEN 12\/12 - BOTH FAILED ON THE SAME POLICY 0620765340. CHECKED CLIENT AND FOUND PERSON 30 HAD A SEQUENCE NUMBER OF 3. ON THE SB BEING USED BY THE JOB THE SEQUENCE FOR PERSON 30 IS 1. FOUND THAT IS TRUE IN THE SA FILE ALSO. ONLY THE CURRENT FILE HAS A PERSON 30 WITH A SEQUENCE OF 3. ",
  "SOLUTION": "OVERRIDE TO POINT TO THE CURRENT PENDING AND AUXSEG2 FILES INSTEAD OF THE SB FILES. USED PARMDATE 12\/12. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$9601",
  "PROBLEM": "- -------- 1) COPIED THE POLICY AND AUXSEG1 MASTER FILES - CL.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY TO TEST.CL.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY.D110215 CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG1 TO TEST.CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG1.D110215 2) DELETED THE ",
  "ANALYSIS": "POLICY# 5820399270 FROM THE ABOVE COPIED FILES. 3) PROVIDED THE OVERRIDES FOR POLICY AND AUXSEG1 FILES IN STEP0010. 4) HAD OPS TO RERUN THE JOB FROM LIBRARY TEST.CL.CSC.JCLLIB(CL$$9601) FROM TOP. JOB ENDED OK WITH THE ABOVE RESOLUTION. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$PNDR",
  "PROBLEM": "- -------- 1) FORCE COMPLETED THE JOB. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0010",
  "PROBLEM": "- -------- 1) COPIED CARDIB CLH0010 FROM PROD.CL.CARDLIB TO TEST.CL.CSC.CARDLIB. 2) PROVIDED THE NEW VOLUMES IN COPIED CARDLIB. 3) RERUN THE STEP0040 ONLY. 4) INFORMED TO OPS TO RERUN THE JOB FROM TEST.CL.CSC.JCLLIB 5) JOB-ENDED-OK WITH ABOVE RESOLUTION. ------------ "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "- DUE TO INITIALIZATION PROBLEM OF A VARIABLE IN D8240010 ------- PROGRAM. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "- -------- 1) AS PER SPOOL WE FIGURED OUT THAT THE JOB GOT ABENDED FOR POLICY 0620630180 WE DELETED THE ABENDING POLICY FROM BACKUP OF INPUT FILE 'CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.BILLEXTS.G4180V00' AND RESTARTED THE JOB FROM TOP, JOB ABENDED AGAIN WITH THE SAME REASON -------------------------------- 2) WE RAN THE UNIT VERSION OF THE JOB BY KEEPING JUST ABENDING POLICY IN INPUT FILE AND JOB EXECUTED SUCCESFULLY ----------------------- 3) AS A RESULT, WE CONCLUDED THAT IT MIGHT BE BECAUSE OF INITIALIZATION PROBLEM IN PROGRAM D8240010. ",
  "SOLUTION": "- -------- 1) AS PER THE OFFSET PRESENT IN THE SPOOL WE IDENTIFIED BELOW LOCATION IN PROGRAM COMPUTE WS-NOL-TOTAL-AMOUNT-DUE = WS-TAG-TOTAL-DATA9 * WS-NOL-MONTHS-DUE 2) AS SEEN IN THE DEFINITION THE VARIABLE IS INITIALIZED WITH VALUE '+002' 3) WE INITIALIZED WS-NOL-MONTHS-DUE VARIABLE IN \"PERFORM 100-INITIALIZE THRU 100-EXIT.\" AS SHOWN BELOW: 100-INITIALIZE. ............ ............ CL5124 INITIALIZE CK4-VS-GENERAL-PARMS. CL4392 INITIALIZE CL-DOC-RECORD. *TEST MOVE +002 TO WS-NOL-MONTHS-DUE. <-- INITIALIZE ------------------------------ 4) THIS VARIABLE SHOULD BE INITIALIZED AT ALL THE PLACES WHEREVER IT IS GETTING UTILIZED. 5) COMPILED AND RELINKED IN TO TEMPORARY LOAD 6) PROVIDED OVERRIDE TO PICK NEW LOAD FROM TEMPORARY LIBRARY 7) JOB-ENDED-OK WITH ABOVE SOLUTION ------------ "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "DID NOT FAIL BUT PRODUCED THIS EMAIL: IDOC0340 COMPLETED BUT HAS RATE ERRORS THAT NEED T TO BE INVESTIGATED. BROWSE 'IDOC0340 REPORTS' IN CONTROL-D USER REPORT THIS ALERT WAS TRIGGERED BECAUSE ONE OF THESE MESSAGES WAS FOUND IN THE 'IDOC0340 REPORTS' REPORT: AUUDT061 TABLE LOOKUP FAILURE ERROR OCCURED DURING INDEX RATE LOOKUP RATE RECORD LOCATED FOR INCORRECT PERIOD ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE BOTTOM OF THE REPORT OUT OF CL$$UINT FOR ERRORS: CL.CL$$UINT.STEP0020.SYSRPT IN THIS CASE, THERE WAS THIS MESSAGE: 1827-DUPLICATE RATE ENTRY ON RECORD REVIEW AND DISCUSS WITH ACTUARIAL ON REBUILDING THE RATES ",
  "SOLUTION": "ACTUARIAL RESUBMIT THE CL$$UINT FORM WITH THE CORRECTED RATES. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "FORGOT TO CHANGE THE MAINFRAME TIME FOR DAYLIGHT SAVINGS TIME. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "TIME WAS 9AM, MAINFRAME TIME WAS 8AM BIGGEST IMPACT WOULD BE THE 4PM CUTOFF FOR TRADES. IF THIS WAS NOT FIXED BY 4PM, WE COULD HAVE GAIN\/LOSS FOR THE LAST HOUR 3-4PM THAT WE WERE BEHIND. NEXT IMPACT WAS THE 11AM PAGE CYCLE. WE PUT ON HOLD. ALSO DETERMINED: -DB2 SHOULD NOT BE AFFECTED, ALTHOUGH TIMESTAMP IS A PART OF THE CLIENT ID, WHAT EVER CLIENTID THAT WAS BUILT WOULD BE LINKED AND ATTACHED TO ALL SUB TABLES. NO AFFECT. -INFORMATICA SCHEDULING WOULD NOT BE IMPACTED. OPERATIONS DETERMINED THEY CAN DYNAMICALLY CHANGE THE TIME IN ALL CICS REGIONS WITHOUT TAKING THE REGIONS DOWN. -THEY DID HAVE A CONCERN ABOUT TRX THAT ARE SCHEDULED, IE. 0005,0009, BUT WE INFORMED THEN THAT WE CAN DO THOSE MANUALLY IF NEEDED. SINCE WE HAD ENOUGH TIME BEFORE THE TIME CHANGE, WE RELEASED PAGES AND THEY COMPLETED BEFORE THE TIME CHANGE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "TO CHANGE THE TIME AT 12:15 ACTUAL TIME SO THAT WE WERE NOT ON THE HOUR, WHICH MIGHT CONFLICT WITH JOBS THAT KICK OFF ON THE HOUR. NOTIFIED USERS TO AVOID DOING TRX UPDATES BETWEEN 12:10 AND 12:20PM. THE MAINFRAME TIME WAS CHANGED FROM 11:15 TO 12:15 (THIS ONLY TOOK ABOUT 2-3 MINUTES FOR OPERATIONS) VALIDATION -CHECKED TSO TIME -CHECK TIME IN THE CICS REGIONS -BROUGHT UP POLICY IN GUI. -BROUGHT UP POLICY IN 3270. -SINCE 0005 HAD BEEN RUNNING AT 1 HR INTERVALS, 9:50, 10:50 AND WE WOULD HAVE SKIPPED THE 11:50 RUN, ROUTED TO SYSD AND DID 0005, WHICH KICKED OFF 0005 AT 12:16PM. -THE NOON RUN OF CL$$0035 AUTOMATICALLY KICKED OFF AT 12:21 AS DESIRED SINCE WE HAD JUMPED FROM 11:15 TO 12:15. -SCREENLOG CHANGED IMMEDIATELY AND COMPLETELY WITH NO OVERLAP. -THE LAST GOOD RESPONSE FROM MIB WAS SENT AS RESPONSE TO CICSD ON 2015-03-09 12:13 AFTER THE TIME CHANGE, MIB CONTINUED TO WORK SENT AS RESPONSE TO CICSD ON 2015-03-09 12:33 -NOTIFIED USERS TO RESUME OPERATIONS, BUT TO LOG OFF AND BACK ON CYBERLIFE TO PICK UP THE CORRECT TIME. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0690",
  "PROBLEM": "M&E FILE WAS EMPTY. CLCL$$0690.OMNIMAN(0), CL.ABC.OMEACCT(0), CL.CL$$0690.ADJUST.OUTPUT(0), CL.ADJUST.OUPLOAD(0) ",
  "ANALYSIS": "OMNI CREATED AN EMPTY CL.FUND.PRICES, SO CL$$0010 CREATED CL.FUND.PRICES.SORTED(0) WITH ONLY THE 38 FUNDS THAT DO NOT COME FROM OMNI. THIS GDG WAS NOT DELETED WHEN CL$$0010 WAS RERUN. ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. USE FIRECALL TO DELETE CL.FUND.PRICES.SORTED(-1) 2. USE FIRECALL TO RERUN CL$$0690 OVERRIDING PARMDATE AND CL.CL$$8002.FUND3.SORT(0) WITH (-1). 3. USE FIRECALL TO CHANGE THE DATES FROM 9\/19 TO 9\/22 IN CL.CL$$0690.OMNIMAN(0) AND CL.CL$$0690.ADJUST.OUTPUT(0) 4. ADD OVERIDE TO CL$$0700 STEP0040.SORTIN TO ADD CL.CL$$0690.ADJUST.OUTPUT(-1) FROM #3. 5. SET UP CL$$SEGD TO MERGE CL.CL$$0690.OMNIMAN(-1) FROM #3 AND CL.CL$$0690.OMNIMAN(0). ADD DEPENDENCY TO WAIT FOR CL$$0690. 6. ADD DEPENDENCY TO FTPICL1100 TO WAIT FOR CL$$SEGD. 7. INFORM HEATHER HINOJOSA TO LOAD CL.ABC.OMEACCT(0) FROM THE FIRECALL RUN. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0103",
  "PROBLEM": "2650000030 SUSPENDED AFTER SWEEP WITH A CAP ERROR. AP0340 - TABLE NOT LOCATED CAP\/PART RATE LOOKUP ERROR ",
  "ANALYSIS": "STATED THE 5 YEAR POINT TO POINT CAP LOW BAND RATE FOR ISSUE DATE 04\/14\/2012 HAD THE WRONG EFFECTIVE DATE IN THE INTEREST RATE TABLE. JULIAN DATE 787 925 SHOULD BE 787 926 THIS IS DUE TO A RATE BANDING DATE RANGE CHANGE DONE DURING THE INITIAL INDEXED ANNUITY INSTALL AND AFTER POLICIES WERE ISSUED. NOT THAT MANY POLICIES WERE ISSUED DURING THE INITIAL INSTALL MONTH. TODAY'S RATES ARE ENTERED FOR THE 15TH TO COVER THE 15TH THRU THE NEXT MONTH'S 14TH. BUT AT STARTUP, THE RATES WERE ENTERED FOR THE 14TH OR THE ACTUAL SWEEP DATE. ACTUARIAL IS AWARE OF THIS ISSUE AND IS TASKED WITH CHANGING THE ADJUSTED DATES FOR THESE RATE RECORDS FOR DURATION 5, 7 AND 9 YEAR PLANS UNTIL THESE POLICIES HIT PORTFOLIO METHOD. THEY CHANGED THE ADJUSTED DATE ON MOST RECORDS BUT MISSED ONE. RAN TEST.CL.DLCTOOLS(PRTTB61) TO PRINT ENTIRE CKAPTB61 TBL. USED X ALL TO LOCATE DATES IN QUESTION AND YIELDED. 119SIX5N,XA,C,787,925,02,00.000,002.50,100.00,001.29 119SIX5Q,XA,C,787,925,02,00.000,002.50,100.00,001.29 ",
  "SOLUTION": "FMB TEST.CL.WET.CL$$TB61.FMB.G0001V00 FROM CL.CL$$TB61.FMB(0) AND EXTRACTED AFFECTED RECORDS. USED MY OWN UNIQUE AUDIT NUMBER, D42214 REPEATED THE TWO TBAD RECORDS SO I HAD 4. CHANGED FIRST TWO RECORDS TBAD TO TBMN AND ACTION=DELETE THEN UPDATED THE DATE ON THE TBAD RECORDS. RAN CL$$0018 AND UNSUSPENDED THE POLICY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0126",
  "PROBLEM": "DUPLICATE KEY ERROR ON POLICY 3361148336 CL.CL$$0120.STEP0090.FM01FM02.G4023V00 CONTAINED 600+ ACH DRAFTS THE KEY HAS A TWO DIGIT SEQUENCE NUMBER, SO IT CREATED DUPLICATE KEYS. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WHY DIDN'T THE POLICY GET ERROR AP0314 TO LIMIT THE NUMBER OF BILLS CREATED? BEFORE THE CYCLE BEGAN ON 03\/31, THE BILLED TO DATE ON THE POLICY WAS 04\/15\/1914 AND PAID TO DATE WAS 04\/15\/2014. THE ISSUE DATE OF THE POLICY IS 07\/15\/1988. A BILLED TO DATE LESS THAN THE ISSUE DATE IMMEDIATELY INDICATES SOMETHING WRONG WITH THE BILLED TO DATE (AND THE POLICY). BUT JUST FOR THE SAKE OF LOOKING AT WHY ULC100 DID NOT LIMIT THE PAC DRAFTS, ANMOL RUN A CYCLE WITH DISPLAYS IN HIS OWN WORLD AND HE FOUND THAT THE ULC100 TEST WAS BYPASSED FOR THE POLICY BECAUSE FBRBILDT-BILLING-DATE (BILLING DATE - CONTAINS THE PROCESSING DATE THAT THE LAST BILLING EXTRACT WAS CREATED FOR THIS POLICY) WHICH IS GENERALLY LESS THAN THE BILLED TO DATE WAS GREATER THAN THE BILLED TO DATE. THIS COULD BE DUE TO THE CENTURY BEING OFF IN THE BILLED TO DATE. FEBRUARY MONTH END BILLED TO DATE : 04\/15\/2014 PAID TO DATE : 04\/15\/2014 BILLING DATE : 022814 BEFORE CYCLE OF 033114 BILLED TO DATE : 04\/15\/1914 PAID TO DATE : 04\/15\/2014 BILLING DATE : 022814 AFTER CYCLE OF 033114 BILLED TO DATE : 11\/15\/1964 PAID TO DATE : 11\/15\/1964 BILLING DATE : 033114 WE FOUND THAT THE 1914 BILLED TO DATE WAS ENTERED VIA THE 2606 TRANSACTION IN 3270. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DELETED THE RECORDS FOR CONTROL NUMBER # 0857646 FROM BOTH THE INPUT FILE. RESTORED THE POLICY TO PRIOR MONTH END. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0865",
  "PROBLEM": "8 ERROR 59 AT CHARACTER POSITION 14: ILLEGAL COUNTER TYPE CHANGE. ERROR 59 AT CHARACTER POSITION 23: ILLEGAL COUNTER TYPE CHANGE. ERROR 59 AT CHARACTER POSITION 32: ILLEGAL COUNTER TYPE CHANGE. ERROR 59 AT CHARACTER POSITION 41: ILLEGAL COUNTER TYPE CHANGE. ERROR 59 AT CHARACTER POSITION 50: ILLEGAL COUNTER TYPE CHANGE. ERROR 59 AT CHARACTER POSITION 59: ILLEGAL COUNTER TYPE CHANGE. RESET <R,1\/SC,211,0\/SC,212,0\/SC,213,0\/SC,214,0\/SC,215,0\/SC,216,0>�99 * * * * * * ( 7) <RESET\/SETNEW> ",
  "ANALYSIS": "POLICY,3360028758, WITH AN 04 AGENT RECORD WAS MISSING DETAIL RECORDS. 3360028758000020012504042014BR501 04939 ROAD U04<MRKTMS9A> NOTE: THE ABOVE LINE IS THE ONLY LINE IN THE INPUT FILE FOR THIS POLICY NUMBER! ",
  "SOLUTION": "THAT ALL STEPS RAN AND HAD REASONABLE OUTPUT IN THE COMPOSE STEPS. -NOTICED AUL AGENTS AREN'T SUPPOSE TO GET PRINTED OUTPUT -THE ABENDING STEP ALSO HAD SIGNIFICANT OUTPUT IMPLYING THAT JUST THE OFFENDING RECORD WAS SKIPPED. -ITS NOT A ONE FOR ONE RECORD SO NO WAY TO BALANCE, YOU HAVE TO EYEBALL IT. -NO NEED TO DROP THE RECORD SINCE IT APPEARS THE OFFENDING RECORD WAS SKIPPED AN NO OUTPUT PRODUCED FOR THAT ONE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0021",
  "PROBLEM": "PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) ",
  "ANALYSIS": "1: (TO LOCATE BAD POLICIES & GET JOB RESTARTED ASAP) LOOKED AT IDIREPRT STEP0030 & DID A FIND ON 'D7XX' (WHERE XX IS THE COMPANY CODE - WHICH COULD BE 00 FOR AUL, 05 FOR SL, AND O1 FOR PML). LOOKED AT STEP0030 SYSOUT AND MAXED TO BOTTOM. SAW WAS TRYING TO PROCESS SL POLICIES..SO WAS PRETTY SURE PROBLEM WAS WITH SL POLICY. SO WENT INTO STEP0030 IDIREPRT AND DID A FIND ON 'D705' AND MAX'D TO RIGHT. FOUND 2 POLICIES, NOTE: WILL BE THE D7XX POLICY BELOW YOUR P0020 FILE DATA SET NAME . . . . . . : CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.GXXXXXX FILE ATTRIBUTES . . . . . : ORGANIZATION=SEQUENTIAL, WHICH TURNED OUT TO BE RELATED POLICIES (ONE A LIFE AND THE OTHER IT'S COB. SO COPIED PROD FILE CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT(0) TO TEST.CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.P032814 & REMOVED BOTH POLICIES. RAN CL$$0020 IN 'TEST' RESTARTING IN STEP30 & OVERRIDES IN STEP30 & STEP45 TO PICK UP EDITED FILE. JOB FINISHED OK. SO MAKE FRESH BACKUP FILE BY RECOPYING PROD FILE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "1: (TO LOCATE BAD POLICIES & GET JOB RESTARTED ASAP) USE FC ACCESS TO EDIT PROD FILE & REMOVE BAD POLICIES. CONTACTED PCD & HAD JOB RESTARTED IN STEP0030 WITH OVERRIDES IN STEP30 & 45 PICKING UP EDITED PROD FILE. JOB FINISHED OK. PUT IN EMAIL TO PCD (DAN LOUIE AND STEVE BLASZKIEWICZ) - FOR CL$$0021 - RESTART=JSTEP010.STEP0030 - WITH THESE OVERRIDES: - \/\/STEP0030.SEQUEN DD DSN=CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT(0) - \/\/STEP0045.SORTIN DD DSN=CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT(0) ANALYSIS 2: (DETERMINE PROBLEM WITH BAD POLICIES) THE PROBLEM IS COMING FROM CKVPMMVC WHICH IS TRYING TO DO A DATE CONVERSION ON EXTRA LIFE(03) SEGMENT CEASE DATE. --> THERE ARE MULTIPLE 03 SEGMENTS ON THIS POLICY WITHOUT HAVING --> A CEASE DATE WHICH APPEARS TO BE THE PROBLEM. 03 0058 00000000 00000000 102 5 0 00 1 00\/00\/1900 F .00 .00 .00 00\/00\/1900 00\/00\/1900 03 0058 00000000 00000000 102 6 0 00 1 00\/00\/1900 F .00 .00 .00 00\/00\/1900 00\/00\/1900 03 0058 00000000 10000000 2 5 0 00 1 00\/00\/1900 F .00 .00 .00 00\/00\/1900 03\/24\/2014 03 0058 00000000 10000000 2 6 0 00 1 00\/00\/1900 F .00 .00 .00 00\/00\/1900 03\/24\/2014 03 0058 00000000 00100000 1 5 0 00 1 03\/24\/2069 F .00 .00 .00 03\/24\/2069 03\/24\/2014 03 0058 00000000 00100000 1 6 0 00 1 03\/24\/2069 F .00 .00 .00 03\/24\/2069 03\/24\/2014 SOLUTION 2: UPDATE TICKET WITH FIRECALL AND RESTART INFORMATION, THEN REASSIGN THE TICKET TO TRIAGE: CUST.OA.IND.TRIAGE. ASK THEM TO NOTIFY USERS 'DO NOT REORDER PAGES ON THESE POLICIES UNTIL PROBLEM HAS BEEN RESOLVED!' AND GIVE THEM THE INFORMATION FROM ANALYSIS 2 (SEE --> ABOVE). NOTE: IF USER REORDERS PAGES AS IS, WILL CAUSE ADDITIONAL ABENDS AND DELAY PRINT DELIVERY! "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "SITESCOPE INDICATING PROBLEM WITH 3465114840 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "11-24@05:22:39 CICSD MQ07 AUDLOG: DSNT408I SQLCODE = -911, ERROR: 11-24@05:22:39 CICSD MQ07 AUDLOG: ROLLED BACK DUE TO DEADLOCK O ",
  "SOLUTION": "T-SYSTEMS SAID MQ07 WAS DISABLED AND THEN REENABLED AND THEN THE QUEUE WAS CLEANED OUT. LATER FOUND OUT IT WAS A MAINTENACE CONFLICT: THE T-SYSTEMS DB2 DBA HAD THE JOBS THAT RUN PRIOR TO MQAF9450 HELD IN ORDER FOR HIM TO PERFORM SOME ROUTINE SYSTEM MAINTENANCE. THIS IS SOMETHING HE OCCASIONALLY HAS TO DO AND HAS BEEN WITHOUT INCIDENT. �HOWEVER, THERE WAS SOME MISCOMMUNICATION BETWEEN 99 THE DBA AND THE OPERATORS AND THE JOBS DIDN'T GET RELEASED WHEN THE DBA THOUGHT HE HAD ASKED FOR THEM TO BE RELEASED. ONCE THE DBA REALIZED THE JOBS HADN'T BEEN PROPERLY RELEASED, HE HAD THEM RELEASED AND EVERYTHING RAN AS EXPECTED. UNFORTUNATELY, THIS WAS WAY LATER THAN NORMAL AND THE DEADLOCKS WERE THE RESULT. JOB "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "BRIAN GOT CALLED SATURDAY MORNING INTO A CONFERENCE CALLED ABOUT OLS AND ACCOUNT SERVICES DOWN. AT FIRST THEY WERE SAYING ALL OF... BUT LATER FOUUND IT WAS ONLY ONE POLICY. PROBLEM: MQJE001: COMPLETION CODE 2, REASON 2033 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "HE HAD USER TRY AGAIN AND IT STARTED WORKING. THEY WERE ABOUT TO BOUNCE CICS WHEN THEN REALIZED OTHER POLICIES WERE WORKING. SO THEY ENDED UP DOING NOTHING. ",
  "SOLUTION": "SO THEY ENDED UP DOING NOTHING. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$UINT",
  "PROBLEM": "DID NOT ABEND BUT ACTUARIAL REPORTED AN ERROR IN THE REPORT, AND DID NOT GET DESIRED RESULTS. 0101-STMT CODE MISSING\/INVALID ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB PRINTS A FULL FILE REPORT AND A MAINTENANCE REPORT THE MAINTENACE REPORT DID NOT GENERATE BECAUSE OF THIS ERROR. CHECKED THE PROGRAM CKUBINTB AND ERROR POINTS TO THE INPUT FILE. THE USER HAD A BLANK RECORD AT THE END OF THE DATA. ",
  "SOLUTION": "USER REMOVE THE BLANK RECORD AND RE-REQUEST CL$$UINT. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "GUI OUTAGE DUE TO ERROR CKDX0302 CKDX0302 COMMUNICATION LINK CANNOT BE ESTABLISHED ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CONNECTION IS LOST DUE TO FAILURE IN CL$$CLDD ",
  "SOLUTION": "INSTRUCTION IN H:\\CYBRLIFE\\PRODUCTION_SUPPORT_TEAM\\ HOW TO HANDLE CKDX0302 COMMUNICATION LINK CANNOT BE ESTABLISHED.DOC "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "ACCOUNT SERVICES - GETS ERROR MESSAGE AND ALL INFO IS JUMBLED ON THE SCREEN. USER GETS ERROR \"SERVLET EXCEPTION IN : WEB\/INF\/JSP\/INFORCE\/HEADERINCLUDE JSP CAN NOT GET VALUE FOR EXPRESSION # POLICY DATA OWNER NAME\" ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THERE IS NO 'ACTIVE' OWNER FOR THIS POLICY. THERE SHOULD BE AN 'ACTIVE' OWNER SEGMENT FOR EVERY POLICY. WEBSOLUTIONS IS NOT SUPPOSE TO FIX THIS. INDIVIDUAL IS SUPPOSE TO FIX THE POLICY ON OUR SIDE. THERE MAY BE AN 89\/90 SEGEMNT THAT EXIST, BUT IF THE OWNER IS TERMINATED, THIS PROBLEM OCCURS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "SEND TO TRIAGE TO HAVE USERS CORRECT THE POLICY SO THERE IS AN ACTIVE OWNER 89\/90 SEGMENT ON THE POLICY. "
 },
 null,
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0865",
  "PROBLEM": "CMP000037-I: COMPOSITION ERROR LOG FOLLOWS . . . . . . CMP000038-E: LINE 263; CIRCA OUTPUT PAGE 5 IN TEXT STRING FOOTNT04; CALLED AT LINE 263 OF SECONDARY INPUT FILE CMP000050-E: ERROR 4 AT CHARACTER POSITION 83: UNDEFINED COMMAND NAME. FOOTNT04 YOUR POLICY WILL LAPSE BEFORE THE NEXT POLICY ANNIVERSARY,``<BD\/ANNVDAT\/LT>`` UNLESS A PREMIUM OF AT LEAST * ``<BD\/PREMAMT\/LT>``IS RECEIVED BEFORE ``<``<BD\/RECVDAT\/LT>''. * * ",
  "ANALYSIS": "STOP 8 IN COMPOSE PGM=COMPUSET CC=8 ASTRICK IN ABOVE LINES INDICATES WHERE THE COMPUSET ERRORS ARE. STEP0890 IS PRINTING THE AGENT COPIES. THE CUSTOMER COPY DID NOT GET THIS ERROR. SO COMPARED AGENT FILE AGAINST CUSTOMER FILE (CL.CL$$0865.LPUL.OTAGCUST.G0604V00 VS CL.CL$$0865.LPUL.OTAGAGNT.G0604V00) & LOOKED FOR 'FOOTNT04' WHERE ERROR OCCURRED. CUSTOMER COPY HAS 3 DATA TAGS <#ANNVDAT=08\/01\/2014>, <#PREMAMT= $2,540.00 >, <#RECVDAT=09\/30\/2013> NOW FOUND IN THE AGENT FILE. ONLY HAPPENED IN 1 POLICY: 1000779658. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD JOB FORCED COMPLETE AND NOTIFIED TRIAGE THAT AGENT COPY OF ANNUAL STATEMENT HAS AN ERROR. TRIAGE PULLED STATEMENT AND WAS ABLE TO REPLACE P.5 OF AGENT COPY WITH P.5 OF CUSTOMER COPY. WM IDEA WAS OPENED: SRQ00017064 LOTS MORE DETAILS CAN BE FOUND IN K:\\IT WORK\\! IDEAS\\SRQ00017064\\ IDEA SRQ00017064.DOCX. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0007",
  "PROBLEM": "POLICY INFO NOT FEEDING TO OLS OR ACCOUNT SERVICES. 0720092710 ONLINE SERVICES (OLS) - ADDRESSES NOT MATCHING ON OLS BIRTHDAY LIST FROM LIFE EVENTS WITH CYBERLIFE ",
  "ANALYSIS": "INSERT FILES CREATED FROM CL$$0007 NOT FTD'D PROPERLY TO WEB SERVICES. ",
  "SOLUTION": "****THIS PROCEDURE USES A QUIKJOB INSTEAD OF THE MANUAL EDIT **** ****PROCEDURE OUTLINED IN EARLIER BOMBLOG ENTRIES, AND IS ES- **** ****PECIALLY USEFUL FOR SITUATIONS INVOLVING MULTIPLE POLICIES **** (1) RUN TEST.CL.JCLLIB(COPYOLS7) TO BACKUP \"THE 6 FILES\": CL.CL$$0007.POL.ADR(0) CL.CL$$0007.POL.COVERAG(0) CL.CL$$0007.POL.DIR(0) CL.CL$$0007.POL.PLAN(0) CL.CL$$0007.POL.PLANDIR(0) CL.CL$$0007.POL.WRAGT(0) (2) EDIT THE FILE TEST.CL.RDB.TBOLSPOL WITH THE APPLICABLE POLICY NUMBERS (3) RUN TEST.CL.JCLLIB(QJOLSFI7) WHICH IS THE QJ TO CREATE THE \"CLEANED\" (TEST) VERSION OF THE 6 FILES (4) IN FIRECALL, DELETE THE CURRENT VERSION OF THE 6 FILES & COPY IN THE \"CLEANED\" (TEST) VERSION OF THE 6 FILES. YOU CAN USE TEST.CL.JCLLIB(UPDOLS7) FOR THIS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0838",
  "PROBLEM": "U4038 IIGZ0020S A LOGIC ERROR OCCURRED. NEITHER FILE STATUS NOR A DECLARATIVE WAS SPECIFIED FOR FILE IMISCVAL IN PROGRAM D724DVAL AT RELATIVE LOCATION X'1858'. THE STATUS CODE WAS 46. FROM COMPILE UNIT D724DVAL AT ENTRY POINT D724DVAL AT COMPILE UNIT OFFSET +00001858 AT ENTRY OFFSET +00001858 AT ADDRESS 0DC024A0. WRONG ",
  "ANALYSIS": "BY NIGHTTIME SUPPORT: THE FOLLOWING ELEVEN POLICIES WERE PRESENT IN FILES CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR(0) AND CL.DLS.LIFECUST.SORT.DUPOUT BUT WERE NOT PRESENT IN THE FILE CL.CL$$0020.MISCVAL.G1511V00. 0720276090 0720281740 0720283480 0720286520 0720277440 0720283270 0720283570 0720286580 0720279010 0720283400 0720285760 WRONG ",
  "SOLUTION": "TOOK BACKUPS OF FILES & DELETED ALL 11 POLICIES FROM THE CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR & CL.DLS.LIFECUST.SORT.DUPOUT FILES AND HAD JOB RESTARTED. CORRECT ANALYSIS: THE ONLY POLICY OF THE ABOVE 11 THAT NEEDS TO HAVE AN ENTRY IN THE MISCVAL FILE IS POLICY 0720276090 BECAUSE IT HAS AN EBIR RIDER. THE OTHER 10 POLICIES WOULD HAVE WORKED FINE HAD THEY BEEN LEFT IN THE JOB. CAN TELL WHICH POLICIES SHOULD HAVE AN ENTRY IN MISCVAL FILE BY LOOKING FOR EBIR IN CL.DLS.RIDER.SORT.DUPOUT FILE. YOU CAN DO A SEARCH ON 'EBIR'. ANY 072 POLICY WITH AN 'EBIR' IN THE RIDER FILE SHOULD ALSO APPEAR IN THE MISCVAL FILE. IN THIS CASE, 0720274590, 0720274800, & 0720276090 ALL HAVE AN 'EBIR' IN THE RIDER FILE. HOWEVER, ONLY 0720274590 & 0720274800 APPEARED IN THE MISCVAL FILE. SO BY REMOVING THE ONE POLICY 0720276090 (USING THE SAME FILE BACKUPS AND DELETES) THE JOB WOULD HAVE RUN SUCCESSFULLY. SOLUTION: REMOVE ONLY THE POLICIES MISSING FROM THE MISCVAL FILE THAT HAVE AN 'EBIR' IN THE RIDER FILE. DO FILE BACKUPS AND DELETES AS IN WRONG SOLUTION AND HAVE JOB RERAN. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0801",
  "PROBLEM": "IN 05\/17, CYBERLIFE PROD CYCLE, JOB CL$$0801 ABENDED WITH SOC4 IN STEP0010. CEE3204S THE SYSTEM DETECTED A PROTECTION EXCEPTION (SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=0C4) FROM COMPILE UNIT D7240400 AT ENTRY POINT D7240400 AT COMPILE UNIT OFFSET +00001EA4 AT ENTRY OFFSET +00001EA4 AT ADDRESS 000094EC. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "INITIALLY THE JOB ABENDED FOR '29655 47202\", I RAN THE JOB IN UNIT WORLD AND FOUND THAT THE JOB IS ABENDING FOR ALL MOST ALL THE INPUT RECORDS AFTER THE ABENDING RECORD. HAD TALK WITH SANDY JEFF, PER DISCUSSION, IT IS OK TO REMOVE ALL THE RECORDS AFTER THE ABENDING RECORDS TO CONTINUE THE CYCLE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "REQUESTED OPERATION TO DELETE ALL THE RECORDS FROM \"29655 47202 Y\" TO \"SVF67 SZG13 Y\", AND RERUN THE JOB FROM THE TOP. JOB ENDED OK WITH THE RESOLUTION NEXT DAY: DETERMINED PROBLEM WAS THAT PROGRAM ONLY ALLOWS FOR 100 INPUT RECORDS AND USER WAS PASSING CLOSE TO 200. USER CAN EITHER BREAK THIS INCREMENTS OF 100 OR RERUN WITH A VERSION OF D7240400 THAT HAS PVEDIT ---- PAN.CL.DPANLIB(D7240400)--------------------- CHA COMMAND "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$0030 IN 06\/24\/26 NIGHT CYCLE, JOB CL$$0030 ABENDED WITH S04C AT STEP0120. MESSAGE FROM SPOOL - A SYSTEM ABEND 0C1 OCCURRED IN MODULE CKPFA07 CSECT CKETRGET AT OFFSET X'45A'. ABENDING POLICY #2650038530 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "****************** IMPORTANT NOTE ***************************** * * * READ ENTIRE ",
  "SOLUTION": "AS IT INCLUDES INCORRECT STEPS AS WELL * * * ****************** IMPORTANT NOTE ***************************** IT ABENDED FOR POLICY 2650038530.AS PART OF RESOLUTION POLICY WAS BYPASSED FROM BACKUP OF PENDING & AUXSEG2 AND JOB ENDED OK. BUT LATER FOLLOWING JOBS ABENDED DUE TO CLIENT ISSUE. CL$$0008 CL$$0035 CL$$0660 CL$$0815 CL$$8001 THE REASON OF ABOVE JOB FAILURE IS BECAUSE THE PURGE (PURG) UPDATES IN CL$$0030 WAS APPLIED TO PENDING\/AUXSEG2 BACKUP FILE INSTEAD OF CURRENT PRODUCTION FILE. AS A RESULT, THE PENDING CLIENT UPDATES WENT OUT OF SYNC WITH THE VSAMS. THE PROBLEM WITH THE 2650038530 POLICY IS THAT THERE WAS AN EXTRA 0002 RECORD ON THE VSAM THAT WAS NOT IN CLIENT. SOLUTION AT THE END OF CYCLE THIS PROBLEM WAS DETECTED AND IT WAS A MIGRATION DAY TO RESOLVE THE CLIENT SYNC PROBLEM, MADE AN EXCEPTION AND CLOSED THE PENDING\/AUXSEG2 IN CICSD(SINCE UAT TESTERS STOPPED WORKING). TOOK THE BACKUP PENDING\/AUXSEG2 FILE AND COPIED THEM TO CURRENT PRODUCTION AND THE SNAP INTERMEDIATE AND SNAP AFTER FILES. RHONDA AND BILL CHECKED AND CONFIRMED THAT NO PENDING UPDATES OCCURRED AFTER CL$$0030 TILL END OF THE CYCLE. ****************** IMPORTANT NOTE ***************************** * * * AS PART OF LESSON LEARNT WE SHOULD NEVER BYPASS THE POLICY * * FROM CL$$0030 JOB. * * * * CL$$0030 IS AN UPDATE JOB NOT AN EXTRACT JOB. * * * * ALWAYS CURRENT PROD FILE SHOULD BE USE IN JOB CL$$0030. * * * ****************** IMPORTANT NOTE ***************************** "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$0030 IN 05\/09\/2013 CYCLE CL$$0030 ABENDED WITH X'45' IN MODULE CKPFA07 WHICH IS A CLIENT ERROR. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "IT ABENDED FOR POLICY 0720271220.AS PART OF RESOLUTION POLICY WAS DELETED FROM PENDING & AUXSEG2 AND JOB ENDED OK.BUT AS PART OF LESSEN LEARNT WE SHOULD FIRST CHECK THE POLICY IN TABLE,IN ORDER TO CHECK THE TABLE NAME FIND KEYWORD CKCSTGET ,LIKE IN THIS CASE THE TABLE NAME FOUND WAS CISLOR AND IF YOU TRY TO TABLE CISLOR IN CKCSTGET YOU WILL SEE THE QUERY WHICH WAS IN EXECUTION AT THAT TIME.OPEN THE TABLE AND TRY MAPPING IT WITH 89 SEGMENT(TAKE PENDING PRINT WITH CISOFF).IN THIS CASE WE FOUND PERSON CODE \"00\" WITH SEQUENCE '02\" MISSING IN TABLE SO THATS WHY GOT CLIENT ERR. IDEAL SOLUTIOM WAS TO REMOVE THIS 89 SEGMENT ROW FROM PENDING OR AUXSEG2 FILE BY CHANGING IT TO SEGMENT 99. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$0010 IN 02\/04\/2013 CL PROD CYCLE, JOB CL$$0010 ENDED NOT OK WITH CC=01 IN STEP0070. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PRICES FOR SPFUND WAS MISSING IN THE FILE \"CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES(+0)\" ",
  "SOLUTION": "PERFORMED FOLLOWING STEPS:- USE THE FOLLOWING TO RETRIEVE THE S & P PRICES SOURCE: K:\\INDSYS\\PRODUCT DEVELOPERS TEAM\\PRODUCT DESIGN DOCUMENTATION (CYBERLIFE) \\INDEX ANNUITY\\INDEX ANNUITY S AND P CLOSING PRICE FEED.DOCX COPIED CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES.G3454V00 TO TEST.CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES. PROD3454. INSERTED FOLLOWING ROW PROVIDED BY DAVE AS THE LAST ROW IN THE ORIGINAL FILE. V00SPFUND10011020220130204201301495711088 DELETED -( USING FIRECALL ID) CL.FUND.PRICES.SORTED.G1913V00 CL.FUND.PRICES.SORTE2.G1913V00 CL.CL$$0010.ERRRPT.G1892V00 REQUESTED OPERATION TO RERUN JOB STEP0060 WITH BELOW OVERRIDE. \/\/STEP0060.SORTIN � DD �DSN=CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES(+0), � �� � 00282399 \/\/ � � � � � DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) � 00282499 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0700",
  "PROBLEM": "CL.CL$$0700.FUNDS.DETAIL(0) CREATED TRADE RECORDS WITHOUT NUMBER OF SHARES. CREATED AN ERROR IN OMNI TRADE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "POLICY 2453214560 PROCESSED AND REVERSED A WITHDRAWAL ON THE SAME DAY. D724FNDD WILL SKIP A 69 SEGMENTS WHEN FLAG C2 = 1 (REVERSAL) AND FUAUVALU-ASOF-UNIT-VALUE = 0. THIS POLICY'S 69 SEGMENTS HAD FLAG C2 = 1, FUAUVALU-ASOF-UNIT-VALUE = UNIT VALUE, FUAUNITS-NUMBER-OF-UNITS = 0. ",
  "SOLUTION": "INFORMED SEPARATE ACCOUNTS THAT A TRADE WAS NOT NEEDED. FURTHER ANALYSIS NEEDED ON IF 69 SEGMENT WAS WRONG OR IF D724FNDD NEEDS TO BE CHANGED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0127",
  "PROBLEM": "CORPORATE ONCALL FELT THAT THE INCREASE OF POLICIES ON THE CL.FIN.BANK.** GDG FILES FROM 10\/12 TO 10\/13-15 WAS EXCESSIVE AND PERHAPS WRONG. 10\/12\/12 CL.FIN.BANK.AUL.EXTS.G2610V00 280 RECORDS 10\/13-15\/12 CL.FIN.BANK.AUL.EXTS.G2611V00 7340 RECORDS 10\/12\/12 CL.FIN.BANK.PML.EXTS.G2125V00 30 RECORDS 10\/13-15\/12 CL.FIN.BANK.PML.EXTS.G2126V00 2890 RECORDS 10\/12\/12 CL.FIN.BANK.SL.EXTS.G2610V00 90 RECORDS 10\/13-15\/12 CL.FIN.BANK.SL.EXTS.G2611V00 870 RECORDS THE INPUT FILE FROM CL$$0120 TO CL$$0127 INCREASED BY THESE AMOUNTS: 10\/11\/12 CL.ACH.BANK.EXTS.G3470V00 270 RECORDS 10\/12\/12 CL.ACH.BANK.EXTS.G3471V00 390 RECORDS 10\/13-15\/12 CL.ACH.BANK.EXTS.G3472V00 11130 RECORDS ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE FIRST OF THE MONTH AND THE 15TH OF THE MONTH ARE HEAVY DATES FOR BILLING. THE NUMBERS COULD BE RIGHT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "USED ULTIM TEST.CL.ULTIM(PACPOLS2) TO CREATE A REPORT OF POLICIES WITH BILLING DATES OF THE 13TH, 14TH OR 15TH. RAN SAME JOB WITH A REPORT OF BILLING DATE 10\/12. THE RESULTS CONFIRMED THE LARGE INCREASE IS VALID. 414 RECORDS PROCESSED FOR THIS REPORT - 10\/12 10,947 RECORDS PROCESSED FOR THIS REPORT - 10\/13-15 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0004",
  "PROBLEM": "POLICIES NOT FEEDING TO OLS OR ACCOUNT SERVICES. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "INSERT FILES CREATED FROM CL$$0004 NOT FTD'D PROPERLY TO WEB SERVICES. ",
  "SOLUTION": "****THIS PROCEDURE USES A QUIKJOB INSTEAD OF THE MANUAL EDIT **** ****PROCEDURE OUTLINED IN EARLIER BOMBLOG ENTRIES, AND IS ES- **** ****PECIALLY USEFUL FOR SITUATIONS INVOLVING MULTIPLE POLICIES **** (1) RUN TEST.CL.JCLLIB(COPYOLS) TO BACKUP \"THE 4 FILES\": CL.CL$$0004.DIRECT CL.CL$$0004.DIRECT.SRT(0) CL.CL$$0004.POL.DIR(0) CL.CL$$0004.POL.PLN(0) (2) EDIT THE FILE TEST.CL.RDB.TBOLSPOL WITH THE APPLICABLE POLICY NUMBERS (3) RUN TEST.CL.JCLLIB(QJOLSFIX) WHICH IS THE QJ TO CREATE THE \"CLEANED\" (TEST) VERSION OF THE 4 FILES (4) IN FIRECALL, DELETE THE CURRENT VERSION OF THE 4 FILES & COPY IN THE \"CLEANED\" (TEST) VERSION OF THE 4 FILES. YOU CAN USE TEST.CL.JCLLIB(UPDOLS) FOR THIS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1940",
  "PROBLEM": "IDI0002I MODULE M7240CCR, CSECT CKETRINV, OFFSET X'18E': ABEND S0C1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CKETRLST HAVING PROBLEMS IN 0114-BUILD-COMP-AGENTS. TRIED RESTARTING FROM TOP WITHOUT ANY CHANGES TO RULE OUT CONTENTION POSSIBLITY, BUT IT STILL ABENDED. LOOKING IN DUMP, TABLE AREA SEEMED MAXED OUT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "INCREASED WORK-AGENT-ID IN M7240CCR FROM 500 TO 900. RESTARTED FROM TOP WITH TEMP LOADLIB JOB ENDED OK. WMS IDEA SRQ000014584 CREATED TO FIX PROBLEM PERMAMENTLY "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0020",
  "PROBLEM": "PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C4 (PROTECTION) AT LOCATION 0001F4 IN ELEMENT CKPPFP90 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS POLICY WAS MADE WITHDRAWN YESTERDAY NO PAGES ARE NEEDED. IT HAD BEEN SITTING AS PENDING SINCE 2007 ",
  "SOLUTION": "BYPASSED POLICY AND RESTARTED JOB IN STEP0030. --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0014",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB CL$$0014 WAITED FOR JOB PAC$1005 WHICH IN TURN WAS INDIRECTLY WAITING FOR AN AGENCY JOB AGCY5010 (WHICH WAS RUNNING LONG). OPERATIONS INFORMED US THAT AGCY5010 JOB IS RUNNING COMPARATIVELY SO LONG IN AGENCY AGCY CYCLES AND DUE TO THAT CL PROD CYCLE WAS DELAYED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB CL$$0014 EXPECTS AN INPUT PAYMENTS FILE FROM JOB PAC$1005. ",
  "SOLUTION": "AS PER OUR DISCUSSAION WITH RHONDA, IN ORDER TO RESUME THE DELAYED CL PROD CYCLE, WE HAVE PROVIDIED AN EMPTY INPUT FILE (IN PLACE OF INPUT FILE FROM PAC$1005) AS AN OVERRIDE IN CL$$0014 FOR LAST NIGHT AND THEN HAD OPS RELEASE THE JOB CL$$0014. FOLLOWING OVERRIDE WAS PUT IN JOB CL$$0014: \/\/STEP0070.IINPUT DD DSN=TEST.CL.PAC.CL.OCLPYMTL.EMPTY.D071712, \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) \/\/STEP0075.IINPUT DD DSN=TEST.CL.PAC.CL.OCLPYMTL.EMPTY.D071712, \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) JOB ENDED OK. SINCE WE RAN CL$$0014 WITH AN EMPTY INPUT PAYMENT FILE, IN THE NEXT CL PROD CYCLE THE THE GDG VERSION PAC.CL.OCLPYMTL(-1) SHOULD BE CONCATENATED ALONG WITH PAC.CL.OCLPYMTL(0) VERSION. SO THAT THE PREVIOUS DAY RECORDS SHOULD ALSO BE PROCESSED IN THE NEXT CYCLE. WHEN THE PAC$1005 DOES NOT RUN OR FOR ANY REASON PAC.CL.OCLPYMTL(0) IS NOT DELIVERED TO CL$$0014, SEND AN EMAIL TO DISTRIBUTION LIST \"ILFS APP\". EXPLAIN WHAT DID PROCESS AND WHAT DID NOT PROCESS. IN THE SITUATION WHEN CL$$0014 WAS RELEASED BEFORE PAC$1005 COMPLETED, THE PAYMENTS WERE NOT CREATED IN CYBERLIFE, BUT THE BANK DRAFTS WERE SENT TO THE BANK FROM PAC$1005. THE BUSINESS NEEDS THIS INFORMATION. 1\/21\/22 RSW "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0860",
  "PROBLEM": "-STEP=STEP0030 PGM=IKJEFT1B ABENDED - COND CODE S04C IEC614I PRLSE FAILED - RC 016, DIAGNOSTIC INFORMATION IS (081A00C4) , STEP0030,STOR65,CL.CL$$0860.SAPPH.G3229V00 IEC216I A14-04,IFG0202E,CL$$0860,STEP0030,SEQUEN5,27CC,STOR65,CL.CL$$086 IEC999I IFG0209L,CL$$0860,STEP0030 IEC614I PRLSE FAILED - RC 016, DIAGNOSTIC INFORMATION IS (081A00C4) , STEP0030,PUB010,SYS12199.T045654.RA000.CL$$0860.T4245034.H01 IEC216I A14-04,IFG0202E,CL$$0860,STEP0030,SYS00002,228E,PUB010,SYS12199. IEA794I SVC DUMP HAS CAPTURED: 195 DUMPID=002 REQUESTED BY JOB (CL$$0860) DUMP TITLE=CL$$0860 DADSM PARTREL ERROR TCB= 0085E758 W\/A=7FFF 9730 IEC999I IGG0290A,CL$$0860,STEP0030,228E,PUB010, IEC999I SYS12199.T045654.RA000.CL$$0860.T4245034.H01 +IDI0092S SHORT TERM INTERVAL EXCEEDED, THE SUBTASK IS CANCELED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DASD ISSUE OPENING OR CLOSING OR RELEASING THE FILE ",
  "SOLUTION": "AT FIRST, CSC TRIED RENAMING CL.CL$$0860.SAPPH.G3229V00 AS CL.CL$$0860.SAPPH.D071612 AND RESTARTED IN STEP0020. THAT DIDN'T WORK, GOT SAME ERROR, WE TRIED DELETING CL.CL$$0860.SAPPH(0) AND RECEIVED SAME ERROR ON NEXT TRY. CONTACTED T-SYSTEMS STORAGE. THEY TOLD US TO REMOVE THE RLSE PARAMETER FROM STEP0030 AND STEP0035. \/\/STEP0030.SEQUEN5 DD SPACE=(CYL,(300,30)) \/\/STEP0035.SORTOUT DD SPACE=(CYL,(300,30)) RESTARTED FROM TOP AND JOB ENDED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0838",
  "PROBLEM": "CC=8 CONTROL STATEMENTS FOLLOW. TRIGGERDB=DVDLIFE PAGEDEFINITIONLANG=XRX ALLOWERRORS=20 UNABLE TO PERFORM VARIABLE REPLACEMENT. UNSUPPORTED USE OF SL\/BEGIN\/END\/* IN LINE 41 OF MODLIST TRIGGER: 6, PRODUCT: AUL WHOLELIFE 2007 PAGES, COMPANY-CD: 00, CONTRACT-NUM: 0720219510 TOTAL ERRORS: 1. TOTAL DOCUMENTS PROCESSED: 5. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "USUALLY THIS MEANS THERE IS A PROBLEM WITH THE DLS ASSEMBLY PROCESS, MEANING THERE IS A FIELD MISSING OR MISMATCH IN THE DLS PRODUCT. TO 'TRACE' THE PROBLEM NEED: TO COPY CARDLIB 1) TO COPY CARDLIB 'CLDLSWL' INTO YOUR OWN LIBRARY & ADD ASMTRACE EX. TRIGGERDB=DVDLIFE PAGEDEFINITIONLANG=XRX ALLOWERRORS=20 ASMTRACE NOTE: DETAILED INSTRUCTIONS CAN BE FOUND AT: K:\\DLSIND\\HOW TOS & ERRORS\\ASMTRACE FOR DLSBATCH DEBUGGING 2) COPY THE APPROPRIATE CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G* FILE & DELETE ALL BUT THE PROBLEM POLICY - MAKE SURE TO USE 'PRESERVE' OR 'PRESERVE ON' WHEN EDITING THIS FILE! 3) RERUN YOUR VERSION OF CL$$0020 STARTING IN STEP0030, THEN --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! RUN CL$$0836, AND THEN CL$$0838 (POINTING TO THE ABOVE CARDLIB MEMBER YOU HAVE SET UP). ONCE IT RUNS YOU CAN PUT A QUESTION MARK ON THE JOB (?) & LOOK AT 'DLSTRACE CL$$0838 STEP0110'. HERE YOU CAN SEE EACH DLS PIECE USED OR FAILED (NOT USED)....AND IF IT ABENDS THAT SHOULD BE THE LAST PIECE IN THE TRACE LOG (!HOPEFULLY!). ",
  "SOLUTION": "IF IT IS A DLS PROBLEM, NEED TO WORK WITH DLS PERSON TO SEE IF IT CAN BE RESOLVED. IF THE PROBLEM WAS CAUSED BY THE FILE TRUNCATION ERROR (WHERE ZIP CODE VALUES GOT MESSED UP) THEN THE RERUN OF CL$$0838 WILL PROBABLY RUN OK. IF THIS HAPPENS, HAVE USER REORDER PAGES IN THE 11:00 AM CYCLE SO IT CAN FLOW THRU THE NATURAL PROCESS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0021",
  "PROBLEM": "+PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0CF (FLOATING DVIDE PROGRAM D724DLIF AT OFFSET X'DF8C'. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "0620557880 !!!!!!!! IMPORTANT NOTE RE CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT FILE!!!!!!!!! !!!!! CL$$0020\/CL$$0021 !!!! IMPORTANT NOTE: IF EDITING A CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT(0) !!!! FILE MAKE SURE YOU HAVE 'INITIAL MACRO . . PRESERVE' OR !!!! TYPE 'PRESERVE ON' ON THE COMMAND LINE! OTHERWISE YOU RISK !!!! TRUNCATING THE FILE WHICH CAN\/WILL CAUSE THE DATA TO !!!! BE BAD. USUALLY CAN TELL IN OWNER ZIP OR INSURED'S ZIP CODE !!!! FIELD IN THE DLS FILES (AFTER CL$$0020 HAS RAN). FOR EX. !!!! HAPPENED IN WL POLICY SO LOOKED AT CL.DLS.LIFECUST(0) USING !!!! COPYLIB DDLIFE & WAS ABLE TO SEE: !!!! DCUSOWNR-OWNER1-ZIP............... X'F7F5F2F4F3000000' !!!! INSTEAD OF DCUSOWNR-OWNER1-ZIP............... 01776 !!!! MOST OF THE TIME THESE TRUNCATION PROBLEMS WILL NOT AFFECT !!!! PRINTING OF THE PAGES BECAUSE THOSE FIELDS ARE FOR THE MOST !!!! PART - NOT PRINTED ANYWHERE...FOR THE MOST PART!!! !!!! OCCASSIONALLY IT CAN CAUSE SOMETHING ELSE TO MESS UP ON THE !!!! DLS ASSEMBLY - SO THAT POLICY SHOULD BE RERAN FROM CL$$0020. !!!!!!!! IMPORTANT NOTE RE CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT FILE!!!!!!!!! ",
  "SOLUTION": "MADE COPY OF THE FILE, DELETING BAD POLICY AND RESTARTED IN STEP0030 WITH EDITED FILE. --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! NOTIFIED TRIAGE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0103",
  "PROBLEM": "USER ABEND 0001 OCCURRED IN MODULE CKAP01V CSECT CKABEND AT OFFSET X'116'. THE ABEND WAS CAUSED BY MACHINE INSTRUCTION 4DE037C8 (BRANCH AND SAVE) IN MODULE CKAP01V CSECT CKDCARTH AT OFFSET X'552'. CALLING CHAIN CKAP01V CKUBMC00 CKUBMC00 P+3B34 E+3B34 CKAP01V CKUBHMNT CKUBHMNT P+1D08 E+1D08 CKAP01V CKDCARTH CKDCARTH P+552 E+552 CKAP01V CKABEND CKABEND P+116 E+116 CKAP01V CKUB01V CKUB01V P+6CC E+6CC ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE ABENDING POLICY # WAS 2052241230. ",
  "SOLUTION": "AS PER THE BOMBLOG INSTRUCTIONS PERFORMED THE FOLLOWING STEPS 1)HAD PCD RUN RESTORE JOBS CL$$R060 AND CL$$RCL4. 2)TOOK A BACKUP OF CL.VSAM.BASEOL.SCHDFL1 AS CL.VSAM.BASEOL.SCHDFL1.D05151 - USING FIRECALL ID 3)USING FILE MARVEL CHANGED DATES FROM 01349C015 (05\/15\/2012) TO 01351C015 (07\/15\/2012) IN FILE CL.VSAM.BASEOL.SCHDFL1 FOR THE ABENDING POLICY # 2052241230, SO THAT IT WOULD NOT PROCESS FOR CURRENT CYCLE. 4)RENAMED\/DELETED THE OUTPUT GDG DATASETS CREATED FROM PRIOR RUN OF JOBS CL$$0102 AND CL$$0103. 5)ASKED PCD TO RERUN THE JOB CL$$0102 FROM THE TOP(AS CL.VSAM.BASEOL.BATCHPAY WAS NOT EMPTY). 6)AFTER JOB CL$$0102 RAN SUCCESSFULLY,ASKED PCD TO RERUN THE JOB CL$$0103 FROM THE TOP. THE JOB CL$$0103 ENDED OK WITH ABOVE RESOLUTION. NEXT DAY-DETERMINED SOURCE OF ABEND WAS A BAD 64 SEGMENT WHICH IS A KNOWN PROBLEM THAT CAN OCCUR WHEN USER UPDATES THE AGENT FILE IN THE INCORRECT ORDER: BUILDING THE 05 LEVEL THEN THE 01 LEVEL. (PRIOR TO A LIFEPRO MOD, WHEN THEY DID THE TRXS IN THE WRONG ORDER, THE PROGRAM ABENDED, BUT NOW IT BUILDS A BAD 64 SEGMENT, THEN ABENDS IN TIME DRIVEN) 6264,2052241230; . 64 0064 00000000 10011111 01000000 01000000 **\/**\/**** BD*DEC*CNT BD*DEC BD*DEC*CNT BD*DEC*CNT BD*DEC*CNT BD*DEC*CNT BD*DEC*CNT BD*DEC*CN BD*DEC*CNT BD*DEC*CNT RAN CL$$SEGD TO DELETE THE CORRUPT 64 SEGMENT. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0021",
  "PROBLEM": "A SYSTEM ABEND 0C7 OCCURRED IN MODULE CKDPFSPS PROGRAM PROGRAM D724DLIF AT OFFSET X'DF8C'. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WL POLICY 0720203410: 05\/08\/12 WL POLICY 0720201660: 05\/23\/12 IT'S BECAUSE THERE ARE NOT PUA (SEG 14) RECORDS ON THE POLICY. SO BASICALLY THE POLICY IS SET UP WRONG. ",
  "SOLUTION": "THEY NEED AN 'AS' ENTRY IN THE 58 SEGMENT. MADE COPY OF THE FILE, DELETING BAD POLICY AND RESTARTED IN STEP0030 WITH EDITED FILE. --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! NOTIFIED TRIAGE TO FIX THE POLICY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0815",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB ENDED OK, ALL CC OK, BUT THERE WAS AN SQL-811 ERROR IN SYSOUT. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THERE ARE TWO PROBLEMS 1. THERE ARE DUPLICATES IN REPS, BUT SINCE THE PROGRAM USES A DEFAULT TERRITORY, THE DUPLICATE ERROR IS NOT CRITICAL. 2. CONTROLD DEFAULT MISSION CATEGORY WAS NOT SET. NORMALLY ONLY ABENDED JOBS OUPUT ARE HELD IN Q.O. BUT IF D-CAT IS NOT SET TO '*' IN THE SCHEDULE, THAT JOBS OUTPUT WILL BE HELD REGARDLESS OF CONDITION ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. NO ACTION NEEDED. JUST BE AWARE, IF JOB ABENDS AND YOU SEE AN -811 IN STEP0030 SYSOUT, THAT I IS ACCEPTABLE. REPS TEAM DOES NOT PLAN TO FIX THE DATABASE AS THIS KIND OF ERROR IS COMMON IN REPS FOR THE OTHER SYSTEMS. 2. PCD UPDATED SCHEDULE PARAMETER D-CAT TO BE '*'. THE OUTPUT IS NO LONGER HELD WHEN JOB ENDS OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0865",
  "PROBLEM": "A SYSTEM ABEND 0C4 REASON CODE X'4' OCCURED ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOUND ABENDING RECORD 0000756646 (NEXT RECORD) IN IDIREPRT ",
  "SOLUTION": "CREATED COPY OF INPUT CL.CL$$0860.LPUL.SORTED, REMOVED POL# 0000756646 RECORDS FROM FILE COPY, RESTART JOB CL$$0865.STEP0600 WITH OVERRIDE \/\/STEP0600.IINPUT01 DD DSN=TEST.CL.RMC.CL$$0860.LPUL.SORTED "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0861",
  "PROBLEM": "A SYSTEM ABEND 0C4 REASON CODE X'4' OCCURED IN MODULE IDIDA AT OFFSET X'13E000'. AN ATTEMPT WAS MADE TO ACCESS A PROTECTED STORAGE LOCATION USING AN INCORRECT STORAGE ACCESS KEY. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOUND ABENDING RECORD 0000353176 (NEXT RECORD) IN IDIREPRT ",
  "SOLUTION": "CREATED COPY OF INPUT CL.CL$$0860.LPWL.SORTED, REMOVED POL# 0000353176 RECORDS FROM FILE COPY, RESTART JOB CL$$0861.STEP0210 WITH OVERRIDE \/\/STEP0210.IINPUT01 DD DSN=TEST.CL.RMC.CL$$0860.LPWL.SORTED "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0650",
  "PROBLEM": "-805 ERROR +IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V9R1M0 (UK52917 2009\/12\/16) INVOKED BY ID +IDI0089I SUBSYSTEM IDISDB2P RC=4, RSN=40000004 ODBC DLL FUNCTION DSNAOCLI NOT FOUND. SUBSYSTEM IDIS SUBTASK TERMINATION RC=4 40000 +IDI0082E DB2 DB2P CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: ODBC DLL FUNCTION D +IDI0089I SUBSYSTEM IDISUPDI RC=4, RSN=7FFFFFFF ODBC DLL FUNCTION DSNAOCLI NOT FOUND. SUBSYSTEM IDIS SUBTASK TERMINATION RC=4 40000 +IDI0002I MODULE D724CNSL, PROGRAM D72INTER, OFFSET X'18C4': ABEND +IDI0003I FAULT ID F23783 ASSIGNED IN HISTORY FILE SYS2.FA.HIST.BA IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 351 USER COMPLETION CODE=4039 REASON CODE=00000000 IGZ0020S A LOGIC ERROR OCCURRED. NEITHER FILE STATUS NOR A DECLAR D72INTER AT RELATIVE LOCATION X'18C4'. THE STATUS CODE W FROM COMPILE UNIT D72INTER AT ENTRY POINT D72INTER AT COM AT ADDRESS 0DC7B884. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "INFORMATION ABOVE IS DECEPTIVE. LOOKING IN THE DUMP I FOUND THE FOLLOWING -805 DBRM OR PACKAGE NAME DB2P..D724CNSL.18E8991A1EF6BF34 NOT FOU CLRPTA. REASON 03 A BIND HAD BEEN RUN. BUT, SINCE THIS WAS AN INSTALL OF THE PROGRAM AND DBRMLIB, THE BIND SHOULD HAVE WORKED FOUND THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDE TO POINT TO AN OLD LOADLIB JOBLIB DD DISP=SHR,DSN=TEST.CL.LOADLIB.PROD.D012112 ",
  "SOLUTION": "THE OLD LOADLIB IS NOT GOING TO WORK WITHOUT THE MATCHING DBRM. HAD TO REMOVE THE OVERRIDE AND USE THE NEWLY COMPILED PROGRAM JUST INSTALLED. 2 POLICIES ABENDED FOR THE REASON THE LOADLIB OVERRIDE EXISTED. DROPPED THOSE AND CONTINUED. A FIX FOR THIS IS IN TEST AND NEEDS TO GET TO PRODUCTION "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0035",
  "PROBLEM": "CKETRINV, OFFSET X'B90': ABEND U0001 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB DURING THE DAY WENT DOWN A FEW TIMES. LOOKED AT SYSOUT AND SAW THAT IT WAS BOMBING ON DIFFERENT POLICIES. SO FIGURED IT MUST BE A CLIENT CONFLICT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD OPS RESTART FROM THE TOP. JOB FINISHED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0040",
  "PROBLEM": "U0046\/S02E\/B37, SPACE ABEND IN INTERNAL SORT WORK AREA. IEC030I B37-04,IFG0554A,CL$$0040,STEP0020,SORTWK01... IEC030I B37-04,IFG0554A,CL$$0040,STEP0020,SORTWK06 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ABOUT 90% OF THE ACTIVITY RECORD IN INPUT FILE CL.CL$$0040.STEP0015.SEQACTV WERE DISP (DISPLAY TRANSACTION) RECORDS AND THAT INCREASED THE FILE SIZE SIGNIFICANTLY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. TOOK A BACKUP OF 'CL.CL$$0040.STEP0015.SEQACTV' AS 'CL.CL$$0040.STEP0015.SEQACTV.D011612' 2. USING FIRE CALL ID, DELETED ALL DISPLAY TRANSACTION ACTIVITY RECORDS BY RUNNING A SORT JCL ON THE FILE CL.CL$$0040.STEP0015.SEQACTV: 3. HAD OPS RESTART THE JOB CL$$0040 FROM STEP STEP0020. REFER 'TEST.CL.TOOLS(CLR40SRT)' TO DELETE DISP TRANSACTIONS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1160",
  "PROBLEM": "1. JOB ABENDED WITH S322 - TIME OUT ABEND RESTARTED WITH TIME=NOLIMIT PARAMETER, JOB ENDED OK. THE ABENDED STEP USED TO TAKE LESS THAN 100 MINS. THEREFORE TO AVOID FUTURE ABENDS, WE HAD CODED TIME=120 PARAMETER IN JOB CARD BUT IT STILL FAILED WITH S322 IN NEXT CYCLE. CODED ==> \/\/ CLASS=P,MSGCLASS=J,REGION=0M,TIME=120, ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE JES2 JOBCLASS DEFINITION SPECIFIES A TIME LIMIT OF 60 MINUTES FOR EACH JOB STEP. UNFORTUNATELY THE TIME PARAMETER ON THE JOB STATEMENT DOES NOT ALTER THIS LIMIT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "REMOVED TIME=120 PARAMETER FROM JOB CARD AND ADDED THE SAME ON STEP LEVEL. \/\/CL$$1160 EXEC PROC=CL$$1160,TIME.STEP0010=120 JOB EXECUTED SUCCESSFULLY WITH TIME PARAMETER ON STEP LEVEL. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0820",
  "PROBLEM": "CC=40 STEP0020 *************************************** * DATE ON INPUT FILE DOES NOT MATCH * * DATE ON PARM CARD - CHECK PARM CARD * * CHECK INPUT FILE TO MAKE SURE * * CORRECT FILE IS BEING USED * * FILE DATE: 122211 < * PARM DATE: 12-23-11 *************************************** ******************************************** * PROCESS WENT DOWN ON THE FOLLOWING RECORD: ******************************************** *122111 < 122211 < ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CYBERLIFE CYCLE WAS LATE AND DID NOT MEET ON-LINES 12\/22 CYCLE WAS STILL RUNNING AFTER PARMDATE CHANGE ON 12\/23. ON-LINES DID NOT COME UP TILL 10:45AM ",
  "SOLUTION": "ADDED OVERRIDES FOR THE PARMDATE TO BE 12\/22\/2011 RESTARTED JOB FROM THE TOP. OVERRIDES WERE: \/\/STEP0020.PARMDATE DD DSN=TEST.CL.PROD.CARDLIB(PARMDATE) \/\/STEP0020.IDATECRD DD DSN=TEST.CL.PROD.CARDLIB(PARMDATE) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$SEGD",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$SEGD ABENDED WITH FOLLOWING ERROR MESSAGE: IEC130I FVDTBLS DD STATEMENT MISSING + VSAM ERROR - FILE=FVDTBLS, INCODE=6, OUTCODE=8, R15=08, ERRCODE=0080 IEC130I SYSLST DD STATEMENT MISSING IEC130I SYSPRINT DD STATEMENT MISSING ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SEGD WAS SCHEDULED TO DELETE UNWANTED 89 SEGMENT FROM POLICY MASTER FOR THE POLICY #00000752484. JOB WAS ABENDING FOR MISSING 'FVDTBLS' DD NAME. WE DONT RUN SEGD WITH UTABLE AS INPUT. ITS CLIENT ERROR. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RERUN THE JOB WITH CIS OFF LOAD. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$9800",
  "PROBLEM": "SKY SENT A LIST OF AGENTS TO RUN THRU CL$$9800, BUT DID NOT GET DESIRED OUTPUT OR EXPECTED RECORDS. NO ABEND. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WHEN THE JOB IS RAN, THE USER SHOULD SPECIFY THE INPUT FORMAT. AGBR### = AGENCY SA##### = SERVICING AGENT WR#### = WRITING AGENT, LOOKS FOR 01 LEVEL AGENTS KA##### = KEY ACCOUNT, LOOKS FOR ANY LEVEL AGENTS USER HAS REQUESTED WR. ",
  "SOLUTION": "YOU NEED TO KA INSTEAD OF WR BEFORE THE AGENT NUMBER. WR IS LOOKING FOR 01 LEVEL WRITING AGENTS KA LOOKS FOR ANY LEVEL AND SINCE THESE ARE SL AGENT NUMBERS THEY DON'T HAVE A 01 WRITING AGENT LEVEL ENTERED. PROBLEM: SKY SENT ANOTHER LIST OF AGENTS TO RUN UNDER WR INPUT FORMAT. ANALYSIS: EXPECT NUMBER OF RECORDS DID NOT COME OUT. THE LIST CONSISTED OF 412 AGENTS. THE ULTIM SAYS THERE IS A LIMIT OF 100 AGENTS PER RUN. THE INPUT FIELD IS INDEXED AND APPARENTLY THE MAX NUMBER ON AN INDEX IS 100. SOLUTION: RAN CL$$9800 WITH 99 OR LESS INPUT RECORDS PER RUN. IT TOOK 5 RUNS BUT EVENTUALLY WAS ABLE TO GET EXPECTED NUMBER OF RECORDS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1815",
  "PROBLEM": "JESMSGLG: CL$$1815 STEP0115 JSTEP010 - ABEND=S000 U0046\/S02E STEP0115 SYSOUT: ICE046A 0 SORT CAPACITY EXCEEDED - RECORD COUNT 15534 ICE253I 0 RECORDS SORTED - PROCESSED: 15534, EXPECTED: 22752 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ASK OPS TO RESTART THE JOB FROM JSTEP010.STEP0115 WITH FOLLOWING DD OVERRIDE: \/\/STEP0115.SORTIN DD DSN=CL.CL$$1815.STEP0030.PENDING(0) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$8160",
  "PROBLEM": "CC16 ATTENTION! ERRORS WERE SIGNALED IN THIS REPORT CONSOLIDATED ERROR LISTING CYCLE PROGRAM --STATEMENT--- ITEM COND SEG ERROR R 358153 MCCPOLD SET 00204 1 O ",
  "ANALYSIS": "MCCPOLD IS AN ULTIM. THE REPORTS SHOWED THERE WERE ERRORS. THUS THE CC16. ",
  "SOLUTION": "THIS IS AN ISSUE WITH THIS ULTIM WERE A CC16 WILL GET PRODUCED IF THE REPORTS SHOWS ERRORS. THE REST OF THE JOB FINISHED FINE. FORCED JOB OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0839",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND S0C1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "EXECUTING CKTRLGET FOR NOON POLICY PAGES 5200237130 ",
  "SOLUTION": "BACKED UP THE REQUEST FILE CL.DLS.CARECUST.SORT.DUPOUT TO TEST.CL.DLS.CARECUST.SORTDUP.D112311 SEE --> BELOW: DELETED THE REQUEST RECORD OF 5200237130 FROM CL.DLS.CARECUST.SORT.DUPOUT TO BE ABLE TO OBTAIN POLICY PAGES FOR THE OTHER (9) REQUESTS RERAN JOB CL$$0839 FROM THE TOP RESULT WAS A READ ERROR ABEND ON FILE CL.DLS.CARECUST.SORT.ACLIFE IN STEP0030 SUSAN CARMICHAEL TESTED THE ABOVE IN HER UNIT UNIT TEST AND IT RAN SUCCESSFULLY. SHE GENERATED THE POLICY PAGES FOR THE OTHER (9) REQUESTS JOB CL$$0839 WAS THEN FORCED COMPLETE JIF 12\/27\/2011 RERAN JOB CL$$0839 FROM THE TOP USING JIF 12\/27\/2011 ALTERED INPUT FILES: JIF 12\/27\/2011 1. CL.DLS.CARECUST.SORT.DUPOUT (MINUS PA RECORDS) JIF 12\/27\/2011 2. CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR(+0) (MINUS PA RECORDS) JIF 12\/27\/2011 JOB COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. JIF 12\/27\/2011 WE NEEDED TO RUN THE PAGES MANUALLY FOR THE PA CASE JIF 12\/27\/2011 SEPARATELY IN TEST. *****BEGIN IMPORTANT NOTE************* NOTE: WHEN RUNNING CL$$0839: IF THE JOB IS STILL BEING SPLIT BETWEEN XPRESSIONS AND DLS PAGES - BY JUST FORCING THE CL$$0839 JOB COMPLETE WILL NOT ENSURE THAT THE INFORMATICA & XPRESSIONS JOB [IDCPI0839P] RUNS UNLESS STEP0100 IN CL$$0839 COMPLETES SUCCESSFULLY!!!!! *****END IMPORTANT NOTE************* --> TEMP FIX FOR PA POLICIES (091SLAC1S), EX. WHERE USED 5200237130. NOTE: WHEN THIS OCURRED IN TEST, THERE WERE NO PRINTOUTS FOR OTHER POLICIES IN THIS JOB. IF ISSUE RECURRS AND THE FULL INPUT IS NOT RERUN, THEN PAGES OTHER THAN THE ONE IN ERROR WILL NEED TO BE REPRINTED COPY CKVPMDCV DOWN FROM PRODUCTION AND COMMENT OUT THE ENTIRE INIT3800-GET-LIFE-CONTROL-SEG SECTION. OTHERWISE THE PROGRAM WILL GET A S0C1\/ABENDU4087 WHEN RUNNING CL$$0839. D724CAR2 CALLS CKDPCVR WHICH CALLS CKVPMDCV WHICH HAS THE NEW CODE TO ACCESS 89 SEGS WHICH IS NOT NEEDED FOR THESE 091SLAC1 PLANS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0130",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND S07C +PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) AT LOCATION 0001B0 IN ELEMENT CKDCARTH + PSW = 078D2400 8DC7465E +CKSN01 PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. PSW=078D2400 8DC7465E +CKSN02 ABENDING ELEMENT CKDCARTH EPA=0DC744A8 OFFSET 0001B0 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PERFORMED FOLLOWING STEPS :- 1. TOOK A BACK UP OF CL.BASEB.AP.COR.EXT1(0) AS CL.BASEB.AP.COR.EXT1.D111611. 2. DELETED ALL RECORDS OF ABDENDING POLICY FROM ORIGINAL FILE CL.BASEB.AP.COR.EXT1(0) USING FIRECALL 3. ASKED OPS TO RESTART THE JOB FROM THE TOP FURTHER ",
  "SOLUTION": "(NEXT DAY) - THERE WAS A VERY LITTLE CHANCE THAT CKDCARTH WOULD HAVE ANY PROBLEM. IT WAS DECIDED THE PROBLEM SHOULD BE IN PROGRAM MAKING CALL TO CKDCARTH. FROM THE CALL CHAIN, IT WAS FOUND THAT PROGRAM CKCPVAPQ IS MAKING THIS CALL AT FOLLOWING LOCATION - MDPDT500 EQU * CKCALL CKDCARTH,(FLCBHDAT,LOWDATE,CON6,CON0,CON70,ADD) CKIF LOWYEAR,NE,CALDYEAR,GOTO=MDPDT900 CONT, NOT FIRST YEAR MORE ANALYSIS OF CODE SUGGESTED THE PROGRAM IS TRYING TO READ A OWNER'S DOB IN FLCBHDAT WHICH IS THEN PASSED TO CKDCARTH. A POLICY PRINT OF THE POLICY CONFIRMED THAT THIS DATE IS NOT VALID (ZERO DATE). THERE WAS RECENT CHANGE IN OWNERSHIP OF THE POLICY AND THE NEW OWNER HAS A MISSING DOB. THIS IS A DATA PROBLEM HENCE NO FURTHER ACTION IS REQUIRED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0103",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND S04C A SYSTEM ABEND A14 REASON CODE X'4' OCCURRED IN MODULE CKQSAMIC CSECT CKQSAMIC AT OFFSET X'560'. IEC614I PRLSE FAILED - RC 016, DIAGNOSTIC INFORMATION IS 081A00C4) STEP0050,STORB5,CL.CL$$0103.STEP0050.OFFAUD IEC216I A14-04,IFG0202E,CL$$0103,STEP0050,SEQUEN,2A38,STORB5, CL.CL$$0103.STEP0050.OFFAUD +UNHANDLED CONDITION DETECTED BY CKABHDLR (SA14) MAY BE DASD ISSUE WHILE PROGRAM IS TRYING TO PARTIALLY RELEASE OR CLOSE THE OFFAUD FILE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PERFORMED FOLLOWING STEPS :- 1. HAD OPS RUN RESTORE JOBS CL$$R060 AND CL$$RCL4. 2. HAD OPS RERUN THE JOB CL$$0102 FROM THE TOP (AS CL.VSAM.BASEOL.BATCHPAY WAS NOT EMPTY). 3. AFTER JOB CL$$0102 RAN SUCCESSFULLY, HAD OPS RERUN THE JOB CL$$0103 FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0130",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND S0C7 A SYSTEM ABEND 0C7 OCCURRED IN MODULE CKCBAPPC CSECT CKDCARTH AT OFFSET X'1B0'. ABENDING POLICY # 2052264030. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE POLICY IS ABENDING BECAUSE CURRENT OWNER DOES NOT HAVE A DOB. LOOKING AT NOTEPADS ON THIS POLICY, IT LOOK LIKE THIS OWNER IS RECENTLY ADDED (ON 11\/11) TO THE POLICY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "PERFORMED FOLLOWING STEPS :- 1. SEARCH CORRSORT OR SEQUEN2, THIS IS A DRIVER INPUT FILE OF THIS JOB. THE CURRENT RECORD IN THIS FILE IS THE BAD POLICY. 2. TOOK A BACK UP OF CL.BASEB.AP.COR.EXT1(0) AS CL.....D111611 3. DELETED ALL RECORDS OF ABDENDING POLICY FROM ORIGINAL FILE CL.BASEB.AP.COR.EXT1(0) USING FIRECALL 4. ASKED OPS TO RESTART THE JOB FROM TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$8001",
  "PROBLEM": "A USER ABEND 0001 OCCURRED IN MODULE ULTTGPOL CSECT CKABEND AT OFFSET X'116'. THE ABEND WAS CAUSED BY MACHINE INSTRUCTION 0DEF (BRANCH AND SAVE) IN MODULE ULTTGPOL CSECT CKETRINV AT OFFSET X'B70'. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PROBABLY THERE WAS A CONTENTION PROBLEM AND THE JOB WAS NOT ABLE TO ACCESS THE CLIENT FOR ABENDING POLICY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTARTED THE JOB FROM JSTEP060.STEP0010. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0804",
  "PROBLEM": "INCORRECT ATTRIBUTES OF INPUT DATASET CL.CL$$0804.INFILE FTP JOB UPLOADED THE INPUT DATASET IN VB FORMAT WHEREAS PROGRAM R724AGCN IS EXPECTING A FIXED BLOCK (FB) INPUT DATASET. JOB ABENDED WITH S0C7 FOR IN-COMPANY-CODE = X'0030', I THINK THE VALUE X'0030' IS A PART OF RDW OF A VB DATASET. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "1) TOOK A COPY OF CL.CL$$0804.INFILE.G0004V00 INTO TEST.CL.CL$$0804.INFILE.D111511 IN A FIXED BLOCK FORMAT. 2) THE JOB ABENDED WITHOUT PROCESSING ANY RECORD SO I DID NOT RAN RESTORE JOB. 3) ASKED OPS TO RESTART THE JOB CL$$0804 FROM TOP WITH TEST.CL.CL$$0804.INFILE.D111511 DATASET AS AN OVERRIDE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0865",
  "PROBLEM": "CEE3207S THE SYSTEM DETECTED A DATA EXCEPTION(SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=0C7). FROM COMPILE UNIT D7240178 AT ENTRY POINT D7240178 AT COMPILE UNIT OFFSET +0000B0CC AT ENTRY OFFSET +0000B0CC AT ADDRESS 00073D6C. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE JOB ABENDED WITH S0C7 DUE TO BAD POLICY 4041009120. ",
  "SOLUTION": "1) TOOK A BACK UP OF FILE CL.CL$$0860.PMLUL.SORTED AS CL.CL$$0860.PMLUL.SORTED.D091511 2) REMOVED ALL RECORDS OF ABENDING POILCY FROM ORIGINAL FILE: CL.CL$$0860.PMLUL.SORTED 3) RENAMED PRIOR RUN GDG \"CL.CL$$0865.PMLUL.OTAGTHIS.G0707V00\" 4) RESTART THE JOB FROM ABENDING STEP - CL$$0865.STEP0200 5) THIS JOB TAKE LOTS OF TIME TO GET COMPLETE "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0021",
  "PROBLEM": "PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0CF (FLOATING DVIDE) AT LOCATION 0007 PSW = 078D3400 80045A0A REGISTERS AT TIME OF INTERRUPT: 00-07 003326E0 000455E9 0FDEA228 003207FC 0FE1B8E8 003207FC 0FE1B8E8 0 08-15 00320A80 0DCC6FC8 000453F4 00045664 000453E4 003324D8 800459FC 8 HASP375 CL$$0021 ESTIMATED LINES EXCEEDED CKSN01 PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. PSW=078D3400 80045A0A (FLOATING DV CKSN02 ABENDING ELEMENT CKDPPSEY EPA=000452E8 OFFSET 000720 IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V9R1M0 (UK52917 2009\/12\/16) INVOKED BY IDIXDCAP IDI0002I MODULE CKDPFSPS, PROGRAM CKDPPSEY, OFFSET X'720': ABEND S0CF (H ",
  "ANALYSIS": "POLICY MISSING CASH SURRENDER VALUE ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G5909V00 TO TEST.CL.FIX.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT STRIPPED OUT POLICIES 2052403320. RESTARTED IN STEP0030 POINTING TO MY FILE --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! \/\/STEP0030.SEQUEN DD DSN=TEST.CL.FIX.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT NOTIFIED TRIAGE POLICIES WERE STRIPPED AND POLICY PAGES WILL BE LATE TODAY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0110",
  "PROBLEM": "A SYSTEM ABEND 0CB OCCURRED IN MODULE CKCMCALC PROGRAM D724COMP AT OFFSET X'6246'. A PROGRAM-INTERRUPTION CODE 000B (DECIMAL-DIVIDE EXCEPTION) THE DIVISOR WAS ZERO IN A SIGNED DECIMAL DIVISION. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DECIMAL-DIVIDE EXCEPTION ,OCCURED DUE 'FCXCPRCP-RATE-PERCENT' OF COMMISSION RATE SEGMENT(38 SEG) WAS ZERO FOR ABENDING POLICY AND THE ABENDED POLICY WAS :- 0620435210 ",
  "SOLUTION": "1) TOOK BACKUP OF CL.CL$$0105.STEP0080.EXTR(0) AS CL.CL$$0105.STEP0080.EXTR.D100511(USING FIRECALL ID) 2) DELETED ALL RECORDS OF ABENDING POLICIES FROM ORIGINAL FILE CL.CL$$0105.STEP0080.EXTR(0) 3) RAN RESTORE JOB CL$$R110 4) RESTART CL$$R110 FROM TOP "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1110",
  "PROBLEM": "1. ABEND S322 2. S0C1 ABEND IN CKCYFLIO 3. JCLLIB ERROR ",
  "ANALYSIS": "1. TIMEOUT 2.THIS MESSAGE DISPLAYS IN SYSOUT WITH VP\/MS DISPLAYS CKVPMDCV ",
  "SOLUTION": "1: RUN JOB FROM THE TOP WITH TIME=NOLIMIT SOLUTION 2: COPY CL.ME.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY TO YOUR OWN FILE DELETE POLICY 0000339457. ADD THIS OVERRIDE AND RERUN FROM THE TOP. \/\/STEP0010.VSAM1 DD DSN=TEST.CL.GCE.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY.D100111, \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) SOLUTION 3: ASKED OPERATORS TO NOT COMMENT OUT THE EXEC STATEMENT FOR STEP010. JUST ADD THE OVERRIDE FOR VSAM1 IN STEP0010. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1010",
  "PROBLEM": "ABENDS WITH AN S2F3 IN JSTEP010\/STEP0030 THE JOB REQUEUES ITSELF THEN ABENDS. IT IS RUNNING OUT OF VIRTUAL STORAGE SPACE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PROVIDED BY CSC: FOR CL$$1010 ISSUE, THERE ARE TWO ISSUES: 1. MEMORY BLOCKS ACQUIRED BY CKETRLST IN M7241100 ARE NEVER RELEASED. THIS IS FIXED BY ADDING A CALL TO CKETRLST TO CLEAR MEMORY BLOCK. 2. THE LINKCARD DOES NOT SPECIFY A RMODE. FOR THIS, IN ALL PROBABILITY, IT ACQUIRES A RMODE=24, WHICH MEANS IT DOES NOT GET ANY MEMORY ABOVE THE 16 MB LINE. I CHANGED THE LINKCARD WITH AMODE=31 AND RMODE=ANY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. FOR THE 08\/2011 AND 09\/2011 MONTH-ENDS THE JOB WAS RUN WITH AN OVERRIDE IN THE JOBLIB TO TEST.CL.AMS.LOADLIB. 2. THE SOURCE FOR M7241100 WAS LOCATED IN TEST.CL.AMS.SOURCE. IDENTIFIED BY *TEMP* IN COLUMN 1. A COPY WAS PUT IN TEST.CL.P1GCO.ABEND.SOURCE. 3. THE LINK IS IN TEST.CL.AMS.LINKS. A COPY IS IN TEST.CL.P1GCO.ABEND.LINKS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$8001",
  "PROBLEM": "UNEXPLAINED COND CODE 0012 STEP STEP0010\/JSTEP060 OFFSET X'45A': ABEND S0C1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PICKING UP CLIENT ERRORS BECAUSE THIS JOB PROCESSED ON THE NEXT DAY AND DATES WERE ALREADY UPDATED FOR THAT DAY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. DELETE CURRENT GDG FOR CL.CL$$8001.STEP0010.CLPENDXT IF IT IS CREATED. 2. ADD THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDES IN JSTEP060 AND RESTART JOB FROM JSTEP060. \/\/STEP0010.SYSTSIN DD DSN=PROD.CL.CARDLIB(XLEBMAIR), \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) \/\/STEP0010.CLPND DD DSN=CL.SA.VSAM.BASEOL.PENDING, \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) \/\/STEP0010.FVDSEG1 DD DSN=CL.SA.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG1, \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) \/\/STEP0010.FVDSEG2 DD DSN=CL.SA.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG2, \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "ERROR MESSAGE \"WF_EDRSS_PREPROCESSING NOT STARTED\" -------- ",
  "ANALYSIS": "--------- 1. CHECK THE INFORMATICA WORKFLOW LOG FILE: \\\\SWPINFRMT01\\INFA_DATA\\INFA\\WORKFLOWLOGS\\IND_PUBLISHING\\ WF_EDRSS_PREPROCESSING.LOG (ONE MAY NOT HAVE ACCESS TO THIS FILE\/FOLDER - IF NOT, THAT'S OK; PLEASE SEE \"SOLUTION\" BELOW.) 2. SEARCH ON THE WORD \"ERROR\" TO FIND: \"ERROR : LM_36320 [TUE SEP 20 02:04:34 2011] : ... (7536",
  "SOLUTION": "7644) SESSION TASK INSTANCE [WKLT_EDRSS_RELOAD_PERSISTENT_CACHE.S_M_EDRSS_RELOAD_PERSISTENT_ LOOKUP_CACHES]: EXECUTION FAILED.\" 3. CHECK THE SESSION LOG FILE: \\\\SWPINFRMT01\\INFA_DATA\\INFA\\SESSLOGS\\IND_PUBLISHING\\ S_M_EDRSS_RELOAD_PERSISTENT_LOOKUP_CACHES.LOG A SEARCH ON THE WORD \"ERROR\" WILL IDENTIFY NUMEROUS INSTANCES OF ERROR MESSAGE: \"ERROR: CACHE FILE [??] NEEDED BY NAMED LOOKUP TRANSFORMATION [??] IN THIS MAPPING APPEARS TO BE CREATED BY AN UNNAMED CACHE LOOKUP TRANSFORMATION.\" "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$8100",
  "PROBLEM": "-------- \"+IDI0002I MODULE ULTTGPOL, CSECT CKETRGET, OFFSET X'45A': ABEND S0C1 (OPERATION EXCEPTION)\" SYSPDUMP JSTEP098 STEP0010 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "-------- CLIENT CONFLICT ",
  "SOLUTION": "-------- RESTART JOB IN JSTEP098 11\/01\/11 SEE INSTRUCTIONS IN SCHD.CTM.DOC(CL$$8100) 11\/01\/11 WE HAD OPS RERUN ONLY STEPS JSTEP095 AND JSTEP098 11\/01\/11 USING THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDES: ... \/\/JSTEP095 EXEC PROC=CLULTIM, "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0160",
  "PROBLEM": "SOURCE MASK: CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH TARGET MASK: CL.SA.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH ALLOCATING TARGET DATA SET: CL.SA.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH RAN OUT OF TARGET VOLUMES WITH SUFFICIENT SPACE ",
  "ANALYSIS": "INSUFFICIENT SPACE ON DASD VOLUMES ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD OPS CALL DASD TEAM. THE WERE ABLE TO FREE UP SOME SPACE ON SPECIFIED VOLUMES. RERAN JOB FROM TOP. FINSHED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1010",
  "PROBLEM": "IEF453I CL$$1010 - JOB FAILED - JCL ERROR - TIME=08.37.55 # IEF453I CL$$1010 - JOB FAILED - JCL ERROR - TIME=08.37.55 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "COULD NOT FIND ANY REASON FOR THE JCL ERROR ",
  "SOLUTION": "REQUESTED RESTART OF THE JOB AND IT WAS NOT SETUP CORRECTLY, JOB ABENDED AGAIN. RESTART WAS REQUESTED WITHIN JOB CARD AS '\/\/ RESTART=JSTEP010.STEP0030,' JOB COMPLETED SUCCESFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "MODULE D724AGC1, CSECT CKTBLOCT, OFFSET X'43A': ABEND U0001 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SEE IMPORTANT NOTE BELOW WITH ###### GOOD CALL TO AUUDT512: ********** AUTOMONITOR ********** 0002 01 WS-TABLE-PARM 0003 02 TBPTBNAM-TABLE-NAME 'AUUDT512' 0004 02 TBPTADDR-TABLE-ADDRESS-X 0005 03 TBPTADDR-TABLE-ADDRESS 0006 X'00000000' 0007 02 TBPUSRID-USER-ID '.' 0008 02 TBPREQCD-REQUEST-CODE POLICY 0720164640 CALL TO AUUDT512: ********** AUTOMONITOR ********** 0002 01 WS-TABLE-PARM 0003 02 TBPTBNAM-TABLE-NAME 'AUUDT512' 0004 02 TBPTADDR-TABLE-ADDRESS-X 0005 03 TBPTADDR-TABLE-ADDRESS 0006 X'00000000' 0007 02 TBPUSRID-USER-ID '0' 0008 02 TBPREQCD-REQUEST-CODE THE USER-ID IS NOT CORRECT TO THE CALL TO CKTBLOCT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "UPDATE NEEDED TO D724AGC1 THE POLICY HAD 26 - 48 SEGMENTS SO THE TABLE OVERFLOWED TO THE CKSRECSE FORMAT. ###### TO GET CYCLE GOING WE CREATED AN EMPTY FILE. CL.AGCY.DAILY.INPUT.TRANS.G3190V00 FOR AGCY0020 HOWEVER, TALKING WITH JEFF PETERS AFTERWARD SINCE IT WAS MONTH END IT WOULD HAVE BEEN BETTER TO CALL THE REPS ON-CALL PERSON AND HAVE THE INTERFACE HELD. DURING THE MONTH IT'S OKAY TO CREATE AN EMPTY FILE, BUT AT MONTH END THEY WOULD RATHER HOLD THEIR CYCLE FOR THE CORRECTED FILE THAN HAVE TO ###### RE-RUN. 01 WS-AGENT-MASTER-TABLE. WENDY** 05 WS-AMT-TABLE OCCURS 20 TIMES WENDY 05 WS-AMT-TABLE OCCURS 50 TIMES CL5919 INDEXED BY IX. CL5919* INDEXED BY AMT-IX. 10 WS-AMT-AGENT-PHASE PIC X. CL9617 10 WS-AMT-ORIG-WRITE-AGENT PIC X(10). 10 WS-AMT-WRITING-AGENT PIC X(10). 10 WS-AMT-MASTER-AGENT PIC X(10). 01 PHASE-SUB PIC 9(03) VALUE ZEROES. 01 INFO-MATCH PIC X VALUE SPACES. EJECT ************************************************************ * AGENCY STAT LAYOUT ************************************************************ COPY CKSRECSE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1110",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND S04C ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS MESSAGE DISPLAYS IN SYSOUT WITH VP\/MS DISPLAYS CKVPMDCV ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPY CL.ME.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY TO YOUR OWN FILE DELETE THIS POLICY. ADD THIS OVERRIDE AND RERUN FROM THE TOP. \/\/STEP0010.VSAM1 DD DSN=TEST.CL.###.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY.D073011, \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) JAMIE COPIED THE AUXSEG1 FILE AND DELETED THE POLICY FROM IT TOO. I DON'T THINK WE NEED TO DELETE FROM THE AUXSEG1 FILE. IF THE AUXSEG1 FILE IS NEEDED, THE DD IS FVDSEG1. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$9106",
  "PROBLEM": "UNEXPLAINED COND CODE 0012 STEP STEP0010\/JSTEP020 OFFSET X'45A': ABEND S0C1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PICKING UP CLIENT ERRORS BECAUSE THIS JOB PROCESSED ON THE NEXT DAY AND DATES WERE ALREADY UPDATED FOR THAT DAY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD THE OPERATOR RESTART THE JOB FROM THE TOP PARMDATE HAS CHANGED AND IS OK "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) AT LOCATION 0125D2 IN ELEMENT D724CARE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "RECOMPILED AND RAN POLICY THRU TO GET LOCATION. ***LOOK FOR '0125D2' LAST ****** & SEE THAT IT IS FOR FIELD 0125D2 WS-MOYR-CFO THIS IS A COMMON PROBLEM! POLICY THAT ABENDED WAS AN ASSET CARE 2 [099SLACN2]. PROBLEM IS THAT THIS POLICY NEEDS A 53 SEGMENT (AUTO TRANS) SET UP AND A RELATED LIFE POLICY ON THE PENDING SIDE. THE WS-MOYR-CFO DATE IS ONLY POPULATED WHEN THE 53 SEG IS FOUND. ",
  "SOLUTION": "1: TAKE BACKUP OF INPUT FILE TEST.CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT(0) & NAME TEST.CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.D<DATE> [EX. D071211] 2: DELETED ALL THE RECORDS OF ABENDING POLICY FROM ORIGINAL FILE TEST.CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT(0) 3: REQUESTED OPS TO RESTART THE JOB CL$T0020 FROM STEP0030 WITH FOLLOWING OVERRIDES: UNCOMMENT BELOW LINE \/\/* GDG01='0', AND COMMENT OUT BELOW LINE \/\/ GDG01='+1', --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! 4: SEND EMAIL TO TRIAGE ABOUT PROBLEM WITH POLICY & ASK THAT POLICY CREATOR FIX POLICY BEFORE RESUBMITTING\/REORDERING. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0660",
  "PROBLEM": "+UNABLE TO RETRIEVE STUB POOL RECORD +- - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - +IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V9R1M0 (UK52917 2009\/12\/16) INVOKED BY IDIXDCAP +IDI0002I MODULE D724BLTP, CSECT CKETRINV, OFFSET X'B70': ABEND U0001 +IDI0003I FAULT ID F19228 ASSIGNED IN HISTORY FILE SYS2.FA.HIST.BATCH ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FILE CONTENTION. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DELETED DSN CL.CL$$0660.PENDING, RESTARTED IN STEP0030. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "GOT CALL FROM WEB ",
  "ANALYSIS": "TEAM THAT THIS PROGRAM WAS ABENDING AND NO VALUES WERE BEING DISPLAYED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "VERIFIED NO RECENT CODING CHANGES MOVED TO PRODUCTION. WAS TOLD THAT NEW RELEASE OF DB2 HAD MOVED INTO PROD ON SAT NIGHT & PROBABLY HAD SOMETHING TO DO WITH ABEND. 3\/23\/12 MAJOR INSTALL FOR FREEDOM BUILDER PRODUCT, PROGRAM D721SYST NEEDED TO HAVE A NEW COPY. SOLUTION: CONTACTED LINDA PRAED (OUR EXPERT ON MQ SERIES) WHO SUGGESTED CONTACTING DB2 ON-CALL PERSON. PUT WEB PERSON & DB2 PERSON IN CONTACT WITH LINDA. END RESULT WAS THAT CYBERLIFE REGION WAS BOUNCED TO FIX PROBLEM. 6\/27\/11 - RHONDA WATSON INDICATED THAT HAVING THE CICS ON-CALL PERSON DO A NEW COPY ON THAT PROGRAM PROBABLY WOULD HAVE FIXED THE PROBLEM. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0440",
  "PROBLEM": "S3E7 SYSOUT... ORIGINAL MASTER FILE DATE IS INVALID - DATE = 053111 DATE OF OLD MASTER MUST BE = TO START OF PERIOD (CC 10-17 OFDATE CARD) PROBABLE DATE ERROR - REFER TO SYSOUT ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CHECKED THE LAST GEN OF THE FOLLOWING YE FILES... CL.YE.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN (TAPE) CL.YE.POLSEQ.EXTSRLP CL.YE.POLSEQ.EXTSRPM (TAPE) CL.YE.POLSEQ.EXTSRSL ON THE FILES THAT ARE NOT ON TAPE, I COULD SEE THAT THE CREATION DATES WERE NOT YEAR END. SOMEHOW THESE FILES GOT CREATED IN ERROR. I BROWSED THE TWO THAT I COULD OPEN THAT ARE NOT ON TAPE AND SAW THAT THE FILE DATES WERE 5\/31\/2011. ",
  "SOLUTION": "USING FIRECALL I DELETED THE LAST GENS OF THE TWO NOT ON TAPE AND HAD PCD DELETE THE TWO ON TAPE. HAD OPS RERUN JOB FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "ALL IDCPV* JOBS ARE IDOC PRODUCTION VISTA PLUS COMMAND SCRIPT JOBS WITHIN THE XPRESSION JOBSTREAMS. OCCASIONALLY THEY FAIL DURING THE CYCLE. WE HAVE HAD ISSUES WITH THE VISTA PLUS SERVER IN THE PAST (NOT SURE WHAT THOSE ISSUES ARE - PERHAPS AN OVERLOAD OF SOME KIND). ",
  "ANALYSIS": "TO VIEW A FAILED JOB, LOOK IN CONTROL-M ENTERPRISE MANAGER GUI (WINDOWS-BASED CONTROLM, NOT MAINFRAME). ",
  "SOLUTION": "GENERALLY, WE CAN RERUN THE JOB FROM THE TOP AND IT COMPLETES SUCCESSFULLY. IF THE JOB IS RERAN AND FAILS AGAIN, MY NEXT STEP IS TO CHECK VISTA PLUS TO SEE IF THE POLICIES HAVE BEEN LOADED FOR THE GIVEN ODATE. (SEE FILE CL.DLS.CARECUST.SORT.XPR FOR A LIST OF THE POLICIES.) IF THE POLICIES HAVE BEEN LOADED, THEN FORCE COMPLETE THE JOB OKAY. IF THE POLICIES HAVE *NOT* BEEN LOADED, THE JOB CAN BE FORCE COMPLETED OKAY AND THE DATA WILL GET PICKED UP AND LOADED TO VISTA IN THE NEXT CYCLE. CONSULT A DOCUMENTS TEAM MEMBER FOR ANY QUESTIONS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0040",
  "PROBLEM": "SB37 BOTH TIMES 1ST DSN: SEQUEN3 &PREFIX.CL$$0040.STEP0120.TEMP 2ND DSN: SEQUEN8 &PREFIX.CL$$0040.STEP0160.STATS ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SPACE ABEND NEED TO GIVE DATA SET MORE SPACE ",
  "SOLUTION": "SEND OPERATOR OVER RIDE WITH SPACE ALLOCATION. 1ST OVER RIDE: \/\/************************** \/\/STEP0120.SEQUEN3 DD DSN=&PREFIX.CL$$0040.STEP0120.TEMP, \/\/ DISP=(NEW,CATLG,DELETE), \/\/ UNIT=&DISK, \/\/ SPACE=(CYL,(900,150),RLSE), \/\/ DCB=(RECFM=VB,BLKSIZE=9076) \/\/* \/\/STEP0220.SYSIPT DD * %%CLDATE RESTART IN STEP0120 USING CONTROL D\/M\/R JOB GOT PAST ABENDING STEP BUT FAILED WITH SAME ABEND AT A DIFFERENT STEP. 2ND OVER RIDE: \/\/************************** \/\/STEP0120.SEQUEN3 DD DSN=&PREFIX.CL$$0040.STEP0120.TEMP, \/\/ DISP=(NEW,CATLG,DELETE), \/\/ UNIT=&DISK, \/\/ SPACE=(CYL,(900,150),RLSE), \/\/ DCB=(RECFM=VB,BLKSIZE=9076) \/\/* \/STEP0160.SEQUEN8 DD DSN=&PREFIX.CL$$0040.STEP0160.STATS, \/\/ DISP=(NEW,CATLG,DELETE), \/\/ UNIT=&DISK, \/\/ SPACE=(CYL,(600,150),RLSE,,ROUND), \/\/ DCB=(RECFM=VB,BLKSIZE=9076) \/\/* \/\/STEP0220.SYSIPT DD * %%CLDATE RESTART IN STEP0160 USING CONTROL D\/M\/R JOB GOT PAST ABENDING STEP AND COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "+FOR0341I STOP 8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PAGING THRU THE FT06F001 OF THE METINT STEP, YOU WILL SEE THE FOLLOWING: GEN090183-W: VSAM OPEN ERROR ON VSRN02 VSAM STATUS IS 080000A8 HEXADECIMAL XRX002038-E: DUE TO OPEN ERRORS, MERGING AND SAVING IS TERMINATED FROM MERGE LIBRARY: 3. XRX002039-E: DUE TO MERGE LIBRARY FILE ERRORS, ALL DOCUMENT SAVING IS TERMINATED. THIS INDICATES THAT THE DLS MERGE LIBRARY IS UNAVILABLE FOR THIS JOB (ANOTHER JOB IS CURRENTLY USING THE LIBRARY). ",
  "SOLUTION": "IF THE JOB DOES NOT REALLY NEED THIS LIBRARY FORCE COMPLETE THE JOB AND CONTINUE ON. (THIS STATEMENT JOB DOES NOT NEED THIS LIBRARY) "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "+FOR0341I STOP 12 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PAGING THRU THE FT06F001 OF THE METINT STEP, YOU WILL SEE THE FOLLOWING: XRX002247-F: NO DATA WAS IN THE INPUT CIF FILE FOR THE XEROX LPS EMITTER. THE PROGRAM WAS TERMINATED. THIS INDICATES THAT THE INPUT TO THE DLSBATCH STEP HAD DATA BUT THE DLSBATCH OUTPUT WAS EMPTY. THE COMPUSET PRINT STEP WAS UNABLE TO HANDLE AN EMPTY INPUT FILE, THUS IT ABENDS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "NO COMPUSET SOLUTION IS KNOWN AT THIS TIME. FORCE COMPLETE THE JOB AND CONTINUE ON. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$9501",
  "PROBLEM": "CSECT CKETRINV, OFFSET X'B70': ABEND U0001 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOUND POLICY IN IDIREPRT BY DOING A SEARCH ON CURRENT. LOOKED AT POLICY IN CL 3270 AND SAW THAT IT WAS UPDATED TODAY. SO FIGURED IT WAS A CLIENT CONFLICT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RERAN JOB FROM TOP. FINISHED OKAY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0103",
  "PROBLEM": "THE FOLLOWING 2 PROGRAM CHECKS WERE IN PRODUCTION FROM APPEARS THEY BOTH HAD PREMIUM REVERSALS, BUT BEYOND THAT I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE USER WAS DOING OR TRYING TO DO 0720048900 0320 2 AP0320 - ---(( PROGRAM CHECK 0209 2 AP0209 - POLICY WAS SUSPENDED 0320 2 AP0320 - ---(( PROGRAM CHECK 0209 2 AP0209 - POLICY WAS SUSPENDED 0720129610 0320 2 AP0320 - ---(( PROGRAM CHECK 0209 2 AP0209 - POLICY WAS SUSPENDED 0320 2 AP0320 - ---(( PROGRAM CHECK 0209 2 AP0209 - POLICY WAS SUSPENDED ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE CALLING CHAIN CKSUBS ABEND\/PROGRAM CHECK CKQSAMIC CKUTQSES CKUBCMAC CKUBHY00 CKUBCMAC IS TRYING TO WRITE THE OFFLINE RECORD. I QUESTION IF THE PENDING SPR CK1376 HAS ANYTHING TO DO WITH IT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "NONE. IF HAPPENS AGAIN, WE'LL LOOK INTO MORE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0004",
  "PROBLEM": "POLICIES NOT FEEDING TO OLS OR ACCOUNT SERVICES. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "INSERT FILES CREATED FROM CL$$0004 NOT FTD'D PROPERLY TO WEB SERVICES. ",
  "SOLUTION": "- COPY USING TEST.CL.JCLLIB(COPYOLS) CL.CL$$0004.DIRECT TO TEST.CL.PROD.CL$$0004.DIRECT.DXXXXXX CL.CL$$0004.DIRECT.SRT(0) TO TEST.CL.PROD.CL$$0004.DIRECT.SRT.DXXXXXX CL.CL$$0004.POL.DIR(0) TO TEST.CL.PROD.CL$$0004.POL.DIR.DXXXXXX CL.CL$$0004.POL.PLN(0) TO TEST.CL.PROD.CL$$0004.POL.PLN.DXXXXXX - USING FIRECALL DELETE MISSING POLICY NUMBERS IN: CL.CL$$0004.POL.DIR(0) CL.CL$$0004.POL.PLN(0) - MAKE NOTE OF THE DIRECTORY-NAME-ID'S IN COL 26 (9 BYTES) OF CL.CL$$0004.POL.DIR(0). THIS WILL BE NEEDED WHEN DELETING RECORDS IN: CL.CL$$0004.DIRECT CL.CL$$0004.DIRECT.SRT(0) SINCE THERE ARE NO POLICY NUMBERS IN THESE FILES. IF THIS PROCESS DOES NOT WORK, CHECK THAT THE FTP JOBS ARE RUNNING AS SCHEDULED. IF MULTIPLE POLICIES (MORE THAN 5) NEED TO BE DELETED, YOU CAN USE TEST.CL.JCLLIB(QJOLSFIX) TO CREATE FILES WITH THE DROPPED RECORDS, THEN USE FIRECALL TO DELETE THE 4 PRODUCION FILES AND COPY THE UPDATED TEST FILES TO THE PRODUCTION NAME. THE ONLY SETUP REQUIRED IN THAT JOB IS TO CREATE THE INPUT TABLE FILE TEST.CL.RDB.TBOLSPOL. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0007",
  "PROBLEM": "POLICIES NOT FEEDING TO OLS OR ACCOUNT SERVICES. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PER THE WEBSOLUTIONS TEAM, THESE TWO POLICIES WERE DELETED FROM THE BOOK OF BUSINESS DATABASE ON 3\/13\/12. THE REASON BEING UNKNOWN. ",
  "SOLUTION": "- USING FIRECALL COPY: CL.CL$$0007.POL.ADR(0) TO CL.CL$$0007.POL.ADR.DXXXXXX CL.CL$$0007.POL.COVERAG(0) TO CL.CL$$0007.POL.COVERAG.DXXXXXX CL.CL$$0007.POL.DIR(0) TO CL.CL$$0007.POL.DIR.DXXXXXX CL.CL$$0007.POL.PLAN(0) TO CL.CL$$0007.POL.PLAN.DXXXXXX CL.CL$$0007.POL.PLANDIR(0) TO CL.CL$$0007.POL.PLANDIR.DXXXXXX CL.CL$$0007.POL.WRAGT(0) TO CL.CL$$0007.POL.WRAGT.DXXXXXX - USING FIRECALL DELETE MISSING POLICY NUMBERS IN: CL.CL$$0007.POL.COVERAG(0) CL.CL$$0007.POL.PLAN(0) CL.CL$$0007.POL.PLANDIR(0) CL.CL$$0007.POL.WRAGT(0) - MAKE NOTE OF THE DIRECTORY-NAME-ID'S IN COL 14 (9 BYTES) OF CL.CL$$0007.POL.PLANDIR(0) AND COL 107 (9 BYTES) OF CL.CL$$0007.POL.COVERAG(0) BOTH. THIS WILL BE NEEDED WHEN DELETING RECORDS IN: CL.CL$$0007.POL.ADR(0) CL.CL$$0007.POL.DIR(0) SINCE THERE ARE NO POLICY NUMBERS IN THESE FILES. NOTE: I HAD SIZE PROBLEMS WITH FILE MARVEL, SO I WROTE THESE BATCH JOBS TO DO THE UPDATES: TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL7TST) AND (CL7PRD). BLM, 11\/6\/12. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0004",
  "PROBLEM": "POLICIES NOT SHOWING IN OLS. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE POLICY WAS NOT ON CL$$0004 INSERT FILE. WEB SERVICES CONFIRMED IT IS IN THE DATABASE BUT POLICY CAN NOT PULL UP, POLICY IS ACTIVE. RESEARCH AND ",
  "SOLUTION": "STEPS: WEB SOLUTIONS SAID IT IS IN THE DATABASE AND SHOULD DISPLAY, CHECK FOR CL ERROR BY VIEWING SCREEN LOG FILE: 1. MAKE SURE SOMEONE HAS TRIED TO ACCESS THE POLICY IN OLS SO THERE WOULD BE A LOG OF THE ACTION 2. PRINT THE SCREEN LOG FILE, RUN TEST.CL.TOOLS(PRTTEST) 3. SEARCH FOR THE POLICY NUMBER. LOOK FOR OLS TRX CODE 6PX, WHICH MEANS IT CAME FROM OLS (NOT GUI). 4. LOOK TO SEE IF THERE WERE ERRORS, FOUND ONE. POLICY 0710037830 HAS ERROR AP0578 - \"TRANSACTION DATE BEYOND NEXT ANNIVERSARY\" 5. BA NOTIFIED USER THE PAYMENTS NEEDED TO BE CURRENT. FYI, THIS IS TICKET #359662, SAME ISSUE FOUND UNDER #339922 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0004",
  "PROBLEM": "POLICIES NOT SHOWING IN OLS OR ACCOUNT SERVICES. 0 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE POLICY WAS ON THE CL$$0004 INSERT FILE. WEB SERVICES IT CONFIRMED IT IS IN THE DATABASE. POLICY CAN BE PULLED UP BUT IT DOES NOT DISPLAY BECAUSE THE POLICY IS SUSPENDED. RESEARCH AND ",
  "SOLUTION": "STEPS: 1. FOLLOW PROCEDURE TO ENSURE POLICY IS ON THE INSERT FILE IN CL$$0004. 2. IF ON THE INSERT FILE AND WEB SERVICES NEEDS TO CHECK IF IT IS IN THE DATABASE, ASSIGN TICKET TO WEB SERVICES 3. IN THIS CASE, WEB SERVICES SAID THE POLICY IS IN THE DATABASE. YOU CAN PULL IT UP, BUT IT DOES NOT DISPLAY ANY INFORMATION WHEN THE POLICY IS SUSPENDED 4. IF WEB SOLUTIONS HAD SAID IT IS IN THE DATABASE AND SHOULD DISPLAY, IT IS POSSIBLE THAT THERE IS A CL ERROR BEHIND THE SCENES THAT CAN BE VIEWED IN THE SCREEN LOG FILE. MAKE SURE SOMEONE HAS TRIED TO ACCESS THE POLICY IN OLS SO THERE WOULD BE A LOG OF THE ACTION. TO PRINT THE SCREEN LOG FILE, RUN TEST.CL.TOOLS(PRTTEST) AND SEARCH FOR THE POLICY NUMBER. LOOK FOR OLS TRX CODE PX6, WHICH MEANS IT CAME FROM OLS (NOT GUI). LOOK TO SEE IF THERE WERE ERRORS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0004",
  "PROBLEM": "0C1 OCCURRED IN MODULE D7245300 CSECT CKETRGET +100 ROW NOT FOUND FOR FETCH, UPDATE OR DELETE, ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FAILING ON CLIENT AS INFORCE SERVICES IS IN OFFICE AND MAKING UPDATES. ",
  "SOLUTION": "REVIEWED PROGRAM & FOUND IT IS NOT GETTING 90 SEGMENT RE-LINKED AS NON-CLIENT INTO TEMPORARY LIBRARY TEST.CL.PERS.LOADLIB - REQUESTED JOB RERAN FROM TOP WITH FOLLOWING OVER RIDE: \/\/JOBLIB DD DISP=SHR,DSN=TEST.CL.PERS.LOADLIB \/\/ DD DISP=SHR,DSN=PROD.CL.LOADLIB \/\/ DD DISP=SHR,DSN=PROD.CL.OBJLIB JOB FINISHED OK "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0007",
  "PROBLEM": "D724MAIN, CSECT CKETRGET SQLCODE 100 EXPLANATION +100 ROW NOT FOUND FOR FETCH, UPDATE OR DELETE, ",
  "ANALYSIS": "BRIAN GIBSON WAS WORKING ON RESOLVING SOME CLIENT PROBLEMS, HOWEVER ABENDED AGAIN AROUND 8 AM. ",
  "SOLUTION": "WILL ATTEMPT TO RERUN FROM TOP, HOWEVER, INFORCE SERVICES IS IN THE OFFICE AND UPDATING CLIENT. THIS IS FOR CL$$0007 (BOOK OF BUSINESS\\NAME SEARCH) WILL MORE THAN LIKELY CANCEL THIS JOB, ALONG WITH CL$$0008 (PENDING NAME SEARCH) & CL$$0009 (NAME SEARCH) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$9021",
  "PROBLEM": "UNEXPLAINED COND CODE 0012 STEP STEP0010\/JSTEP020 OFFSET X'45A': ABEND S0C1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PICKING UP CLIENT ERRORS BECAUSE THIS JOB PROCESSED ON THE NEXT DAY AND DATES WERE ALREADY UPDATED FOR THAT DAY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "PUT IN OVERRIDES FOR PARMDATE TO POINT TO PREV DAY AND RESTART FROM THE TOP. JSTEP010 \/\/STEP0010.PARMDATE DD DSN=TEST.CL.RSW.CARDLIB(PARMDATE),DISP=SH JSTEP020 \/\/STEP0010.PARMDATE DD DSN=TEST.CL.RSW.CARDLIB(PARMDATE),DISP=SH "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$8001",
  "PROBLEM": "UNEXPLAINED COND CODE 0012 STEP STEP0010\/JSTEP060 OFFSET X'45A': ABEND S0C1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PICKING UP CLIENT ERRORS BECAUSE THIS JOB PROCESSED ON THE NEXT DAY AND DATES WERE ALREADY UPDATED FOR THAT DAY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "PUT IN OVERRIDES FOR PARMDATE TO POINT TO PREV DAY AND RESTART FROM THE TOP. JSTEP060 \/\/STEP0010.PARMDATE DD DSN=TEST.CL.RSW.CARDLIB(PARMDATE),DISP=SH "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0008",
  "PROBLEM": "UNEXPLAINED COND CODE 0012 OFFSET X'45A': ABEND S0C1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PICKING UP CLIENT ERRORS BECAUSE THIS JOB PROCESSED ON THE NEXT DAY AND DATES WERE ALREADY UPDATED FOR THAT DAY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "PUT IN OVERRIDES FOR PARMDATE TO POINT TO PREV DAY AND RESTART FROM THE TOP. \/\/STEP0020.PARMDATE=TEST.CL.RSW.CARDLIB(PARMDATE),DISP=SHR "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0004",
  "PROBLEM": "UNEXPLAINED COND CODE 0012 OFFSET X'45A': ABEND S0C1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LIFEPRO 89 SEGMENTS WERE NOT CURRENT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "UPDATE CLIENT OBJECT RELATION TABLE. UNEXPIRED 1 TO 0. HISTORY DATE TO 12\/31\/9999 RESTART ACCORDING TO SCHD.CTM.DOC "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0820",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP=STEP0050 PGM=D724COM5 ABENDED - COND CODE SFC6 A FILE ATTRIBUTE MISMATCH WAS DETECTED. FILE ABS-FILE IN PROGRAM D724COM FILE SPECIFIED IN THE ASSIGN CLAUSE HAD A RECORD LENGTH OF 403. THERE WAS AN UNSUCCESSFUL OPEN OR CLOSE OF FILE IABSFILE IN PROGRAM D724 NEITHER FILE STATUS NOR AN ERROR DECLARATIVE WERE SPECIFIED. THE STATUS FROM COMPILE UNIT D724COM5 AT ENTRY POINT D724COM5 AT COMPILE UNIT OFFSE AT ADDRESS 00008334. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LIFEPRO PROJECT CHANGED THE LENGTH OF INPUT FILE, BUT THIS FILE STILL HAD THE OLD LENGTH. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DETERMINED THAT AGCY0006 HAD RUN AND HAD CREATED AN INVALID DSN. DECIDED TO IGNORE THE INVALID DSN AND USE PREVIOUS DSN. RESTARTED IN STEP0050 WITH THIS OVERRIDE: JSTEP010 \/\/STEP0050.IABSFILE DD DSN=CL.COMP.COMMSN.G0604V00,DISP=SHR \/\/STEP0060.IABSFILE DD DSN=CL.COMP.COMMSN.G0604V00,DISP=SHR JSTEP020 \/\/ICK4ABC DD DSN=CL.ABC.NETCOMM.EXTS.G0604V00,DISP=SHR "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0007",
  "PROBLEM": "B37-04 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS WAS FIRST RUN AFTER LIFEPRO CONVERSION PROJECT. NEEDED TO BUMP UP OUTPUT FILE FROM 300,30 TO 500,100. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DELETED CL.CL$$0007.POL.PLANDIR.INS AND CL.CL$$0007.POL.PLANDIR.INS USING FIRECALL. SINCE REST OF STEPS FINISHED OKAY WE RESTARTED IN STEP0130 AND RERAN THAT STEP PLUS 0140. CONDITIONED OUT THE STEPS AFTER. USED THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDES AND RESTARTED IN STEP0130... \/\/CL$$0007 EXEC PROC=CL$$0007, \/\/ COND.STEP0150=(0,LE), \/\/ COND.STEP0160=(0,LE), \/\/ COND.STEP0170=(0,LE), \/\/ COND.STEP0180=(0,LE), \/\/ COND.STEP0190=(0,LE), \/\/ COND.STEP0200=(0,LE), \/\/ VOPREFX='CL.VSAM.BASEOL.', \/\/ TBL='CL.VSAM.BASEOL.' \/\/STEP0130.NEWDD DD DSN=CL.CL$$0007.POL.PLANDIR.G1860V00, \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) \/\/STEP0130.OLDDD DD DSN=CL.CL$$0007.POL.PLANDIR.G1859V00, \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) \/\/STEP0130.DELDD DD DSN=CL.CL$$0007.POL.PLANDIR.SUPERC, \/\/ DISP=(NEW,CATLG,DELETE), \/\/ UNIT=SYSDA, \/\/ SPACE=(CYL,(500,100),RLSE), \/\/ DCB=(RECFM=VB,LRECL=518,BLKSIZE=27458) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$2060",
  "PROBLEM": "MODULE Q724DCME, PROGRAM Q724DCME, OFFSET X'E74': ABEND SOC7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CL.AGNTDEFD.BEGIN.PREMIUM POLICY 5200153860 THE ACCUMULATED PREMIUM AMOUNT IN COLUMN 11 HAD LOW VALUES. THIS FILE IS BUILT AT YEAR END IN CL$$4100. RECORDS ARE WRITTEN TO THE FILE IF THERE IS A NOTE PAD PURPOSE TYPE = AGTDF. THIS POLICY HAD THIS NOTE PAD (72 SEG) IN ERROR. IT HAS BEEN REMOVED FROM THE POLICY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPY THE FILE TO TEST NAME, DELETE THE POLICY AND RESTART IN STEP0220 WITH AN OVERRIDE FOR IINPUTB. THIS FILE IS USED EVERY MONTH. DELETE THE RECORD FROM CL.AGNTDEFD.BEGIN.PREMIUM. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0103",
  "PROBLEM": "CKUB01 CEEHDLR CONDITION HANDLER SERVICE INVOKED PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) AT LOCATION 0001B0 IN ELEMENT CKDCARTH CKSN01 PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. PSW=078D2400 8DB74A66 (DECIMAL DATA) CKUB03 CURRENT POLICY 0720075460 CKSN02 ABENDING ELEMENT CKDCARTH EPA=0DB748B0 OFFSET 0001B0 CKUB07 UNABLE TO CONTINUE PROCESSING - JOB ABORTING. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FPCHSDUR-LATEST-HISTORY-DUR < ZERO AND POLICY ANNIVERSARY PROCESSING ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. FOLLOW THE RESTORE PROCEDURES 2. USE ONE OF THESE OPTIONS: A. CHANGE CL.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY, 51 SEGMENT. CHANGE: 02519D TO 00000C OR B. CHANGE THE DATE IN THE SCHEDULER FILE TO A MONTH IN THE FUTURE 3. FOLLOW THE RESTART PROCEDURES. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0060",
  "PROBLEM": "ALLOCATING TARGET DATA SET: CL.SI.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN ABEND SB37 DETECTED, DATA SET EXPANSION STOPPED DATA SET ALLOCATION COMPLETED TARGET DATA SET ALLOCATED, BUT IT IS TOO SMALL - DSNAME: CL.SI.VSAM.BASE TARGET DATA SET CLEANUP - DSNAME: CL.SI.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN PROCESSING FOR STATEMENT #19 COMPLETED, HIGHEST RETURN CODE ENCOUNTERED MAXRC OF 4 EXCEEDED, PROCESSING TERMINATED PROCESSING COMPLETED, HIGHEST RETURN CODE ENCOUNTERED IS 8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "NOT ENOUGH SPACE AVAILABLE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CALLED DASD TEAM ONCALL. KEITH SAID THERE WAS NOT ENOUGH ROOM ON THE VOLUME, SO HE SWITCHED IT OVER TO ANOTHER VOLUME. RERAN FROM THE TOP WITH THIS OVERRIDE: SNAP DATASET ( SOURCE (CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN ) - TARGET (CL.SI.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN ) - VOLUME(CLDSK1) TOLENQF(Y) - REPLACE(Y) ) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$R160",
  "PROBLEM": "---- THURSDAY, 13 JAN 2011 ---- $HASP373 CL$$R160 STARTED - INIT 11 - CLASS P - SYS AUL1 ACF9CCCD USERID ACFSUBID IS ASSIGNED TO THIS JOB - CL$$R160 IEF403I CL$$R160 - STARTED - TIME=00.08.23 -STEP=STEP0010 PGM=SIBBATCH EXECUTED - COND CODE 0008 RC=0000 ELAP= 00 IEF404I CL$$R160 - ENDED - TIME=00.08.25 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS JOB WAS RUN BY MISTAKE. AFTER REVIEWING THE JOB OUTPUT, WE REALIZED THAT NONE OF THE FILES WERE RESTORED BECAUSE THE SNAP FAILED: TARGET DISP CL.VSAM.ACH.AUDIT.CONTROL NEXEC CL.VSAM.ACH.AUDIT.CONTROL.INDEX CL.VSAM.ACH.AUDIT.CONTROL.DATA CL.VSAM.ACH.AUDIT.CNTL.AIX NEXEC CL.VSAM.ACH.AUDIT.CNTL.AIX.INDEX CL.VSAM.ACH.AUDIT.CNTL.AIX.DATA CL.VSAM.ACH.AUDIT.ERRORS NEXEC CL.VSAM.ACH.CONTROL.XREF NEXEC CL.VSAM.BASEOL.ACTIVITY NEXEC ",
  "SOLUTION": "NO ACTION WAS REQUIRED BECAUSE NONE OF THE FILES WERE RESTORED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1180",
  "PROBLEM": "IEF450I CL$$1180 STEP0040 CL$$RCL5 - ABEND=S04E U0000 REASON=00E40347 # STEP=STEP0040 PGM=DSNUTILB ABENDED - COND CODE S04E RC=00E4 ELAP= 00:0 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB FAILED IN STEP0040, BUT I NOTICED THAT STEP0020 GOT A RETURN CODE 08: DSN1999I START OF DSN1COPY FOR JOB CL$$1180 STEP0020CL$$RCL5 DSN1989I DSN1COPY IS PROCESSED WITH THE FOLLOWING OPTIONS: NO CHECK\/NO PRINT\/ 4K\/FULLCOPY \/NON-SEGMENT\/NUMPARTS= 0\/NO DSSIZE= \/PIECESIZ= \/ \/ DSN1998I INPUT DSNAME = CL.ME.BASEB.CISBMAIN.G0123V00 , S DSN1997I OUTPUT DSNAME = CL.DSNDBD.CLS1.TCLS1.I0001.A001 , V DSN1992I VSAM PUT ERROR, RPLERREG = 008, RPLERRCD = 028 DSN1993I DSN1COPY TERMINATED, 00220683 PAGES PROCESSED ",
  "SOLUTION": "SINCE THIS WAS A VSAM ERROR WHILE TRYING TO RESTORE THE ME DATA, I JUST RESTARTED FROM THE TOP. JOB RAN SUCCESSFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1000",
  "PROBLEM": "IEC030I B37-04,IFG0554A,CL$$1000,STEP0080,SYSUT1,228E,PUB010,0427041D,SY IEF450I CL$$1000 STEP0080 CL$$1000 - ABEND=SB37 U0000 REASON=00000004 0 TIME=01.00.37 # IEF450I CL$$1000 STEP0080 CL$$1000 - ABEND=SB37 U0000 REASON=00000004 -STEP=STEP0080 PGM=DSNUTILB ABENDED - COND CODE SB37 RC=0000 ELAP= 00: ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SPACE ERROR IN DSN SYSUT1 IN STEP0080. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTARTED JOB IN STEP0065 WITH OVERRIDE: \/\/CL$$1000 EXEC PROC=CL$$1000 \/\/STEP0080.SYSUT1 DD DSN=&&SYSUT1, \/\/ DISP=(NEW,DELETE,DELETE), \/\/ UNIT=&DISK, \/\/ SPACE=(CYL,(999,999),RLSE) JOB ABENDED AGAIN WITH -904: DSNT408I SQLCODE = -904, ERROR: UNSUCCESSFUL EXECUTION CAUSED BY AN UNA DSNT418I SQLSTATE = 57011 SQLSTATE RETURN CODE DSNT415I SQLERRP = DSNXRSTD SQL PROCEDURE DETECTING ERROR DSNT416I SQLERRD = -190 13172746 0 13222867 -992411648 0 SQL DIA DSNT416I SQLERRD = X'FFFFFF42' X'00C9000A' X'00000000' X'00C9C3D3' I THEN CALLED THE DB2 ONCALL (MARCI), AND SHE HAD TO RESET THE DB2 RESOURCES. WE RESTARTED AGAIN IN STEP0065 SUCCESSFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "-STEP=STEP0110 PGM=DLSBATCH EXECUTED - COND CODE 0016 -STEP=CSET1 PGM=COMPUSET EXECUTED - COND CODE 0000 +FOR0341I STOP 12 -STEP=METINT PGM=XRXINT EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 +FOR0341I STOP 12 -STEP=METINT2 PGM=XRXINT EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 -STEP=GENER1 PGM=ICEGENER EXECUTED - COND CODE 0000 IEF404I CL$T0838 - ENDED - TIME=04.54.29 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "BY PUTTING A ? AND VIEWING SYSPRINT CL$$0838 STEP0110 CRITERIA CHECK ERROR. CUSTOMER FILE DVCUSTLIFE SEGMENT DVRIDER REACHED END OF FILE OR HAS NOT BEEN READ TRIGGER: 1, PRODUCT: AUL WHOLELIFE 2007 PAGES, COMPANY-CD: 00, CONTRACT-NUM: 0720300010 CURRENT RULE DESCRIPTION: SURVIVOR PURCHASE OPTION RIDER SCHEDULE - LR-219 TOTAL ERRORS: 1. TOTAL DOCUMENTS PROCESSED: 0. ",
  "SOLUTION": "THE ABOVE PROBLEM IS A DLS PROBLEM AND A DLS DEVELOPER NEEDS TO RESEARCH THE PROBLEM. FOR THE ABOVE PROBLEM SUE CARMICHAEL MODIFIED A DLS TEXT PIECE FOR THE NEW SPO LR-219 PROJECT THAT WAS CODED IN ERROR AND THE JOB WAS RESTARTED FROM THE TOP "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0901",
  "PROBLEM": "* NOT RESTORED -- DSN=CL.CL$$0864.AUL.OTAGCUST.BKUP.G0022V00 * ABR AUTO RECALL CANCELLED-RESTORE INCOMPLETE-WILL ISSUE U0026 ABEND ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED AT JESYSMSG & SAW THAT FDR RESTORE FAILED ON DATASET: CL.CL$$0864.AUL.OTAGCUST.BKUP.G0022V00. ",
  "SOLUTION": "MANUALLY RESTORED DATASET AND RESTARTED JOB FROM TOP. IT ABENDED ON G0021V00 OF SAME DATASET. RESTORED ALL GENERATIONS OF THAT DATASET AND HAD JOB RESTARTED FROM TOP. STEP0010 COMPLETED BUT NOT SUCCESSFULLY. HAD JOB RESTARTED FROM TOP. JOB RAN FOR OVER 13 CLOCK HRS (OVER 10 CPU HRS) BUT FINISHED OK. ON 01\/17\/11, MARK INCREASED OUR FDR BACKUP LIMIT FROM 100 TO 150. THIS SHOULD ELIMINATE RESTORE PROBLEMS PERTAINING TO THIS MESSAGE: FDR338** MAXIMUM BACKUP FILES EXCEEDED - SPECIFY MAXBACKUP=NNNN TO OVERR "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$GROW",
  "PROBLEM": "IAMW67 IAM SMS ALLOC FAILED RC=X'D8' REAS=X'044E0097' CLUSTER=CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN IN DD REORGPRT: FDRR30 BACKUP STARTED DSN=CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN FDRR31 BACKUP ENDED DSN=CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN FDRR47** DEFINE ERROR -- RETURN CODE 042, REASON IGG0CLIM 216, FDRR32** RELOAD PROCESSING TERMINATED FDRR33** RELOAD FAILED - CODE=U0999,DSN=CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CURRENTLY THE DATASET IS ALLOCATED WITH 4179 CYLINDERS. THE LARGEST ALLOCATION A SINGLE DATASET CAN USE ON A SINGLE VOLUME IS 4369 CYLINDERS. IAMGROW=50 EXCEEDS 4369. ",
  "SOLUTION": "IAMGROW=5 INCREASED THE FILE ENOUGH FOR CL$$0110 TO RUN NEXT DAY: DELETE\/DEFINE AGTFIN WITH THIS IN THE JCL: \/\/IAMOVRID DD * CREATE DD=&ALLDD,DSNTYPE=LARGE "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0110",
  "PROBLEM": "IEC030I B37-04,IFG0554A,CL$$0110,STEP0060,VSAM4,226D,STOR13, 04210010,CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN IAMW13 DD=VSAM4 FILE FULL, REORGANIZATION REQUIRED + VSAM ERROR - FILE=VSAM4 , INCODE=3, OUTCODE=5, R15=08, ERRCODE=001C +- - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CURRENTLY THE DATASET IS ALLOCATED WITH 4179 CYLINDERS. THE LARGEST ALLOCATION A SINGLE DATASET CAN USE ON A SINGLE VOLUME IS 4369 CYLINDERS. THE SECONDARY ALLOCATION IS 500 CYLINDERS, WHICH EXCEEDS 4369. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RUN CL$$R110 TO RESTORE THE FILES. KEITH FLUHARTY WAS ABLE TO RUN CL$$GROW ON CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN WITH 5%. RESTART FROM THE TOP. NEXT DAY: DELETE\/DEFINE AGTFIN WITH THIS IN THE JCL: \/\/IAMOVRID DD * CREATE DD=&ALLDD,DSNTYPE=LARGE "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0420",
  "PROBLEM": "CSECT CKETRGET, OFFSET X'45A' CAUSING S04C, DATE CHANGED IN CLIENT AT 8 1M AND POLICY WAS UPDATED. PER WENDY THIS OFFSET X'45A' WILL ALWAYS BE DATE IN CLIENT NO LONGER CORRECT. - CYCLE WAS DELAYED PRIOR NIGHT ",
  "ANALYSIS": "NOW THAT THE PRODUCTION PARM DATE HAS BEEN CHANGED FROM 11\/3\/10 TO 11\/4\/10 WE WILL TRY RE-RUNNING FROM THE TOP. DID WHAT WENDY SUGGESTED BUT ABOUT 10 MINUTES AFTER THAT RHONDA ASKED IF I REQUESTED JOB WITH OVER RIDE TO PICK UP NON-CICS LOAD - WHICH I DID NOT - THEREFORE IT IS LIKELY THE JOB WILL ABEND AGAIN - OR RUN A REALLY LONG TIME. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RUN WITH THIS OVERRIDE: \/\/JOBLIB DD DISP=SHR,DSN=TEST.CL.WET.LOADLIB.EXHIBIT \/\/ DD DISP=SHR,DSN=PROD.CL.LOADLIB \/\/ DD DISP=SHR,DSN=PROD.CL.OBJLIB "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1110",
  "PROBLEM": "NO DUMP WAS PRODUCED FOR THIS ABEND, DUE TO SYSTEM OR INSTALLATION CL$$1110 STEP0010 JSTEP010 - ABEND=S322 U0000 REASON=00000000 184 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB HAD BEEN RUNNING FOR ALMOST 5 HOURS. MAY APPEAR TO BE LOOPING. IT'S NOT. MAY HAVE TIMED-OUT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RERUN JOB FROM THE TOP WITH TIME=NOLIMIT PARAMETER. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0420",
  "PROBLEM": "00214 2 AP0214 - SPECIFIED RUNDATE INCONSISTENT WITH THE LAST RUNDATE SEVERE ERROR - RUN ABORTED FOR THIS USER ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SINCE WE WERE TRYING TO RUN THIS SAT MORNING, THE CDATES HAD ALREADY CHANGED. THEY NO LONGER MATCHED THE FILE INPUT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RUN WITH THIS OVERRIDE: \/\/JOBLIB DD DISP=SHR,DSN=TEST.CL.WET.LOADLIB.EXHIBIT \/\/ DD DISP=SHR,DSN=PROD.CL.LOADLIB \/\/ DD DISP=SHR,DSN=PROD.CL.OBJLIB \/\/STEP0020.SYSIPT DD * CKVAUL00 09242010 AU 2 09242010 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0105",
  "PROBLEM": "AMERICAN UNITED LIFE INSURANCE COMPANY DATE OF REPORT...09-24-10 DHXC11 - POLICY EXHIBIT TRANSACTIO PROCESSING DATES NUMBER PREVIOUS CURRENT PROCE INPUT FILE 1 09\/23\/10 09\/24\/10 000 INPUT FILE 2 09\/21\/10 09\/22\/10 000 ** NO LOGICAL MATCH ON INPUT DATES - JOB CANCELLED ** USER ABEND 0001 HAS BEEN DETECTED AT LOCATION 0001 PSW = 078D1000 8DA02DB8 REGISTERS AT TIME OF INTERRUPT: 00-07 80000000 80000001 0DA0152C 0DA02CA0 0DA02842 00012910 00000001 0 08-15 00015A80 0DAA0700 0DAE00B8 0DA01A00 00013B78 000266B0 8DA02D86 0 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WE DID NOT COMPLETE CL$$0420 IN THE PREVIOUS CYCLE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "WE RAN CL$$0420 AND CL$$0440 USING FIRECALL. WE THEN RESTARTED CL$$0105 IN STEP0100 WITH AN OVERRIDE FOR THE INPUT FILE: \/\/STEP0100.SEQUEN DD DSN=CL.CL$$0100.POLEX.DAILY.SORTED.G1242V00, \/\/ DISP=SHR "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0008",
  "PROBLEM": "ABENDING ELEMENT CKETRGET EPA=0DA600F0 OFFSET 00045A ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOBS RAN LATE BECAUSE OF PROBLEMS ON FRIDAY NIGHT. A ROW WAS DELETED IN CLIENT PRIOR TO THESE JOBS ON SATURDAY MORNING. THESE JOBS USE THE SA FILES, SO THEY WERE OUT OF SYNC WITH CLIENT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CHANGED THE JOBS TO USE THE CURRENT POLICY FILES INSTEAD OF THE SA FILES. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0120",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC 7 U0999 OFFSET 12B0 IN ELEMENT CKBSBCII FIELD: MBPREMDU-AMOUNT-DUE CONTAINED LOW VALUES INPUT FILE: CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.BILLEXTS(0) ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DID A FIND ON X'00' IN COLUMN 45 WHICH ALSO HAD LOW-VALUES. MBPREMDU-AMOUNT-DUE IS COLUMN 34-39 SO WE COULD HAVE SEARCH FOR X'000000000000' IN COLUMN 34 AS WELL. ",
  "SOLUTION": "THE SEARCH REVEALED 19 RECORDS WITH LOW VALUES IN COLUMN 34-39. SOLUTION: SAVE CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.BILLEXTS(0) AS SUFFIXED NAME CL...D092310 FOR LATER ANALYSIS DROP 19 BAD RECORDS FOR POLICIES FROM THE CURRENT GDG 0620072770 0620086170 0620086180 0620131750 0620150280 0620159640 0620337460 0620372250 0620372260 0620383980 0710042140 0720006190 0720009220 0720016460 0720048370 2453462720 5110027290 5770001340 5770001350 RESTARTED JOB FROM TOP. NEXT DAY, DETERMINED THAT ISSUE CL9410 WHICH TURNED OFF PRENOTES HAD MOVE TO PRODUCTION PRIOR NIGHT. SOME EXISTING PRENOTES HAD NOT FINISHED PROCESSING AND WERE NOT ABLE TO GET THROUGH THE LOGIC DUE TO PRENOTES BEING TURNED OFF. CL9410 SHOULD HAVE BEEN IMPLEMENTED AFTER THE CL CYCLE HAD FINISHED AND NOT BEFORE DUE TO THE OUTSTANDING ACTIVITY. NO OTHER ACTION IS NEEDED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$SEGD",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$SEGD STEP0020 - ABEND=S0C7 U0000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CHECKED IDIREPRT: (A) NOTED THAT THE COBOL SOURCE CODE RELATED TO ERROR IS FIELD FCXCPRCP-RATE-PERCENT(FCXRATSG-IX): FCXCPRCP-RATE-PERCENT(2) = X'0C000C' *** INVALID NUMERIC DATA (B) ALSO NOTED LOADLIB BEING PICKED UP FROM IS: TEST.CL.LOADLIB (I WOULD EXPECT PROD.CL.LOADLIB NORMALLY?) (C) VERIFIED THAT THE TEST VERSION OF R724FX38 DOES EXIST IN TEST.CL.LOADLIB (LIFEPRO CONVERSION IS CURRENTLY IN TEST!) (D) DID A SEARCH OF LIBRARY TEST.CL.COPYLIB ON TEXT 'FCXCPRCP-RATE -PERCENT'; RESULTS RETURNED MEMBER NAME CKFRECCX (E) COMPARED TEST AND PROD VERSIONS OF CKFRECCX - THEY DID NOT MATCH; CHANGES IN THE TEST VERSION AFFECT THE FIELD IN QUESTION IN PROD. ",
  "SOLUTION": "FROM ABOVE ANALYSIS, WE KNOW WE DON'T WANT THE JOB POINTING TO THE TEST VERSION OF PROGRAM R724FX38. THE LEAST INTRUSIVE SOLUTION IS TO RENAME MEMBER TEST.CL.LOADLIB(R724FX38) TO SOMETHING ELSE TEMPORARILY. I USED TEST.CL.LOADLIB(R724JF38). I ASKED OPS TO RERUN THE JOB FROM THE TOP. JOB ENDED SUCCESFULLY! I THEN RESTORED THE NAME OF THE TEST LOADLIB MEMBER FROM R724JF38 TO R724FX38. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1160",
  "PROBLEM": "CKETRGET, OFFSET X'45A' ",
  "ANALYSIS": "M724TAIT HAD BEEN LINKED WITH CLIENT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "LINKED M724TAIT NON-CLIENT. RESTARTED FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0847",
  "PROBLEM": "+FOR0341I STOP 8 -STEP=COMPOSE PGM=COMPUSET EXECUTED - COND CODE 0008 *** ",
  "ANALYSIS": "(COMPUSET PROBLEM) IN S.T, SEE: DDNAME STEPNAME PROCSTEP -------- -------- -------- FT06F001 STEP0360 COMPOSE \"COMPOSITION ERROR LOG FOLLOWS . . . . . . LINE 9; CIRCA OUTPUT PAGE 3 IN HEADER HD2; ERROR 4 AT CHARACTER POSITION 28: UNDEFINED COMMAND NAME. ERROR 4 AT CHARACTER POSITION 44: UNDEFINED COMMAND NAME. <SP,6\/PNT12\/QL,,50\/SSN1LEFT\/QR,570\/SSN1RGHT>�\/ 00 * * LINE 64; CIRCA OUTPUT PAGE 3 IN INCLUDE FILE PROXYMXX;\" --OTHER RELATED CODE IN ERROR: \"<OWNERLBL>``<PNT12B\/OWNER\/COWNRDTA\/PNT12\/SP,6\/QL>\" --EXPLANATION: THE LATEST VERSION OF THE PROXYMXX FILE IS NOT COMPATIBLE WITH THE VARIABLES IN THE TAG FILE. --SSN1LEFT IS NOT DEFINED --SSN1RGHT IS NOT DEFINED --OWNERLBL IS NOT DEFINED --COWNRDTA IS NOT DEFINED *** ",
  "SOLUTION": "FORCE COMPLETE JOB OK. ALERT TRIAGE THAT POLICY PAGES FOR AN OLD, NO-LONGER- ISSUED PRODUCT HAVE BEEN REQUESTED\/CREATED AND THAT THE PRINTOUT MAY NOT BE CORRECT. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0911",
  "PROBLEM": "COND CODE 911 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DISPLAY IN THIS PROGRAM SHOWING POLICY 2453434470 THIS WAS FOUND BY REVIEWING THE SYSOUT OUTPUT. 2453434470 MATCHING EF 0 EF THIS MESSAGE DISPLAYED SEVERAL TIMES. 6\/12\/10 SAME MESSAGE AND SAME POLICY NUMBER ",
  "SOLUTION": "REVIEW SCHD.CTM.DOC TO SEE WHO TO NOTIFY FOR WHAT ERROR MESSAGE. FOR THIS SITUATION - NOTIFIED TRIAGE BY EMAIL AND HAD THE OPERATOR FORCE COMPLETE THE JOB. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0911",
  "PROBLEM": "COND CODE 911 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "INCOMPLETE ACTIVITY REPORT SHOWING SEVERAL POLICIES WITH EXCHANGES. THESE POLICIES ARE AGENT DEF COMP THAT THE EXCHANGES HAPPEN MONTHLY. THE JOB PROCESS ALL THE RECORDS, BUT FLAGS THE COND CODE OF 911. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CONTACTED SEPARATE ACCOUNTS ON-CALL TO LET THEM KNOW AND THEN FORCE COMPLETE THE JOB. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0040",
  "PROBLEM": "+PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) AT LOCATION 00069E IN ELEMENT CKOAMPSE ",
  "ANALYSIS": "TO FIND PROBLEM POLICY, ENTER IDIREPRT DUMP AND DO A FIND ON SEQUEN2. THIS WILL SHOW THE OFFENDING POLICY IN THIS CASE THE OFFENDING POLICY WAS NOT THE PROBLEM THE PROBLEM HAD SOMETHING TO DO WITH A BUNCH OF SPECIAL FMB'S RUN AFTER THE CYCLE HAD STARTED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "AFTER CONSIDERATION OF THE EFFECTS OF THE FMB ON THE OUTCOME OF THIS JOB, IT WAS DECIDED TO USE THE SB ACTIVITY FILE AND IGNORE THE ACTIVITY FROM THE SPECIAL FMBS. OVERRIDES WERE ADDED FOR STEP0020 AND STEP0390 TO OVERRIDE THE VSAM ACTIVITY FILE TO USE THE SB. JOB FINISHED OKAY. TOOLS: SOME TOOLS HAVE BEEN CONSTRUCTED TO HELP WITH THIS JOB "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0838",
  "PROBLEM": "APPEARS TO OCCUR IN CONJUNCTION WITH A WL POLICY (0720084920) FOR THE STATE OF NC *SOLUTION: 1. TO FIND THE POLICY NUMBER - DO A FIND IN THE FILE CL.DLS.AULWL.TAGGED FOR A PART OF THE ERROR MESSAGE. IN THIS CASE, FIND ON '<COLOR,3,0,0,0>DUE TO BASE <$100,000' PAGED UP UNTIL YOU FIND 'POLICY NUMBER' 2. SINCE THIS POLICY PRINTED, HAD NEW BUSINESS PULL AND VERIFY THE PRINTED PAGES BEFORE MAILING THEM. 3. HAD THE JOB FORCE COMPLETED OK. 4. NOTES ON FINDING THE INVALID FIELD IN CASE NEW BUSINESS OR TRIAGE NEEDS HELP DETERMINING DATA CORRECTION ARE FOUND AT K:\\DLSIND\\HOW TOS & ERRORS\\ILLEGAL CHARACTER POSITION XX "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0836",
  "PROBLEM": "-STEP=STEP0320 PGM=DLSBATCH EXECUTED - COND CODE 0000 RC=0000 -STEP=CSET1 PGM=COMPUSET EXECUTED - COND CODE 0000 RC=0000 IEC161I 052(009,P1PSS839)-084,CL$$0836,METINT STEP0330,VSRN02 IEC161I XICS.COMPUSET.DCLIB3,XICS.COMPUSET.DCLIB3.DATA,CATALOG IEC161I 052(009,P1PSS839)-084,CL$$0836,METINT STEP0330,VSRN02 IEC161I XICS.COMPUSET.DCLIB3,XICS.COMPUSET.DCLIB3.DATA,CATALOG +FOR0341I STOP 8 -STEP=METINT PGM=XRXINT EXECUTED - COND CODE 0008 RC=0000 IEC161I 052(009,P1PSS839)-084,CL$$0836,METINT2 STEP0330,VSRN02 IEC161I XICS.COMPUSET.DCLIB3,XICS.COMPUSET.DCLIB3.DATA,CATALOG IEC161I 052(009,P1PSS839)-084,CL$$0836,METINT2 STEP0330,VSRN02 IEC161I XICS.COMPUSET.DCLIB3,XICS.COMPUSET.DCLIB3.DATA,CATALOG +FOR0341I STOP 8 -STEP=METINT2 PGM=XRXINT EXECUTED - COND CODE 0008 RC=0000 -STEP=GENER1 PGM=ICEGENER EXECUTED - COND CODE 0000 RC=0000 IEF404I CL$$0836 - ENDED - TIME=11.43.20 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE ABOVE COND CODE = 8 IN DLS MEANS THAT THE DLS MERGE LIBRARY WAS UNABLE WHEN THIS JOB NEEDED IT BECAUSE ANOTHER JOB HAD CONTROL OF THE DLS LIBRARY ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD THE PRINT ROOM PURGE ALL PRINTOUT FROM THE ABOVE JOB AND HAD THE JOB RESTARTED FROM THE TOP SECOND JOB ENDED WITHOUT ANY PROBLEMS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0020",
  "PROBLEM": "THE JOB DID NOT ABEND HOWEVER NO RECORDS WERE EXTRACTED FROM THE JOB INTO FILE... CL.P0020.S0010.SEQEXTC. THE FILE WAS EMPTY HOWEVER THERE WERE RECORDS ON CL.VSAM.BASEOL.DPFS2. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "AFTER REVIEWING THE CICS LOG IT WAS FOUND THAT CYBERLIFE DID NOT SHUTDOWN PROPERLY, THE '0002' AND '0003' TRANSACTIONS BOTH REJECTED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "THE RECORDS CAN BE EXTRACTED MANUALLY FROM THE SB FILES THE FOLLOWING DAY TO CREATE THE PAGES. ALSO SEE THE WRITE UP IN TEST.CL.BOMBLOG(CICSBOMB) UNDER \"PROD REGION 11\/03\/2006 19:02 P1SLJ\" FOR MORE DETAILS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1HED",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C4 AUVPMFWB DISPLACEMENT F78 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ABENDED ON 2453440720 WHICH IS A KNOWN PROBLEM. THE ",
  "SOLUTION": "IS INSTALLED IN THE TEST REGION AS CL9318. 2453450260 HAS THE SAME PROBLEM NIGHTLY. SOLUTION: I COPIED CL.CL$$1HED.HEDGING.INPUT.G0025V00 TO SAME NAME.D012910. I DELETED THE TWO POLICIES. RESTARTED IN STEP0030 AND ADDED OVERRIDE \/\/STEP0030.SEQUEN DD DSN=CL.CL$$1HED.HEDGING.INPUT(0) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1940",
  "PROBLEM": "LOOKING IN JESMSGLG JES2 - PROGRAM READS 89 LIFE CONTROL TO GET THE INSUREDS NAME: +IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V8R1M0 (UK30777 2007\/10\/31) INVOKED BY ID +IDI0082E DB2 DB2P CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQLALLOCCONNECT SQL SQLRC=-1 {DB2 FOR OS\/390}{ODBC DRIVER} SQLSTATE=58004 ERRLOC=2:170:10 CAF \"OPEN\" FAILED USING DB2 SYSTEM:DB2P AND PLAN:DSNACLI RC=0C AND REASON=00F30040 +IDI0002I MODULE M7240CCR, CSECT CKVSAMIO, OFFSET X'356': ABEND S0 +IDI0003I FAULT ID F07875 ASSIGNED IN HISTORY FILE SYS2.FA.HIST.BA LOOKING IN FA = SEEING SECTION OF CODE WITH PROBLEM COBOL SOURCE CODE: SOURCE LINE # ------ -5 CL5872 ULMCOMM-COMM-PREM-OPTION -4 CL5872 ULMSFPRM-SPEC-FRQ-PREM -3 CL5872 ULMSFBAS-SPEC-FRQ-BASIS-AMT. -2 CL6971 MOVE '3' TO ULMCALC-CALCULATION-OPTION. -1 CL6971 MOVE FCVPHASE-PHASE-CODE TO ULMPHASE-PHASE-CODE. 011223 CL5872 CALL 'CKULMPIF' USING CK4VS-MODE-PREMIUM-PARMS 011224 CL5872 WS-INFORCE-DCB. +1 CL5872 IF ULMRETCD-RETURN-CODE NOT EQUAL '0' +2 CL5872 GO TO SUBR-8100-CALL-CKULMPIF-EXIT. +3 CL5872 MOVE ULMMPREM-MODE-PREMIUM TO WS-PREM-AMT-ACCUM. +4 CL5872 SUBR-8100-CALL-CKULMPIF-EXIT. EXIT. +5 CL6301 SUBR-8200-CALL-CKFVPC66. DATA FIELD DECLARATIONS: SOURCE LINE # ------ 001487 01 WS-INFORCE-DCB. 009237 CL5872 01 CK4VS-MODE-PREMIUM-PARMS. DATA FIELD VALUES: CK4VS-MODE-PREMIUM-PARMS = .G.....................30.00...N..0 NOTE: ABOVE VALUE TRUNCATED AFTER 103 BYTES WS-INFORCE-DCB = ..O0.............+..02...........T-..0..PDC NOTE: ABOVE VALUE TRUNCATED AFTER 103 BYTES OPEN STATUS . . . . . . . : INPUT FILE STATUS CODE. . . . . : 10 A SEQUENTIAL READ STATEMENT WAS ATTEMPTED AND NO NEXT LOGICAL RECORD EXISTED IN THE FILE BECAUSE THE END OF THE FILE HAD BEEN REACHED, OR THE FIRST READ WAS ATTEMPTED ON AN OPTIONAL INPUT FILE THAT WAS NOT PRESENT. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SEE PROJ00003568-CL9276 - CL$$1940 ABEND POST 0801 UPGRADE - IN 08 RELEASE WE UPDATED PROGRAM R724EBR0 UNDER CL8458 TO ALLOW FOR MISC PREM FILE - IT IS POSSIBLE THAT WE NEED TO MAKE SIMILAR CHANGES TO PROGRAM M7240CCR TO GET PAST THIS ABEND SITUATION. THE ABEND ALMOST LOOKS LIKE AN SQL ERROR, BUT FA INFORMATION WOULD INDICATE THE TRUE PROBLEM IS A FILE I\/O NOT WORKING AS EXPECTED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "AT THIS POINT WE CAN ONLY FORCE THE JOB COMPLETE UNTIL CHANGES FOR PROJ00003568-CL9276 ARE INSTALLED INTO PRODUCTION. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0838",
  "PROBLEM": "APPEARS TO OCCUR *ONLY* IN CONJUNCTION WITH A WL POLICY ISSUED IN A NON-APPROVED STATE (IN THIS INSTANCE, NJ). 3. THIS JOB IS FOR THE WL POLICIES ONLY (POLICY PREFIX = 07 FOUND IN COLS 7-8 OF THE FILE CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR(+0) 4. THE STATE IS FOUND IN COLS 36-37 (NJ IS STATE 31) *SOLUTION: VERIFY THAT A POLICY WITH A NON-APPROVED STATE IS ACTUALLY IN THE INPUT FILE --> CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR(+0). IF ONE EXISTS, THEN THE POLICY PAGES WILL NEED TO BE CREATED MANUALLY. IF ONE IS *NOT* FOUND, THEN WE HAVE A BIGGER DLS PROBLEM THAT NEEDS TO BE RESEARCHED. - THE JOB CAN BE FORCE COMPLETED OK. ALL PAGES FOR APPROVED STATES SHOULD PRINT OKAY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0040",
  "PROBLEM": "IEF450I CL$$0040 STEP0380 JSTEP010 - ABEND=S000 U0999 ",
  "SOLUTION": "WE FORCE COMPLETED THE JOB AND MOVED ON IN ORDER TO GET CYCLE COMPLETED AND MAKE TRADES. STEP0380 AND STEP0390 BOTH PRODUCE REPORTS. STEP=STEP0380 PGM=CKOA11 TERMINAL USAGE REPORT STEP=STEP0390 PGM=GOMIBUTL PRINT MIB ERROR REPORT "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0040",
  "PROBLEM": "IEC030I B37-04,IFG0554A,CL$$0040,STEP0020,OUTPUT,228E,PUB010, -STEP=STEP0020 PGM=IDCAMS EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 RC=000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE PROBLEM IS THE JOB WILL NOT ABEND IN STEP0020, IT MAY GO DOWN SOMEPLACE FARTHER DOWN IN THE JOB. ",
  "SOLUTION": "IF STEP0020 HAS A COND CODE=12 THEN THE SPACE PROBABLY NEEDS BUMPED UP FOR THE FOLLOWING STEPS AS WELL .... \/\/STEP0020.OUTPUT DD DSN=&&SEQACTV, \/\/STEP0030.SORTOUT DD DSN=&&SPRQST, \/\/STEP0080.SORTOUT DD DSN=&&SRTAGT, \/\/STEP0115.SORTOUT DD DSN=&&TRANSRT, \/\/ SPACE=(CYL,(100,50),RLSE), "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$8500",
  "PROBLEM": "THIS JOB RUNS A SERIES OF ULTIM PROGRAMS. ON THIS PARTICULAR RUN FOR THIS STEP, WE RECEIVED A CC=0016 CODE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SEE SYSLST FOR JSTEP060; SEARCH FOR \"CONSOLIDATED ERROR LISTING\". THE PROBLEM IS IN THE EXECUTION OF THE \"SET\" STATEMENT FOR PROGRAM LINE 203: \"SET PLNPREM = FTDPINIT-PLANNED-INIT-PREM-AMT.\" THERE ARE A NUMBER OF ERROR OCCURRENCES (512 IN ALL). THE 0016 MEANS THAT A FIELD HAD A DATA OVERFLOW PROBLEM. IN THIS CASE, AN AMOUNT FIELD WAS BEING ASSIGNED NULL OR BLANK FIELDS. THE REPORT SHOWS 0.00 FOR THE CORRESPOND- ING DATA. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAVE OPS FORCE COMPLETE THE JOB OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$IIAM",
  "PROBLEM": "IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 465 SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=B37 REASON CODE=00000004 TIME=03.26.23 SEQ=09037 CPU=0000 ASID=008B CLHT01 FDRR33** BACKUP FAILED - CODE=SB37 ,DSN=CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS PROGRAM IS THE RESPONSIBILITY OF DASD TEAM. SINCE THE JOB FAILED ON THE BACKUP, THEY RECOMMENDED 'FORCE COMPLETING' THE JOB. SO WE DID. NOTE: IF JOB FAILS ON RESTORE STEP, YOU WOULD PROBABLY NEED TO RECREATE THE FILE FROM THE SA. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0103",
  "PROBLEM": "+CKSN01 PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. PSW=078D3400 8D0715B2 (DECIMAL OV +CKUB03 CURRENT POLICY 2051389529 +CKSN02 ABENDING ELEMENT CKDCEXIN EPA=0D071518 OFFSET 000094 +CKUB08 PROGRAM CHECKS EXCEED LIMIT - JOB ABORTING. +CEE0374C CONDITION=CEE3210S TOKEN=00030C8A 59C3C5C5 00000000 887 WHILE RUNNING PROGRAM CKDCEXIN WHICH STARTS AT 0D071518 AT THE TIME OF INTERRUPT ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS FAILED BECAUSED THE 'PROGRAM CHECKS' LIMIT WAS EXCEEDED. WE ACTUALLY DETERMINED THAT THE POLICIES WERE FAILING DUE TO INTEREST RATE UPDATE THAT HAD JUST OCCURRED IN THIS CYCLE (CL$$UINT). ****** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** ",
  "SOLUTION": "WE RAN CL$$R060 AND CL$$RC30 TO RESTORE FILES. THEN WE RAN CL$$RINT TO RESTORE THE INTEREST FILE (BACK OUT THE UPDATES). THEN WE RAN CL$$0102 FROM THE TOP. THEN WE RAN CL$$0103 FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1140",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND=S322 - USED MORE THAN 1 HOUR OF CPU TIME ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOPING ON 3465123730? ",
  "SOLUTION": "UPDATE SEG-SEQ-UA IN D7241079 RERAN WITH OVERRIDES BELOW AFTER \/\/CL$$1140 EXEC PROC=CL$$1140 ADD \/\/STEP0010.STEPLIB DD DISP=SHR,DSN=TEST.CL.LOADLIB \/\/ DD DISP=SHR,DSN=PROD.CL.LOADLIB \/\/STEP0010.PARMDATE DD DSN=TEST.CL.RSW.SHKDWN.R0801(PARMDATE), \/\/ DISP=SHR "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0420",
  "PROBLEM": "BAD POLICY POST 0801 UPGRADE +PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) AT LOCATION 00120E IN ELEMENT CKUBMVLB +IDI0002I MODULE CKAP35V, PROGRAM CKUBMVLB, SOURCE LINE # 6645: ABEND S0C7 (DATA EXCEPTION) *PROBLEM: A USER ABEND 0999 OCCURRED IN MODULE CEEPLPKA AT OFFSET X'1FF594' +PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) AT LOCATION 000C1E IN ELEMENT CKULLPLP ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FIND THE ABENDING POLICY. LOOK FOR POLICY EITHER BY FINDING 'VSAM1' IN THE IDIREPRT OR LOOK IN THE JES OF THE CL$$0103 RUN WHICH WILL SHOW THE SAME ABEND AND THE POLICY NUMBER. *INITIAL FINDINGS : ON LOOKING AT THE CODE WE FOUND THAT WE HAVE FACED SAME ISSUE IN PAST AS WELL WHERE THE VARIABLE WS-LOAN-TBL-OCCURS WAS CHANGED TO 262 UNDER APS261. BUT SEEMS IT IS NOT SUFFICIENT AND THERE ARE NO CHANGES TO THIS FIELD IN RECENT UPGRADES. I BUMPED THE VALUE TO 280 TO CHECK IF ITS WORKING AND JOB ENDED OK. SO, DEFINITELY NEEDS SOME FIX IN CODE CKULLPLP AND CKUBLPLD AGAIN. +PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) AT LOCATION 001 +CKUB03 CURRENT POLICY 2385111700 +CKSN02 ABENDING ELEMENT CKUBMVLB EPA=0D105468 OFFSET 00120E NEED TO SKIP POLICY *ANALYSIS: FIND THE ABENDING POLICY AS ABOVE - 1000776950 **ANALYSIS: FIND THE ABENDING POLICY AS ABOVE - 1000783512 ",
  "SOLUTION": "TEMPORARY SOLUTION IS TO MODIFY TEST.CL.WET.SOURCE(CKVAUL00) AND ADD THE POLICY NUMBER IN PARAGRAPH MAIN4000-CHECK-VSAM-INFORCE WHERE THE HARDCODED SKIP LOGIC IS. RUN TEST.CL.JCLLIB(COMPEXHB) RUN TEST.CL.JCLLIB(LINKEXHB) RESTART CL$$0420 FROM TOP WHICH IS ALREADY SET TO POINT TO TEST.CL.WET.LOADLIB.EXHIBIT *SOLUTION: SAME AS ABOVE. TEST.CL.YAM.SOURCE(CKVAUL00) MODIFIED. NOTE THAT THE ABOVE COMPILE AND LINK JOBS ARE NOT CORRECT ANYMORE,SO UNIT JOBS WERE USED TO COMPILE & LINK RESTART CL$$0420 FROM TOP WITH LOADLIB OVERRIDE TEST.CL.YAM.LOADLIB.EXHIBIT **SOLUTION: AS THE JOB WAS ALREADY ABENDING BECAUSE OF POLICY 1000776950 AND OVERRIDE OF CARD CLIVBYPS WAS ALREADY PRESENT IN JOB SO WE BYPASSED THE POLICY 1000783512 USING THE CARD TEST.CL.TOOLS(CLIVBYPS) AS: ��������������������������������� 01973000 VIEW TEST.CL.TOOLS(CLIVBYPS) COMMAND "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0420",
  "PROBLEM": "BAD POLICY (INVALID NUMERIC VALUE IN FIELD FNPPGDAT-PURGE-DATE) 0000 INSTEAD OF 0000 0C00 0C0C +PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) AT LOCATION 001AF0 IN ELEMENT CKUBAV00 PSW = 078D0400 8E9AA166 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FIND THE ABENDING POLICY. NEED TO SKIP POLICY 5820075380 IN ABENDING JOB CL$$0420. ",
  "SOLUTION": "TEMPORARY SOLUTION IS TO MODIFY TEST.CL.YAS.SOURCE.PROD(CKVAUL00) ADD THE POLICY NUMBER IN PARAGRAPH MAIN4000-CHECK-VSAM-INFORCE WHERE THE HARDCODED SKIP LOGIC IS. RUN TEST.CL.JCLLIB(COMPEXHB) RUN TEST.CL.JCLLIB(LINKEXHB) RESTART CL$$0420 JOB FROM TOP BY OVERRIDE NEW LOADLIB FROM OVERRIDE LIBRARY. AS A PERMANENT SOLUTION: ASK USER TO CORRECT THE PURGE DATE(FNPPGDAT-PURGE-DATE) IN 72 SEGMENT. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0826",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB WAS LOOPING (NO SIO) ",
  "ANALYSIS": "HAD OPS KILL JOB WITH A DUMP. LOOKED IN IDIREPRT AND DID A FIND ON CURRENT. WENT TO CURRENT RECORD AND FOUND POLICY 3465123730. IN IDIREPRT IT SHOWED THAT IT WAS LOOPING WHILE GOING THROUGH THE 69 SEGMENTS. THIS POLICY HAS AN ENORMOUS AMOUNT OF 69 SEGMENTS. PROBABLY A PROBLEM WITH A COUNTER. ",
  "SOLUTION": "MADE A COPY OF THE SA POLICY FILE. USED FIRECALL AND DELETED THE 3465123730 RECORD. HAD OPS PUT IN AN OVERRIDE TO POINT TO THE SA FILES THROUGHOUT THE JOB. JOB FINISHED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0650",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C4 - +IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V8R1M0 (UK30777 2007\/10\/31) INVOKED BY ID +IDI0082E DB2 DB2P CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQLALLOCCONNECT SQL SQLRC=-1 {DB2 FOR OS\/390}{ODBC DRIVER} SQLSTATE=58004 ERRLOC=2:170:10 CAF \"OPEN\" FAILED USING DB2 SYSTEM:DB2P AND PLAN:DSNACLI RC=0C AND REASON=00F30040 +IDI0002I MODULE D724CNSL, CSECT CKETRGET, OFFSET X'45A': ABEND S0 +IDI0003I FAULT ID F07395 ASSIGNED IN HISTORY FILE SYS2.FA.HIST.BA IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 322 USER COMPLETION CODE=4039 REASON CODE=00000000 TIME=07.15.17 SEQ=09310 CPU=0000 ASID=0042 PSW AT TIME OF ERROR 078D1400 84875AEE ILC 2 INTC 0D ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE ''OFFSET X'45A'' TELLS US THERE WAS A CLIENT ERROR ",
  "SOLUTION": "PER INSTRUCTIONS IN DOC LIBRARY, I DID THE FOLLOWING: DO NOT RESTART THIS JOB IF ABEND AFTER 9:00AM. HAVE PCD GET RID OF THE CDFT AND FORCE JOB COMPLETE. ADD OVERRIDE TO JCL TO BRING IN 2 FILES AS INPUT INTO CL$$0650 STEP0070 FOR THE NEXT NIGHTLY CYCLE. \/\/STEP0070.SORTIN DD DSN=CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT(+0) \/\/ DD DSN=CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT(-1), \/\/ DISP=SHR \/\/* "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$IIAM",
  "PROBLEM": "CC8 SPACE PROBLEMS ",
  "ANALYSIS": "OPS CALLED ME ABOUT THIS, THEN CALLED BACK TO SAY PER THE DOC, THE DASD PEOPLE ARE IN CONTROL OF THIS. SO I WAS OFF THE HOOK...UNTIL 2:30 AM WHEN LAVONNA CALLED TO SAY SHE COULD NOT GET IT TO WORK AND NEEDED TO KNOW WHAT I WANTED HER TO DO. I REFERRED HER TO MANAGER ON CALL WHO INSTRUCTED HER TO: ",
  "SOLUTION": "USE THE SA VERSION TO RECREATE THE AUSEGH FILE, THEN RUN A REPRO TO BACK IT UP (HAD TO DO TO TAPE), THEN DELETE REDEFINE, USING THEIR CONTROL CARDS AND REPRO-ING BACK IN. THIS IS THE OLD FASHION WAY OF REORGANIZING A FILE. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "S0C4 ABEND A USER ABEND 0001 OCCURRED IN MODULE D724DTCC CSECT CKABEND AT OFFSET X'116'. THE ABEND WAS CAUSED BY MACHINE INSTRUCTION 0DEF (BRANCH AND SAVE) IN MODULE D724DTCC CSECT CKETRINV AT OFFSET X'B70'. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "12-03@03:43:54 MTAAPPLX: RETURN FROM D724DTCC RC:+0 RSN:+0 CMPL=( 12-03@03:43:54 MTAAPPLX: CALLING APPLICATION D724DTCC WITH MESSAGE POLICY NUMBER: 2453216390 POLICY NUMBER: 2453229080 POLICY NUMBER: 2453369330 12-03@05:39:01 MTAAPPLX: RETURN FROM D724DTCC RC:+0 RSN:+0 CMPL=( 12-03@05:39:01 MTAAPPLX: CALLING APPLICATION D724DTCC WITH MESSAGE 12-03@06:35:10 MTAAPPLX: RETURN FROM D724DTCC RC:+0 RSN:+0 CMPL=( 12-03@06:35:10 MTAAPPLX: CALLING APPLICATION D724DTCC WITH MESSAGE 12-03@07:19:31 MTAAPPLX: RETURN FROM D724DTCC RC:+0 RSN:+0 CMPL=( 12-03@07:19:31 MTAAPPLX: CALLING APPLICATION D724DTCC WITH MESSAGE CEE3250C THE SYSTEM OR USER ABEND U 001 R=NULL WAS ISSUED. FROM COMPILE UNIT CKABEND AT ENTRY POINT CKABEND AT COMPI AT ADDRESS 0D470318. THIS JOB WAS RUNNING PRIOR TO THE PARMDATE CHANGE AGAINST REGULAR VSAM FILES. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAVE REX GREGORY (OR WHOEVER THE EMAIL CAME FROM) RERUN JOB FROM TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0837",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP0090 ENDED WITH A COND CODE = 008 REPRO - INFILE(SEQ7) - OUTFILE(VSAM7) 0IDC3302I ACTION ERROR ON CL.VSAM.DLS.RIDER 0IDC3314I **RECORD OUT OF SEQUENCE - KEY FOLLOWS: -000000 F0F0F0F7 F2F0F0F7 F2F7F2F0 D3D960F1 F9F44040 40F0F0F1 0IDC0005I NUMBER OF RECORDS PROCESSED WAS 106 0IDC0001I FUNCTION COMPLETED, HIGHEST CONDITION CODE WAS 8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "POLICY 0720072720 HAS 2 LR-194 RIDER RECORDS WITH THE PERSON-CD OF 001 ON BOTH RECORDS. SEE CL.DLS.RIDER.SORT.DUPOUT (COLS 22-23) CAUSING DUPLICATE RECORDS (KEY = COLS 1 - 23) PROBLEM WAS CAUSED BY THE CLERK ADDING THE 2 RIDERS NOTE: IF THE TWO RECORDS ARE NOT TRULY DUPLICATES OF EACH OTHER OR THE PERSON-CD ON BOTH RECORDS IS OTHER THAN 001, PLEASE FOLLOW THE BOMBLOG INSTRUCTIONS DESCRIBED IN ANOTHER BOMBLOG ENTRY FOR DUPLICATE RECORDS WITH PERSON-CD 998. YOU CAN SEARCH ON 'RECORD OUT OF SEQUENCE' TO FIND THE NEXT BOMBLOG ENTRY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "* FILE CL.DLS.RIDER.SORT.DUPOUT (INPUT CL$$0837) FILE CL.DLS.RIDER.G4199V00 (INPUT TO CL$$0838 - WL) FILE CL.DLS.RIDER.SORT.DUPOUTW (INPUT TO CL$$0838) 1. BACKUP THE ABOVE FILES 2. USING FIRECALL - DELETE THE 2ND LR-194 RECORD FOR THIS POLICY FROM ALL OF THE ABOVE PROD FILES 3. ASK OPS TO DELETE ANY OUTPUT FROM THE FIRST RUN OF CL$$0837 4. ASK OPS TO RESTART THE JOB FROM THE TOP 5. NOTIFY TRIAGE.IND OF THE ABOVE PROBLEM SO THEY CAN TELL THE BUSINESS AREA TO CORRECT THE POLICY ON CYBERLIFE "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0106",
  "PROBLEM": "S3E7 PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED IN SYSLST AND MAXED DOWN TO THE BOTTOM TO SEE WHAT BLOCK OF POLICIES THE JOB WAS ON WHEN IT WENT DOWN. IT WAS IN THE 20523 AREA. WENT INTO IDIREPRT AND DID A SEARCH ON 20523 AND FOUND THE POLICY THE JOB WENT DOWN ON... 2052313990. 12\/02\/2009 2:47AM DROPPED POLICY 2052334500 12\/02\/2009 3:24AM DROPPED POLICY 2052373270 ALSO FOUND THE POLICIES BY SEARCHING THE IDIREPRT FOR THE WORD 'CURRENT' OF THE INPUT FILE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "MADE A COPY OF CL.CL$$0106.STEP0085.FINDATA, USED FIRECALL AND DELETED THE RECORDS FOR 2052313990. HAD OPS RESTART JOB IN STEP0090. NOTE: THIS PROBLEM HAS NOT REOCCURRED, BUT IF IT STARTS HAPPENING AGAIN, WE WANT TO FIND A PERMANENT FIX. P1BLM 12\/10\/09. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1910",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP0010 PGM=DSNUTILB EXECUTED - COND CODE 0008 DSNU000I DSNUGUTC - OUTPUT START FOR UTILITY, UTILID = CL$$1910 DSNU1044I DSNUGTIS - PROCESSING SYSIN AS EBCDIC DSNU050I DSNUGUTC - COPY TABLESPACE CLS1.TCLS1 DSNUM ALL FULL YES SHRLEVEL REFERENCE DSNU407I DSNUBCKB - DATA SET ALREADY USED FOR PREVIOUS IMAGE IMAGE COPY DDNAME SYSCOPY DSNU408I DSNUBCKB - 'CL.ME.BASEB.CISBMAIN.G0108V00' EXISTS WITH VOLUME=(CATG) FILE SEQUENCE NUMBER=0 RBA=X'0977B17E4000' DATE=09\/10\/10 TIME=15:53:13 DSNU012I DSNUGBAC - UTILITY EXECUTION TERMINATED, HIGHEST RETURN CODE=8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS IS AN IMAGE COPY JOB THE FILE 'CL.ME.BASEB.CISBMAIN.G0108V00' ALREADY EXISTED BUT WITH BAD DATA. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD THE JOB RESTARTED FROM THE TOP & IT FINISHED OK AND CREATED THE NEXT GEN OF THIS FILE (G0109V00) NOTIFIED RHONDA, SANDI & WENDY - ASKING THEM TO VERIFY & DELETE THE G0108V00 GEN, IF NEED BE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0110",
  "PROBLEM": "PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) AT LOCATION 00AE72 IN ELEMENT CKCMCC00 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB WAS DYING ON FIRST TWO HEADER RECORDS. DIDN'T EVEN GET TO A POLICY RECORD. LOOKED AT INPUT AND DISCOVERED THAT THE RESTORE JOB FROM THE 0801 UPGRADE BACKOUT GOT A NOT CAT2. SO CL.BASEB.COMM.ACCT.EXT1 AND CL.BASEB.COMM.ACCT.EXT2 WERE NOT RESTORED AND STILL IN THE 0801 FORMAT. WE NEEDED TO BE IN THE 0401 FORMAT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RAN CL$$R110, RELOADED CL.BASEB.COMM.ACCT.EXT1 AND CL.BASEB.COMM.ACCT.EXT2 FROM BACKUPS. RESTARTED JOB FROM TOP. JOB ENDED OK. "
 },
 null,
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$8100",
  "PROBLEM": "+UNABLE TO RETRIEVE STUB POOL RECORD +IDI0002I MODULE ULTTGPOL, CSECT CKETRINV ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FILE CONFLICT ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD JOB RESTARTED IN JSTEP096, FINISHED OK. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "-STEP=CSET1 PGM=COMPUSET IEC161I 052(009,IDOCM15I)-084,IDOC0105,METINT STEP0120 IEC161I XICS.COMPUSET.IDOC.DCLIB,XICS.COMPUSET.IDOC.DCL IEC161I CATALOG.OEM IEC161I 052(009,IDOCM15I)-084,IDOC0105,METINT STEP0120 IEC161I XICS.COMPUSET.IDOC.DCLIB,XICS.COMPUSET.IDOC.DCL IEC161I CATALOG.OEM +FOR0341I STOP 8 -STEP=METINT PGM=XRXINT EXECUTED - COND CODE 0008 FT06F001 STEP0120 METINT GEN090183-W: VSAM OPEN ERROR ON VSRN02 VSAM STATUS IS 080000A8 H XRX002038-E: DUE TO OPEN ERRORS, MERGING AND SAVING IS TERMINATE LIBRARY: 3. XRX002039-E: DUE TO MERGE LIBRARY FILE ERRORS, ALL DOCUMENT SAVI TERMINATED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FIND FT06F001 STEP0120 METINT BY PUTTING A ? ON THE JOB IN THE OUTPUT QUE AND THEN DISPLAY WHAT'S IN THIS STEP TO FIND THE W (WARNING) & E (ERROR MESSAGES). ",
  "SOLUTION": "THE WARNING AND ERROR MESSAGES INDICATED THAT THE DLS MERGE LIBRARY WAS UNAVALIBLE AT THE TIME THAT THIS JOB NEEDED IT. SINCE THIS JOB DOES NOT ACTUALLY USE THE MERGE LIBRARY FOR THIS DOCUMENT, THEN THE JOB CAN BE FORCE COMPLETED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$R030",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$R030 WAS RUN INSTEAD OF CL$$RC30. CL$$R030 LOADS THE PENDING AND AUXSEG2 SB FILES. CL$$RC30 LOADS THE DATABASE AFTER CL$$0030. ****** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** WE WERE RESTARTING CL$$0103 AND REQUESTED CL$$0060 AND CL$$RC30. WE DID NOT DISCOVER THAT CL$$R030 WAS RUN UNTIL THE NEXT DAY WHEN JOBS THAT READ THE PENDING FILE WERE ABENDING. THE PURGED POLICIES ON THE PENDING FILE HAD BEEN RESTORED BY CL$$R030, BUT THE CLIENT ROWS WERE PURGED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ALL THE PENDING FILE INTERFACES CREATED BY CL$$0030 AND CL$$0040 WERE CORRECT FOR 8\/31\/09. WE WERE CONCERNED THAT DUPLICATE ACCOUNTING, CHECKS, REQUIREMENT FOLLOW UPS AND EMAILS AND APP & PAID (AGCY) RECORDS WOULD BE CREATED IN THE 9\/1\/09 CYCLE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CL$$0008 AND CL$$0033 - USED TO SI PENDING AND AUXSEG2 FILES TO COMPLETE THE 8\/31\/09 CYCLE. WE HELD THE 9\/1\/09 CYCLE AFTER CL$$0030 TO DELETE DUPLICATE RECORDS. THEN WE RELEASED CL$$0040 AND CHECKED FOR DUPLICATES. THEN RELEASED THE REST OF THE CYCLE. THE PENDING FILE PROCESSING IN CL$$0030 WAS DATE DRIVEN. THE ONLY FILE WITH DUPLICATES WAS CL.BILLEFT.EXTRACTS. WE DELETE THE DUPLICATES. THERE WAS POTENTIAL FOR DUPLICATES IN CL.REQMTCOR, BUT IT WAS TOO DIFFICULT TO IDENTIFY. THIS FILE IS USED FOR IN HOUSE LETTERS CREATED IN CL$$0130. WE DID NOT DELETE ANY RECORDS. CL$$0040 IS DRIVEN BY THE ACTIVITY FILE, SO NO DUPLICATES WERE CREATED ON 9\/1\/09. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0021",
  "PROBLEM": "+CKDCARTH DATE PARAMETER HAS INVALID FORMAT ",
  "ANALYSIS": "2 POLICIES HAVE INCORRECT DATES SOMEWHERE IN THE RECORD 5200174230 5200174240 ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G5909V00 TO TEST.CL.FCC.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G5909 STRIPPED OUT POLICIES 5200174230 AND 5200174240. RESTARTED IN STEP0030 POINTING TO MY FILE \/\/STEP0030.SEQUEN DD DSN=TEST.CL.FCC.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G59099 --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! NOTIFIED TRIAGE POLICIES WERE STRIPPED AND POLICY PAGES WILL BE LATE TODAY. POLICIES ARE CURRENTLY BEING RESEARCHED FOR DATES. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0021",
  "PROBLEM": "+UNHANDLED CONDITION DETECTED BY CKABHDLR +TOKEN = 00030023 59C9C7E9 00000001 +IGZ0035S THERE WAS AN UNSUCCESSFUL OPEN OR CLOSE OF FILE VULNAIC IN PRO +D724DIO AT RELATIVE LOCATION X'12F0'. NEITHER FILE STATUS NOR AN ERROR +DECLARATIVE WERE SPECIFIED. THE STATUS CODE WAS 96. +UNHANDLED CONDITION DETECTED BY CKABHDLR +TOKEN = 000300C6 59C3C5C5 00000000 +CEE0198S THE TERMINATION OF A THREAD WAS SIGNALED DUE TO AN UNHANDLED C +IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V8R1M0 (UK30777 2007\/10\/31) INVOKED BY IDIXDCAP +IDI0002I MODULE CKDPFSPS, PROGRAM D724DIO, OFFSET X'12F0': ABEND U4038 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FILE VULNAIC WAS REFERENCED IN THE PROGRAM BUT WAS NOT REFERENCED IN THE PROC. ",
  "SOLUTION": "FILE VULNAIC HAD BEEN ADDED TO PROC CL$$0020 BUT WAS NOT ADDED TO PROC CL$$0021. I ADDED VULNAIC TO PROC CL$$0021 USING A TEMPORARY OVERRIDE AND RESTARTED IN STEP0030. --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1910",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$1910 STEP0010 CL$$1910 STEPLIB - DATA SET NOT FOUND ",
  "ANALYSIS": "STEPLIB DD DSN=DB2.SDSNLOAD.&DB2SS DATASET: DB2.SDSNLOAD.DB2S DID NOT EXIST ",
  "SOLUTION": "ADDED OVERRIDE TO POINT TO DB2.SDSNLOAD (WHICH IS DB2P) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0019",
  "PROBLEM": "CC 12 +IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V8R1M0 (UK30777 2007\/10\/31) INVOKED BY IDIXDCAP +IDI0002I MODULE ULTTGPOL, CSECT CKETRINV, OFFSET X'1A2': ABEND S0C1 (OP +IDI0003I FAULT ID F04986 ASSIGNED IN HISTORY FILE SYS2.FA.HIST.BATCH IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 227 USER COMPLETION CODE=4039 REASON CODE=00000000 TIME=22.22.58 SEQ=04559 CPU=0000 ASID=0039 LOOKED IN JSTEP0010 SYSOUT AND IT MENTIONS CKETRINV AS THE PROGRAM THE JOB WENT DOWN IN. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED IN THE BOMBLOG AND EVERYWHERE I SAW CKETRINV IT MENTIONS IT BOMBED DUE TO A FILE CONFLICT AND TO RERUN THE JOB. ",
  "SOLUTION": "FROM THE DOC, HAD OPS RUN CL$$R017, CL$$0017 AGAIN AND THEN CL$$0019 FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0015",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED IN IDIREPRT AND SAW... DATA ITEM . . . . . . . . : BLW=0000+040 AT ADDRESS. . . . . . . : 0CF8D0F8 LENGTH. . . . . . . . . : X'1' DATA ITEM STORAGE . . . : 61 *\/* I THEN WENT INTO THE INPUT FILE CL.CL$$0015.REPS.SORTED(&GENOT) AND DID A SEARCH FOR \/ THOUGHOUT THE FILE TO SEE IF ANYTHING LOOKS SUSPICIOUS. FORTUNATELY I FOUND IN THE FIRST COLUMN WHERE THE AGENT NUMBER RESIDES RECORDS THAT HAD 06\/26\/2009. THIS OBVIOUSLY WAS INCORRECT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "BECAUSE THE JOB WAS FORCED OKAY AT NIGHT, THE NEXT MORNING I MADE A COPY OF THE CL.CL$$0015.REPS.SORTED(0) FILE AND DELETED THE INCORRECT RECORDS. SUBMITTED FORMS TO HAVE THE CORRECTED COPIED FILE CONCATENATED IN STEPS 0040, 0050, & 0060 WITH THE NORMAL CL.$$0015.REPS.SORTED(&GENOT) MAKING SURE THAT THE COPIED CORRECTED FILE IS FIRST IN THE CONCATENATION. THIS IS ALSO NECESSARY FOR JOBS CL$TACF AND CL$MACF AS THEY WENT DOWN ALSO. 07\/11\/2009 - SOLUTION: BECAUSE THE JOB DID NOT WORK THIS SECOND DAY, THE CL.CL$$0015.REPS.SORTED(0) FILE WAS COPIED AND THE BAD RECORDS WERE DELETED. SUBMITTED FORMS TO HAVE THE (NOW 3 DAYS OF TRANSACTIONS) CONCATENATED IN STEPS 0040, 0050, & 0060 WITH THE NORMAL CL.CL$$0015.REPS.SORTED($GENOT) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1HED",
  "PROBLEM": "IEF450I CL$$1HED STEP0050 CL$$1HED - ABEND=SB37 U0000 REASON=00000004 2 TIME=15.15.05 # IEF450I CL$$1HED STEP0050 CL$$1HED - ABEND=SB37 U0000 REASON=00000004 -STEP=STEP0050 PGM=XLEBMAIN ABENDED - COND CODE SB37 RC=0000 ELAP= 00: ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SPACE PROBLEM. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD TO OVERRIDE SPACE ALLOCATION AND RESTART IN STEP0040. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$8130",
  "PROBLEM": "+UNABLE TO RETRIEVE STUB POOL RECORD +- - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - +IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V8R1M0 (UK30777 2007\/10\/31) INVOKED BY IDIXDCAP +IDI0002I MODULE ULTTGPOL, CSECT CKETRINV, OFFSET X'B48': ABEND U0001 +IDI0003I FAULT ID F04650 ASSIGNED IN HISTORY FILE SYS2.FA.HIST.BATCH IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 938LICATE OF FAULT ID F04647 IN HISTORY FIL USER COMPLETION CODE=4039 REASON CODE=00000000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FILE CONTENTION ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTARTED FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$9109",
  "PROBLEM": "+IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V8R1M0 (UK30777 2007\/10\/31) INVOKED BY IDIXDCAP +IDI0082E DB2 DB2P CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQLALLOCCONNECT SQLERROR SQLRC=-1 {DB2 FOR OS\/390}{ODBC DRIVER} SQLSTATE=58004 ERRLOC=2:170:10 CAF \"OPEN\" FAILED USING DB2 SYSTEM:DB2P AND PLAN:DSNACLI RC=0C AND REASON=00F30040 +IDI0044I CURRENT FAULT IS A DUPLICATE OF FAULT ID F04647 IN HISTORY FIL COUNT IS 2F04647 ASSIGNED IN HISTORY FILE SYS2.FA.HIST.BATCH +IDI0053I FAULT HISTORY FILE ENTRY SUPPRESSED +IDI0002I MODULE ULTTGPOL, CSECT CKETRGET, OFFSET X'466': ABEND S0C1 (OP ***** 11\/30\/2009 - SINCE 0801 UPGRADE, THE OFFSET WILL BE X'45A' ***** - FIRST CHECK THE CL.CARDLIB(PARMDATE) TO MATCH THE INFORCE POLICY FILE OR ME FILE ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FILE CONTENTION ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTARTED FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$9201",
  "PROBLEM": "+IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V8R1M0 (UK30777 2007\/10\/31) INVOKED BY IDIXDCAP +IDI0082E DB2 DB2P CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQLALLOCCONNECT SQLERROR SQLRC=-1 {DB2 FOR OS\/390}{ODBC DRIVER} SQLSTATE=58004 ERRLOC=2:170:10 CAF \"OPEN\" FAILED USING DB2 SYSTEM:DB2P AND PLAN:DSNACLI RC=0C AND REASON=00F30040 +IDI0002I MODULE ULTTGPOL, CSECT CKETRGET, OFFSET X'466': ABEND S0C1 (OP +IDI0003I FAULT ID F04647 ASSIGNED IN HISTORY FILE SYS2.FA.HIST.BATCH ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FILE CONTENTION ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTARTED FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0021",
  "PROBLEM": "PROGRAM CHECK OCCURED..TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA). IN ELEMENT D724CARE ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ASSET CARE ANNUITY POLICY (099SLACN2) SET UP WITHOUT AUTOMATIC TRANSACTION SEGMENT (53) ON PENDING SIDE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DELETED POLICY 5820021510 FROM P0020 FILE & HAD PCD RESTART JOB FROM STEP0030....SEE CL$$0020 FOR MORE DETAILS OF THIS REOCCURING PROBLEM! --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0837",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP0090 ENDED WITH A COND CODE = 008 REPRO - INFILE(SEQ7) - OUTFILE(VSAM7) 0IDC3302I ACTION ERROR ON CL.VSAM.DLS.RIDER 0IDC3314I **RECORD OUT OF SEQUENCE - KEY FOLLOWS: -000000 F0F0F0F7 F2F0F0F4 F9F4F3F0 D3D960F1 F8F44040 40F9F9F8 0IDC0005I NUMBER OF RECORDS PROCESSED WAS 48 0IDC0001I FUNCTION COMPLETED, HIGHEST CONDITION CODE WAS 8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "POLICY 0720049430 HAS 2 LR-184 RIDER RECORDS WITH THE PERSON-CD OF 998 ON BOTH RECORDS. SEE CL.DLS.RIDER.SORT.DUPOUT (COLS 22-23) CAUSING DUPLICATE RECORDS (KEY = COLS 1 - 23) PROBLEM WAS CAUSE DURING ISSUE CL8509 (PUA CHANGES) ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. IN THE FILE CL.DLS.RIDER.SORT.DUPOUT (INPUT CL$$0837) 2. CHANGED THE 1ST LR-184 RIDER PERSON-CD TO 001 3. CHANGED THE 2ND LR-184 RIDER PERSON-CD TO 601 4. HAD THE JOB CL$$0837 RESTARTED FROM THE TOP 5. JOB COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY NOTE: PROGRAM PROBLEM IN D724DLIF IS BEING CORRECTED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$001A",
  "PROBLEM": "UNABLE TO RETRIEVE STUB POOL RECORD IEF450I CL$$001A STEP0010 CL$$001A - ABEND=S000 U0001 REASON=00000000 STEP=STEP0010 PGM=D724OLDF ABENDED - COND CODE S001 RC=0000 IDI0002I MODULE D724OLDF, CSECT CKETRINV, OFFSET X'B48': ABEND U0001 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "AN ABEND WITH REFERENCE TO CKETRINV INDICATES A LIKELY FILE CONFLICT; A NECESSARY FILE WAS PROBABLY IN USE BY ANOTHER PROGRAM AT THE TIME THE JOB RAN. ",
  "SOLUTION": "REQUESTED OPS RERUN JOB FROM THE TOP; JOB COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "PROBLEM: +UNABLE TO RETRIEVE STUB POOL RECORD +IDI0082E DB2 DB2P CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQLALLOCCONNECT SQLERROR SQLRC=-1 {DB2 FOR OS\/390}{ODBC DRIVER} SQLSTATE=58004 ERRLOC=2:170:10 CAF \"OPEN\" FAILED USING DB2 SYSTEM:DB2P AND PLAN:DSNACLI RC=0C AND REASON=00F30040 +IDI0002I MODULE D72434VP, CSECT CKETRINV, OFFSET X'B48': ABEND U0001 +IDI0003I FAULT ID F03351 ASSIGNED IN HISTORY FILE SYS2.FA.HIST.BATCH IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 577 IEF450I CL$$0011 STEP0010 JSTEP010 - ABEND=S04C U0000 REASON=00000000 STEP=STEP0010 PGM=IKJEFT1B ABENDED - COND CODE S04C RC=0000 FROM IDIREPRT: A USER ABEND 0001 OCCURRED IN MODULE D72434VP CSECT CKABEND AT OFFSET X'116'. (IF DB2 ERROR, SUCH AS BAD DATA, WOULD SEE X'466') - THE ABEND WAS CAUSED BY MACHINE INSTRUCTION 0DEF (BRANCH AND SAVE) IN MODULE D72434VP CSECT CKETRINV AT OFFSET X'B48'. (PROGRAM CKETRINV IS INDICATION THAT THIS IS A CONFLICT RATHER THAN A DB2 ERROR.) ",
  "ANALYSIS": "POLICY 5200032270 WAS MOST LIKELY BEING WORKED ON BY ONE OF THE USERS AT THE TIME THE JOB WAS RUNNING. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RAN DIAGNOSTIC JOBS TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$I0011) INFORCE TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$P0011) PENDING THESE 2 PROGRAMS ARE ESSENTIALLY EXECUTIONS OF STEP0010 AND STEP0020 FROM JOB CL$$0011. IF NO ABENDS OR OTHER ERRORS ARE INDICATED BY EITHER OF THE 2 JOBS ABOVE, THEN CL$$0011 CAN BE FORCE COMPLETED OKAY. NO PROBLEMS WERE FOUND IN EITHER JOB! "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$IIAM",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB ENDED WITH A COND CODE = 0008 IEC030I B37-04,IFG0554A,CL$$IIAM,STEP0010,SYS00018, 04210010,CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN ",
  "ANALYSIS": "& ",
  "SOLUTION": "PER THE PROBLEM LOG - NOTIFY THE DASD ON-CALL PERSON NOTIFIED LAVONNA NICHOLS, PER THE ON-CALL LIST LAVONNA CALLED ME WITH THE OPERATOR AND PRIMARY ON-CALL PERSON CONFERENCED IN. BECAUSE OF THE SPACE PROBLEM THE AGTFIN FILE WAS DELETED, SO THE QUESTION WAS WHERE TO COPY THE FILE FROM SO WE COULD CONTINUE ON WITH CYCLE. LAVONNA SNAPPED THE SA VERSION OF THE AGTFIN FILE TO THE REGULAR VSAM FILE NAME AND FORCE COMPLETED CL$$IIAM. ALTHOUGH THE IIAM JOB CREATES A BACKUP OF THE FILE ITS TRYING TO REORG, SO THAT VERSION COULD HAVE BEEN USED. CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN.BACKUP THE NEXT DAY WE HAD TO SETUP A DELETE, REDEFINE AND REPRO OF THE FILE TO RUN AFTER CL$$0010 AND BEFORE IIAM RUNS AGAIN TO ALLOCATE MORE SPACE TO THE FILE AND GET US OUT OF EXTENTS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0103",
  "PROBLEM": "PROGRAM CHECK TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) AT LOCATION 002990 IN ELEMENT CKUBCMPD +CKUB03 CURRENT POLICY 2453468660 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE AGENT PHASE CODE IN THE 02 SEGMENT = 255 ",
  "SOLUTION": "NOTIFIED THE BAS. THEY ARE GOING TO REISSUE THE POLICY AND CORRECT THE AGENT. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1170",
  "PROBLEM": "FOUND BY A ? ON STEP0200 AND VIEWING FT06F001 STEP0210 METINT GEN090183-W: VSAM OPEN ERROR ON VSRN02 VSAM STATUS IS 080000A8 HEX XRX002038-E: DUE TO OPEN ERRORS, MERGING AND SAVING IS TERMINATED LIBRARY: 3. XRX002039-E: DUE TO MERGE LIBRARY FILE ERRORS, ALL DOCUMENT SAVING TERMINATED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE ABOVE MESSAGE REFERS TO THE DLS MERGE LIBRARY THIS LIBRARY WAS BEING USED BY ANOTHER JOB AT THE TIME THAT THIS JOB REQUESTED THE LIBRARY ",
  "SOLUTION": "SINCE THIS JOB DOES NOT NEED THE MERGE LIBRARY AT AT THIS TIME, THE JOB WAS FORCE COMPLETE "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0861",
  "PROBLEM": "IS THAT THE STATEMENT WILL NOT BE GENERATED. THEREFORE, IF A STATEMENT WITH THE FOLLOWING CRITERIA DID NOT GENERATE, THIS IS THE REASON. NO STATEMENT CRITERIA: POLICY IS STATUS 45 AND HAS DIVIDEND OPTION WL ANNUAL STATEMENTS ",
  "ANALYSIS": "STOP 8 - COND CODE 0008 THERE IS AN UNDEFINED COMMAND IN THE STYLE FILE, AND IS USUALLY IDENTIFIED BY THE *. THE COMPOSE OUTPUT WITH THE ERROR IS PASTED HERE. CMP000037-I: COMPOSITION ERROR LOG FOLLOWS . . . . . . CMP000038-E: LINE 312; CIRCA OUTPUT PAGE 1 IN TEXT STRING R606; CALLED AT CHAR 27 OF TEXT STRING R515 CALLED AT CHAR 37 OF TEXT STRING POLVALBE CALLED AT LINE 312 OF SECONDARY INPUT FILE CMP000050-E: ERROR 4 AT CHARACTER POSITION 23: UNDEFINED COMMAND NAME. R606 <DVBIRFAC>`OF ONE-YEAR TERM INSURANCE.<NL>!THE B * THE CMP000038-E MESSAGE INDICATES THE STYLE FILE CHAIN OF COMMANDS FOR THIS TAG, WITH THE MOST RECENT ON THE TOP LINE. IN THIS EXAMPLE, TAG POLVALBE EXECUTES TEXT STRING R515 WHICH EXECUTES TEXT STRING R606 WHICH CONTAINS THE MISSING DVBIRFAC TAG FIELD. THE TAG IS MISSING DUE TO THE POLICY STATUS OF RPU, WHICH TERMINATES THE POLICY RIDERS. THE DIVIDENDS STILL ATTEMPT TO PROCESS THE BIR DIV OPTION, WITH ERRORS. WMS IDEA SRQ00004509 HAS BEEN SUBMITTED TO ADDRESS THIS PROBLEM. DIVIDEND OPTION NEEDS TO BE CHANGED OR THIS WILL CONTINUE TO HAPPEN. ",
  "SOLUTION": "POLICY 0710067100 NOTE: (TO FIND THE OFFENDING POLICY, SEE FILE CL.CL$$0861.OTAGCUST(+0). SEARCH RECORDS WHICH HAVE A VALUE OF '17<#POLNBR=' IN COLUMNS 59 THRU 69. THE POLICY NUMBER WILL APPEAR IN COLUMNS 70 THRU 79.) THIS MAY BE ACCURATE ONLY IF POLICY HAS BEEN DIVERTED. POLICIES MAY BE DIVERTED FOR OTHER REASONS AS WELL. SOLUTION: IN THIS INSTANCE, CUSTOMER COPY DID PRINT BUT WITH THE DVBIRFAC IT PICKED UP FROM ANOTHER POLICY IN THE OTAGCUST FILE. AGENT COPY DID NOT PRINT DUE TO THE ERROR ABOVE. TYPICALLY, BOTH CUSTOMER AND AGENT COPIES WILL ERROR. FORCE JOB COMPLETE. NOTIFY TRIAGE AND INFORCE SVCS OF THE POLICY PROBLEM AND THAT NO STATEMENT WILL PRINT. NOTE: AT THE TIME OF 3\/13\/10 ERROR, THIS POLICY (0710067100) HAS A PULQS PURPOSE CODE ENTERED IN A NOTEPAD SEGMENT. THIS WAS LIKELY ENTERED DUE TO THE KNOWN PROBLEM WITH THE STATEMENT. THIS RESULTS IN THE STATEMENT BEING PLACED IN THE DIVERTED STACK OF OUTPUT FOR BOTH THE CUSTOMER COPY AND THE AGENT COPY. IN THIS INSTANCE, THE DVBIRFAC AMOUNT WAS BLANK ON THE STATEMENT. THE STATEMENTS DID PRINT, AND CUST COPY IS ON VISTA. NOTE: 3\/14\/11 ERROR - SAME POLICY AND SAME RESULT AS 3\/13\/10 NOTE: 6\/02\/11 ERROR - POLICY 0710013810. CUST COPY DID PRINT BUT WITH THE DVBIRFAC IT PICKED UP FROM ANOTHER POLICY IN THE OTAGCUST FILE. AGENT COPY DID NOT PRINT DUE TO THE ERROR ABOVE. FORCE JOB COMPLETE. NOTIFY TRIAGE AND INFORCE SVCS OF THE POLICY PROBLEM. NOTE: 8\/18\/11 ERROR - POLICY 0710024680. CUST COPY DID PRINT AND GO TO VISTA PLUS WITH BLANK DVBIRFAC AMOUNT. AGENT COPY SHOULD HAVE PRITNED WITH A WRONG DVBIRFAC AMOUNT. FORCE JOB COMPLETE. NOTIFY TRIAGE AND INFORCE SVCS OF THE POLICY PROBLEM. NOTE: 5\/15\/12 ERROR - POLICY 0710016750. CUST COPY DID PRINT AND GO TO VISTA PLUS WITH BLANK DVBIRFAC AMOUNT. AGENT COPY SHOULD HAVE PRITNED WITH A WRONG DVBIRFAC AMOUNT. FORCE JOB COMPLETE. NOTIFY TRIAGE AND INFORCE SVCS OF THE POLICY PROBLEM. NOTE: 6\/02\/12 ERROR - SAME POLICY NUMBER AS PREV YEAR 6\/02\/12 ERROR - POLICY 0710013810. CUST COPY DID PRINT AND ASSUME DVBIRFAC IS INCORRECT - PICKED UP FROM 02 ANOTHER POLICY IN THE OTAGCUST FILE - ASSUME SAME AS 02 LAST YEAR. FORCE JOB COMPLETE. NOTIFY TRIAGE AND INFORCE SVCS OF THE POLICY PROBLEM. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0836",
  "PROBLEM": "FOUND IN THE SYSPRINT DD: NO TEXT PIECES QUALIFIED DURING ASSEMBLY. TRIGGER: 1, PRODUCT: IVA 2007 POLICY PAGES, COMPANY-CD: 00, CONTRACT-NUM: 2453446640 TOTAL ERRORS: 1. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "1) LOOK IN PROD CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR(0) FILE FOR POLICY'S ISSUE STATE. (IN COLUMN 36) HERE IT IS 14 WHICH IS IL. OR CAN LOOK AT 01 SEG FOR ISSUE STATE. (FOR 04\/30\/2008 - THE STATE IS NJ) (FOR 12\/05\/2008 - THE STATE IS TN) (FOR 12\/10\/2008 - THE STATE IS FL) 2) LOOK AT 02 SEG FOR FORM #. IN THIS CASE IS IVA2007 (FOR 04\/30\/2008 - THE FORM # IS LA-31 AC) (FOR 12\/05\/2008 - THE FORM # IS SA34) (FOR 12\/10\/2008 - THE FORM # IS SA32) 3) LOOK AT CKAPTB65 TABLE IN PROD CICS FOR COMPANY CODE 00. YOU WILL SEE THAT IL HAS NOT BEEN APPROVED FOR THIS PRODUCT. TABLE= CKAPTB65 000 IVA2007 ID 11\/30\/2006 Y <-- ENTRY FOR IL WOULD BE HERE 000 IVA2007 IN 11\/30\/2006 Y - ",
  "SOLUTION": "1) FORCE JOB COMPLETE (OTHER POLICIES WOULD HAVE PRINTED) & 2) EMAIL TRIAGE THAT THE JOB ABENDED ON POLICY NUMBER 2453446640 FOR THE STATE OF IL WHICH HAS NOT BEEN APPROVED IN PRODUCTION YET (TRIAGE WILL EMAIL THE USERS WITH THE POLICY NUMBER AND REASON). ALSO CC: DENISE WILLIAMS AND DONALD NIETEN OF CSS (2\/16\/09) ONLY ON PRODUCTION RUNS "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0840",
  "PROBLEM": "01\/24\/2009 00.01.12 DI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V8R1M0 (UK30777 2007\/10\/31) INVOKED BY IDIXDCA DI0082E DB2 DB2P CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQLALLOCCONNECT SQLERROR QLRC=-1 {DB2 FOR OS\/390}{ODBC DRIVER} SQLSTATE=58004 RRLOC=2:170:10 CAF \"OPEN\" FAILED USING DB2 SYSTEM:DB2P AND LAN:DSNACLI RC=0C AND REASON=00F30040 DI0002I MODULE D7240021, PROGRAM D7240021, OFFSET X'36F8': ABEND S0C7 ASP375 CL$$0840 ESTIMATED LINES EXCEEDED DI0003I FAULT ID F02039 ASSIGNED IN HISTORY FILE SYS2.FA.HIST.BATCH A995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 403 USER COMPLETION CODE=4039 REASON CODE=00000000 IME=00.05.06 SEQ=10889 CPU=0000 ASID=0027 STEP0010 CL$$0840 - ABEND=S04C U0000 REASON=00000000 432 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOUND CURRENT INPUT RECORD THAT WAS ERRORING OUT WHICH WAS 3465037950 AND HAD 3 RECORDS DELETED FOR THIS POLICY ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD OPERATOR RESTART THIS JOB IN STEP0010 RESTARTED END OK "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0690",
  "PROBLEM": "THE M&E TRADE AND ACCOUNTING FILES WERE EMPTY DUE TO INCORRECT GDG USED FOR IPRICES FILE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DUE TO THE NON-PRICING CYCLE, CL.FUND.PRICES.SORTED(-1) SHOULD NOT HAVE BEEN USED FOR THE 'NEXT DAY' CYCLE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RAN PARALLEL JOB USING -2 GDG. SEE K:\\CYBERLIFE\\FILECALL\\BEFOREAFTER PRINTS\\FC7423... "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1160",
  "PROBLEM": "IEF450I CL$$1160 STEP0010 CL$$1160 - ABEND=S04C U0000 REASON=00000 TIME=02.50.36 # IEF450I CL$$1160 STEP0010 CL$$1160 - ABEND=S04C U0000 REASON=000 -STEP=STEP0010 PGM=IKJEFT1B ABENDED - COND CODE S04C RC=0000 ELA IEF404I CL$$1160 - ENDED - TIME=02.50.36 A SYSTEM ABEND 0CB OCCURRED IN MODULE M724TAIT PROGRAM CKULNLEC AT X'5B8'. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKING IN FAULT ANALYZER, I DETERMINED THE CURRENT RECORD WAS POLICY 0710065820. THIS POLICY IS ALREADY IN THE BOMBLOG, LISTED BECAUSE IT HAS BEEN BYPASSED PREVIOUSLY IN CL$$1111. ",
  "SOLUTION": "I SNAPPED CL.SA.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY TO A TEST DSN. I USED FILE MARVEL TO EDIT THE TEST DSN AND REMOVE THIS POLICY. I THEN HAD THE OPERATOR OVERRIDE THE JCL WITH MY TEST DSN AND RESTARTED FROM THE TOP. !!!!!IMPORTANT NOTE:!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! !!!! EMAIL BRET SMITH THE DATA SET THAT WAS CREATED TO OVERRIDE !!!! !!!! THE FIX!!! HE NEEDS IT EARLY TO RUN HIS PARALLEL JOB. !!!! !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0165",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB NOT SUBMITTED MESSAGE IN CONTROL D. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WENT TO PROD.SCHD.JCLLIB AND DID A JSCAN ON MEMBER. GOT MESSAGE: MEMBER NOT FOUND & SYNTAX ERROR %%INCLIB SCHD.CTM. AUTOEDIT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD OPS CONTACT PCD. THEY HAD INCORRECTLY SET UP THE DATE OVERRIDES IN SCHD.CTM.AUTOEDIT. PCD CORRECTED IT AND JOB FINISHED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0070",
  "PROBLEM": "IEC130I SYSPDUMP DD STATEMENT MISSING +UNABLE TO RETRIEVE STUB POOL RECORD +- - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - IEF450I CL$$0070 STEP0005 JSTEP010 - ABEND=S000 U0001 REASON=00000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PER SYSOUT FOR STEP0005, ** NO POLICY MASTER RECORD FOR POLICY: 1620326270 (SEC)** NO POLICY MASTER RECORD FOR POLICY: 3360079466 (SEC)** NO POLICY MASTER RECORD FOR POLICY: 3360158353 (BKG)** NO POLICY MASTER RECORD FOR POLICY: 3361296325 (JIF)** NO POLICY MASTER RECORD FOR POLICY: 3360101640 (JIF)** NO POLICY MASTER RECORD FOR POLICY: 0710069620 (PSS)** NO POLICY MASTER RECORD FOR POLICY: 3361080089 (BLM)** NO POLICY MASTER RECORD FOR POLICY: 3361197136 (FCC)** NO POLICY MASTER RECORD FOR POLICY: 3465109230 (BKG)** NO POLICY MASTER RECORD FOR POLICY: 3360230327 (WHH)** NO POLICY MASTER RECORD FOR POLICY: 3361049140 ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. COPIED FILE BANK.CL.PAYMENTS(0) TO MY OWN FILE 2. REMOVED RECORD FOR POLICY 1620326270 FROM BANK.CL.PAYMENTS(0) 3. HAD OPS RESTART THE JOB FROM THE TOP JOB COMPLETED OKAY. (SEC) JOB COMPLETED OKAY AFTER REMOVING 2ND BAD POLICY. BKG NOTE: I WAS UNABLE TO MODIFY BANK.CL.PAYMENTS USING FIRECALL. HAD TO MODIFY MY COPY OF FILE AND USE THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDE... \/\/STEP0004.SORTIN DD DSN=TEST.CL.BKG.BANK.PAYMENTS.D033109, \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) I SENT AN EMAIL TO TRIAGE (TRIAGE IND\/AUL@AUL) TO ALERT THEM OF THE BAD DATA. WHH NOTE: REMOVED POLICY FROM COPY OF BANK.CL.PAYMENTS AND RERAN FROM STEP0004 WITH OVERRIDE POINTING TO COPY: "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0861",
  "PROBLEM": "STOP 8 - COND CODE 0008 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "POLICY 0710004060 ",
  "SOLUTION": "FORCED THE JOB COMPLETE AND NOTIFIED TRIAGE AND RESOLUTION TEAM. TRIAGE NOTIFIED THE BUISNESS AREA THAT THIS POLICY WOULD BE INCORRECT. HOLD UNTIL ISSUE IS RESOLVED. PROBLEM TURNED OUT TO BE MUCH LARGER. DAN H. OPENED AN 'IDEA' FOR THIS ISSUE TO BE WORKED. NOTIFIED TRIAGE AND RESOLUTION TEAM THAT IDEA HAS BEEN OPENED AND THEY SHOULD NOTIFY BUISNESS AREA. CLOSING ALTIRIS TICKET #202725 WITH EMAIL FROM DAN'S 'IDEA'. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0862",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C7 IN CKUBAV00 CALLED FROM D7240150 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "POLICY 5448922250 ",
  "SOLUTION": "I REMOVED THE POLICY FROM CL.CL$$0860.SLUL.SORTED THE SAVED FILE WITH THE POLICY IS: TEST.CL.CL$$0860.SLUL.SORTED.D121908.PRD JOB WAS RESTARTED FROM THE TOP AND COMPLETED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0840",
  "PROBLEM": "-STEP=CSET1 PGM=COMPUSET EXECUTED +FOR0341I STOP 8 -STEP=METINT PGM=XRXINT EXECUTED - COND CODE 0008 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DO A ? ON THE JOB AND VIEW THE STEP FT06F001 STEP0079 METINT PAGING DOWN YOU WILL SEE THE FOLLOWING STATEMENTS GEN090183-W: VSAM OPEN ERROR ON VSRN02 VSAM STATUS IS 080000A8 HEXA XRX002038-E: DUE TO OPEN ERRORS, MERGING AND SAVING IS TERMINATED F LIBRARY: 3. XRX002039-E: DUE TO MERGE LIBRARY FILE ERRORS, ALL DOCUMENT SAVING TERMINATED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "THIS MEANS THAT ANOTHER JOB HAS CONTROL OF THE MERGE LIBRARY AT THE SAME TIME THAT THIS JOB REQUESTED IT. FOR CONFIRMS, THIS LIBRARY IS NOT NEEDED SO THE JOB CAN BE FORCE COMPLETED. NOTE::::: NOT ALL DLS JOBS CAN BYPASS THE NEED FOR THE MERGE LIBRARY LIKE CONFIRMS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1110",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C4 DECIMAL-DIVIDE EXCEPTION IN CKULNLEC ",
  "ANALYSIS": "M724CSVL DISPLAYED: THE SYSTEM DETECTED A DECIMAL-DIVIDE EXCEPTION (SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=0CB). ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPY CL.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY OR CL.ME.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY (VERIFY FROM THE PROC WHICH TO USE) TO TEST.CL.WAM.VSAM.POLICY AND USED FILE MARVEL TO DELETE POLICY 0710065820. ADDED OVERRIDE: \/\/STEP0010.VSAM1 DD DSN=TEST.CL.WAM.VSAM.POLICY AND RERAN FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1940",
  "PROBLEM": "IN JESMSGLG JES2 +IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V8R1M0 (UK30777 2007\/10\/31) INVOKED BY IDIXDCAP +IDI0002I MODULE M7240CCR, PROGRAM CKULMPIF, OFFSET X'B98': ABEND U4038 +IDI0003I FAULT ID F01550 ASSIGNED IN HISTORY FILE SYS2.FA.HIST.BATCH IN SYSOUT CL$$1940 STEP0010 PARMDATE: 12-11-08 PARMTYPE: R PARMYRS: 10 CEE3703I IN HANC CONTROL BLOCK, THE EYE CATCHER IS DAMAGED. CEE3704I EXPECTED DATA AT 0013B000 : HANC. 0013AFE0: F090F092 F094F096 F098F09A F09CF09E F0A0F0A2 00000000 07000 0013B000: C8C1D5C3 0DB21000 0CFE9000 00000000 0013B001 0013B300 00002 CEE0802C HEAP STORAGE CONTROL INFORMATION WAS DAMAGED. FROM COMPILE UNIT CKULMPIF AT ENTRY POINT CKULMPIF AT COMPILE U AT ADDRESS 0007D570. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKS LIKE THE INTERNAL TABLE AGENT-TABLE HAS OCCURS SET TO 200, IN DUMP THAT TABLE APPEARS TO BE COMPLETELY FULL. COPIED PROGRAM M7240CCR TO DPAN NAMED M7240CCRTR. CHANGED OCCURS & COORESPONDING SUBSCRIPT FIELD TO 500, RAN IN UNIT TEST LAND, JOB COMPLETED OK. WHEN WE POPULATE THE TABLE WE ARE OVER FLOWING ON THIS AGENT SL AGENT SD908. AN IDEA WAS SUBMITTED IN WMS AND CL ISSUE 8707 WAS CREATED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "NEED TO FIX PROGRAM FOR THE COMPOSITE AGENT REPORT TO GENERATE FOR SL AGENT SD908 (OR ANY OTHER WITH MORE THAN 200 AGENTS). WILL NEED TO FORCE JOB COMPLETE FOR THIS ABEND FOR NOW. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) IN PROGRAM D724CARE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "POLICIES 5827502340 & 5827502350 ARE PROBLEMS. CL$$0020 STEP0030 READ IMPORTANT TIP BELOW FOR ALL TYPES ABENDS !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! !!!!!IMPORTANT TIP FOR FINDING THE ABENDING POLICY!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! GO INTO SYSPDUMP AND DO A FIND ON D7XX (WHERE XX IS THE COMPANY CODE OF ABENDING POLICY. SINCE D724CARE IS ONLY FOR ASSET CARE WE KNOW THE PROBLEM IS WITH COMPANY CODE 05. SO IN THIS CASE WOULD DO A FIND ON D705. CONTINUE TO DO A FIND AND REFIND UNTIL YOU GET TO AN ACTUAL REGISTER & THEM PAGE TO RIGHT...SHOULD SEE A POLICY NUMBER. EXAMPLE OF WHAT YOU SEE WHEN YOU PAGE RIGHT D705 F5F8F2F7 F5F0F2F3 F4F0F0F0 F0804040 ",
  "SOLUTION": "600...........P. 5827502340 NOTE: D724CARE = COMPANY CODE 05 (ASSET CARE) D724DLIFE = COMPANY CODE 00 (AUL WL) D724DVUL = COMPANY CODE 00 (VUL) COMPANY CODE 0A (PML UL) D724DANN = COMPANY CODE 00 (AUL ANNUITIES) COMPANY CODE 05 (RATEGUARD\/SL ANNUITIES) D724DSLT = COMPANY CODE 00 (AUL TERM) COMPANY CODE 05 (SL TERM) !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$RBR4",
  "PROBLEM": "IEF450I CL$$RBR4 STEP0010 CL$$RBR4 - ABEND=S000 U0888 STEP0010 PGM=FDRABR ABENDED - COND CODE S378 RC=0000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CONFLICT WITH ANOTHER JOB THAT WAS RUNNING ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAVE OPS RESTART FROM THE TOP CL$$RBR4 STEP0010 FDRABR 10\/07\/2017 09.38.19 P1WHH PROBLEM: IEF450I CL$$RBR4 STEP0010 CL$$RBR4 - ABEND=S000 U0888 STEP0010 PGM=FDRABR ABENDED - COND CODE S378 RC=0000 ANALYSIS: SAME ERROR CODE BUT THIS TIME IT WAS: FDR111** VOL=CLDSKB,DSN=CL.ME.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH HAS INSUFFICIENT SPACE ALLOCATED - 00150150 TRACKS NUMBER OF TRACKS NECESSARY=00150225 RESTORE ENDED WITH NO DATA SETS RESTORED VOL=CLDSKH SOLUTION: HAD TO PULL IN COG_NA_MAINFRAME_ZOS_STORAGE TO ALLOCATE MORE SPACE. RERAN FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "STEP=STEP0060 PGM=IDCAMS EXECUTED - COND CODE 0008 STEP=STEP0180 PGM=IDCAMS EXECUTED - COND CODE 0008 STEP=STEP0180 PGM=IDCAMS EXECUTED - COND CODE 0008 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE REPRO SHOWED A DUPLICATE RECORD ON THE INPUT FILE CL.BASEB.AP.COR.EXT1(-0) - FROM JOB CL$$0103.STEP0120 9\/24\/2012 - NOTING DUPLICATE POLICY 0710013360 ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. THE DUPLICATE RECORD WAS DROPPED BY THE SYSTEM (CODE 0008) FILE IDOC.IDOC0160.OAPLCUST(0) - IN STEP0060 FILE IDOC.IDOC0160.OAPLAGTE(0) - IN STEP0180 2. THE FIRST RECORD WAS PROCESSED BY DLS (SEE STEP0070 & 080 FOR THE CUSTOMER (SEE STEP0170 & 180 FOR THE AGENT 3. HAD THE OPERATOR FORCE COMPLETE THE JOB 4. ASKED TRIAGE.IND TO NOTIFY THE BUSINESS AREA OF THE DROPPED RECORD "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "+CKTBLSPC - TABLE ENTRY COUNT INCONSISTENT IN TABLE CKVUTDB2 +- - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PROGRAM NEEDS TO BE RELINKED FOR THE INCREASE SIZE TO THE UTABLES ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. RELINKED THE PROGRAM TO TEST.IDOC.PROD.LOADLIB 2. SUBMITTED FORM TO PCD TO MOVE LOADLIB TO PRODUCTION 3. SUBMITTED FORM TO PCD TO DELETE GDG CREATED IN ABOVE RUN AND TO RESTART THE JOB FROM THE TOP 4. RESTART ENDED SUCCESSFULLY "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1HED",
  "PROBLEM": "+CKTBLSPC - TABLE ENTRY COUNT INCONSISTENT IN TABLE CKVUTDB2 +- - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PROGRAM NEEDS TO BE RELINKED FOR THE INCREASE SIZE TO THE UTABLES HOWEVER, THE PRODUCTION JCL SHOWS THAT THIS JOB IS BEING EXECUTED FROM GAIL'S LIBRARY TEST.CL.GCO.LOADLIB.CL8555 ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. GAIL RELINKED THE PROGRAM TO HER LOADLIB 2. SUBMITTED FORM TO PCD TO RESTART THE JOB IN STEP0030 WITH AN OVER-RIDE FOR THE INPUT FILE (PER THE BOMBLOG) 3. RHONDA HAD THE ME FILES RELOADED AND RESUBMITTED THE JOB 4. JOB ENDED SUCCESSFULLY "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1960",
  "PROBLEM": "+CKTBLSPC - TABLE ENTRY COUNT INCONSISTENT IN TABLE CKVUTDB2 +- - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PROGRAM NEEDS TO BE RELINKED FOR THE INCREASE SIZE TO THE UTABLES ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. RELINKED THE PROGRAM TO TEST.CL.PROD.LOADLIB 2. SUBMITTED FORM TO PCD TO MOVE THE LOADLIB MEMBER 3. HAD JOB RESTARTED FROM THE TOP - ENDED SUCCESSFULLY "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1010",
  "PROBLEM": "IEF453I CL$$1010 - JOB FAILED - JCL ERROR - TIME=03.25.52 # IEF453I CL$$1010 - JOB FAILED - JCL ERROR - TIME=03.25.52 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "GDG NOT SETUP FOR THE FOLLOWING OUTPUT FILE CL.CL$$1010.ULTRAVAL.PML.GAAP ",
  "SOLUTION": "SUBMITTED FORM TO PCD TO CREATE THE ABOVE GDG (LIMIT 24) AFTER PCD CREATE THE DATASET, HAD JOB RESTARTED IN STEP0027 JOB COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "-ALL OF THESE JOBS ABENDED DUE TO THE ENLARGED UTABLES IN PRODUCTION & THE BATCH PROGRAMS ASSOCIATED WITH EACH OF THESE JOBS NEED TO BE RECOMPILED & RELINKED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE ABOVE WAS DETERMINED BECAUSE EACH OF THE JOBS HAD A SIMILAR MESSAGE TO THE FOLLOWING CKTBLSPC - TABLE ENTRY COUNT INCONSISTENT IN TABLE CKVUTDB2TDB2 - - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - - - IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V8R1M0 (UK30777 2007\/10\/31) INVOKED BY IDIXDCAP ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. RECOMPILED & RELINKED PROGRAMS D8240020, D8240070, D8240380, & D8240390 2. HAD THE OBJLIB & LOADLIB FOR THESE PRGMS MOVED TO PROD 3. HAD THE JOBS RESTARTED FROM THE TOP (ALL ENDED OK) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0660",
  "PROBLEM": "+IDI0082E DB2 DB2P CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQLALLOCCONNECT SQLERROR SQLRC=-1 {DB2 FOR OS\/390}{ODBC DRIVER} SQLSTATE=58004 ERRLOC=2:170:10 CAF \"OPEN\" FAILED USING DB2 SYSTEM:DB2P AND PLAN:DSNACLI RC=0C AND REASON=00F30040 +IDI0044I CURRENT FAULT IS A DUPLICATE OF FAULT ID F01302 IN HISTORY FIL COUNT IS 2 +IDI0053I FAULT HISTORY FILE ENTRY SUPPRESSED +IDI0002I MODULE D724BLTI, CSECT CKETRGET, OFFSET X'466': ABEND S0C1 (OP ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CLIENT WAS UPDATED ON POLICY 2052346300 BEFORE THIS JOB RAN. ",
  "SOLUTION": "THIS JOB CURRENTLY RUNS AGAINST THE SA FILES. WAIT UNTIL THE PARMDATE HAS CHANGED, ADD THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDES AND RERUN FROM THE TOP. \/\/CL$$0660 EXEC PROC=CL$$0660, \/\/ VOPREFX='CL.VSAM.BASEOL.', \/\/ TBL='CL.VSAM.BASEOL.' SOLUTION: FOR THE FRIDAY 10\/30\/09 ABEND, I RERAN ON SATURDAY. PEOPLE WERE WORKING THAT DAY AND UPDATING CLIENT. I FOLLOWED THE INSTRUCTIONS ABOVE. BUT THE PARMDATE DOES NOT UPDATE ON SAT. I ADDED THESE OVERRIDES. REPLACE \/\/STEP0020.SYSIPT DD * %%CLDTE %%CLDAT7 WITH \/\/STEP0020.PARMDATE DD DSN=TEST.CL.RSW.SHKDWN.R0401(PARMDATE), \/\/ DISP=SHR \/\/STEP0020.SYSIPT DD * 10302009 10312009 REPLACE \/\/STEP0030.SYSIPT DD * %%CLDTE %%CLDAT7 WITH \/\/STEP0030.PARMDATE DD DSN=TEST.CL.RSW.SHKDWN.R0401(PARMDATE), \/\/ DISP=SHR \/\/STEP0030.SYSIPT DD * 10302009 10312009 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0020",
  "PROBLEM": "ANY PROBLEM REQUIRING A JOB RESTART ",
  "ANALYSIS": "IMPORTANT DATA WILL BE WIPED OUT IF RESTARTED FROM TOP ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTART THE JOB AT STEP0030 - FOLLOW DIRECTIONS IN JOB *** NEVER RESTART JOB FROM THE TOP! *** --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "STATE LIFE RECORDS GOT REJECTED DURING THE BATCH COMP CYCLE. THEY HAD THE SAME PROBLEM - THE ANNIV_DT IS NOT VALID (1900-00-00). THE DATE NEEDS TO BE CORRECTED AND THESE RECORDS RETRANSMITTED TO COMP. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS POLICY IS AN IMMEDIATE CARE - THE COMMISSION IS ADVANCED ON THE PENDING SIDE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "REVIEW CL.CL$$0103.STEP0030.COMPADV TO DETERMINE THE POLICY CAUSING THE PROBLEM - 1900-00-00 IN COL 156. DO A 60D1 ON THE POLICY IN PRODUCTION TO FIND THE ANNIVERSARY DATE. CREATE A COPY OF THE PROD GDG WHICH CONTAINS ONLY THE INVALID RECORDS AND CHANGE THE ANNIVERSARY DATE INDICATED ON PROD. EMAIL THE DSN OF THE CORRECTED FILE BACK TO COMP. CL.COMP.COMMSN.G0019V00 "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "LAST NIGHT WE HAD THREE STATE LIFE RECORDS GET REJECTED DURING OUR BATCH COMP CYCLE. ALL THREE RECORDS ARE FOR PRODUCER SHY39. ALL THREE HAVE THE SAME PROBLEM, THE ANNIV_DT IS NOT VALID (1900-00-00). THE DATE NEEDS TO BE CORRECTED AND THESE RECORDS RETRANSMITTED TO COMP. THIS AGENT WOULD HAVE GOTTEN ABOUT $5,000 IN COMMISSIONS IF THE RECORD HAD RUN INTO COMP, SO SOMEONE MAY BE LOOKING FOR THEIR MONEY. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS POLICY IS AN IMMEDIATE CARE - THE COMMISSION IS ADVANCED ON THE PENDING SIDE. D724ICMP BUILDS THE ANNIVERSARY DATE USING FBRLSTDF-LAST-ANN-DATE-FIELDS. THE POLICY IS NOT YET INFORCE THEREFORE THIS DATE IS INVALID. THE PROGRAM SHOULD USE FCVISSDF-ISSUE-DATE-FIELDS TO BUILD THE COMP-POL-ANNIV-DT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "UNTIL THE PROGRAM IS UPDATED AND INSTALLED INTO PROD, REVIEW CL.CL$$0103.STEP0030.COMPADV TO DETERMINE THE POLICY CAUSING THE PROBLEM - 1900-00-00 IN COL 156. DO A 60D1 ON THE POLICY IN PRODUCTION TO FIND THE ANNIVERSARY DATE. CREATE A COPY OF THE PROD GDG WHICH CONTAINS ONLY THE INVALID RECORDS AND CHANGE THE ANNIVERSARY DATE INDICATED ON PROD. EMAIL THE DSN OF THE CORRECTED FILE BACK TO COMP. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "-ALL OF THESE JOBS ABENDED DUE TO INVALID CARDLIB MEMBERS IN PRODUCTION BEING OVERLAID WITH MODL MEMBERS ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THERE WAS AN ERROR IN THE 10\/1\/2008 RELEASE. THE CHANGES WERE BACKED OUT AND THE WRONG CARDLIB LIBRARY WAS USED TO RESTORE THE PRODUCTION FILR. ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. RELOAD THE PRODUCTION FROM THE CORRECT BACKUP & REAPPLIED THE CORRECT RELEASE MEMBERS 2. HAD THE JOBS RESTARTED FROM THE TOP (ALL ENDED OK) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$CLDD",
  "PROBLEM": "CLD1 OR CLU1 MAY PRODUCE THIS ERROR ON THE CONSOLE: **CLERR CLD1** ERROR ON FILE DURING SWAP **CLERR CLD2** ERROR ON FILE DURING SWAP **CLERR CLD3** ERROR ON FILE DURING SWAP **CLERR** CONTACT THE CYBERLIFE ON-CALL PERSON **CLERR CLU1** ERROR ON FILE DURING SWAP **CLERR CLU2** ERROR ON FILE DURING SWAP **CLERR CLU3** ERROR ON FILE DURING SWAP **CLERR** CONTACT THE CYBERLIFE ON-CALL PERSON *THESE MESSAGES WILL BE HIGHLIGHTED ON THE MASTER CONSOLE ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOK INTO THE CICSD LOG TO SEE WHY THE FILE FAILED DURING THE SWAP. *FOR DUMMIES: GO TO Q.H SCREEN; TYPE \"LOG\" DO A FIND ON CLERR. LOOK A COUPLE LINES ABOVE THAT. +DFHFC0952 CICSD DYNAMIC ALLOCATION OF NON-RLS FILE FFFFFFFF FAILED. RETURN CODE X'0004',X'0210' IN MODULE DFHFCFS. +DFHFC0955 CICSD ASSOCIATED DATA SET IS CICS.AUL.IAM.FFFFFFFF. +**CLERR** ERROR ON FILE DURING SWAP ",
  "SOLUTION": "IF YOU SEE CODE '0210', THE FILE WAS OPEN BY SOMEBODY ELSE OR JOB DEPENDENCIES HAVE BEEN ALTERED SUCH THAT ANOTHER CL JOB WAS RUNNING WHILE CL$$CLU1 OR CL$$CLD1 WAS RUNNING WHICH SHOULD NOT HAPPEN. 1. MAKE SURE THE OFFENDING FILE GETS CLOSED OR THE CL JOB THAT WAS RUNNING HAS ENDED. 2. FOR A CLERR THAT OCCURED FROM CLD1,2, OR 3 TRX, WHICH IS THE CL$$CLD1 JOB, RESUBMIT CL$$CLD1. FOR A CLERR THAT OCCURED FROM CLU1,2, OR 3 TRX, WHICH IS THE CL$$CLU1 JOB, RESUBMIT CL$$CLU1. IN EITHER CASE, YOU SHOULD GET THIS MESSAGE: 22.04.52 JOB00975 +**CLGOODP CLD1** COMPLETED 22.05.00 JOB00975 +**CLGOODP CLD2** COMPLETED 22.05.03 JOB00975 +**CLGOODP CLD3** SWAP SUCCESSFULLY COMPLETED 3. VERIFY THAT THE SWAP OCCURED PROPERLY FOR ALL FILES. BROWSE THE CICS LOG AND MAX TO THE BOTTOM THEN TYPE: F 'HAS BEEN ALLOCATED TO DATA SET' PREV ********* FOR CL$$CLD1 *********** THE FIRST HIT AND MOST OF THE PREVIOUS HITS SHOULD POINT TO 24X7 FILES. SAMPLE: CICSD NON-RLS FILE FVDDP04 HAS BEEN ALLOCATED TO DATA SET CL.S24X7.VSAM NOT ALL FILES ARE 24X7, BUT 95% ARE SO YOU WOULD WANT TO SEE CL.S24X7.... ALLOCATED TO MOST OF THE FILES. IF YOU DON'T SEE THIS, THE SWAP DID NOT OCCUR. ********* FOR CL$$CLU1 ************ THE FIRST HIT AND MOST OF THE PREVIOUS HITS SHOULD POINT TO REGULAR FILES. SAMPLE: CICSD NON-RLS FILE FVDDP04 HAS BEEN ALLOCATED TO DATA SET CL.VSAM.BASEOL YOU SHOULD NOT SEE CL.S24X7.... ALLOCATED TO THE FILES. IF YOU DON'T SEE REGULAR FILES ALLOCATED, THE SWAP DID NOT OCCUR. 4. NEXT DAY, ADJUST ANY JOB DEPENDENCIES IF NECESSARY. PROBLEM: DO A FIND ON CLERR. LOOK A COUPLE LINES ABOVE THAT. +DFHFC0952 CICSD DYNAMIC ALLOCATION OF NON-RLS FILE FFFFFFFFFFF FAILED. RETURN CODE X'0004',X'1708' IN MODULE DFHFCFS. +DFHFC0955 CICSD ASSOCIATED DATA SET IS CICS.AUL.XXX.FFFFFFFFF. +**CLERR** ERROR ON FILE DURING SWAP SOLUTION: IF YOU SEE CODE '1708', THE FILE IS NOT THERE OR HAD AN OPEN ERROR. PROBLEM: IF YOU DO A FIND ON CLERR AND THIS IS THE ONLY ERROR. **CLERR** ERROR ON FILE DURING SWAP SOLUTION: THEN THE DD NAME IS NOT DEFINED FOR THE FILE. RUNNING CL$$CLDD-SHOULD WARN YOU IF YOUR MISSING A DD IN CICS. YOU SHOULD NEVER GET THIS CONDITION. PROBLEM: YOU DO NOT FIND ANY HITS ON CLERR BUT GET THIS MESSAGE: IEE341I CICSD NOT ACTIVE ANALYSIS: THE CICS REGION WAS NOT UP TO ISSUE THE TRANSACTIONS JOBS THAT CAN GET THIS ERROR - CL$$CLD1 CL$$CLU1 SOLUTION: YOU NEED TO CALL OPERATIONS TO FIND OUT WHY CICSD IS NOT UP. PROBLEM: CL$$CLDD & CL$$CLUD JOBS GET AN ERROR. PGM=SRVCUTL EXECUTED - COND CODE 0016 RC=0000 SRVCUTL-000I: 000I: CICSD FILE REQUEST 4 (FVDACTV CLO DIS) REQUEST FAILED, RESP =016 000I: CICSD FILE REQUEST 5 (FVDAFAD CLO DIS) REQUEST FAILED, RESP =012 000I: CICSD FILE REQUEST 6 (FVDAGTD CLO DIS) WAS SUCCESSFUL, RESP =000 ANALYSIS: RESP =012 MEANS THE FILE IS NOT DEFINED TO CICS. RESP =016 MEANS THE FILE IS DEFINED AS A REMOTE FILE TO CICS. SOLUTION: DEPENDS ON THE ERROR. PROBLEM: CL$$NEWC JOB GETS GOOD CONDITION BUT RESP=027 JOB03201 -STEP=STEP0001 PGM=SRVCUTL EXECUTED - COND CODE 000 RC=0000 SRVCUTL- 006I: CICSD PROG REQUEST 1 (MARKPGM NEW ) REQUEST FAILED, RESP =027 ANALYSIS: RESP =027 MEANS THE PROGRAM IS NOT DEFINE TO CICS OR NEVER WAS LOADED INTO STORAGE. SOLUTION: NOTHING. THE FIRST TIME IT GETS LOADED WILL BE A NEWCOPY ALMOST ALL CYBERLIFE PROGRAMS ARE DEFINED TO CICS & NOT USING AUTOINSTALL, SO WE SHOULD NEVER GET INTO THIS TYPE OF ERROR. RESP CODE 027 STILL GETS A GOOD CONDITION CODE BECAUSE NOTHING IS IS WRONG IN AN AUTOSTALL CICS REGION. IT JUST MORE OF A WARNING. PROBLEM: IF CL$$CLDD OR CL$$CLUD GET ERROR 1313, ANALYSIS: WITH THIS MESSAGE, SRVCUTL-002E: THE LINK REQUEST HAS FAILED. RETURN CODES ARE: 00000088 00000203 SRVCUTL-004S: >>>> ABORTING FURTHER PROCESSING <<<< SOLUTION: THE CICS REGION IS DOWN OR IS CORRUPTED. IF THE REGION IS UP AND YOU GET THIS MESSAGE YOU NEED TO CALL THE CICS ONCALL PERSON TO ASSIST WITH THIS ERROR. PROBLEM: IF CL$$CLDD OR CL$$CLUD GET ERROR 1313, ANALYSIS: WITH THIS MESSAGE, SRVCUTL-000I: CICST FILE REQUEST 1 (EXACACHE CLO ENA) REQUEST FAILED, RESP =012 SRVCUTL-000I: CICST FILE REQUEST 1 (EZACACHE OPE ENA) REQUEST FAILED, RESP =017 SOMETHING IS WRONG WITH THE FILE. RESP =012 MEANS THE FILE IS NOT DEFINED TO CICS. RESP =016 MEANS THE FILE IS DEFINED AS A REMOTE FILE TO CICS. RESP =017 MEANS THE FILE COULD NOT BE OPENED. SOLUTION-FOR RESP 012, IF FILE IS NOT NEEDED, FORCE JOB OK. (THIS OCCURED WITH AUXSEGI WHEN THE 0801 UPGRADE WAS BACKED OUT) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0838",
  "PROBLEM": "-STEP0110 PGM=DLSBATCH EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "1. DISPLAY THE STEP (USING THE ? BY THE JOB_NAME) 2. YOU WILL SEE SOMETHING SIMILAR TO THE FOLLOWING: - CRITERIA CHECK ERROR. CUSTOMER FILE DVCUSTLIFE SEGMENT DVPOLSM REACHED END OF FILE OR HAS NOT BEEN READ. TRIGGER: 6, PRODUCT: AUL WHOLELIFE 2007 PAGES, COMPANY-CD: 00, CONTRACT-NUM: 0720031450 CURRENT RULE DESCRIPTION: STATE SPECIFIC REPLACEMENTS - TOTAL ERRORS: 1. 3. THE \"TRIGGER\" LINE ABOVE WILL GIVE YOU THE POLICY NUMBER. (IN THIS CASE - POLICY # = 0720031450) 4. THE PROBLEM WITH THIS POLICY WAS A COMPLEX CHANGE THAT NEW BUSINESS & TRIAGE HAD TO CORRECT ON CYBERLIFE ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. DELETE ALL RECORDS FOR THE ABOVE POLICY FROM THE FILES: CL.DLS.LIFECUST.SORT.DUPOUT CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR(0) CL.DLS.POLSUMM.SORT.DUPOUT CL.DLS.POLSUMM.CASHVAL.DUPOUT 2. HAVE THE OPERATOR PURGE ALL PRINTOUT FROM THE BAD RUN 3. HAVE THE JOB RESTARTED FROM THE TOP OR CALL YOUR FRIENDLY DLS DEVELOPER "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$IIAM",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB ENDED WITH A COND CODE = 0008 -STEP=STEP0010 PGM=FDRREORG EXECUTED - COND CODE 0008 IKJ56225I DATA SET CL.VSAM.BASEOL.HISTORY ALREADY IN USE, TRY LA IKJ56225I DATA SET IS ALLOCATED TO ANOTHER JOB OR USER FDRR32** BACKUP PROCESSING TERMINATED FDRR33** BACKUP FAILED - CODE=00008,DSN=CL.VSAM.BASEOL.HISTORY ",
  "ANALYSIS": "& ",
  "SOLUTION": "PER THE PROBLEM LOG - NOTIFY THE DASD ON-CALL PERSON NOTIFIED MARK WILLIAMS, PER THE ON-CALL LIST "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "2008 IF THE CYCLE HAS COMPLETED AND NEEDS TO BE RE-RUN FROM THE MIDDLE (AFTER CL$$0060), USE THE FOLLOWING. !!!!!!!!!!!UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES IS CL$$0010 TO BE RERUN!!!!!!!!!!!!!! DETERMINE WHAT JOBS NEED TO BE RE-RUN BASED ON THE CIRCUMSTANCES. !!!!!!!!!!!UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES IS CL$$0010 TO BE RERUN!!!!!!!!!!!!!! REVIEW THE ASSET CARE\/COMP\/OLD MUTUAL PRODUCTION RELEASE INSTALL DOC AT H:\\CYBRLIFE\\PRODUCTION_SUPPORT_TEAM\\RELEASE INSTALL 10-18-08\\ASSET CARE. DOC "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0127",
  "PROBLEM": "JCL ERROR: IEF212I CL$$0127 STEP0017 JSTEP010 SORTIN - DATA SET NOT FOUND # IEF453I CL$$0127 - JOB FAILED - JCL ERROR - TIME=00.12.51 # IEF272I CL$$0127 STEP0017 JSTEP010 - STEP WAS NOT EXECUTED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "AN OVER-RIDE FOR THE SORTIN DD HAD A TYPO IN IT \/\/STEP0017.SORTIN DD DSN= TEST.CL.RELEASED.ERRORS.SORTED � 00 THE ABOVE DD HAD A SPACE FOLLOWING THE DSN= ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD THE OPERATOR CORRECT THE DD AND RESTART THE JOB FROM THE TOP ... THE RESTART ENDED OK "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$SEGD",
  "PROBLEM": "JCL ERROR: IEFC627I INCORRECT USE OF AMPERSAND IN THE UNIT FIELD IEFC009I KEYWORD UNIT IS MUTUALLY EXCLUSIVE WITH KEYWORD UNIT ON THE DD STATEMENT ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE \"OUTPUT\" DD DEFINITION CONTAINED 2 ASSIGNMENTS FOR UNIT (ONE CONTAINED A SYMBOLIC): \/\/ UNIT=&DISK, \/\/ UNIT=SYSDA, ",
  "SOLUTION": "COMMENTED OUT THE LINE CONTAINING THE SYMBOLIC, &DISK: \/\/* UNIT=&DISK, \/\/ UNIT=SYSDA, REQUESTED OPS RESTART THE JOB FROM THE TOP; JOB RAN\/COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0001",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$0001 HAD A CONDITION CODE 12 LAST NIGHT WITH THIS MESSAGE: VERIFY FILE(VSAM12) IDC3302I ACTION ERROR ON CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN IDC3351I ** VSAM I\/O RETURN CODE IS 116 - RPLFDBWD = X'00080074' IDC3003I FUNCTION TERMINATED. CONDITION CODE IS 12 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "3.4 SHOWED THAT THE FILE EXISTED ON STOR13 AND DATA COULD BE VIEWED. WHOHAS SHOWED NO CONFLICTS. FILE MARVEL SHOWED THE FILE TO BE EMPTY. IF THE VOLUME STOR13 WAS ENTERED HOWEVER, THE CONTENTS COULD BE BROWSED SANDI TRACKED THE PROBLEM TO MONDAY NIGHT'S RUNNING OF CL$$IIAM WHICH HAD THIS PROBLEM: IEC030I B37-04,IFG0554A,CL$$IIAM,STEP0010,SYS00018,226D,STOR13,04210010, CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=B37 REASON CODE=00000004 TIME=00.50.28 SEQ=04262 CPU=0000 ASID=0081 PSW AT TIME OF ERROR 075C1000 80DB8CB6 ILC 2 INTC 0D IEA848I NO DUMP WAS PRODUCED FOR THIS ABEND, DUE TO SYSTEM OR INSTALLATI IAMW39 DD=SYS00018 11665691 RECORDS ACCEPTED PRIOR TO ABEND IGD104I CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN RETAINED, DDNAME=S IEF285I CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN.BACKUP CATALOGED IEF285I VOL SER NOS= STOR58. ",
  "SOLUTION": "LAVONNA NICHOLS SAW A NUMBER OF PROBLEMS WITH THE AGENT FINANCIAL FILE INCLUDING THE FACT THAT IT WAS SMALLER\/TRUNCATED THAN THE ORIGINAL. THE RESTORE PROCEDURE FOR JOB CL$$IIAM IS TO RUN JOB FDRREORG TO RESTORE THE FILE THAT FAILED TO REORG. THIS WAS NOT DONE MONDAY NIGHT. RHONDA NOTED THAT THE FILE IS NOT UPDATED IN THE ONLINE ENVIRONMENT. THEREFORE THE FILE THAT WE WANTED WAS THE FILE AT THE END OF THE PREVIOUS NIGHT'S CYCLE THAT WAS CORRUPTED IN THE REORG PROCESS. LAVONNA RAN FDRREORG TO RESTORE THE FILE FROM THE END OF THE PREVIOUS NIGHT'S CYCLE. THIS WORKED AND THE CYCLE WAS RESUMED AT 1:45. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1180",
  "PROBLEM": "BOTH STEPS ENDED WITH A COND CODE 0016 BUT ALL STEPS IN THE JOB COMPLETED ",
  "ANALYSIS": "& ",
  "SOLUTION": "CC0016 USUALLY MEANS A FIELD OVERFLOWED IT'S LENGTH. ULTIM PRINTS ASTERISKS IN THE FIELD WITH THE OVERFLOW. IF THIS IS WHAT HAPPENED, FORCE THE JOB OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0700",
  "PROBLEM": "THIS STEP ENDED WITH A COND CODE 0008 IDCAMS SYSTEM SERVICES VFY FILE(OUTPUT) IDC0001I FUNCTION COMPLETED, HIGHEST CONDITION CODE WAS 0 REPRO INFILE(INPUT) - OUTFILE(OUTPUT) REUSE IDC3302I ACTION ERROR ON CL.VSAM.BASEOL.FND1 IDC3314I **RECORD OUT OF SEQUENCE - KEY FOLLOWS: 000000 F2F0F0F8 60F0F860 F0F5F2F2 F3F0F5F8 E3E5C2D4 C3C7 IDC0005I NUMBER OF RECORDS PROCESSED WAS 26993 IDC0001I FUNCTION COMPLETED, HIGHEST CONDITION CODE WAS 8 IDC0002I IDCAMS PROCESSING COMPLETE. MAXIMUM CONDITION CODE WAS ",
  "ANALYSIS": "& ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. REVIEWED FILE CL.ADJUST.OUTPUT (OUTPUT OF SORT FROM STEP0026 & FOUND THE FOLLOWING DUP RECORDS 2008-08-05223058TVBMCG*0000B0000000012737 2008-08-05223058TVBMCG*0000S0000000033724 2. THE SECOND RECORD ABOVE WAS DROPPED BY THE JOB 3. HAD THE JOB FORCE COMPLETED 4. SENT AN ALERT EMAIL TO TRIAGE.IND AND M.AUL.CORPFIN.SEPACCTSOMNI (SEPARATE ACCOUNTING) LETTING THEM KNOW THE FUND THAT WAS DROPPED "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0700",
  "PROBLEM": "DUPLICATE RECORD ON CL.VSAM.BASEOL.FND1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "& ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. HAD THE JOB FORCE COMPLETED 2. SENT AN ALERT EMAIL TO TRIAGE.IND AND M.AUL.CORPFIN.SEPACCTSOMNI (SEPARATE ACCOUNTING) LETTING THEM KNOW THE FUND THAT WAS DROPPED "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0836,",
  "PROBLEM": "FOLLOWING FOUND IN THE JCL LISTING -STEP=CSET1 PGM=COMPUSET EXECUTED - COND CODE 0000 +FOR0341I STOP 8 -STEP=METINT2 PGM=XRXINT EXECUTED - COND CODE 0008 +FOR0341I STOP 8 DOING A ? WITHIN THE JOB AND VIEWING THE FOLLOWING DD 07\/24\/08 FT06F001 STEP0130 METINT 08\/22\/08 FT06F001 STEP0110 METINT THEN PAGE DOWN IN THIS DD TO SEE THE FOLLOWING ERROR MESSAGE XRX090030-W: THE MERGE LIBRARY: 3 WAS NOT PROPERLY CLOSED AFTER THE LAST UPDATE. (STATUS: 0). THE LAST DOCUMENT SAVE OR DELETION MAY NOT HAVE BEEN COMPLETED CORRECTLY, WHICH MAY CAUSE ERRORS WHILE ACCESSING THE MERGE LIBRARY IN THIS RUN. TO REMOVE THE ERRORS, IT MAY BE NECESSARY TO DELETE THE FAULTY DOCUMENT(S) OR TO USE DOCUTL TO COMPRESS THIS MERGE LIBRARY. PROCEDD WITH CAUTION. (THE JOB STOPPED ALTOGETHER ON THE STEP WITH THE ERROR.) ",
  "ANALYSIS": "& ",
  "SOLUTION": "UPDATED: 1. YOU GET SOMEONE ON LAVONNA NICHOLS TEAM TO 07\/2\/09 COMPRESS OR RE-ORG THE MERGE LIBRARY --->> YOU NEED TO FILL OUT AN ALTIRIS TICKET & ASSIGN TO --->> 'IS HOST PLATFORM'! (THEY NEED TO BE ABLE TO TRACK THEIR --->> TIME TO THIS PROBLEM). DSN=XICS.COMPUSET.DCLIB3 *** OR *** DSN=XICS.COMPUSET.DCLIB4 TO IDENTIFY WHICH DCLIB#, CHECK THE JESJCL FOR THE ABENDING STEP - LOOK AT THE COMPUSET PROC THAT IMMEDIATELY FOLLOWS THAT DLSBATCH STEP, AND CHECK THE FILE NAME USED IN THE METINT STEP FOR DD VSRN02. THIS FILE NAME MAY ALSO BE FOUND IN THE JESMSGLG RIGHT ABOVE THE METINT STEP THAT IS IN ERROR. 2. HAVE THE OPERATOR PURGE THE BAD RUN - DON'T FORGET TO - HAVE THE OPERTOR PURGE THE PRINTOUT - HAVE THE VISTAPLUS OUTPUT PURGED ALSO (DON EVANS OR WHOEVER THE VISTA PLUS SUPPORT IS). 3. HAVE THE JOB RERUN FROM THE TOP "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$Q867",
  "PROBLEM": "COND CODE 0012 IN STEP0180 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SEE STEP0180 SYSPRINT IN Q.ST 'CONFLICTING DCB PARAMETERS' INPUT FILE CL.CL$$0867.IVA.OTAGTHIS(+1): LRECL=13605 OUTPUT FILE CL.QE.CL$$0867.IVA.OTAGTHIS(+1):LRECL=13654 ",
  "SOLUTION": "EMAILED PCD TO... (A)DELETE THE (EMPTY) OUTPUT FILE (B)INSERT THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDE INTO CL$$Q867 JCL: ------------------------- \/\/STEP0180.SYSUT2 DD DSN=CL.QE.CL$$0867.IVA.OTAGTHIS(+1), \/\/ DISP=(NEW,CATLG,DELETE), TO BKUP \/\/ UNIT=SYSDA, \/\/ SPACE=(CYL,(1200,120),RLSE), \/\/ DCB=(MODELDCB,RECFM=VB,LRECL=13605,BLKSIZE=27998) ------------------------- ...AFTER STATEMENTS... ------------------------- \/\/STEP0010.IINPUT01 DD DSN=TEST.CL.JIF.CL$$0860.IVA.SORTED.D063008 \/\/STEP0010.PARMDATE DD DSN=TEST.CL.JIF.CARDLIB(PARMDATQ) \/\/STEP0010.IPREVPRM DD * 06-27-08 \/* ------------------------- (C)RESTART JOB FROM STEP0180 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$2400",
  "PROBLEM": "COND CODE 0012 IN STEP0020 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SEE STEP0020 SYSPRINT IN Q.ST 'CONFLICTING DCB PARAMETERS' INPUT FILE CL.CL$$0866.VUL.OTAGTHIS(-0): LRECL=13605 OUTPUT FILE CL.QE.CL$$0866.VUL.OTAGTHIS(+1):LRECL=13601 ",
  "SOLUTION": "EMAIL PCD TO... (A)DELETE THE (EMPTY) OUTPUT FILE (B)INSERT THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDE INTO CL$$2400 JCL: ------------------------- \/\/STEP0020.SYSUT2 DD DSN=CL.QE.CL$$0866.VUL.OTAGTHIS(+1), TO BKUP \/\/ DISP=(NEW,CATLG,DELETE), \/\/ UNIT=SYSDA, \/\/ SPACE=(CYL,(800,100),RLSE), \/\/ DCB=(MODELDCB,RECFM=VB,LRECL=13605,BLKSIZE=27998) ------------------------- ...AFTER STATEMENTS... ------------------------- \/\/CL$$2400 EXEC PROC=CL$$2400 \/\/STEP0010.SYSUT1 DD DSN=TEST.CL.JIF.CL$$0860.SAPPH.D063008 ------------------------- (C)RESTART JOB FROM STEP0020 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0840",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND=S322 - THIS MEANS THE JOB TIMED OUT ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ONLY GDG CREATED WAS INPUT INTO ABENDING STEP. NEED TO ADD TIME PARAMATER AND RESTART IN ABENDING STEP. ",
  "SOLUTION": "SENT E-MAIL TO PCD, TO DO THE FOLLOWING: WE SHOULD BE ABLE TO RESTART IN THE ABENDING STEP WITH A TIME OVER SO WANT TO CHANGE EXISTING JOB CARD (IS ALREADY IN PROD.OPER.JCLLI FROM: \/\/CL$$0840 JOB (P,SPLT),'CONFIRMS',CLASS=P,TYPRUN=HOLD, \/\/ GROUP=CONTROLD, \/\/ REGION=0M, \/\/ MSGCLASS=J TO BE: \/\/CL$$0840 JOB (P,SPLT),'CONFIRMS',CLASS=P,TYPRUN=HOLD, \/\/ GROUP=CONTROLD,TIME=1440, \/\/ RESTART=CL$$0840.STEP0010, \/\/ REGION=0M, \/\/ MSGCLASS=J JOB UP AND RUNNING IT IS EXPECTED TO RUN 6 OR MORE HOURS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0836",
  "PROBLEM": "VSAM FILE ERROR -STEP=STEP0190 PGM=IEFBR14 EXECUTED - COND CODE 0000 RC=0000 +IAMW09 DD=DVINSRD OPEN ERROR - FILE DEFINED BUT NOT LOADED -STEP=STEP0200 PGM=DLSBATCH EXECUTED - COND CODE 0016 RC=0000 -STEP=CSET1 PGM=COMPUSET EXECUTED - COND CODE 0000 RC=0000 +FOR0341I STOP 12 -STEP=METINT PGM=XRXINT EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 RC=0000 +FOR0341I STOP 12 AND THE FOLLOWING MESSAGE FOUND IN STEP0200: - UNABLE TO OPEN DATABASE DVINSRD DUE TO A FILE OPEN ERROR. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "REVIEWED THE VSAM FILE (DVINSRD) CL.VSAM.DLS.INSURED THIS FILE SHOULD HAVE AT LEAST ONE RECORD (POLICY DATA OR AN ALL 9S RECORD) THE FILE IS EMPTY INPUT WAS THE CL.DLS.INSURED(0) FILE - THIS FILE HAD ONE RECORD WHICH THE JOB DID NOT PICK IT UP ",
  "SOLUTION": "WITH SUE'S HELP (FIRECALL), THE ONE RECORD (5820001370) WAS DELETED AND THE JOB RESTARED FROM THE TOP "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0910",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB LOOPING ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB NORMALLY TAKES SECONDS. OPS CALLED, CONCERNED IT MAY BE LOOPING. HAD JOB CANCELLED WITH A DUMP. ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED INPUT FILE TO TEST.CL.CL$$0910.MLIR.DT050208 AND DELETED POLICY 5448939640 FROM PROD INPUT FILE. RESTARTED IN STEP0020 - JOB COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1HED",
  "PROBLEM": "IDI0082E DB2 DB2S CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQLALLOCCONNECT SQLERROR SQLRC=-1 {DB2 FOR OS\/390}{ODBC DRIVER} SQLSTATE=58004 ERRLOC=2:170:10 CAF \"OPEN\" FAILED USING DB2 SYSTEM:DB2 PLAN:DSNACLI RC=0C AND REASON=00F30040 IEF285I SYS08284.T151446.RA000.CL$$1HED.IDIAOIN.H01 D MODULE Q724HMLN, CSECT CKETRGET, OFFSET X'466': ABEND S0 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PROD.CL.CARDLIB(Q724HMLN) POINTS TO MONTH END FILES AND THIS JOB WAS BEING RUN AGAINST DAILY FILES. ",
  "SOLUTION": "PUT IN OVERRIDE TO POINT TO DB2P INSTEAD OF DB2S. \/\/STEP0030.SYSTSIN DD DSN=TEST.CL.CARDLIB(D724HMLN) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1110",
  "PROBLEM": "IDI0082E DB2 CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR SQLALLOCCONNECT SQLERROR 769 SQLRC=-1 {DB2 FOR OS\/390}{ODBC DRIVER} SQLSTATE=58004 ERRLOC=2:170:10 CAF \"OPEN\" FAILED USING DB2 SYSTEM: DB2S AND PLAN:DSNACLI RC=0C AND REASON=00F30040 A USER ABEND 0001 OCCURRED IN MODULE M7242700 CSECT CKABEND AT OFFSET X'116' ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CLIENT CONFLICT WITH CL$$1HED WHICH ALSO RUNS AGAINST THE ME FILES. ",
  "SOLUTION": "VERIFIED THAT THE CLIENT FOR POLICY 0710028060 WAS OK. HAD JOB RESTARTED FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$I800",
  "PROBLEM": "VARIES STEP 1: CD COPIES CL.MAILING.OUTPUT(0) TO INFORMATICA PRODUCTION SERVER STEP 2: CL$$I800 RUNS EXECUTING WORKFLOW THAT WILL REFORMAT FILE TO NEW RIVER EXTRACT LAYOUT STEP 3: CD COPIES TARGET FILE FROM INFORMATICA SERVER TO FTP SERVER STEP 4: FTP'S FILE TO NEW RIVER WITH PGP ENCRYPTION. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "VARIES - DEPENDING UPON WHERE PROCESS FAILED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CONTACT DOREEN KLOMSTAD OR LINDA PRAED TO FIX PROBLEM AND RESTART WORKFLOW "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$9108",
  "PROBLEM": "IN JESMSGLG JES2 SHOWS IEF403I CL$$9108 - STARTED - TIME=12.48.26 +UNABLE TO RETRIEVE STUB POOL RECORD +- - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - +IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V5R1M0 (UK00798 2005\/02\/23) INVOKED $HASP375 CL$$9108 ESTIMATED LINES EXCEEDED IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 517 USER COMPLETION CODE=4039 REASON CODE=00000000 TIME=13.12.17 SEQ=08285 CPU=0000 ASID=0045 PSW AT TIME OF ERROR 078D1000 85BEEFC6 ILC 2 INTC 0D NO ACTIVE MODULE FOUND NAME=UNKNOWN ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB IS A MONTHLY ULTIM REPORT & IT DOES NOT HAVE A RESTART DOC? ONLY RUNNING ONE ULTIM REPORT STEP. THE ULTIM IS TRYING TO GET A 69 ACTIVITY SEGMENT. BECAUSE THE ON-LINES ARE UP AND ACTIVITY IS BEING CREATED WE CAN HAVE THIS KIND OF ABEND HAPPEN. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAVE OPS RESTART FROM TOP AND HOPE WE DO NOT BUTT HEADS WITH ON-LINE UPDATES AGAIN. SOLUTION2: PRIOR RUN FAILED WITH SAME PROBLEM. PER LINDA PRAED SINCE WE ARE TRYING TO GET THE 69 ACTIVITY SEGMENT IS OK TO POINT TO SA. * SENT E-MAIL TO PCD TO ADD OVER RIDE TO POINT TO SNAP AFTER VSAM FILES. RE- RUN FROM TOP FINISHED OK THIS TIME. PLEASE PLACE THE FOLLOWING ONE TIME OVER RIDE IN JOB CL$$9108 AFTER \/\/JSTEP010 EXEC PROC=CLULTIM, ADD \/\/ VOPREFX='CL.SA.VSAM.BASEOL.', WITH OVER RIDE SHOULD LOOK LIKE: PROD.OPER.JCLLIB(CL$$9108) - 01.22 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0837",
  "PROBLEM": "FOUND IN THE SYSPRINT DD: NO TEXT PIECES QUALIFIED DURING ASSEMBLY. TRIGGER: 1, PRODUCT: IVA 2007 POLICY PAGES, COMPANY-CD: 00, CONTRACT-NUM: 2453446640 TOTAL ERRORS: 1. 04\/30\/2008: PROBLEM FOUND IN THE SYSPRINT DD: NO TEXT PIECES QUALIFIED DURING ASSEMBLY. TRIGGER: 1, FIXED ANNUITY PAGES, COMPANY-CD: 00, CONTRACT-NUM: 2052358270 TOTAL ERRORS: 1. 12\/05\/2008: PROBLEM FOUND IN THE SYSPRINT DD: NO TEXT PIECES QUALIFIED DURING ASSEMBLY. TRIGGER: 2, PRODUCT: SL ANNUITY CARE PAGES, COMPANY-CD: 05, CONTRACT-NUM: 5820014310 TOTAL ERRORS: 1. 12\/05\/2008: PROBLEM FOUND IN THE SYSPRINT DD: NO TEXT PIECES QUALIFIED DURING ASSEMBLY. TRIGGER: 2, PRODUCT: SL LEGACY CARE PAGES, COMPANY-CD: 05, CONTRACT-NUM: 5820015510 TOTAL ERRORS: 1. 02\/09\/2009: PROBLEM FOUND IN THE SYSPRINT DD: NO TEXT PIECES QUALIFIED DURING ASSEMBLY. TRIGGER: 2, PRODUCT: SL ANNUITY CARE PAGES, COMPANY-CD: 05, CONTRACT-NUM: 5820018200 TOTAL ERRORS: 1. 02\/11\/2009: PROBLEM FOUND IN THE SYSPRINT DD: NO TEXT PIECES QUALIFIED DURING ASSEMBLY. TRIGGER: 9, PRODUCT: SL ANNUITY CARE PAGES, COMPANY-CD: 05, CONTRACT-NUM: 5820018600 TOTAL ERRORS: 1. 02\/13\/2009: CONTRACT-NUM: 5200026360 CONTRACT-NUM: 5820019250 BOTH ARE FOR HAWAII. 02\/24\/2009: NO TEXT PIECES QUALIFIED DURING ASSEMBLY. TRIGGER: 4, PRODUCT: SL ANNUITY CARE PAGES, COMPANY-CD: 05, CONTRACT-NUM: 5820018960 TOTAL ERRORS: 1. STATE OF FL (STATE CODE 10) NOT APPROVED IN PROD 06\/12\/2009: 09\/11\/2009: - FCC SAME 38\/SA34 01\/25\/2011: - FCC SAME 24\/SA35 - 5820177410 NO TEXT PIECES QUALIFIED DURING ASSEMBLY. TRIGGER: 4, PRODUCT: SL ANNUITY CARE PAGES, COMPANY-CD: 05, CONTRACT-NUM: 5820030280 TOTAL ERRORS: 1. STATE OF 'OR' (STATE CODE 38) FORM SA34 NOT APPROVED IN PROD ",
  "ANALYSIS": "(03\/31\/2008) 1) LOOK IN PROD CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR(0) FILE FOR POLICY'S ISSUE STATE. (IN COLUMN 36) HERE IT IS 14 WHICH IS IL. OR CAN LOOK AT 01 SEG FOR ISSUE STATE. (FOR 04\/30\/2008 - THE STATE IS NJ) (FOR 12\/05\/2008 - THE STATE IS TN) (FOR 12\/10\/2008 - THE STATE IS FL) (FOR 01\/25\/2011 - THE STATE IS MN) 2) LOOK AT 02 SEG FOR FORM #. IN THIS CASE IS IVA2007 (FOR 04\/30\/2008 - THE FORM # IS LA-31 AC) (FOR 12\/05\/2008 - THE FORM # IS SA34) (FOR 12\/10\/2008 - THE FORM # IS SA32) (FOR 01\/25\/2011 - THE FORM # IS SA35) 3) LOOK AT CKAPTB65 TABLE IN PROD CICS FOR CO CODE 00. YOU WILL SEE THAT IL HAS NOT BEEN APPROVED FOR THIS PRODUCT. TABLE= CKAPTB65 000 IVA2007 ID 11\/30\/2006 Y <-- ENTRY FOR IL WOULD BE HERE 000 IVA2007 IN 11\/30\/2006 Y - (FOR 12\/05\/2008: LOOK AT CKAPTB65 TABLE IN PROD CICS FOR CO CODE 05. YOU WILL SEE THAT TN HAS NOT BEEN APPROVED FOR THIS PRODUCT. TABLE= CKAPTB65 005 SA34 SD 06\/01\/2006 Y <-- ENTRY FOR TN WOULD BE HERE 005 SA34 UT 09\/11\/2006 Y) ",
  "SOLUTION": "1) FORCE JOB COMPLETE & 2) EMAIL TRIAGE THAT JOB CL$$0837 ABENDED ON POLICY NUMBER 2453446640 FOR THE STATE OF IL WHICH HAS NOT BEEN APPROVED IN PRODUCTION YET (TRIAGE WILL EMAIL THE USERS WITH THE POLICY NUMBER AND REASON). ALSO CC: DENISE WILLIAMS AND DON NIETEN OF CSS (2\/16\/09) ONLY ON PRODUCTION RUNS "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0020",
  "PROBLEM": "S3E6; OCA (DECIMAL OVERFLOW) IN PROGRAM *CKDPPSRF ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PROBLEM WAS ON POLICY 0620331950. NOT SURE WHY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED PROD CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT(0) FILE & REMOVED BAD POLICY. HAD JOB RESTARTED FROM STEP0030. --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! JOB RAN SUCCESSFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$8150",
  "PROBLEM": "ERR-G POS 49 (156-B) DEFINITION NOT PERMITTED ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DID NOT FIND THIS JOB IN BOMBLOG BUT DID FIND THE ERR-G FROM OLD ULTIM JOB BACK IN 2005. IT SAID DAH H. OFFERED SUGGESTION HOW TO FIX. SO TALKED TO DAH H. HE LOOKED AND FOUND THAT FUND VALUE COPYLIB (FNULTDEF) HAD INCREASED IN LENGTH TO 20000, BUT THE CARDLIB (UDCL8150) STILL HAD LENGTH OF 10000. ",
  "SOLUTION": "MADE COPY OF CARDLIB (UDCL8150) & CHANGED LENGTH FROM 10000 TO 20000. HAD JOB RESTARTED FROM TOP WITH OVERRIDE: \/\/STEP0010.SYSDICT DD DSN=TEST.CL.SEC.CARDLIB(UDCL8150),DISP=SHR. JOB FINISHED SUCCESSFULLY. (SENT EMAIL TO R. WATSON REQUESTING PERMANENT FIX NEEDED) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0836",
  "PROBLEM": "IS THAT FILE CL.DLS.WRITAGT.SORT.DUPOUT IS TRUELY EMPTY. IT NEEDS TO HAVE 9'S IN COLS 1 - 30. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS FILE IS USED AS INPUT FOR VSAM RECORD: CL.VSAM.DLS.WRITAGT IN JOBS CL$$0836, CL$$0837, CL$$0838, & CL$$0839. --> ISSUE CL8065 WAS OPENED ON 1\/7\/08 TO ADDRESS THIS PROBLEM --> AND IS BEING WORKED ON BY DOCUMENTS TEAM. ",
  "SOLUTION": "WORK AROUND IS TO EDIT CL.DLS.WRITAGT.SORT.DUPOUT (USING FIRECALL) BY INSERTING 9S IN COLUMNS 1 - 30. THEN HAVE JOB CL$$0836 RESTARTED IN STEP0080 WHICH IS A DELETE\/ DEFINE STEP FOR THE VSAM FILES. JOB DID FINISH OK & THEN REMAINING POLICY PAGE JOBS (CL$$0837, 838, & 839) FINISH OK ALSO. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "DATA SET MODL.CL.SA.VSAM.BASEOL.DXXREF ALREADY IN USE, TRY LATER ",
  "ANALYSIS": "READ SCHD.CTM.DOC FOR JSTEP0020, STEP0010 WHICH SAID TO RUN CL$$D160 & THEN RESTART IN JSTEP020.STEP0010. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RAN MODL.CL.JCLLIB(CL$$D160) & THEN HAD OPS RESTART JOB FROM JSTEP0020.STEP0010. HOWEVER, TO OPS THIS MEANS: -->OPS USED: \/\/RESTART EXEC PROC=CTRTROLR, -->OPS USED: \/\/ PARM=('RR,CL$M0160,38URI,RL,PROC0020.STEP0010,.', -->OPS USED: \/\/ 'DDD,00') "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0839",
  "PROBLEM": "NO TEXT PIECES QUALIFIED DURING ASSEMBLY. TRIGGER: 3, PRODUCT: SL ANNUITY CARE PAGES, COMPANY-CD: 05, CONTRACT-NUM: 5820006740 TOTAL ERRORS: 1. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "1) LOOK IN PROD CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR(0) FILE FOR POLICY'S ISSUE STATE. (IN COLUMN 36) HERE IT IS 14 WHICH IS IL. 050505582000674001000000069ANCNSM 14 OR CAN LOOK AT 01 SEG FOR ISSUE STATE. 2) LOOK AT 02 SEG FOR FORM #. IN THIS CASE IS SA34. 3) LOOK AT CKAPTB65 TABLE IN PROD CICS FOR CO CODE 05. YOU WILL SEE THAT IL HAS NOT BEEN APPROVED FOR THIS PRODUCT. TABLE= CKAPTB65 005 SA34 ID 04\/19\/2006 Y <-- ENTRY FOR IL WOULD BE HERE 005 SA34 IN 05\/23\/2006 Y ",
  "SOLUTION": "1) FORCE JOB COMPLETE & 2) EMAIL TRIAGE THAT JOB CL$$0839 ABENDED ON POL 5820006740 FOR STATE OF IL WHICH HAS NOT BEEN APPROVED IN PROD & THE USERS WILL NEED TO EMAIL PAT SOUTH'S TEAM TO REQUEST MANUAL PAGES. ALSO CC: DENISE WILLIAMS AND DON NIETEN OF CSS (2\/16\/09) ONLY ON PRODUCTION RUNS "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0126",
  "PROBLEM": "SB37 B37-04,IFG0554A,CL$$0126,STEP0030,SORTOUT,226B,STOR11,CL.SORT.ACH. CONTROL.XREF ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THOUGHT SINCE IT WAS A SORT STEP I'D ADD THE OVERRIDES... \/\/STEP0030.SORTWK01 DD SPACE=(CYL,(200,50)), \/\/ UNIT=SYSDA \/\/STEP0030.SORTWK02 DD SPACE=(CYL,(200,50)), \/\/ UNIT=SYSDA \/\/STEP0030.SORTWK03 DD SPACE=(CYL,(200,50)), \/\/ UNIT=SYSDA AND RESTART FROM STEP0030. THIS DIDN'T WORK. CALLED DASD ON-CALL PERSON GREG WARD. HE CALLED MARK WILLIAMS. MARK SAID SINCE IT WAS GETTING THE SB37 ON THE SORTOUT WE SHOULD BUMP UP THE SPACE ON THAT. HE WAS SURPRISED IT WASN'T ON CYL. ",
  "SOLUTION": "ADDED THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDE... \/\/STEP0030.SORTIN DD \/\/ DD \/\/ DD DSN=CL.BASEB.ACH.CONTROL.XREF(-0) \/\/STEP0030.SORTOUT DD DSN=CL.SORT.ACH.CONTROL.XREF, \/\/ DISP=(NEW,CATLG,DELETE), \/\/ UNIT=SYSDA, \/\/ SPACE=(CYL,(200,50)), \/\/ DCB=(LRECL=178,RECFM=FB,BLKSIZE=8900) \/\/STEP0030.SORTWK01 DD SPACE=(CYL,(200,50)), \/\/ UNIT=SYSDA \/\/STEP0030.SORTWK02 DD SPACE=(CYL,(200,50)), \/\/ UNIT=SYSDA \/\/STEP0030.SORTWK03 DD SPACE=(CYL,(200,50)), \/\/ UNIT=SYSDA CHANGED THE SPACE LINE FOR THE SORTOUT FROM SPACE=(8900,(800,80),RLSE) TO SPACE=(CYL,(200,50)). RESTARTED FROM STEP0030. JOB FINISHED OKAY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$SEGD",
  "PROBLEM": "S001 +IAMW04 DD=FVDSEG1 OPEN ERROR - DATASET NOT AVAILABLE, IN USE BY CL$$0013 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG1 IN USE BY ANOTHER JOB ",
  "SOLUTION": "WAITED UNTIL OTHER JOB FINISHED AND RERAN FROM TOP. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "PROBLEM: PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) AT LOCATION 00306C IN ELEMENT D724CARE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PROGRAM ABENDED BECAUSE IMMEDIATE CARE POLICY 5824301670 HAD BAD DATA IN FIELD FENVARBA-VARIABLE-AREA IN THE 86 SEGMENT. IF IPCT IS FOUND, PROGRAM EXPECTS IT FOLLOWED BY A SPACE THEN ONE OR TWO NUMBERS WITH A % SIGN. (EXPECTED: IPCT 03%) WHAT IT HAD WAS IPCT03%. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DROPPED POLICY FROM TEST.CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT FILE & RERAN CL$T0020. JOB FINISHED SUCCESSFULLY. THEN HAD TESTING TEAM FIX 86 SEGMENT AND REORDER PAGES FOR NEXT CYCLE. --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "-STEP=CSET1 PGM=COMPUSET EXECUTED - COND CODE 0000 RC=0000 +FOR0341I STOP 12 -STEP=METINT PGM=XRXINT EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 RC=0000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "AT THE DLS LEVEL, SOME CRITERIA IS NOT BEING MET AND AN EMPTY FILE IS BEING SENT TO THE EMITTER (IE. NO DOCUMENTS NEED TO BE CREATED FOR THIS PARTICULAR STEP). * A SIMILAR PROBLEM IS SOMETIMES ENCOUNTERED IN THE IDOC0515 JOB AS WELL. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAVE OPS FORCE THE JOB COMPLETE\/OK NOTE: IN THE FUTURE, TO CORRECT THIS ISSUE, WE WILL NEED TO UPDATE THE JCL TO DO AN EMPTY FILE CHECK. SEE DLS WORKGROUP \"ACTS DOCUMENTS\" AND DLS PRODUCT \"ACTS EOB DEATH\" FOR CRITERIA. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$9800",
  "PROBLEM": "-STEP=STEP0010 PGM=IKJEFT01 EXECUTED - COND CODE 0016 RC=0000 ELAP= 00:15:38.13 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "OUTPUT WAS GENERATED; SEE Q.ST SYSPRT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "BECAUSE THE OUTPUT RECORD WAS CREATED - THE JOB WAS FORCE COMPLETED OK *HELPFUL NOTE: PER DAN HUNSINGER, \"THERE ARE VARIOUS REASONS AS TO WHY YOU MIGHT GET CONDITION CODE 16. IN THIS CASE YOU WILL FIND THAT THE NAMES THAT ARE BEING JOINED ARE GREATER THAN THE SPACE WE ALLOWED FOR THE JOINED NAME.\" (SEE Q.ST SYSLST 'CONSOLIDATED ERROR LISTING' ... XLFJOIN (504-A) VAL > MAXIMUM ...) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$2010",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP0010 PGM=IKJEFT01 EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 QRB ABENDED DURING QUOTE PROCESS TRYING TO RETRIEVE HISTORY FOR A POLICY. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ISOLATED THE SCOPE TO A SINGLE POLICY 2388050030. THE CALLING CHAIN OF THE ABEND IS: Q7241010 Q7241010 Q7241010 P+30C4 Q7241010 D72INTER D72INTER P+14B0 Q7241010 CKUBVALX CKUBVALX P+98A Q7241010 CKULWDRF CKULWDRF P+B06 Q7241010 CKULHSIO CKULHSIO P+10C4 Q7241010 CKDCARTH N\/A P+3E2 THE ACTUAL ABEND OCCURS AT CKCYFLIO CEE3201S THE SYSTEM DETECTED AN OPERATION EXCEPTION (SYSTEM COMPLE FROM COMPILE UNIT CKCYFLIO AT ENTRY POINT CKCYFLIO. ON 1\/2\/08, A 6\/14\/07 DEATH CLAIM WAS ADDED EFFECT 1\/2\/08. PROGRAM IS TRYING TO RETRIEVE HISTORY DURATION 236 19 YEARS X 12=228 MONTHS 228+6 MONTHS SINCE ISSUE + 2 MONTHS =236. THE HIGH DURATION AT MONTH END WAS 231. THE PROGRAM GETS S0C1 TRYING TO READ CKCYFLIO FOR DURATION 236. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DROP 2388050030 FROM CL.ME.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY AND RERUN CL$$2010 FROM TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0510",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$0510 STEP0030 CL$$0510 - ABEND=S000 U0116 ICE116A K SORT CAPACITY EXCEEDED ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PRODUCTION ONLY ALLOWED THE FOLLOWING SPACE OPTIONS: SIZE=1048576,MAXLIM=1048576,MINLIM=450560, THE STEP REALLY NEEDED OPTIONS: SIZE=6291456,MAXLIM=1048576,MINLIM=450560, THIS APPEARS TO ONLY REQUIRE A RESTART ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTART JOB IN STEP0030 PER SCHD.CTM.DOC "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "FUNDS WERE NOT AVAILABLE UNTIL 4 AM. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "04:10 MS0074A WILL NOW RUN *** CDFT1038 MAY RUN WHEN READY. CONTACT LINDA PRAED TO SEE WHAT NEEDS TO BE DONE TO GET CL$$ STARTED. 04:13 CONTACT LINDA KIENTZ. LINDA PRAED NEEDS TO VERIFY FILE IS THERE. 04:15 CONTACT LINDA PRAED. LINDA WILL LOOK AT. 04:35 LINDA PRAED WILL CONTACT LINDA KIENTZ. 04:54 LINDA PRAED CAN'T FIND FILE TO VERIFY. LINDA WILL CONTACT STEVE LOPER. 05:05 STEVE LOPER CALLED. NEED TO CALL DAN DRAKE. 05:09 CONTACT DAN DRAKE. PER DAN FILE IS ON UNIT BOX. PER DAN REMOVE INPUT REQUIREMENT FOR RSUXUNF300. 05:13 CDFT1038 CYUVLOD GOOD. CL$$0010 STARTED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "IN FUTURE, REMOVE INPUT REQUIREMENT FOR RSUXUNF300. PROBLEMS WITH FUNDS WILL BE FOUND IN CL$$0012. ADDITIONAS CLEAN-UP: CL$$0004 - DB2 CONFLICTS - DELETED CDFT1091 AND FORCED OK CL$$0007 - DB2 CONFLICTS - DELETED CDFT1137, CL$$0008, CL$$0009 AND FORCED OK CL$$0420 - DB2 CONFLICTS - DELETED CL$$0430, CL$$0440 AND FORCED OK CL$$0430 - ADDED OVERRIDES TO ALLOW MULTI-DAY PROCESSING IN 12\/06 CYCLE: \/\/STEP0030.SYSIPT DD * CKVL80PE 12042007 12042007 %%CLDAT7-%%CLDAT7 AP-VSAM "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$GROW",
  "PROBLEM": "FDRS42 CLUSTER REDEFINED DSN=CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG1 FDRR52** OPEN FAILED FOR TARGET DATASET - R15=008,CODE=128, DSN=CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG1 FDRR32** RELOAD PROCESSING TERMINATED FDRR97** DYNAMIC DEALLOCATION ERROR - COMP=04,CODE=0438, INFO=0000,DDNAME=SYS00001 IKJ56247I FILE SYS00001 NOT UNALLOCATED, IS NOT ALLOCATED FDRR33** RELOAD FAILED - CODE=U0999, DSN=CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PROC RUN IS CL$$IIAM. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CL$$IIAM IS HANDLED BY THE DASD TEAM. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1170",
  "PROBLEM": "-IAMW09 DD=FVDSEG1 OPEN ERROR - FILE DEFINED BUT NOT LOADED VSAM ERROR - FILE=FVDSEG1, INCODE=6, OUTCODE=9, R15=08, ERRCODE=00A0 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CL$$1000 CREATED ME AUXSEG1 FILE THAT WAS EMPTY DUE TO CL$$GROW ABEND. ",
  "SOLUTION": "USING FIRECALL, I SNAPPED CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG1 TO CL.ME.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG1. JOB RESTARTED FROM TOP AND COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1060",
  "PROBLEM": "-IAMW09 DD=FVDSEG1 OPEN ERROR - FILE DEFINED BUT NOT LOADED VSAM ERROR - FILE=FVDSEG1, INCODE=6, OUTCODE=9, R15=08, ERRCODE=00A0 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CL$$1000 CREATED ME AUXSEG1 FILE THAT WAS EMPTY DUE TO CL$$GROW ABEND. ",
  "SOLUTION": "USING FIRECALL, I SNAPPED CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG1 TO CL.ME.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG1. JOB RESTARTED FROM TOP AND COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1010",
  "PROBLEM": "-IAMW09 DD=FVDSEG1 OPEN ERROR - FILE DEFINED BUT NOT LOADED VSAM ERROR - FILE=FVDSEG1, INCODE=6, OUTCODE=9, R15=08, ERRCODE=00A0 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CL$$1000 CREATED ME AUXSEG1 FILE THAT WAS EMPTY DUE TO CL$$GROW ABEND. ",
  "SOLUTION": "USING FIRECALL, I SNAPPED CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG1 TO CL.ME.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG1. JOB RESTARTED FROM TOP AND COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$9800",
  "PROBLEM": "-STEP=STEP0010 PGM=IKJEFT01 EXECUTED - COND CODE 0016 RC=0000 ELAP= 00:21:39. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "RHONDA WATSON DETERMINED THAT THE JOB DID CREATE THE OUTPUT RECORD. ",
  "SOLUTION": "BECAUSE THE OUTPUT RECORD WAS CREATED - THE JOB WAS FORCE COMPLETED OK "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$RBR3",
  "PROBLEM": "EF450I CL$$RBR3 STEP0010 CL$$RBR3 - ABEND=S000 U0888 REASON=00000000 309 -STEP=STEP0010 PGM=FDRABR ABENDED - COND CODE S378 RC=0000 ELAP= 00:45:05.58 FDR320** UNABLE TO RESTORE REASON=6 DSN=CL.ME.VSAM.BASEOL.AGENT FDR320** UNABLE TO RESTORE REASON=6 DSN=CL.ME.VSAM.BASEOL.INTRATES 6 DATASET ENQUEUE FAILED FOR THIS DATASET. DSNENQ=NONE WILL OVERRIDE THIS CHECK ",
  "ANALYSIS": "RESTARTED THE JOB FROM THE TOP AND THE JOB ENDED OK "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$RBR3",
  "PROBLEM": "EF450I CL$$RBR3 STEP0010 CL$$RBR3 - ABEND=S000 U0888 REASON=00000000 452 TIME=20.09.19 -STEP=STEP0010 PGM=FDRABR ABENDED - COND CODE S378 RC=0000 ELAP= 01:07:14.18 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE ABEND WAS DUE TO AN EMERGENCY RE-IPL ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTARTED THE JOB FROM THE TOP AND THE JOB ENDED OK 05\/09\/2008 - SOMEONE RESTARTED THE JOB AT 5:49PM & 05\/13\/2008 AND THE JOB ENDED OK - P1PSS "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$RC99",
  "PROBLEM": "****** NOTE CL$$RC99 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL5 *************** IEF450I CL$$RC99 STEP0040 CL$$RC99 - ABEND=S2F3 U0000 REASON=00000000 895 TIME=17.57.02 -STEP= PGM=DSNUTILB ABENDED - COND CODE S2F3 RC=0000 ELAP= 00:55:35.85 I\/O BLKS= ****** NOTE CL$$RC99 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL5 *************** IEF453I CL$$RC99 - JOB FAILED - JCL ERROR - TIME=17.57.40 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE ABEND WAS DUE TO AN EMERGENCY RE-IPL ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTARTED THE JOB FROM THE TOP AND THE JOB ENDED OK "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND=S04C (SOC4) UNABLE TO RETRIEVE STUB POOL RECORD - - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V8R1M0 (UK30777 2007\/10\/31) INVOKED BY IDI IDI0082E DB2 DB2P CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQLALLOCCONNECT SQLE SQLRC=-1 {DB2 FOR OS\/390}{ODBC DRIVER} SQLSTATE=58004 ERRLOC=2:170:10 CAF \"OPEN\" FAILED USING DB2 SYSTEM:DB2P AND PLAN:DSNACLI RC=0C AND REASON=00F30040 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WHEN FIRST FIND OUT THAT JSTEP10 GOES DOWN, RUN TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$I0011) SO THAT THE INFORCE SIDE CAN BE CHECKED WHILE YOUR WORKING ON THE PENDING SIDE AS THE INFORCE SIDE TAKES A LONG TIME. YOU MAY WANT TO CALL OPS AND HAVE THEM BUMP UP PRIORITY ON YOUR JOB SO IT CAN FINISH SOONER. DIDN'T FIND IN THE SYSUDUMP SQL ERROR CODE. DID FIND SOME POLICIES IN THE DUMP. DID A 60D1 ON THOSE POLICIES IN CYBERLIFE 3270. THEY CAME UP WITH NO PROBLEMS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "JUST RAN TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$I0011 AND CL$P0011). THEY BOTH FINISHED FINE. HAD OPS RESTART FROM TOP. *SOLUTION: RAN TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$I0011 AND CL$P0011). CL$P0011 * FINISHED FINE BUT CL$I0011 ABENDED. COULDN'T FIND * SQL ERROR IN FILE, SO WAS GOING TO RUN TEST.CL.TOOLS * (SQL$DUPA) TO SEE IF DUP ROW OR OTHER. BUT SQL$DUPA IS * NOT A VALID JOB. FOUND POLICY (3465044300) IN DUMP. * RAN CL$I0011 AGAIN, STARTING WITH NEXT POLICY IN * POLICY FILE (CL.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY) - WHICH FOUND BY * USING FILE MARVEL. JOB COMPLETED OK, SO KNEW IT WAS * ONLY 1 BAD POLICY. TRIED LOOKING THIS POLICY UP IN * CICS BUT BLEW UP. POLICY WAS TOO LARGE AND EXCEEDED * THE CLIENT LIMIT OF 14,000. RECORD ITSELF ONLY HAD * 13,092 BYTES BUT IT STARTS ADDING THE 90 SEGMENTS * WHICH PUT IT OVER THE LIMIT. * --> HOW TO DETERMINE IF RECORD EXCEEDS LIMIT: CAN LOOK AT RC * IN CICS BUT THAT FIELD IS IN HEX SO NOT EASY TO READ * SEE 12763 (HEX) ON NEXT LINE * (RC 12763 $ 0 3465044300 0 1 1 10000000 114) * NOTE: THE ABOVE LINE IS FROM CICS AFTER SOME OF THIS * POLICIES SEGMENTS HAD BEEN DELETED. * THE BELOW PRINT WAS MADE FROM THE SB FILES WHICH * SHOWS THE RECORD SIZE PRIOR TO THE SEGMENT DELETES. * --> HOWEVER; IF YOU RUN A POLICY PRINT JOB IT WILL DISPLAY * IT AS NUMERIC - SEE 13092 BELOW. * (RC 13092 $ 0 3465044300 0 1 1 10000000 112) * NOTE: AGAIN 13,092 IS CLOSE TO THE 14,000 BYTE LIMIT BUT * IT WILL START ADDING 90 SEGS WHICH WILL CAUSE IT TO * OVERFLOW. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND=S04C (SOC4) UNABLE TO RETRIEVE STUB POOL RECORD - - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V5R1M0 (UK00798 2005\/02\/23) INVOKED BY IDI IDI0082E DB2 CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQLALLOCCONNECT SQLERROR SQLRC=-1 {DB2 FOR OS\/390}{ODBC DRIVER} SQLSTATE=58004 ERRLOC=2:170:10 CAF \"OPEN\" FAILED USING DB2 SYSTEM:DB2P AND PLAN:DSNACLI RC=0C AND REASON=00F30040 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WHEN FIRST FIND OUT THAT JSTEP10 GOES DOWN, RUN TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$I0011) SO THAT THE INFORCE SIDE CAN BE CHECKED WHILE YOUR WORKING ON THE PENDING SIDE AS THE INFORCE SIDE TAKES A LONG TIME. YOU MAY WANT TO CALL OPS AND HAVE THEM BUMP UP PRIORITY ON YOUR JOB SO IT CAN FINISH SOONER. DIDN'T FIND IN THE SYSUDUMP SQL ERROR CODE. DID FIND SOME POLICIES IN THE DUMP. DID A 60D1 ON THOSE POLICIES IN CYBERLIFE 3270. THEY CAME UP WITH NO PROBLEMS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "JUST RAN TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$I0011 AND CL$P0011). THEY BOTH FINISHED FINE. HAD OPS FORCE CL$$0011 OKAY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1160",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC4 (S04C) EXCI CALL OPEN PIPE FAILED RESP 8 REASON EXCI CALL OPEN PIPE FAILED RESP 8 REASON - - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB IS SUPPOSE TO WAIT FOR CICSD TO BE UP BEFORE EXECUTED. WE WERE STILL IN THE MIDDLE OF CYCLE. JOB DID WAIT FOR THE OTHER DEPENDENCY TO GET FULFILLED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD OPS PUT A HOLD ON JOB AND WAIT UNTIL CICSD COMES UP TO THEN KICK OFF THE JOB. REASON JOB KICKED OFF: THEY HAD A PROBLEM BRINGING DOWN CICSD. SO WHEN THEY FINALLY BROUGHT IT DOWN, THEY BROUGHT IT BACK UP AND DOWN AGAIN. BY BRINGING IT BACK UP, IT FULFILLED THE DEPENDENCY. STEVE B. IS GOING TO MODIFY CICSPSHD(SHUTS CICSD DOWN) TO CLEAR THIS CONDITION WHEN IT RUNS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0600",
  "PROBLEM": "HERE WHAT THE ABEND LOOKS LIKE IEFC452I CL$$0600 - JOB NOT RUN - JCL ERROR 736 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "UNTIL PROBLEM POLICY # IS FIXED WE NEEDED AND OVER RIDE TO POINT TO A LOAD THAT BYPASSES PROCESSING ON THIS POLICY. THIS IS RELATED TO THIS ABEND. 2453018360 FUNDVAL RECORD: V 0472 F @ NOT FOUND ON FUNDVAL 1 ",
  "SOLUTION": "SENT AND E-MAIL TO PCD NEEDED A COMMA BUT THEY HAD A PERIOD IN THE FOLLOWING OVER RIDE. \/\/STEP0310.STEPLIB DD DSN=TEST.CL.TDR.DSTLOAD,DISP=SHR \/\/ DD DSN=PROD.CL.LOADLIB.DISP=SHR <- PERIOD BEFORE DISP=SHR THE JCL MAINTENANCE FORM HAD A COMMA, IS PROBABLY JUST A TYPO. ASK PCD TO FIX AND RE-RUN. SECOND RUN WORKED OK, BUT RAN LONG. CONTACT NICOLE R PARK\/AUL@AUL TO LET HER KNOW THAT DST FAN MAIL FILES WILL BE LATE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$RBR3",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND LOOKS LIKE THIS TMS014 IEF234E K 0AE1,070957,PVT,CL$$RBR3,STEP0010 IEF450I CL$$RBR3 STEP0010 CL$$RBR3 - ABEND=S000 U0888 REASON= ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS JOB APPEARS TO BE CONFLICTING WITH SOMETHING ELSE WHEN IT ABENDS, WE HAVE BEEN JUST RE-RUN FROM TOP AND IT RUNS OK. ",
  "SOLUTION": "ASKED PCD TO RUN IT AFTER CL$$IIAM AND IT RAN OK THE SECOND TIME AROUND. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0600",
  "PROBLEM": "PROGRAM DISPLAYS A MESSAGE AND THEN STOPS RUNNING 2453018360 FUNDVAL RECORD: V 0472 F @ NOT FOUND ON FUNDVAL 1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PER JEAN EASTON, A 2666 TRANSACTION VIA 3270 WAS PROCESSED ON THIS POLICY, CHANGING THE MATURITY AGE TO 99, WHICH CHANGED THE MATURITY DATE TO 01\/18\/2012, WHILE THE MAXIMUM DATE REMAINED AT 01\/18\/2028. THE OTHER THING WAS THAT DUE TO THE TRANSACTION, CYBERLIFE E-PROCESSED MONTHLIVERSARIES FROM 1\/18\/1999 FORWARD. APPEARS TO BE LOOKING FOR THE FUND VALUE RECORD WITH THE CURRENT DATE, BUT THIS FUND ID ONLY HAS RECORDS UP TO YEAR 2004 ON THE FUND FILE. **NOTE** NOTE: ",
  "SOLUTION": "DID NOT WORK, SEE SOLUTION2 SOLUTION1: PER RHONDA WATSON, COPY ACTIVITY FILE FROM TIME DRIVEN AND REMOVE THE POLICY FROM THE FILE. THEN FOLLOW RESTART INSTRUCTIONS. PER RESTART IF STEP 310 HAS STARTED TO PROCESS RUN CL$$R600, RE-RUN FROM TOP. COPY: CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT.G2398V00 CREATED: TEST.CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT.BKUP.G2398 REMOVED RECORDS FOR POLICY 2453018360 FROM COPIED FILE AND ASK PCD TO RE-RUN FROM TOP WITH OVER RIDE TO POINT THIS FILE JOB ENDED WITH CONDITION 50 ON THIS STEP AGAIN. **NOTE** NOTE: SOLUTION1 DID NOT WORK, SEE SOLUTION2 SOLUTION2: PER SANDI JEFFS, COPY THE PROGRAM D724DSTA TO TEST ADD AN OVER RIDE TO BYPASS PROCESSING THIS POLICY. REQUEST THE CL$$R600 RAN, THEN RE-RUN POINTING TO MY UNIT TEST LOAD LIBRARY FOR THIS STEP. CREATED TEST.CL.TDR.DSTLOAD TO USE FOR THIS PER RHONDA IT IS NOW ALMOST 4 PM, SO WILL HAVE PCD REMOVE JOB FROM SCHEDULE, AND DOUBLE UP ON THE ACTIVITY FILE COMING IN ***********TO BRING IN THE -1 ACTIVITY FILE INTO STEP0210: \/\/STEP0210.SORTIN DD DSN=CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT(-1), \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) \/\/ DD DSN=CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT(-0), \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) ***********TO PICK UP SPECIAL LOAD LIBRARY IN TO STEP0310: \/\/STEP0310.STEPLIB DD DSN=TEST.CL.TDR.DSTLOAD,DISP=SHR \/\/ DD DSN=PROD.CL.LOADLIB,DISP=SHR NOTE: UNTIL THIS POLICY IS FIXED THIS ABEND WILL CONTINUE TO HAPPEN. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0837",
  "PROBLEM": "10\/03\/2007 COND CODE = 0008 THERE WAS DUPLICATE RIDER RECORD FOR POLICY 2453426100 (RIDER LR-163) AS INDICATED BY THE JCL LOG FOR THIS STEP PROBLEM: 06\/20\/2008 COND CODE = 0008 BOTH JOBS HAD THE SAME COND CODE AND SAME PROBLEM THERE WAS DUPLICATE RIDER RECORD FOR POLICY 2453429340 (RIDER LR-196) AS INDICATED BY THE JCL LOG FOR THIS STEP ",
  "ANALYSIS": "10\/03\/2007 REVIEWED THE JCL LOG FOR THIS STEP AND DETERMINED THAT THE SECONDARY RIDER & INVACCT FILES HAD THE DUPS. ANALYSIS: 06\/20\/2008 (BOTH JOBS HAD BEEN FORCE COMPLETED IN ERROR) REVIEWED THE JCL LOG FOR THIS STEP AND DETERMINED THAT THE SECONDARY RIDER FILE HAD THE DUPS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "10\/03\/2007 WITH THE HELP OF PCD (DAN DRAKE) THE FOLLOWING HAPPENED 1. DELETED ONE RECORD FROM THE FILE CL.DLS.RIDER.SORT.DUPOUT 2. DELETED EVERY OTHER RECORD FROM THE CL.DLS.INVACCT.SORT.DUPOUTA 3. RESTARTED THE JOB CL$$0837 FROM THE TOP SOLUTION: 06\/20\/2008 1. WITH A COPY OF THE INPUT FILE: CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT(0) RERAN CL$$0020 IN MY ENVIRONMENT 2. DELETED ONE OF THE EXTRA RIDER RECORDS FROM TEST.CL.PSS.DLS.RIDER(0) 3. RERAN CL$$0836 & CL$$0837 TO GET CORRECTED PAGES SOLUTION: 01\/09\/2009, 06\/09\/2009 1. USING FIRECALL REMOVED DUP RECORDS FROM: CL.DLS...RIDER.SORT.DUPOUTA & .INVACCT.SORT.DUPOUTA 2. HAD OPS RERUN CL$$0837 FROM THE TOP RAN SUCCESSFULLY. 3. DISCUSSED THIS PROBLEM WITH PAT - AT THIS TIME, NO ISSUE WAS CREATED SINCE IT HAPPENS SO INFREQUENTLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0600",
  "PROBLEM": "SYSTEM ABEND CODE 04E REASON CODE 00C50109 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "QW ON REASON CODE IS A DB2 TERMINATE PROBLEM ",
  "SOLUTION": "RUN CL$$R600; RESTART IN STEP0300. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$RC30",
  "PROBLEM": "SYSUT2 CL.DSNDBD.CLCISDB.CISBMAIN.I0001.A001, NOT FOUND ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CL$$0030 CREATED CL.DSNDBD.CLCISDB.CISBMAIN.J0001.A001. WE COULD NOT SEE THAT IN CL$$0030, BUT THAT IS THE DATASET THAT WAS CATALOGED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "TALKED TO ROBERT BIZLEY. HE SAID THE COPY UTILITY WILL CREATE I0001 OR J0001. ADDED OVERRIDE STEP0020.SYSUT2 DD DSN= CL.DSNDBD.CLCISDB.CISBMAIN.J0001.A001 AND RERAN FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$ABR1",
  "PROBLEM": "THE PROBLEM ACTUALLY HAPPENED IN CK4, BUT SAME PROBLEM\/ RESOLUTION CAN HAPPEN IN CL. *TMS007 IEC501A M 0AE1,070275(BCEA;0000005),SL,,CK4$ABR1, STEP0020.CK4$ABR1,FDRABR.LASTAPE.APPLBKP4.COPY2 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CK4$ABR1 WAS WAITING ON A TAPE VOLUME THAT WAS NOT AVAILABLE. OPERATIONS USES OVERRIDES FOR FDRABR.LASTAPE TO STACK BACKUP JOBS ON THE SAME TAPE. THESE FILES GET DELETED WHEN ABR$9999 RUNS, WHICH IS NORMALLY AFTER ALL ABR APPLICATION BACKUPS ARE COMPLETE AND BEFORE THE VAULT JOB RUNS. FOR SOME REASON YESTERDAY, THE APPLBKP4 DID NOT GET DELETED. AS A RESULT, OUR JOB WAS TRYING TO STACK ON THE TAPES FROM THE NIGHT BEFORE. TAPE11 IS THE OFFSITE TAPE AND WAS AT THE VAULT, THUS NOT AVAILABLE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "WHEN THIS OCCURS, JUST CANCEL THE JOB AND RESTART FROM THE TOP. WHEN YOU CANCEL AND RESTART, IT WILL ASK FOR NEW SCRATCH TAPES FOR BOTH TAPE1 AND TAPE 11. IF YOU HAVE THIS HAPPEN, SHOOT OPERATIONS A NOTE SO THEY CAN SEE WHAT HAPPENED. USUALLY IT IS DUE TO SOMETHING RUNNING LATE, ETC. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0835",
  "PROBLEM": "CC16 IN STEP0030. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PROBLEM IS THAT INPUT FILE FROM STEP0020 (WHICH IS CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR(0)) HAD BAD DATA IN IT. HOW YOU CAN EASILY TELL THERE IS BAD DATA IS TO LOOK DOWN THRU THE DPFSEXTR FILE AND SEE WHERE DATA IS OUT OF ALIGNMENT. THIS USUALLY HAPPENS WHEN THERE IS BAD DATA IN THE FILE. EXAMPLE BELOW - CAN SEE THAT LINE 3 & 4 ARE NOT IN SAME FORMAT AS LINES 1, 2, 5, 6, ETC. 1)000000072000907003042000071WL 36071PUARO 01 2)000000072000907003043000071WL 36071PUARO 01 3) 205111976090001 00 4) 205111976099001 00 5)000000205235407001000000069ACM2Q0 42 00 6)000000205235407090001000069ACM2Q0 42 00 ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED DPFSEXTR FILE AND DELETED BAD RECORDS (WHICH ARE LINES 3 & 4 IN ABOVE EXAMPLE. SENT OPS EMAIL ASKING THEM TO RESTART JOB FROM TOP USING OVERRIDE POINTING TO EDITED FILE. ***SAMPLE EMAIL BELOW********* PLEASE RESTART CL$$0835 FROM THE TOP USING THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDE: \/\/STEP0020.SORTIN DD DSN=TEST.CL.SEC.BASEB.DPFSEXTR.PG4549 ***SAMPLE EMAIL ABOVE********* RESULT: JOB FINISHED SUCCESSFULLY (*) THERE WAS NOTHING TO PRINT SO HAD JOB FOCED COMPLETE. NOTE: THIS SAME FILE IS USED IN JOB CL$$0838 - SEE THIS JOB BELOW "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0838",
  "PROBLEM": "CC16 IN STEP0010. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PROBLEM IS THAT INPUT FILE IN STEP0010 (WHICH IS CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR(0)) HAD BAD DATA IN IT. HOW YOU CAN EASILY TELL THERE IS BAD DATA IS TO LOOK DOWN THRU THE DPFSEXTR FILE AND SEE WHERE DATA IS OUT OF ALIGNMENT. THIS USUALLY HAPPENS WHEN THERE IS BAD DATA IN THE FILE. EXAMPLE BELOW - CAN SEE THAT LINE 3 & 4 ARE NOT IN SAME FORMAT AS LINES 1, 2, 5, 6, ETC. 1)000000072000907003042000071WL 36071PUARO 01 2)000000072000907003043000071WL 36071PUARO 01 3) 205111976090001 00 4) 205111976099001 00 5)000000205235407001000000069ACM2Q0 42 00 6)000000205235407090001000069ACM2Q0 42 00 ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED DPFSEXTR FILE AND DELETED BAD RECORDS (WHICH ARE LINES 3 & 4 IN ABOVE EXAMPLE. 1. FIRST, HAVE OPS DELETE ALL PRINT OUTPUT FROM THE BAD RUN. IF THE OUTPUT HAS ALREADY GONE TO THE PRINTER, THEN BE SURE TO ALERT TRIAGE THAT THIS OUTPUT MAY OR MAY NOT BE COMPLETE OR CORRECT AND THAT A SECOND SET WILL BE CREATED. 2. SECOND, SENT OPS AN EMAIL ASKING THEM TO RESTART THE JOB FROM THE TOP USING THE OVER-RIDE POINTING TO THE EDITED FILE. ***SAMPLE EMAIL BELOW********* PLEASE RESTART CL$$0838 FROM THE TOP USING THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDE: \/\/STEP0010.IEXTR DD DSN=TEST.CL.JIF.BASEB.DPFSEXTR.D052010 ***SAMPLE EMAIL ABOVE********* RESULT: JOB FINISHED SUCCESSFULLY NOTE: IN PRODUCTION, NOTIFY TRIAGE.IND OF THE POLICY NUMBERS DROPPED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$RBR3",
  "PROBLEM": "COND CODE S378 ABEND=S000 U0888 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB HAS BEEN RUNNING SUCCESSFULLY FOR A LONG TIME. MUST BE JUST A CONFLICT DURING THE RUN. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RERUN JOB FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0815",
  "PROBLEM": "THE XML PAGE CANNOT BE DISPLAYED CANNOT VIEW XML INPUT USING XSL STYLE SHEET. PLEASE CORRECT THE ERROR AND THEN CLICK THE REFRESH BUTTON, OR TRY AGAIN LATER. WHITESPACE IS NOT ALLOWED AT THIS LOCATION. ERROR PROCESSING RESOURCE 'FILE:\/\/\/G:\/XML FILES\/TEST.CL.CL$$0815.WHOLSALE.XMLRE... ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ORIGINAL CODE: <INSUREDNAME>CARRINGTON, BEAU M<\/INSUREDNAME> <AGENTNAME>ART JETTER & COMPANY<\/AGENTNAME> <UWAPPROVAL> <\/UWAPPROVAL> IN XML, \"&\" IS USED TO \"ESCAPE\" SPECIAL CHARACTERS SUCH AS < AND > ",
  "SOLUTION": "WRITE LOGIC TO REMOVE AMPERSANDS FROM THE EXTRACT. SEE H:\\CYBRLIFE\\BEST PRACTICES\\CODING\\ WHITESPACE NOT ALLOWED.DOC "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "2 IEFC019I MISPLACED DD STATEMENT ",
  "SOLUTION": "ADDED \/\/* AFTER \/\/*LOGONID ACFSUBID \/\/* "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0008",
  "PROBLEM": "S04C -STEP=STEP0010 PGM=IEFBR14 EXECUTED - COND CODE 0000 RC=0000 ELA +IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V5R1M0 (UK00798 2005\/02\/23) INVOKED BY ID +IDI0082E DB2 CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQLALLOCCONNECT SQLERROR SQLRC=-1 {DB2 FOR OS\/390}{ODBC DRIVER} SQLSTATE=58004 ERRLOC=2:170:10 CAF \"OPEN\" FAILED USING DB2 SYSTEM:DB2P AND PLAN:DSNACLI RC=0C AND REASON=00F30040 $HASP375 CL$$0008 ESTIMATED LINES EXCEEDED $HASP375 CL$$0008 ESTIMATE EXCEEDED BY 25,000 LINES IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 280 USER COMPLETION CODE=4039 REASON CODE=00000000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE PRODUCTION CYCLE WAS RUNNING LATE AS WE GOT OUR FUND PRICES LATE. NORMALLY THIS WOULD RUN AT END OF CYCLE BEFORE ON-LINES ARE UP. THIS KIND OF ABEND HAS BEEN KNOWN TO HAPPEN IN CL$$0035 WHILE READING PENDING VSAM. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RE-RUN FROM TOP IN HOPES WE WILL NOT HIT PENDING RECORD BEING UPDATED, TRIED THIS 3 TIMES KEPT HITTING PENDING RECORDS BEING UPDATED. SOLUTION2: RE-RUN FROM TOP, WITH THE FOLLOWING JCL OVERRIDE TEMPORARY JCL CHANGE FOR THE FOLLOWING: \/\/* \/\/CL$$0008 EXEC PROC=CL$$0008 \/\/* CHANGE TO BE, JUST FOR THIS RUN: \/\/* \/\/CL$$0008 EXEC PROC=CL$$0008, \/\/ VOPREFX='CL.SA.VSAM.BASEOL.' \/\/* JOB ENDED OK WITH THIS OVER RIDE "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0035",
  "PROBLEM": "S04C 09.00.03 JOB01329 -STEP=STEP0005 PGM=IEFBR14 EXECUTED - COND COD 09.01.00 JOB01329 IEC130I SYSPDUMP DD STATEMENT MISSING< - - - - 09.01.01 JOB01329 +IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V5R1M0 (UK00798 2005\/0 09.01.03 JOB01329 +IDI0082E DB2 CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQLAL 433 SQLRC=-1 {DB2 FOR OS\/390}{ODBC DRIVER} SQLSTA 433 ERRLOC=2:170:10 CAF \"OPEN\" FAILED USING DB2 433 PLAN:DSNACLI RC=0C AND REASON=00F30040 LAST ENTRY FROM SYSOUT: CONTRACT NUMBER1: 0620257520 2052343380 - LAP 3465110950 - PSS 2453398340 - LKM 0710055290 - LKM 3465112960 - BKG 0700059220 - TDR 0710061750 - LKM 0620277250 - LKM 0620282330 - LKM 0620287130 - SEC 0620287540 - SEC 0620288230 - LAP 0620287580 - LKM 3465115660 - SEC 0620292050 - SEC 5820000090 - SEC 0620295810 - SEC 2453419000 - PSS 0720002450 - SEC 2453426360 - TDR 2453426520 - LKM 2453425680 - LKM 0620313130 - LKM 2453461600 - FCC 0720052780 - WHH 0620396350 - WHH ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED AT HELD CUE AND FOUND SQLCODE=100 WHICH INDICATES A MISSING ROW IN CLIENT FOR POLICY 0620257520. LOOKED AT CLIENT TABLE AND DID APPEAR TO BE MISSING. HOWEVER, LOOKED AT POLICY ON 3270 AND SAW THAT POLICY HAD BEEN UPDATED AS OF 5\/19\/06 WHICH MEANS IT WAS PROBABLY BEING UPDATED AS THE JOB WAS RUNNING. SO VERIFIED NEED TO RESTART JOB FROM TOP. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD JOB RESTARTED FROM TOP. JOB COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0860",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C7 PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) AT LOCATION 00168A IN ELEMENT CKUBANSV ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DROPPED THESE POLICIES, ONE AT A TIME, UNTIL MY TEST JOB ENDED OK. 2453222810 2453222820 2453262490 2453397730 2453397740 NOTIFIED HEIDE WEIS THAT THESE POLICIES WERE BAD AND THAT NO STATEMENT WOULD BE GENERATED. PER HEIDE, THESE POLICIES HAD ACTIVITY POSTED ON 7\/10 THAT WAS EFFECTIVE 6\/29 AND THE RESULT DOES GENERATE REVISED STATEMENTS THAT THEY SEND TO THE CLIENT. IN THIS CASE, SHE SAID IT WAS NOT THAT BIG OF A DEAL TO SKIP THE SENDING OF THE STATEMENTS FOR THESE. ADDED SOME DISPLAYS TO CKUBANSV AND DETERMINED THE PROBLEM TO BE THE CONFIRMATION ID ASSIGNED TO THIS TRANSACTION. THE PROGRAM IS ATTEMPTING TO FLOW THROUGH THIS LOGIC: IF FUAFTYP-FPA-TYPE (WS-ACCT-SUB) EQUAL 'II' MOVE FUAFPRE-FPA-PRE-TEFRA (WS-ACCT-SUB) TO WS-MAT-INT-INCOME (WS-MAT-SUB) GO TO SUBR17999-SCAN-PSEUDO-EXIT. IT IS PICKING UP THE 'II' FROM THE CONFIRMATION ID INCORRECTLY. 2453222810 HAS A CONFIRMATION ID = GT6YW3IIAFJ THE OTHER 4 POLICIES ALSO HAD AN 'II' IN THIS FIELD. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RERAN JOB WITH OVERRIDE TO MY FILE LESS THE 5 DROPPED POLICIES AND IT ENDED OKAY. NOTIFIED CYBERLIFE IND, WHO WILL WRITE UP AN ISSUE AND GET IT PRIORITIZED TO RESOLVE THE PROBLEM. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "SVSJ018I, ,WRNG.LEN.RECORD,0000007F000000,BSAM SVTM052I STEP09 COPY CDFT5023( 2,246) SNODE=AULCD.PC4390 85 SVTM052I FROM CL.CARVM.ERRS SVTM052I TO SLPFLE01.ONEAMERICA...EPORTS AUL DOWNLOAD C SVTM052I #### COMPLETED 00000010\/SVSJ018I SNTB002I ** CONNECT:DIRECT FAILED STEP COMPLETION ** CTO282I DSN=CDFAIL CDFT5023 CLULTRAV REPORT FAILED SEE CDFTJOBS DO DETERMINE WHO TO CALL ******** CONNECT:DIRECT FILE TRANSFER FAILED ********* 859 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "COULD NOT FIGURE THIS OUT AND SINCE WAS ERROR REPORT COPIED Q.LOG ENTRY AND LEFT FOR MONDAY AM RESOLUTION. ",
  "SOLUTION": "FORWARED INFO ON TO CDFT ON-CALL PERSON SINCE FILE WAS THERE AND LOOKED OK. SOLUTION: PER NOTE FROM DAN DRAKE.... CDFT5023 IS DEPENDENT ON CL$$1010, BUT, SOMEBODY (ACTUARIAL?)ASKED FOR A CONTROLD REPORT (CL.CARVM.ERRS) FROM CL$$1010 TO BE DOWNLOAD ALSO (THIS IS FAIRLY NEW), SO, CDFT5023 CAN'T RUN AS SOON AS CL$$1 DONE, IT HAS TO WAIT FOR CONTROLD TO PRINT THE REPORT TO A DISK FI 10 OR 15 SECONDS PROBABLY WOULD HAVE BEEN ENOUGH (THAT'S WHY IT LOOKED FINE WHEN YOU CHECKED). I ADDED A DEPENDENCY TO CDFT5023 TO WAIT FOR CONTROLD TO PRINT THE ALSO NOTE ABOUT CDFT JOBS: IF THE FILE WAS CREATED BY CYBERLIFE JOB, THEN THE CDFT PROBLEM IS TO BE HANDLED BY CL ON-CALL PERSON! "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0850",
  "PROBLEM": "S013 IEC141I 013-18,IGG0191B,CL$$0850,STEP0010,SYSREQ,2216,PRD007, +IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V5R1M0 (UK00798 2005\/02\/23) INVOKED IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 666 SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=013 REASON CODE=00000018 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SAW THAT SYSREQ WAS CARDLIB, SO CHECKED PROD.CL.CARDLIB AND SAW MEMEBER WAS NOT THERE. NOTICED WAS ULTIM STEP, SO CHECKED PROD.CL.ULTIM AND SAW MEMBER WAS THERE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "OPED JCLLIB AND PUT IN OVERRIDE FOR THIS. DID JCL CHECK AND SAW MORE MEMBERS WERE ALSO MISSING FROM PROD.CL.CARDLIB. ADDED OVERRIDES FOR ALL MISSING & HAD OPS RESTART FROM TOP. \/\/STEP0010.SYSREQ DD DSN=PROD.CL.ULTIM(URAUDEXT) \/\/STEP0015.SYSREQ DD DSN=PROD.CL.ULTIM(URPWEXT) \/\/STEP0020.SYSREQ DD DSN=PROD.CL.ULTIM(URNBAEXT) \/\/STEP0025.SYSREQ DD DSN=PROD.CL.ULTIM(URGAAEXT) \/\/STEP0030.SYSREQ DD DSN=PROD.CL.ULTIM(URABCEXT) \/\/STEP0045.SYSREQ DD DSN=PROD.CL.ULTIM(URDETDIF) JOB FINISHED SUCCESSFULLY! "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0130",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND S04C ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB WENT DOWN IN THE SAME PLACE. LOOKED AT THE RECORD COUNT FOR SYSLST AND IT WAS THE SAME EVERY TIME I RERAN THE JOB AFTER DELETING RECORDS FROM THE INPUT FILE. SINCE THE RECORD COUNT WAS ALWAYS THE SAME, WE FIGURED IT WAS HITTING A MAX ON SOMETHING... ESPECIALLY SINCE THIS WAS DURING THE OPTIMIZATION CYCLE. LOOKED AT THE REPORT IN SYSLST, MAXED TO THE BOTTOM AND SHIFTED TO THE RIGHT. THE PAGE NUMBER IS 999. CKCBAPPC WAS TRYING TO ADD ONE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "BROUGHT DOWN CKCBAPPC INTO PANLIB. CHANGED PAGENO DS PL2 TO PAGENO DS PL5 ASSEMBLED AND LINKED IN MY WORLD AND RERAN JOB POINTING TO MY LOADLIB. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0165",
  "PROBLEM": "KNEW SNAP JOBS WOULD FAIL BECAUSE NEEDED 3 VOLSERS BUT THE CARDLIB ONLY POINTED TO 2. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CARDLIB (CLH0160) POINTED TO 2 VOLSERS BUT NEEDED 3. ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED CARDLIB CLH0160 TO MY LIBRARY AND ADDED A 3RD VOLSER, SO CARDLIB WAS NOW: CLHSI1 CLHSI2 CLDSK1 FOR MORE DETAILS ON THIS SEE SOLUTION FOR CL$$0010 ON 6\/26\/07. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0155",
  "PROBLEM": "KNEW SNAP JOBS WOULD FAIL BECAUSE NEEDED 3 VOLSERS BUT THE CARDLIB ONLY POINTED TO 2. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CARDLIB (CLH0155) POINTED TO 2 VOLSERS BUT NEEDED 3. ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED CARDLIB CLH0155 TO MY LIBRARY AND ADDED A 3RD VOLSER, SO CARDLIB WAS NOW: CLHSI1 CLHSI2 CLDSKB FOR MORE DETAILS ON THIS SEE SOLUTION FOR CL$$0010 ON 6\/26\/07. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0060",
  "PROBLEM": "SOURCE MASK: CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH TARGET MASK: CL.SI.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH ALLOCATING TARGET DATA SET: CL.SI.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH NOT ENOUGH TARGET VOLUMES SUPPLIED - SOURCE:3 TARGET:2 RETURN CODE: 8 (8-7) FROM EXTENT_ALLOCATION FOR DSNAME: CL.SI. TARGET DATA SET CLEANUP - DSNAME: CL.SI.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH IDCAMS FAILED WITH RC: 00000008 WHILE DELETING DATA SET: CL.SI DELETE CL.SI.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH PURGE CC=8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CARDLIB (CLH0060) POINTED TO 2 VOLSERS BUT NEEDED 3. ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED CARDLIB CLH0060 TO MY LIBRARY AND ADDED A 3RD VOLSER, SO CARDLIB WAS NOW: CLHSI1 CLHSI2 CLDSK3 HAD OPS RESTART JOB IN JSTEP020.STEP0010. COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. FOR MORE DETAILS ON THIS SEE SOLUTION FOR CL$$0010 ON 6\/26\/07. *PROBLEM 11\/18\/09: SOURCE MASK: CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN TARGET MASK: CL.SI.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN IEC030I B37-04,IFG0554A,CL$$0060,STEP0010,SYS00021,226E, STOR14,0427041D,CL.SI.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN SOLUTION 11\/18\/09: DO A SNAP OF AGTFIN OFF TO THE SIDE ADD \/\/STEP0010.SYSIN DD DSN=TEST.CL.WAM.CARDLIB(CLH0060),DISP=SHR TO JCL AND RESTART. THIS REMOVED THE AGTFIN FILE FROM THE SNAP. **PROBLEM 12\/03\/09: SOURCE MASK: CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN TARGET MASK: CL.SI.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN IEC030I B37-04,IFG0554A,CL$$0060,STEP0010,SYS00021,226E, STOR14,0427041D,CL.SI.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN SOLUTION 12\/03\/09: 1. DID A REPRO OF SOURCE MASK FILE TO A TEST.CL.PSS FILE USING DEL\/DEF FOUND IN TEST.CL.PSS.CARDLIB(CLDOAFA) FOR THE OUTPUT TEST FILE. WHY? - IN CASE A RESTORE IS NEEDED OF THE AGTFIN FILE BEFORE THE CYCLE IS COMPLETED. 2. REMOVED THE AFTFIN FILE FROM THE SNAP JOB WITH OVER-RIDE \/\/STEP0010.SYSIN DD DSN=TEST.CL.PSS.CARDLIB(CLH0060), \/\/ DISP=SHR 3. HAD OPS RESTART THE JOB IN JSTEP0020.STEP0010 WITH THE ABOVE OVER-RIDE RESTART JOB COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY **PROBLEM 12\/04\/09: ACTUAL SAME PROBLEM AS 12\/03\/09 ABOVE SOLUTION 12\/04\/09: 1. CREATED A TEST CARDLIB FOR MEMBER CLH0060 & UPDATED IT WITH A NEW VOLUME FOR THE AGTFIN FILE (GOT NEW VOLUME FROM MARK WILLIAMS) 2. GAVE FOLLOWING OVER-RIDE TO OPERATOR FOR JOB CL$$0060 \/\/STEP0010.SYSIN DD DSN=TEST.CL.PSS.CARDLIB(CLH006X), \/\/ DISP=SHR 3. HAD OPS RESTART THE JOB IN JSTEP0020.STEP0010 WITH THE ABOVE OVER-RIDE 4. ALSO SUBMITTED LMR TO UPDATE VOLUME IN PRODUCTION RESTART JOB COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0010",
  "PROBLEM": "SOURCE MASK: CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH TARGET MASK: CL.SB.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH ALLOCATING TARGET DATA SET: CL.SB.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH NOT ENOUGH TARGET VOLUMES SUPPLIED - SOURCE:3 TARGET:2 RETURN CODE: 8 (8-7) FROM EXTENT_ALLOCATION FOR DSNAME: CL.SB. TARGET DATA SET CLEANUP - DSNAME: CL.SB.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH IDCAMS FAILED WITH RC: 00000008 WHILE DELETING DATA SET: CL.SB *** TIMEFINDER MF SNAP V5.6.0 (013) *** DELETE CL.SB.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEGH PURGE (CC = 8) ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CARDLIB (CLH0010) POINTED TO 2 VOLSERS BUT NEEDED 3. ONLY STEP0040 ABENDED, ALL OTHER STEPS PROCESSED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "LAVONNA NICHOLS HAD IDENTIFIED THE PROBLEM & CALLED ME. SHE INSTRUCTED ME TO USE THE COMMAND (QW S = CLDS*) WHILE IN ANY PDS FILE TO SEE THE VOLSERS AND HOW MUCH FREE SPACE WAS AVAILABLE. SEE COLUMN: VOLUME FREE % (14) - THEN USE THE LARGEST ONES (ONE PER SNAP JOB. THIS IS THE SB SNAP JOB. COPIED CARDLIB CLH0010 TO MY LIBRARY AND ADDED A 3RD VOLSER, SO CARDLIB WAS NOW: CLHSB1 CLHSB2 CLDSK2. HAD OPS RERUN STEP0040 ONLY POINTING TO MY CARDLIB (TEST.CL.SEC.CARDLIB(CLH0010). JOB COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0650",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C4 - TRYING TO CLOSE A FILE IN THAT WAS NEVER OPENED YOU ALSO SEE 27000+ LINES DISPLAYING NO CLIENT DATA. THIS JOB SHOULD ALWAYS HAVE DATA COMING OUT OF THE JOB. THE OUTPUT FILE ONLY HAD THE 2 HEADER RECORDS THAT ARE PRODUCED AT THE END OF THE JOB BEFORE THE CLOSES. A USER ABEND 4038 OCCURRED IN MODULE CEEPLPKA AT OFFSET X'BE560'. THERE WAS AN UNSUCCESSFUL CLOSE OF FILE OINTERPT IN MODULE D724CNSL PROGRAM D72INTER AT OFFSET X'18AA'. THE FILE STATUS CODE WAS 42, WHICH INDICATES: A CLOSE STATEMENT WAS ATTEMPTED FOR A FILE NOT IN THE OPEN MODE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "TABLE CLADMIN OAS_PRDCR_VW DID NOT HAVE ANY DATA IN IT. THIS TABLE IS SUPPORTED BY REPS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CONTACTED RON IRELAN TO FIND OUT WHY THE TABLE WAS EMPTY. THEY HAD PROBLEMS WITH THEIR RELOAD LAST NIGHT. ONCE THEIR JOB FINISHED RE-RAN CL$$0650. COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. CHECK THE STATUS OF JOB AGCY3002. THIS JOB NEEDS TO BE FINISHED SUCCESSFUL IN ORDER FOR OUR JOB TO COMPLETE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$IIAM",
  "PROBLEM": "CC8 SPACE PROBLEMS ",
  "ANALYSIS": "OPS CALLED ME ABOUT THIS, THEN CALLED BACK TO SAY PER THE DOC, THE DASD PEOPLE ARE IN CONTROL OF THIS. SO I WAS OFF THE HOOK...UNTIL 2:30 AM WHEN LAVONNA CALLED TO SAY SHE COULD NOT GET IT TO WORK AND NEEDED TO KNOW WHAT I WANTED HER TO DO. I REFERRED HER TO MANAGER ON CALL WHO INSTRUCTED HER TO: ",
  "SOLUTION": "USE THE SA VERSION TO RECREATE THE AUSEGH FILE, THEN RUN A REPRO TO BACK IT UP (HAD TO DO TO TAPE), THEN DELETE REDEFINE, USING THEIR CONTROL CARDS AND REPRO-ING BACK IN. THIS IS THE OLD FASHION WAY OF REORGANIZING A FILE. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "CYCLE WAS FINISHED BUT JOB WAS STILL WAITING. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB HAD DEPENDENCIES ON SEVERAL POLICY PAGE JOBS AND ONE LIST BILL JOB, BUT THESE WERE NOT SCHEDULED TO RUN IN THIS CYCLE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD OPS REMOVE DEPENDENCIES AND JOB WAS RELEASED. JOB RAN SUCCESSFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "JOB ABENDED WITH JCL ERROR. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB HAD RESTART STEP0130. BUT SHOULD NOT HAVE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD OPS REMOVE RESTART COMMAND AND RESTART JOB FROM TOP. JOB RAN SUCCESSFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0838",
  "PROBLEM": "CRITERIA CHECK ERROR. CUSTOMER FILE DVCUSTLIFE SEGMENT DVPOLSM REACHED END OF FILE OR HAS NOT BEENREAD. TRIGGER: 1, PRODUCT: AUL WHOLELIFE POLICYPAGES, COMPANY-CD: 00, CONTRACT-NUM: 0710023630 CURRENT RULE DESCRIPTION: STATE SPECIFIC RIDERS TOTAL ERRORS: 1. TOTAL DOCUMENTS PROCESSED: 0. AVERAGE RATE: 0.000 ELAPSED SECONDS PER DOCUMENT. RUN TERMINATED DUE TO ERRORS. NOT ALL DOCUMENTS WERE PROCESSED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "BAD POLICY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED PROD FILES TO MY OWN LIBRARIES AN REMOVED BAD POLICY. PUT IN OVERRIDES AND SENT FOLLOWING EMAIL TO M.AUL.SYS.COMPUTEROPERATIONS TO RESTART JOB FROM TOP. (START EMAIL) PLEASE RESTART CL$$0838 FROM THE TOP USING THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDES: \/\/STEP0010.IEXTR DD DSN=TEST.CL.SEC.BASEB.DPFSEXTR.P060507 \/\/STEP0030.ILIFECST DD DSN=TEST.CL.SEC.DLS.LIFECUST.SORT.DUPOUT \/\/STEP0060.SORTIN DD DSN=TEST.CL.SEC.DLS.POLSUMM.SORT.DUPOUT \/\/STEP0080.SEQ1 DD DSN=TEST.CL.SEC.DLS.LIFECUST.SORT.DUPOUT \/\/STEP0080.SEQ7 DD DSN=TEST.CL.SEC.DLS.RIDER.SORT.DUPOUT \/\/STEP0080.SEQ11 DD DSN=TEST.CL.SEC.DLS.BENE.SORT.DUPOUT \/\/STEP0090.ICUSTFIL DD DSN=TEST.CL.SEC.DLS.LIFECUST.SORT.DUPOUT (END EMAIL) JOB SUCCESSFULLY COMPLETED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0838",
  "PROBLEM": "IEF861I FOLLOWING RESERVED DATA SET NAMES UNAVAILABLE IEF863I DSN = CL.VSAM.DLS.LIFECUST CL$$0838 RC = 04 IEF099I JOB CL$$0838 WAITING FOR DATA SETS ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PROD VSAM FILE WAS OPEN AND HAS TO BE CLOSED FOR THE POLICY PAGE JOBS TO RUN. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CALLED PCD AND HAD THEM CLOSE THE FILE. (SOLUTION SAME FOR ALL POLICY PAGE JOBS - CL$$0836, CL$$0837, 838, 839) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0440",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND S378 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "KNEW THE PROBLEM HAD TO DO WITH SPACE. CALLED MARK WILLIAMS. HE SAID THAT WITH IT BEING MONTH END, THE JOB PROBABLY WAS NEEDING SPACE IT COULDN'T GET. SINCE THIS JOB RUNS DAILY WITH NO PROBLEMS WE COULD PROBABLY GET AWAY WITH JUST RERUNNING THE JOB. BUT IF WE WANTED TO MAKE SURE FOR THE FUTURE, WE SHOULD PUT SORTWK IN THE PROC FOR THIS STEP. ",
  "SOLUTION": "LOGGED INTO FIRECALL AND DELETED LATEST GDG OF CL.CL$$0440.PEANSWRS.EXTPOLEX. RERAN JOB FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0850",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND S001 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED AT THE 5 INPUT FILES FOR THIS STEP AND ONE WAS EMPTY...CL.CL$$0850.PWACC. ",
  "SOLUTION": "LOGGED INTO FIRECALL AND DELETED THE 5 INPUT GDGS CREATED IN THE PREVIOUS STEPS USED IN STEP0035. CL.CL$$0850.ABCAUD CL.CL$$0850.AUDACC CL.CL$$0850.GAACC CL.CL$$0850.GBACC CL.CL$$0850.PWACC SUBMITTED A JCL MAINTENANCE FORM TO PCD TO ADD THE OVERRIDE... \/\/STEP00XX.OACCEXT DD SPACE=(27966,(0,350),RLSE) (WHERE XX IS THE STEP THAT CREATED THE EMPTY DATASET.) HAD PCD RESTART JOB FROM TOP. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "SIBBATCH EXECUTED - COND CODE 0008 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "IN ABENDING STEP DO F EXPECTED TO FIND WHERE THE SYNTAX ERROR IN THE CARD IS NOTE THERE CAN BE MORE THAN ONE SYNTAX ERROR IN A SNAP CARD EMCP001I SNAP DATASET ( SOURCE (TEST.CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AGENT EMCP001I TARGET (TEST.CL.SB.VSAM.BASEOL.AGENT EMCP001I VOLUME(TEST01) HCPYMODE(SHARED) - EMCP010E * EMCP016E RIGHT PAREN EXPECTED; FOUND: - EMCP033E SKIPPING TO END OF COMMAND ",
  "SOLUTION": "NEEDED TO EDIT CARD TEST.CL.CARDLIB(CLH0010) TO REMOVE EXTRA COMMA ON VOLUME LINE VOLUME(TEST01) HCPYMODE(SHARED) - - "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0014",
  "PROBLEM": "USER COMPLETION CODE=4039 REASON CODE=00000000 IEF450I CL$$0014 STEP0070 CL$$0014 - ABEND=S000 U4038 REASON =00000001. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "INPUT FILE PAC.CL.OCLPYMTL(-0) WAS EMPTY. PROBLEM IS RELATED TO HOW EMPTY FILES ARE HANDLED NOW WITH THE NEW STORAGE BOX IMPLEMENTED 5\/29\/07. PER SANDI, BRETT SMITH WILL NEED TO FIX THIS ON THE PAC$ SIDE. PER BRETT, THIS FILE IS EMPTY AFTER THE 28TH DAY OF THE MONTH. ISSUE CL7590 CREATED AS A BLANKET ISSUE TO FIX PROBLEM WHEN ULTIM CREATES AN EMPTY FILE AND THAT FILE IS ACCESSED BY ANOTHER PROCESS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "JOB WAS FORCED COMPLETE WITH NO FURTHER ACTION. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0839",
  "PROBLEM": "IEC020I 001-4,CL$$0839,STEP0076,IDDCARE,2772,STOR43, IEC020I CL.DLS.CARECUST.SORT.DUPOUT IEC020I DCB EROPT=ABE OR AN INVALID CODE, AND\/OR NO SYNAD EXIT SPECIFIED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "INPUT FILE WAS EMPTY. PROBLEM IS RELATED TO HOW EMPTY FILES ARE HANDLED NOW WITH THE NEW STORAGE BOX IMPLEMENTED 5\/29\/07. IF THIS BEGINS TO OCCUR FREQUENTLY, THEN WE NEED TO MODIFY THE JOB TO CHECK FOR EMPTY FILES. ",
  "SOLUTION": "JOB WAS FORCED COMPLETE WITH NO FURTHER ACTION. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0838",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND=S000 U4038 COND CODE SFC6 08\/18\/08*** A LOGIC ERROR OCCURRED. NEITHER FILE STATUS NOR DECLARATIVE WAS SPECIFIED FOR FILE ILIFECST IN PROGRAM D724DVAL AT RELATIVE LOCATION X'09FA'. THE STATUS CODE WAS 46. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "POLICY 0710070440 WAS ON THE INPUT PAGES TRANSACTION FILE BUT IT DID NOT APPEAR ON THE CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR(0) FILE POLICY 0710070400 WAS NOT ON THE INPUT PAGES TRANSACTION FILE BUT WAS ON THE THE CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR(0) FILE 08\/18\/08**POLICY 0720020020 WAS ON CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR FILE BUT NOT ON THE INPUT PAGES TRANS FILE. 02\/08\/07**POLICY 0710015000 WAS ON CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR FILE BUT NOT ON THE INPUT PAGES TRANS FILE. 06\/25\/07 *POLICY 0710069320 WAS ON CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR FILE BUT NOT ON THE INPUT PAGES TRANS FILE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED FILE TO TEST.CL.PSS.P0020.SORTOUT.PRODWL.D051907 REMOVED THE TWO POLICIES LISTED ABOVE AND RAN THE PAGES OUT OF MY LIBRARY - FORCE COMPLETED THE PROD JOB. 06\/25\/07 *COPIED FILE TO TEST.CL.SEC.BASEB.DPFSEXTR.P062507 REMOVED POLICY AND HAD JOB RESTARTED WITH OVERRIDE. 06\/25\/07 *NOTE: POLICY SHOWS INCOMPLETE ON CICS REGION "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0839",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND=S000 U4038 COND CODE SFC6 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THERE ARE NO INPUT RECORDS HOWEVER THIS PROGRAM EXPECTED SOME RECORDS ",
  "SOLUTION": "FORCE COMPLETED THE PRODUCTION JOB "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0106",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP0100 ABENDED IEA705I ERROR DURING FREEMAIN SYS CODE = 378-1C CL$$0106 STEP0100 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PROC AND CARD HAD NOT CHANGED IN A LONG TIME. 1C A USER HAS REQUESTED THAT STORAGE AT VIRTUAL ADDRESS 0 B THIS CAN HAPPEN IF THE USER INTENDED AN ENTIRE SUBPOOL, INCORRECTLY SPECIFIED A NON-ZERO LENGTH WITH AN ADDRESS ZERO LENGTH MUST BE SPECIFIED ON A SUBPOOL FREEMAIN OR S RELEASE. ANOTHER POSSIBILITY IS THAT THE USER HAS SPECIF WRONG ADDRESS. THIS MESSAGE IMPLIES A MEMORY PROBLEM. SINCE NON OF OUR SORT STEPS HAVE INDIVIDUAL REGION CARDS, WE PROBABLY DON'T NEED TO ADD ONE. THE REGION CARD IS IN THE JCL AND SHOULD BE ENOUGH. DECIDED TO RERUN THE SORT STEP IN UNIT TEST LAND. THE UNIT TEST SORT ENDED OK. SO THIS IMPLIES THE ORIGINAL JOB JUST COULDN'T GET THE MEMORY IT NEEDED AT THE TIME. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTARTED CL$$0106 IN STEP0100. JOB ENDED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0866",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND=S0C7 +IDI0002I MODULE D7240082, PROGRAM D7240082, SOURCE LINE # 10509: ABEND S0C7 (DATA EXCEPTION) ",
  "ANALYSIS": "03\/31\/2007 - POLICY 3465093109 HAD STMT DATE OF 1\/1\/-6 - 12\/31\/06. THESE ARE QUARTERLY STMTS NOT ANNUAL STATEMENTS. ANALYSIS: 02\/21\/2008 - FOR POLICY 3465099400 THE REQUESTED DATES WERE 1\/1\/2006 - 12\/31\/2006 & 1\/1\/2007 - 12\/31\/07 THESE ARE QUARTERLY STMTS NOT ANNUAL STATEMENTS. ANALYSIS: 06\/18\/2008 - FOR POLICY 3465013950 THE REQUESTED DATES WERE 8\/13\/1999 - 12\/1\/2003 THESE ARE QUARTERLY STMTS NOT ANNUAL STATEMENTS. ANALYSIS: 07\/03\/2010 - FOR A HANDFUL OF POLICIES, MORE THAN 500 TRANSACTIONS WERE PRESENT FOR THE TIME PERIOD. WE HAVE A LIMIT OF NO MORE THAN 500 OCCURRENCES IN COBOL PROGRAM D7240082. VIEW IDIREPRT: SEE \"PAGE3-LINES OCCURS 500 INDEXED BY PAGE3-IDX...\" ANALYSIS: 10\/02\/2010 - MORE THAN 500 TRANSACTIONS WERE PRESENT FOR THE TIME PERIOD. WE HAVE A LIMIT OF NO MORE THAN 500 OCCURRENCES IN COBOL PROGRAM D7240082. FOUND A CHANGE IN PANLIB UNDER CL9628. AFTER DELETING ONE POLICY AND ABENDING ON THE NEXT RECORD AND SEEING MORE WITH > 500 RECORDS DECIDED TO USE THE CODE IN PANLIB. COMPILED TO SLJ.OJBLIB, LINKED INTO TEST.CL.PROD.LOADLIB AND ADDED TEST.CL.SLJ.PROCLIB TO THE JOB TO POINT TO THE NEW VERSION. JOB ENDED SUCCESSFULLY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "03\/31\/2007 - REMOVED POLICY FROM INPUT FILE AND HAD JOB RESTARTED FROM TOP. FINISHED OK. CONTACTED USER WHO SAID THEY ARE NOT SUPPOSE TO ORDER STATEMENTS LIKE THAT BUT A NEW GIRL HAD. NO FUTURE RESEARCH NEEDED AT THIS TIME. SOLUTION: 02\/21\/2008 - REMOVED POLICY FROM INPUT FILE AND HAD JOB RESTARTED FROM TOP. FINISHED OK. TRIAGE.IND TO TALK TO THE USERS SOLUTION: 06\/18\/2008 - THIS WAS THE ONLY POLICY ON THE INPUT FILE SO THE JOB WAS FORCE COMPLETED. TRIAG.IND TO TALK TO THE USERS. SOLUTION: 07\/03\/2010 - REMOVED POLICIES FROM THE INPUT FILE; RERAN FROM STEP0020, WITH OVERRIDE: \"STEP0020.SORTIN DD DSN=CL.CL$$0866.VUL.OTAGTHIS(-0)\" - ALERTED TRIAGE OF THE PROBLEM (VIA EMAIL). THE ERRORED STATEMENTS WERE GENERATED USING A MANUALLY-RUN BATCH JCL JOB. - A FIX IS IN THE WORKS TO PREVENT THIS PROBLEM FROM OCCURRING IN THE FUTURE! SOLUTION: 10\/02\/2010 - REMOVED POLICIES FROM THE INPUT FILE USING TEST.CL.TOOLS(WAAPDRP1) ABEND IN THE SAME STEP NEXT POLICY. FOUND A CHANGE IN PANLIB UNDER CL9628 AFTER DELETING ONE POLICY AND ABENDING ON THE NEXT RECORD. COMPILED FROM PANLIB TO SLJ.OJBLIB, LINKED INTO TEST.CL.PROD.LOADLIB AND ADDED TEST.CL.SLJ.PROCLIB TO THE JOB TO POINT TO THE NEW VERSION. JOB ENDED SUCCESSFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0020",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB ABENDING IN SOC7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "POLICY 0620303550 WAS GETTING A SOC07. ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED FILE TO TEST.CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.GV4355 EDIT PROD FILE REMOVING POLICY LISTED ABOVE OPS RESTARTED JOB USING CONTROL-R - COMPLETED --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! SUCCESSFULLY SENT REPLY TO 'CL ALERT'. 'CL$$0020 ABENDED DUE TO POLICY 0620303550. NO PAGES WILL BE GENERATED FOR THIS POLICY.' "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0035",
  "PROBLEM": "USER COMPLETION CODE=4039 REASON CODE=00000000 THIS HAS ABENDED SEVERAL TIMES DUE TO SLOW MAINFRAME RESPONSE TIME AND THE PENDING RECORD BEING UPDATED AT TIME OF RUN. I WAS INSTRUCTED TO KEEP RESTARTING IN STEP0010. JOB WAS SUBMITTED A FINAL TIME: 07\/27\/07 22:00. JOB COMPLETED WITH GOOD CONDITION CODES. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOUND POLICY IN DUMP - 2052350720 0620293340 - 03\/12\/07 5200000190 - 03\/12\/07 0710066930 - 03\/19\/07 0620296950 - 03\/22\/07 2453418700 - 05\/08\/07 0620301550 - 05\/10\/07 5820001440 - 05\/23\/07 0710007610 - 07\/17\/07 0620310830 - 07\/27\/07 PENDING RECORD WAS LIKELY BEING UPDATED AT THE TIME OF THIS RUN. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTARTED JOB IN STEP0010. FINISHED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0008",
  "PROBLEM": "+UNABLE TO RETRIEVE STUB POOL RECORD +- - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - +IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V5R1M0 (UK00798 2005\/02\/23) INVOKED BY IDIXDCAP +IDI0082E DB2 CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQLALLOCCONNECT SQLERROR 235 SQLRC=-1 {DB2 FOR OS\/390}{ODBC DRIVER} SQLSTATE=58004 ERRLOC=2:170:10 CAF \"OPEN\" FAILED USING DB2 SYSTEM:DB2P AND PLAN:DSNACLI RC=0C AND REASON=00F30040 $HASP375 CL$$0008 ESTIMATED LINES EXCEEDED $HASP375 CL$$0008 ESTIMATE EXCEEDED BY 25,000 LINES IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 334 USER COMPLETION CODE=4039 REASON CODE=00000000 A USER ABEND 0001 OCCURRED IN MODULE D724PAIN CSECT CKABEND AT OFFSET X'116' THE ABEND WAS CAUSED BY MACHINE INSTRUCTION 0DEF (BRANCH AND SAVE) IN MO D724PAIN CSECT CKETRINV AT OFFSET X'B48'. EVENT FAIL MODULE PROGRAM EP # TYPE POINT NAME NAME NAME EVENT LOCATION (*) -- ------------ ----- -------- -------- -------- ---------------------- 1 CALL DSNECP10 DSNECP10 N\/A P+206 2 CALL DSNECP10 DSNECP19 DSNECP19 P+1710 3 LINK DSNECP10 DSNECP16 N\/A P+554 4 CALL D724PAIN D724PAIN D724PAIN P+E10 5 CALL D724PAIN CKETRGET CKETRGET P+FC4 6 CALL ***** D724PAIN CKETRINV CKETRINV P+B48 7 ABEND U0001 D724PAIN CKABEND CKABEND P+116 8 CALL CEEPLPKA N\/A CEEHDSP E+3C6C 9 ABEND U4039 CEEPLPKA N\/A CEEHSDMP E+D4 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PREVIOUS ABENDS IN CL$$0008 HAVE LOOKED IDENTICAL TO THIS ONE EXCEPT THAT THEY OCCURED IN PROGRAM CKETRGET. THOSE ABENDS WERE CAUSED BY A USER UPDATING A POLICY WHEN THE PROGRAM TRIES TO READ IT WHICH TRIGGERS A CLIENT ABEND. CKETRINV HAS HAD NEARLY IDENTICAL ABENDS IN CL$$0035 WHICH WAS CAUSED BY THE SAME SITUATION. CKETRINV IS CALLED FROM CKETRGET. ",
  "SOLUTION": "ASSUMING THIS IS A SITUATION WHERE A USER WAS UPDATING A POLCIY AND CAUSED A CLIENT ABEND, I HAD OPS RERUN CL$$0008 FROM THE TOP WITH THIS OVERRIDE WITH TODAY'S DATE (IT IS BEFORE THE 8:30 DATE CHANGE TIME) BECAUSE OF POTENTIAL CLIENT UPDATES MADE THIS MORNING: \/\/STEP0020.PARMDATE DD * 03-02-07 AN ABEND WITH THIS MESSAGE ENSUED: $HASP708 CL$$0008 PARMDATE OPEN FAILED RC=03 DATA SET ALREADY OPENED DSNAME=ACFSUBID.CL$$0008.JOB01371.D0000101.? IEC141I 013-C0,IGG0199G,CL$$0008,STEP0020,PARMDATE ASSUMING THAT THE DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) OF THE OVERRIDEN CARD WAS CUASING A PROBLEM, I CREATED A NEW PARMDATE CARD AND HAD OPS TRY THIS OVERRIDE: \/\/STEP0020.PARMDATE DD DSN=TEST.CL.WHH.CARDLIB(PARMDATE), \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) THIS WORKED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1160",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND=S04C U0000 REASON=00000000 117 +IAMW04 DD=VSAM3 OPEN ERROR - DATASET NOT AVAILABLE, IN USE BY JOB CICSD + VSAM ERROR - FILE=VSAM3 , INCODE=1, OUTCODE=9, R15=08, ERRCODE=00A8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JCL HAS THIS OVERRIDE: \/\/STEP0010.VSAM3 DD DSN=CL.VSAM.BASER.ISSUEAGE,DISP=SHR ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD OPS RELEASE THE ISSUEAGE FILE FROM CICSD. SINCE STEP0010 IS THE FIRST STEP OF THE JOB, I HAD OPS RESTART FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "S04C WITH ABEND806 CSV003I REQUESTED MODULE DSNHDECP NOT FOUND CSV028I ABEND806-04 JOBNAME=CL$$0011 STEPNAME=STEP0010 IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 825 SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=806 REASON CODE=00000004 TIME=19.00.02 SEQ=13042 CPU=0000 ASID=0090 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DSNHDECP IS DB2 MODULE (DSN INDICATES DB2) AND WAS MISSING FROM LINK. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD OPS CONTACT DB2 ON-CALL PERSON. HE INDICATED THIS MODULE HAD BEEN REPLACED EARLIER THAT DAY, BUT NO NOTIFICATION HAD BEEN MADE TO CYBERLIFE TEAM. DB2 TEAM HAD TO SCRAMBLE AND GET THIS PROGRAM RESTORED. ONCE THEY WERE DONE, OPERATIONS RESTARTED JOB FROM TOP. ASKED OPS TO BUMP UP PRIORITY SO JOB WOULD FINISH IN TIME SO WOULD NOT DELAY NIGHTLY CYCLE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0837",
  "PROBLEM": "GOT COMPUSET ERROR IN CSET1: CMP000038-E: LINE 23,198; CIRCA OUTPUT PAGE 18 IN SECONDARY INPUT CMP000050-E: ERROR 16 AT CHARACTER POSITION 37: RULE PARAMETER IS NEGATIVE. ( 23198) <COLOR,3,0,0,0>`<BOX,0,0,1,0,0,1,0,0> * ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ERROR WAS ON LE-274 FOR PA. THERE IS A LINE AT END OF THE FOLLOWING STATEMENT, 'CHECK IF THIS ENDORSEMENT SUPERSEDES A A PRIOR ROTH IRA ENDORSEMENT ____' HOWEVER, THE UNDERSCORE _______ IS DEFINED AS A BOX. THE ERROR WAS: RULE PARAMETER IS ZERO OR NEGATIVE. THE BOX COMMAND NEEDS A WIDTH AND\/OR DEPT BUT HAS NETHER. SO NEED TO CHANGE THIS CODE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "BOX COMMAND WAS REMOVED, TEST RAN. DLS PIECE NEEDS MIGRATED UP TO PERMANENTLY FIX. NOTE: ERROR CAN BE FOUND IN CL.DLS.ANNCUST.IVA02.TAGGED "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0839",
  "PROBLEM": "MODULE NOT FOUND CKSPHBU2 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS IS AN ASSIST TO CKVSAMIO AND RESIDES IN PROD.CL.LOADLIB ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD PROD.CL.LOADLIB ADDED TO PROD.SCHD.JCLLIB "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0838",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND=S000 U4038 REASON=00000001 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "2 NEW WHOLE LIFE POLICIES CAME THROUGH FOR POLICY PAGES, BUT THEIR ISSUE HAS NOT YET BEEN INSTALLED IN PRODUCTION. THE LIFECUST DLS FILE DID NOT HAVE THE POLICIES AS IT IS NOT YET INSTALLED, BUT THE DPFS RECORDS DID EXIST. THIS COULD HAPPEN AGAIN PRIOR TO THE DLS CHANGES BEING INSTALLED INTO PRODUCTION. AFFECTED POLICIES: 0720000010 AND 0720000030 (2\/9) 0720000030 & 0720000290 (2\/13) 0720000070 & 0720000540 (2\/14) 0720000700 & 0720000730 (2\/15) 0720000270, 0720000530, 0720000550 (2\/20) 0720000380 & 0720000400 (2\/27 FOR 2\/26) 0720000560, 0720000750, 0720000980, 0720001210 (2\/27) 072000-- 0080,0250,0260,0380,0520,1200,1350 (2\/28) 072000-- 0440,0640,1280,1290,1300,1430 (3\/01) 0720000- 570,580,870,940,950 (3\/05 FOR 3\/2) 072000 - 0600,1260,1450,1470, & (3\/05 CON'T) 07100 - 64290, 61460, 64190 ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED THE DPFS FILE TO A TEST VERSION, DELETED RECORDS FOR THE POLICIES FROM THE TEST VERSION. RERAN JOB FROM THE TOP USING THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDE: \/\/STEP0010.IEXTR DD DSN=TEST.CL.LKM.BASEB.DPFSEXTR.G4236 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0809",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND=S04C ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DETERMINED THE PROBLEM POLICY WAS 2453377580 BY DOING A FIND ON \"CURRENT\" IN THE DUMPS. THIS POLICY WAS IN THE DUMPS MULTIPLE TIMES. COPIED THE POLICY FILE TO A TEST VERSION, DELETED ABOVE POLICY FROM TEST VERSION, RAN STEP10 IN MY WORLD. JOB FINISHED OK. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RERAN JOB FROM THE TOP USING THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDE: \/\/STEP0010.VSAM1 DD DSN=TEST.CL.VSAM.SHKBKG.BASEOL.POLICY, \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0867",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP=STEP0030 PGM=D7240081 ABENDED - COND CODE S0C7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "POLICY 2453280900 IS BEING WORKED ON BY SOMEONE ON THE INFORCE TEAM AND KATHY HANNAH SAID THEY PULL THE CONFIRM AND STMT EACH MORNING FROM THE OUTPUT. IF THIS HAPPENS ON THIS POLICY AGAIN, CHECK WITH KATHY ON THE POLICY NUMBER TO SEE IF THIS IS STILL OK TO BYPASS. OUT IN VISTA PLUS YOU CAN SEE WHERE THE TEAMMEMBER IS REPRODUCING MULTIPLE REPRINTS OF THE QUARTERLY STATEMENT EVERY FEW NIGHTS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "I COPIED THE FILE FROM PRODUCTION DOWN TO TEST AND EDITED TEST.CL.CL$$0867.IVA.OTAGTHIS.P012607 REMOVING THE HUNDREDS OF LINES FOR THIS POLICY. THE OTHER THREE POLICIES ON THE FILE ALL HAD FLAGS TO NOT PRINT THEIR STATEMENTS ANYWAYS. JOB WAS FORCED OK. ADDITIONAL INFO ON 1\/31\/2007: SAME POLICY AS ABOVE. DROPPED THE BAD RECORDS FOR THIS POLICY FROM A COPY OF THE IVA.OTAGTHIS FILE AND HAD PCD RESTART JOB IN STEP0020 WITH OVERRIDE FOR EDITED FILE. \/\/STEP0020.SORTIN DD DSN=TEST.CL.XXX.CL$$0867.IVA.OTAGTHIS PER KAH, THE SERVICE REP MAY NEED THE MONTH OF FEBRUARY TO COMPLETE ALL OF THE ACTIVITY THAT IS TO BE REBUILT FOR THIS POLICY. THE ACTIVITY THAT IS CREATED IS EXCEEDING THE 500 RECORD LIMIT THAT IS CODED IN D7240081. THE 500 RECORD LIMIT IS FINE FOR NORMAL PROCESSING. ADDITIONAL INFO ON 11\/16\/2007 (P1JIF): 3 POLICIES APPEARED ON CL.CL$$0867.IVA.OTAGTHIS.G1708V00; ONE OF THOSE CONTAINED 633 RECORDS (MAX ALLOWED IS 500) - POLICY 2453318800. THIS IS WHY THE JOB ABENDED. *** LOOK AT THE INPUT FILE: CL.CL$$0860.IVA.OTAGTHIS(0) AND CHECK *** THE DATE PARAMETERS FOR THAT POLICY. COLUMN 82 FOR 16 BYTES: *** 0101200812312008, THIS IS A QUARTERLY STATEMENT BUT THE INPUT *** PARAMETERS ARE FOR AN ENTIRE YEAR. NOT A VALID TIME PERIOD. *** MOST LIKELY THIS POLICY IS BEING REBUILT. I SPOKE WITH KARLA REMEIKA WHO CHECKED ON THIS POLICY AND ANOTHER (2453313630) - THESE WERE TRIGGERED TO CREATE BECAUSE OF YESTERDAY'S SURRENDER TRANSACTIONS. SHE CHECKED WITH THE USERS - STATEMENTS ARE NOT NEEDED. I CHECKED WITH HEIDI WEIS ABOUT POLICY 2453325180 (THIS WAS A SURRENDER AND A DEATH CLAIM). SHE SAID THAT WE DO NOT NEED THE STATEMENT. I ASKED DON IN OPERATIONS TO FORCE COMPLETE THE JOB (CL$$0867 J761). "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0035",
  "PROBLEM": "USER COMPLETION CODE=4039 REASON CODE=00000000 1\/16\/08: PROBLEM: ABEND=S000 U0001 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOUND POLICY IN DUMP - 0620281530 PENDING RECORD WAS LIKELY BEING UPDATED AT THE TIME OF THIS RUN. 1\/16\/08: ANALYSIS: MOST LIKELY BEING UPDATED AT TIME OF RUN ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTARTED JOB IN STEP0020. FINISHED OK. 1\/16\/08: SOLUTION: RESTARTED JOB FROM TOP. FINISHED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0420",
  "PROBLEM": "-STEP=STEP0020 PGM=IKJEFT1B FLUSHED - COND CODE 0000 RC=000 IEF453I CL$$0420 - JOB FAILED - JCL ERROR - TIME=00.18.08 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SEQUEN - SPACE REQUESTED NOT AVAILABLE SEQUEN - SPACE=(CYL,(2000,200),RLSE) ",
  "SOLUTION": "ADDED THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDE: \/\/STEP0020.SEQUEN DD SPACE=(CYL,(1700,200),RLSE) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0835",
  "PROBLEM": "RECEIVED CC16 IN ULTIM SAYING HAD A COMPILER ERR. SEE CL$$0838 ERROR FROM 11\/10\/2006 FOR MORE INFO. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CL$$0835 - THE INPUT FILE WAS EMPTY. CL$$0838 - INPUT FILE NOT EMPTY SO NOT SURE WHY ULTIM STEP RECEIVED ERROR - THIS JOB DID PRODUCE 7 SETS OF POLICY PAGES IN STEP0110. DISCUSSED WITH RHONDA WHO INDICATED THAT SOMETIMES ULTIMS GET THE CC16 IF A FIELD IS EXPECTIN VALUES BUT IS BLANK (EX. ADDRESSES FROM ALIS SYSTEM) ",
  "SOLUTION": "DECIDED TO FORCE JOBS COMPLETE SINCE ONE FILE WAS EMPTY AND THE OTHER JOB CREATED OUTPUT. VERIFIED NOTHING HAD CHANGED IN JOBS, PROCS, AND ULTIMS FOR MANY MONTHS. IF HAPPENS AGAIN, MAY WANT TO RESEARCH FURTHER. 01\/04\/07 - HAPPENED AGAIN BUT SAME RESULTS; OUPUT WAS CREATED 05\/25\/07 - INPUT FILES NOT EMPTY. FORCED JOBS OKAY. REFER TO CL$$0838 ERROR FROM 11\/10\/2006 FOR DETAILS. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "ECOMMERCE HAD A PROBLEM WITH THEIR LOAD JOB ON 12\/6 AND 12\/7. THEY NEEDED CYUVLOD.TXT RESENT FOR EACH DAY. THIS FILE CONTAINS UNIT VALUES. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS FILE IS CREATED IN CL$$0010. ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPY THE APPROPRIATE GENERATION OF CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES(GDG) TO A DISK FILE. SEND THE FILE AS AN ATTACHMENT IN A EMAIL TO THE REQUESTER. IF THEY NEED MULITPLE DAYS, SEND SEPARATE FILES FOR EACH DAY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0012",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND=S000 U0001 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CHECKED SYSUT2 IN STEP0040 AND NOTICED THE FOLLOWING FF0018 - INPUT DATE RANGE INVALID CALCULATED DATE NOT EQUAL LOW DATE RANGE DATE ON ALL OF THE FUNDS. LAST WEEK WAS THANKSGIVING. THE DATE RANGE SHOULD HAVE BEEN FROM 11\/23 THRU 11\/27. THE FILE WE GOT FROM OMNI HAD FROM 11\/25 THRU 11\/27. *(4\/13\/09) LOOKED AT SYSUT2 IN STEP0040 & SAW THIS MESSAGE ON *SOME OF THE FUNDS: * 'FF0018 - INPUT DATE RANGE INVALID' * 'LAST VALUATION DATE NOT LESS THAN LOW DATE RANGE DATE' *LAST WEEK INVOLVED A HOLIDAY (GOOD FRIDAY) WHERE NO CYCLE WAS RAN. *CHECKED PREV GEN OF CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES OR (-1 GEN) & SAW THAT *FUND DATE WAS 04092009 THRU 04092009. SO THESE DATES SHOULD *BE 04102009 THRU 04132009. ",
  "SOLUTION": "USING FIRECALL I CHANGED ALL 11252006 IN COLUMN 15 TO 11232006 IN FILE CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES.G1888V00, HAD OPS RUN CL$$R012, AND THEN HAD OPS RERUN CL$$0012 FROM THE TOP. *SOLUTION (4\/13\/09): USING FIRECALL, CHANGED ALL 04092009 IN *COLUMN 15 TO 04102009 IN FILE CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES.G2488V00. *(16 LINES GOT CHANGED). HAD OPS RUN CL$$R012 & AFTER COMPLETED *HAD OPS RERUN CL$$0012 FROM THE TOP. **SOLUTION (11\/30\/09) USING FIRECALL, CHANGED ALL 11282009 IN **COLUMN 15 TO 11262009 IN FILE CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES.G2648V00. **(16 LINES GOT CHANGED). HAD OPS RUN CL$$R012 & AFTER COMPLETED **HAD OPS RERUN CL$$0012 FROM THE TOP. **SOLUTION (12\/03\/13) CLIPSP500 HAD AN ERROR EARLIER IN THE EVENING. RESOURCE CONTENTION ON THE LAST RUN DATE FILE. WE USED A SAMPLE CARD PROVIDED TO CREATE CL.FUND.PRICES.INDEXES BUT ONE OF THE DATES HAD THE WRONG YEAR V00SPFUND10011120320121203201201795154684 (2012 WAS WRONG YEAR), SO CL$$0012 HAD A PROBLEM DUE TO DUE THE INCORRECT DATE PRESENT FOR SPFUND IN THE PRICES FILE - CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES.G3662V00 THE SAMPLE CARD IS MENTION IN THIS DOCUMENT: SOURCE: K:\\INDSYS\\PRODUCT DEVELOPERS TEAM\\PRODUCT DESIGN DOCUMENTATION (CYBERLIFE) \\INDEX ANNUITY\\INDEX ANNUITY S AND P CLOSING PRICE FEED.DOCX TO CORRECT CL$$0012 COPIED - CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES.G3662V00 TO TEST.CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES.PRD1203 USING FIRECALL ID - P1AADB, CHANGED THE DATE FOR SPFUND FROM 12032012 TO 12032013 IN THE ORIGINAL FILE. ASKED OPS TO RUN THE RESTORE JOB - CL$$R012 ONCE THE RESTORE JOB ENDED OK, ASKED OPS TO RUN THE JOB CL$$0012 FROM THE TOP. JOB ENDED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0838",
  "PROBLEM": "CC16 IN STEP0010 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ULTIM HAD THIS MESSAGE IN THE STEP'S OUTPUT: ---> NOTE POS 16 (086-A) WARNING: DECIMAL ALIGNMENT DEACTIVATED I LOOKED AT THE FILE, AND FOUND THAT THE LAST 2 LINES ON THE CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR(0) FILE ARE: 000000346511380003045000972VSLS100 5099LTCJ 01 ---> 545001172090001 00 THE LAST LINE IS THE PROBLEM. THIS POLICY'S ENTRY HAS NO COMPANY CODE VALUES IN THE FIRST 6 POSITIONS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "I COPIED THE CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR(0) AND THEN DELETED THE BAD RECORD FROM THE FILE. I HAD OPS RERUN THE JOB FROM THE TOP. NOTE: THIS ERROR DOES NOT STOP THE JOB. I DID NOT CATCH THIS PRIOR TO MY RERUN, SO I CONTACTED THE NEW BUSINESS AREA AND GRABBED THE FIRST STACK OF OUTPUT FROM THE ORIGINAL RUN AND LEFT THEM THE SECOND RUN'S STACK OF OUTPUT. THERE MAY NOT HAVE BEEN A PROBLEM WITH THE DATA. I COMPARED ONE POLICY'S DATA PAGE VALUES AND FOUND NO DIFFERENCES. IF THIS HAPPENS AGAIN, WE MAY WANT TO PURSUE WHAT CREATES THE BAD DPFSEXTR RECORD. NOTE2: FURTHER RESEARCH HAS BEEN DONE AND HAS PROVEN THAT THIS IS NOT A PROBLEM. THE 90 RECORD, WHICH IS THE ONLY RECORD ON THE POLICY WITH THE BLANK COMPANY CODE, IS REMOVED FROM THE FILE BY THIS ULTIM AND THUS HAS NO EFFECT ON THE RESULTING POLICY PAGES. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0420",
  "PROBLEM": "EACH JOB WENT DOWN WITH S0C4 USER COMPLETION CODE=4039 REASON CODE=00000000 ON 9\/17\/08, CL$$0420 WENT DOWN WITH S04C, BUT THE PROBLEM WAS THE SAME: POLICIES WITH CLIENT PROBLEMS. ON 10\/21\/10: SAME PROBLEM, POLICY 5820162010 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOUND SAME POLICY IN DUMP FOR EACH JOB - 2051364463. CKETRGET AT COMPILE UNIT OFFSET +00000466 THERE WAS A CLIENT PROGRAM ON THIS POLICY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "I COPIED THE SA VSAM FILE FOR THE POLICY AND DELETED THE FOLLOWING POLICY 2051364463 FROM MY COPY. EVEN THOUGH CL$$0006 AND CL$$0007 ARE NON-CALL JOBS, I RERAN EACH JOB PER SCHD.CTM.DOC NOTES WITH MY COPY OF THE FILE. BOTH CL$$0004 AND CL$$0007 HAD CLIENT PROBLEMS AND THEREFORE THE POLICY WILL NOT SHOW IN 3270 THE NEXT DAY. TO IDENTIFY THAT THERE WAS A CLIENT PROBLEM LOOK IN IDIREPRT FOR: I B M F A U L T A N A L Y Z E R S Y N O P S I S \"A SYSTEM ABEND 0C1 OCCURRED IN MODULE D724MAIN CSECT CKETRGET AT OFFSET X'466'.\" A PROGRAM INTERRUPTION CODE 0001 (OPERATION EXCEPTION) IS ASSOCIATED WITH THIS ABEND AND INDICATES A CLIENT PROBLEM. BE SURE TO IDENTIFY 'CLIENT PROBLEM' IN THE EMAIL SENT OUT. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0006",
  "PROBLEM": "EACH JOB WENT DOWN WITH S0C4 USER COMPLETION CODE=4039 REASON CODE=00000000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOUND SAME POLICY IN DUMP FOR EACH JOB - 2453061460. CKETRGET AT COMPILE UNIT OFFSET +00000466 THERE WAS A CLIENT PROGRAM ON THIS POLICY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "I COPIED THE SA VSAM FILE FOR THE POLICY AND DELETED THE FOLLOWING POLICY 2453245870 FROM MY COPY. EVEN THOUGH CL$$0006 AND CL$$0007 ARE NON-CALL JOBS, I RERAN EACH JOB PER SCHD.CTM.DOC NOTES WITH MY COPY OF THE FILE. --- I MADE CHANGES TO CL.SA.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY USING MY FIRECALL LOGON ID. --P1JIF "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0420",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$0420 WENT DOWN WITH S0C7 IN STEP 20 IN PROGRAM CKUBCVL2 *PROBLEM: SAME AS ABOVE BUT ABENDING PROGRAM IS CKUBMVLB ",
  "ANALYSIS": "*ANALYSIS: PROD JOB WAS POINTING TO TEST.CL.WET.LOADLIB.EXHIBIT SO APPEARS BILL WAS WORKING ON A FIX BUT NOT FIXED YET. ",
  "SOLUTION": "I COPIED THE SA VSAM FILES FOR THE POLICY AND AUXSEG1 DELETED THE FOLLOWING POLICY 2453245870 FROM MY COPIES RERAN FROM THE TOP USING OVERRIDES FOR MY COPIES OF THE FILES. *SOLUTION: SAME AS ABOVE SOLUTION BUT BAD POLICY WAS 2385111700 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0020",
  "PROBLEM": "NO PAGES WERE EXTRACTED FROM THE EVENING POLICY PAGES RUN. 11\/06\/2006 - SAME PROBLEM BUT WITH FILE DPFILE03 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CICSD DID NOT SHUTDOWN CYBERLIFE CORRECTLY, SO NO PAGES WERE EXTRACTED. CL$$0020 THINKS DPFS2 IS STILL ACTIVE AND WILL NOT EXTRACT FROM AN ACTIVE EXTENT FILE. IF THE SHUTDOWN HAD WORKED CORRECTLY IT WOULD HAVE FLIPPED DPFS2 TO BE 'F' FOR FULL IN THE SYSSTAT FILE OTHERWISE THE INDICATOR IS AN 'A' FOR ACTIVE. IF YOU LOOK AT THE CL.SB.VSAM.BASEOL.SYSSTAT FILE YOU CAN SEE THE INDICATORS. THE 'E' INDICATES EMPTY. ...DPFILE01 FYNN DPFILE02 ANNN DPFILE03 ENNN DPF IN THE ABOVE EXAMPLE DPFS1 WAS FLIPPED AT NOON FOR THE NOON PAGES TO BE EXTRACTED. THE 'F' INDICATES THE EXTENT FILE IS FULL AND THE 'Y' INDICATES THE RECORDS HAVE BEEN EXTRACTED. THE OTHER THING TO LOOK FOR IS THE 'OFF THE AIR' MESSAGE IN THE LOG FOR CICSD. THE FOLLOWING ARE THE MESSAGES YOU WOULD SEE IF THE SYSTEM SHUTDOWN CORRECTLY. +CKQS01 - QUIESCEING FOR TRANSACTION: 0002(#01843) +CKCI21-AUTOMATIC 0002 SHUTDOWN FROM PLT +CKFL10 19.00.37 DPFS FILE FVDDPFS CLOSED +CKFL09 19.00.37 VSAM FILE CLOSES COMPLETED +CKCIPLT3 RELEASED SHARED PCT AREA +CKST06 19.00.37 CK4\/VS SYSTEM OFF THE AIR ON FRIDAY NIGHT THE CKFL10 AND CKFL09, CKCIPLT3 AND CKST06 DID NOT OCCUR. ",
  "SOLUTION": "SINCE THE DPFS, SYSSTAT AND ACTIVITY FILES ARE INITIALIZED AT THE END OF OUR BATCH CYCLE EVERY NIGHT, THE DOCUMENTS TEAM HAS TO DO A MANUAL PROCESS TO EXTRACT THE DATA FROM THE SB DPFS FILE THE FOLLOWING WORK DAY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "+PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) AT LOCATION 00 +CKSN01 PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. PSW=078D1400 8C8570F2 (DECIMAL D +CKSN02 ABENDING ELEMENT CKPRTRAN EPA=0C856998 OFFSET 00075400754 +IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V5R1M0 (UK00798 2005\/02\/23) INVOKED BY IDIXDCA +IDI0082E DB2 CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQLALLOCCONNECT SQLERROR 798 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "IT APPEARS THAT THE ABEND WAS DUE TO THE DELETION OF SOME REQUIREMENTS FROM UTABLES. THESE SHOULD HAVE BEEN APPLIED FROM ISSUE #7166, BUT THESE CAUSED ERRORS. KATHY AND SANDI LOOKED AT SOME TABLES IN MODL AND NOTICED THE ERROR. ",
  "SOLUTION": "WE DECIDED TO RERUN THE JOB POINTING TO THE SA VERSION OF UTABLES FROM THE 10\/17 MODL CYCLE. SCHD.CTM.DOC(CL$$0030) CALLS FOR THE RUNNING OF CL$$R030, ****** NOTE: CL$$RC10 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL2 ******** CL$$RC10 AND CL$$R017, THEN RERUNNING CL$$0017, CL$$0018 AND CL$$0030. WE NOTIFIED THE CYBERLIFE\/IND TEAM THAT THESE CHANGES WERE NOT INCLUDED IN THE MODL CYCLE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0600",
  "PROBLEM": "CC20 PROBLEM READING ACF: 1 KEY: E APPLICATION TERMINATED DUE TO ACF**>> RUN ABORTED <<** POLICY = 2453401400 *POLICY = 2453466650 (P1JIF 02\/24\/09) ",
  "ANALYSIS": "D724DSTI COULD NOT FIND THE AGENT BECAUSE THERE IS NO SERVICING AGENT OR AGENCY ON THE 01 SEGMENT OF THE POLICY. *NO AGT\/AGCY FOUND IN SEGMENT 01 FOR POLICY 2453466650 ANALYSIS2: LOOK AT THE SERVICING AGENT FOR POLICY. SEE IF THIS AGENT OR ANY IN THEIR HIERARCHY HAS A NUMBER IN THEIR NEXT LEVEL CODE AND A BLANK IN THE NEXT LEVEL AGENT. THE BLANK IN THE NEXT LEVEL AGENT FIELD IS WHAT IS CAUSING THE PROBLEM. ",
  "SOLUTION": "MADE A COPY OF CL.CL$$0600.ACTIVITY. USED FIRECALL AND DELETED RECORDS FOR POLICY 245301400. DELETED CL.CL$$0600.DFA.RECORDS AND HAD PCD RESTART JOB FROM STEP0220 PER SCHD.CTM.DOC(CL$$0600). *SAME FOR 2453466650 (P1JIF 02\/24\/09) *NOTIFIED TRIAGE OF PROBLEM (P1JIF 02\/24\/09) CALLED NICOLE PARK TO LET HER KNOW THAT OUR DST FILE DID NOT GO OUT ON FRIDAY NIGHT. EMAILED BETTY MOOMAW'S AREA TO HAVE SOMEONE FIX THE PROBLEM OF THIS POLICY NOT HAVING A SERVICE AGENT\\AGENCY IN THE 01 SEGMENT. OR EMAIL BETTY MOOMAW'S AREA TO HAVE SOMEONE BLANK THE NEXT LEVEL CODE FOR THE PROBLEM AGENT. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "VPMS MODEL IS LOOPING AE46 20061004133722 COMPUTE(1,P_SEVEN_PAY)CALL LIMIT (2500) EXCEED ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOK FOR INVALID VALUES BEING PASSED TO MODEL. IF ALL LOOKS VALID, SEND ATTRIBUTES AND PROPERTY TO CURT FOR REVIEW. ONLY AN ATTRIBUTE CORRECTION OR A MODEL CHANGE CAN FIX THIS. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "VPMS LOAD FAILURE AE03 20061004115042 LOADSESSION(SEVENPAY) AE03 20061004115042 SHARED: ALLOCATING 9120KB LOADBUFFER AE03 20061004115046 SHARED: 684025 ALLOCS, 7250641 BYTES, 7257028 AE03 20061004115046 LOADSESSION: CAN NOT SHARE SEVENPAY AE03 20061004115046 CKVPMG7C CAUSED ERROR: 2 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CICS REGION DSA (ABOVE THE LINE) WAS TO SMALL EDSALIM=80M, ",
  "SOLUTION": "INCREASE THE MAX REGION ABOVE THE LINE TO 200M "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$Q860",
  "PROBLEM": "ABENDED WITH AN OC7 (DECIMAL DATA) NOTES FROM 7\/5\/2006: BASE SYSTEM PROBLEM IN CKUBANST. THERE WAS A DIFFERENCE IN LENGTHS OF THESE WORKING STORAGE FIELDS. RHONDA WATSON PASSED THIS INFO ON TO CSC. CL7049 WAS WRITTEN UP TO DOCUMENT THE CHANGE MADE TO FIX THE 6\/30\/06 STATEMENT. GENERAL-PARMS IS 77472 LONG. WS-SAVE-GENERAL-PARMS IS 9000 LONG. IN CKUBANST, GENERAL-PARMS IS MOVED TO WS-SAVE-GENERAL-PARMS, THEN LATER IS MOVED BACK TO GENERAL-PARMS. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "BY LOOKING IN THE DUMP FOR THE WORD 'CURRENT' OF THE FILE NAME = SEQUEN FOUND THE RECORD IN ERROR (POLICY 2453386510). SAME POLICY ON 6\/30\/06. ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. COPIED PROD INPUT FILE FROM CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT.G2139V00 TO TEST.CL.PSS.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT.G2139 FOR 10\/3\/06 2. DELETED ALL RECORDS FOR THIS POLICY OFF THE TEST FILE 3. DELETED THE CURRENT GEN OF OUTPUT FILE: CL.CL$$0860.SAPPH.G1768V00 4. ASKED THE OPERATOR (JERRY REES) TO RESTART THE JOB FROM THE TOP USING TEST.CL.LKM.JCLLIB(CL$$Q860) THIS JOB HAD THE OVER-RIDE FOR THE TEST FILE IN STEP0020.SORTIN (WE DID NOT HAVE FIRE-CALL) NEW JOB COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1180",
  "PROBLEM": "FDR ABENDED ON CL$$RBR3.STEP0010 FDR RESTORE # IEF450I CL$$1180 STEP0010 CL$$RBR3 - ABEND=S000 U0888 -STEP=STEP0010 PGM=FDRABR ABENDED - COND CODE S378 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FDR CHOKED ON RESTORING 1 FILE THAT WAS NOT USED IN CL$$1180. I FOUND THAT BY DOING A FIND ON '**'. KEEP HITTING F-5 NEXT KEY TO GET PAST THE NORMAL EXLCUDE STATEMENTS AND THEN YOU WILL GET TO THE ERROR(S). FDR156** ALLOCATE FAILED FOR 02045 CYL COMP=X'0014-041A041D' VOL=S FDR326** RESTORE ENDED WITH NO DATA SETS RESTORED VOL=STOL15 DSN=CL.ME.SA.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN ",
  "SOLUTION": "SINCE ALL OTHER RESTORED FILES COMPLETED OK, (THIS SHOULD BE THE LAST LINE OF THE OUTPUT) FDR998** FDRABR COMPLETED WITH ERRORS DECIDED TO MOVE ON WITH NEXT STEP BY RESTARTING IN ****** NOTE CL$$RC99 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL5 *************** CL$$RC99.STEP0010 JOB ENDED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0155",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C 4 ABEND STEP0020 PGM=IKJEFT01 EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 POLICY REQUEST DATE DEPT\/DESK MESSAGE 00-2052142820 02\/12\/99 948KH I\/O ERROR ENCOUNTERED ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED AT DUMP. DETERMINED I\/O CODE WAS A 2, DUPLICATE WRITE ERROR. HAD TO COMPILE SOURCE TO PDS DUE TO 20 BYTE PAN AUDIT. NOTICED THAT DURATION ON 66 SEG WAS 89 52, WHICH = 37 MONTHS. HOWEVER, THE ONLINE HISTORY FILE CONTAINED DURATIONS 1 TO 89. SO THE 66 SEG IS OUT OF SYNC WITH THE ONLINE HISTORY FILE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "TEMP SOLUTION AT NIGHT. RAN CL$$R0155 COPIED CL.CL$$0020.STEP0010.HISTREQ.G0254V00 TO TEST.CL.CL$$0020.STEP0010.HISTREQ.D082806 THEN DELETED PROBLEM POLICY - FIRECALL REPORT 6667. RESTARTED JOB - COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. WE ARE GOING TO LEAVE THE POLICY AS IS TO SEE IF THE PROBLEM IS CORRECTED WHEN IT ARCHIVES AGAIN. 08-29-06 CHECKED WITH KATHY - THEY NEED THIS POLICY TO BE CORRECTED SO THAT THEY CAN DO A ZERO-PAY PREMIUM TO FIX AN INTEREST RATE PROBLEM. 09-28-07 POLICY 3465013950 - THE DURATION ON 66 SEG WAS 95 61. HOWEVER, THE HISTORY FILE CONTAINED DURATIONS 1 TO 95. THE 66 SEG IS OUT OF SYNC WITH THE HISTORY FILE. EMAILED KATHY AND TRIAGE TEAM TO REQUEST A FILE MARVEL TO CHANGE THE LOW DURATION (FULLHDUR-LOW-HISTORY-DUR) TO 00000C. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0007",
  "PROBLEM": "8\/8\/2006 P1RSW PROBLEM: IWRITINGAGENTCL.INS HAD 68,000 RECORDS. WHEN THE SERVER JOB ATTEMPTED TO INSERT 68,000 RECORDS THAT ALREADY EXISTED IT CREATED ERRORS. AFTER 10,000 ERRORS, THE JOB ENDED AND JANET BOEHM WAS NOTIFIED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CL.CL$$0007.POL.WRAGT.G0707V00 CREATED ON 8\/8 HAS THIS AT THE END OF THE FILE \"I\/O ERROR DETECTED, I\/O TERMINATED\". APPROXIMATELY 68,000 RECORDS WERE MISSING AT THE END OF THE FILE. TIM NOONE SAID THE FDR COMPAKTOR JOBS HAD ISSUES ON 8\/7 AND 8\/8. LAVONNA NICHOLS IS CONTACTING THE VENDOR OF THE SOFTWARE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "ON 8\/11 A.M., I RAN STEP0190 & STEP0200 COMPARING THE 8\/7 & 8\/10 WRAGT FILES TO CAPTURE WHAT WE LOST ON 8\/8. JANET APPLIED MY INS AND DEL FILES AND THEN RE-APPLIED THE 8\/10 INS AND DEL FILES. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0440",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB LOOPING - PRODUCTION OPERATOR CANCELLED 2ND RUN WITH A DUMP OR JOB LOOPING AND IT ENDED ON IT'S OWN WITH AN ABEND S322 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOUND POLICY 3465106350 IN DUMP 11\/10\/06 - 3465107610 PROBLEM POLICY WAS THE LAST POLICY IN THE SYSLST... 0710064440. LOOK FOR THE CURRENT RECORD IN SEQUEN4 IN IDIREPRT. POLICY SHOULD BE IN THAT RECORD. ",
  "SOLUTION": "USING FIRECALL, BACKED UP CL.CL$$0100.POLEX.YTDEXT.G0465V00 (17481 RECORDS) TO TEST.CL.CL$$0100.POLEX.YTDEXT.D080906 AND CL.CL$$0420.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN.G0463V00 (1,077,863 REC) TO TEST.CL.CL$$0420.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN.D080906 DELETED POLICY 3465106350 USING FM FROM YTDEXT FILE SANDI USING ULTIM FOR DELETE FROM POLSEQ FILE UTLIM IS TEST.CL.TOOLS(WAPPOLSQ) PER ACTUARIAL, THEY DO NOT NEED TODAY'S RUN BUT NEEDS TOMORROW'S RUN WITH ACTIVITY FROM BOTH DAYS. EACH DAY NEEDS TO BE RUN SEPARATELY TO CORRECTLY PROCESS THE FILE. ALTHOUGH IT MAY BE POSSIBLE TO COMBINE THE TRANSACTION FILES, WE DO NOT KNOW HOW TO DO SO AT THIS TIME. 6\/25\/08 - LOOPING WHEN RESEARCHING THESE POLICIES TO FIND THE ACTUAL ONE THAT IS LOOPING. CHECK THE SEQUEN4 PREVIOUS, CURRENT, AND NEXT RECORDS TO CHECK RIDERS, NOT TAKEN STATUS'S. TODAY'S PROBLEM WAS THE PREVIOUS RECORD 5200011760 WAS IN A NOT TAKEN STATUS THOSE RECORDS WERE DELETED FROM THE SEQUEN4 FILE WHICH IS THE CL.CL$$0100.POLEX.YTDEXT FILE "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0440",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB LOOPING - PRODUCTION OPERATOR CANCELLED 2ND RUN WITH A DUMP ",
  "ANALYSIS": "08\/09 AND 08\/10 CYCLE RUNS OF CL$$0440 LOOPING. POLICY 3465106340 HAS ENTRY IN YTDEXT FILE BUT NOT IN POLSEQ FILE (ERRORED IN CL$$0420). ",
  "SOLUTION": "08\/10\/06 RUN USING FIRECALL, BACKED UP CL.CL$$0100.POLEX.YTDEXT.G0466V00 (17481 RECORDS) TO TEST.CL.CL$$0100.POLEX.YTDEXT.D081006 DELETED POLICY 3465106340 USING FM FROM YTDEXT FILE RE-RAN FROM TOP - COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. PER ACTUARIAL, THEY DO NOT NEED TODAY'S RUN BUT NEEDS TOMORROW'S RUN WITH ACTIVITY FROM BOTH DAYS. EACH DAY NEEDS TO BE RUN SEPARATELY TO CORRECTLY PROCESS THE FILE. ALTHOUGH IT MAY BE POSSIBLE TO COMBINE THE TRANSACTION FILES, WE DO NOT KNOW HOW TO DO SO AT THIS TIME. SOLUTION: 08\/09\/06 RUN DUE TO DELETION OF WRONG POLICY 08\/10, HAD TO COPY TEST.CL.CL$$0100.POLEX.YTDEXT.D080906 (17481 RECORDS) TO TEST.CL.CL$$0100.POLEX.YTDEXT.AUG0906 DELETED POLICY 3465106340 USING FM FROM YTDEXT FILE ADDED OVERRIDES TO CL$$0440 TO USE \/\/STEP0020.IEXTR DD DSN=TEST.CL.CL$$0100.POLEX.YTDEXT.AUG0906 \/\/STEP0030.SEQUEN3 DD DSN=CL.CL$$0420.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN.G0463V00 \/\/ DD DSN=CL.CL$$0420.POLSEQ.EXTSRSL.G0463V00 \/\/ DD DSN=CL.CL$$0420.POLSEQ.EXTSRPM.G0463V00 RE-RAN FROM TOP - COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. PER ACTUARIAL, THEY DO NOT NEED TODAY'S RUN BUT NEEDS TOMORROW'S RUN WITH ACTIVITY FROM BOTH DAYS. EACH DAY NEEDS TO BE RUN SEPARATELY TO CORRECTLY PROCESS THE FILE. ALTHOUGH IT MAY BE POSSIBLE TO COMBINE THE TRANSACTION FILES, WE DO NOT KNOW HOW TO DO SO AT THIS TIME. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0600",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND=S04C IN SYSTSPRT 'SYSTEM ABEND CODE 0C7' ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CREATED CL$$0600.STEP0310 IN MY WORLD. HAD TO CREATE MY OWN VERSION OF CL.VSAM.BASEB.AMPHIST. COMPILED AND LINKED PROD VERSION OF D724DSTA IN MY WORLD. RAN JOB. LOOKED IN DUMP TO FIND THE LINE IN PROGRAM WHERE IT WAS GOING DOWN. HAD TO DO WITH ZIP-CODE. WENT INTO IDIREPRT AND DID A FIND ON 'CURRENT' TO FIND THE PROBLEM POLICY...2453324230. LOOKED AT POLICY IN PRODUCTION, 62D1. OWNER, INSURED AND PAYOR (SAME PERSON) HAD A BOGUS ZIP CODE 'GRANB-URY'. ZIP MUST BE NUMERIC. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD JEAN EASTON IN KATHY'S AREA CONTACT A USER TO HAVE THEM FIX ZIP CODE. ONCE THIS WAS DONE, HAD OPS RUN CL$$R600 AND THEN RESTART CL$$0600 IN STEP0300. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0910",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB LOOPING - TEST CYCLE ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB NORMALLY TAKES SECONDS. OPS CALLED, CONCERNED IT MAY BE LOOPING. HAD JOB CANCELLED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "XPEDITED WITH FILE. PROGRAM LOOPING BECAUSE NO OWNER ADDRESS ON THE TEST POLICY - 5448864640. LAP - ISSUE 7093 HAS BEEN CREATED FOR THIS PROBLEM. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0012",
  "PROBLEM": "+IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V5R1M0 (UK00798 2005\/02\/23) INVOKED BY IDIXDC IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 057 USER COMPLETION CODE=0040 IEF450I CL$$0012 STEP0005 CL$$0012 - ABEND=S000 U0040 REASON=00000000 TIME=21.40.31 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE HEADER DATE FOR CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES.G1801V00 (THE COPY OF THE OMNI FILE CL.FUND.PRICES) HAD A 07\/21\/06 DATE (THE PREVIOUS CYCLE DATE) IN THE HEADER RECORD. THE FUND PRICES WERE THE SAME AS THE PREVIOUS GENERATION ALSO. THE DOC DOESN'T STATE IT SPECIFICALLY BUT THE PROC DOES: \/\/* U040 ABEND INDICATE THE FUNDVAL HEADER DATE DOES NOT MATCH PARMDATE ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD OPS CALL THE OMNI ON-CALL PERSON TO GET A NEW FUNDS FILE GENERATED. THEN HAD THEM: UNCATALOG AND DELETE CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES.G1801V00 UNCATALOG AND DELETE CL.FUND.PRICES.SORTED.G0261V00 UNCATALOG AND DELETE CL.FUND.PRICES.SORTE2.G0261V00 UNCATALOG AND DELETE CL.CL$$0010.ERRRPT.G0258V00 RAN CL$$0010 WITH THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDE: \/\/CL$$0010 JOB (P,712W),'BEFORE CYCLE BACKUPS',MSGCLASS=J, \/\/ RESTART=CL$$0010.STEP0050, \/\/ CLASS=P,TYPRUN=HOLD,GROUP=CONTROLD,REGION=0M \/\/* \/\/CL$$0010 EXEC PROC=CL$$0010 \/\/* MADE SURE OPS DIDN'T LET OTHER JOBS BE TRIGGERED BY CL$$0010'S COMPLETION. RERAN CL$$0012 FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0103",
  "PROBLEM": "S04C +CKSN01 PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. PSW=078D0400 8C8503EE (OPERATION +CKUB03 CURRENT POLICY 2453357500 +CKSN02 ABENDING ELEMENT CKETRMAP EPA=0C850328 OFFSET 0000C4 +CKUB07 UNABLE TO CONTINUE PROCESSING - JOB ABORTING. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED AT THE BOTTOM OF FILE CL.CL$$0100.CKAP01V.DEBUG TO SEE WHICH POLICY JOB WENT DOWN ON. THIS HAPPENED TO BE THE SAME AS THE PROGRAM CHECKED POLICY, 2453357500. LOOKED IN DUMPS FOR THIS POLICY. IT WAS FOUND IN QUITE A NUMBER OF DIFFERENT PLACES. FIGURED THIS MUST BE THE PROBLEM POLICY. LOOKED IN THE SCHEDULER FILE, CL.VSAM.BASEOL.SCHDFL1, FOR THIS POLICY. SET FILE MARVEL TO HEX. (THE DATE FORMAT IN THE SCHEDULER FILE IS NNNNNCNNNC.) FOR THIS POLICY IT WAS 01277C028C. PLUGGED THIS INTO CKDATE IN THE CFO INTERNAL DATE FIELD. CAME BACK WITH 05\/28\/2006 ****** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD OPS RUN CL$$R060 AND CL$$RC30. USING FIRECALL, IN FILE MARVEL I CHANGED 01277C028C TO 01279C028C FOR 07\/28\/2006. (JUST NEED TO SET IT SOMETIME INTO THE FUTURE.) THE FILE CL.VSAM.BASEOL.BATCHPAY WAS NOT EMPTY SO HAD OPS RERUN CL$$0102 FROM THE TOP AND THEN RERUN CL$$0103 FROM THE TOP. NOTE: REVIEW CL.VSAM.BASEOL.BATCHPAY WITH FILE MARVEL, NOT TSO 3.4 TO DETERMINE IF EMPTY. WHH 02\/22\/08 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0106",
  "PROBLEM": "SB37 SORTOUT. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ADDED OVERRIDES FOR SORTOUTS IN STEP0080, STEP0210 AND STEP0390: SPACE=(27998,(5000,231),RLSE,,ROUND) AND RESTARTED. JOB COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0600",
  "PROBLEM": "ERROR S2F3. IT GETS THE ERROR AND REQUEUES THE JOB TO RUN AGAIN. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE APPEARS TO EXCEED A THRESHHOLD. IN M724CSVL IN CL$$1110 ON 3\/31\/06, IT WAS DUE TO EXCESSIVE OPENING OF A FILE. I DID NOT SEE THIS IN THE PROGRAMS, BUT THEY ARE QUITE COMPLEX. I QUESTION THE OVERHEAD IN CKTBLOCT, WHICH IS CALLED MANY TIMES PER POLICY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. FROM MY JOB, I CHANGED THE SORT STATEMENT IN STEP0210 TO INCLUDE THE POLICIES LE 2453372030 AND CREATED ONE FILE. THEN CHANGED THE SORT TO INCLUDE THE POLICIES GT 2453372030 AND CREATED THE SECOND FILE. 2. I RAN STEP0220 TWICE FROM MY JOB TO CREATE TWO FILES. I USED THE FIRECALL BECAUSE STEP0220 OPENS THE AMP HISTORY FILE FOR UPDATE. 3. I RAN THE SORT IN STEP0230 WITH THE TWO FILES I CREATED IN STEP0220. I USED THE FIRECALL AND CREATED THE PRODUCTION DATASET. 4. I HAD THE OPERATORS RESTART THE JOB IN STEP0235. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "+PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C1 (OPERATION) AT LOCATION 000 + PSW = 078D2000 8C831228 +REGISTERS AT TIME OF INTERRUPT: +00-07 0008B9EC 0008B860 00000000 0C830DC0 0C911A11 0C90CCA0 0C911A0E +08-15 00000001 8C831200 0C905498 0C831DC0 0C905664 0008B780 8C831214 +CKSN01 PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. PSW=078D2000 8C831228 (OPERATION) +CKSN02 ABENDING ELEMENT CKETRGET EPA=0C830DC0 OFFSET 000466 +IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V5R1M0 (UK00798 2005\/02\/23) INVOKED BY IDIXDCAP +IDI0082E DB2 CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQLALLOCCONNECT SQLERROR 040 SQLRC=-1 {DB2 FOR OS\/390}{ODBC DRIVER} SQLSTATE=58004 ERRLOC=2:170:10 CAF \"OPEN\" FAILED USING DB2 SYSTEM:DB2P AND PLAN:DSNACLI RC=0C AND REASON=00F30040 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CL$$POLD AND CL$$SQLB WERE RUN AT THE BEGINNING OF THE CYCLE TO DELETE POLICY 2453301810 BUT THE PENDING POLICY WAS NOT DROPPED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "****** NOTE: CL$$RC10 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL2 ******** PER SCHD.CTM.DOC(CL$$0030) RAN CL$$R030, CL$$RC10 AND CL$$R017. THEN RE-RAN CL$$POLD, CL$$SQLB, USED FILE MARVEL TO DELETE THE PENDING RECORDS, RE-RAN CL$$0017 AND CL$$0030. JOB COMPLETED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0110",
  "PROBLEM": "SO4C VSAM4 IS THE AGTFIN FILE ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE LENGTH ON THE WRITE TO THE AFA FILE APPEARS TO BE ZERO, CANNOT DETERMINE WHY. WILL TRY TO RECREATE SITUATION IN TEST. ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED CL.CL$$0105.STEP0080.EXTR.G0050V00 TO A TEST FILE NAME. THEN DELETED THE RECORDS FOR THE POLICY IDENTIFIED IN THE DUMP UNDER SEQUEN2 FROM THE PRODUCTION FILE USING FIRECALL. REQUESTED CL$$R110 TO RUN. THEN HAD CL$$0110 RESTARTED FROM THE TOP. POLICY PULLED WAS 4040002290. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0110",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C4 *ANALYSIS: COMMISSION RATE FILE ERROR. AS PER SYSOUT IT SEEMS COMMISSION RECORD COULD NOT BE FOUND FOR THE KEY 'C 750499 C1ATCQ P' FOR AGENT 25620. CKCMCC00 CALLS D724COM6 TO LOOK FOR COMMISSION RATE RECORD FROM COMMRATE FILE AND DOES NOT FINDS ANY RECORD. ON RETURNING TO CKCMCC00, IT CALLS CKABEND FORCEFULLY SINCE COMMISSION RECORD WAS NOT FOUND. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "COMMISSION RATE FILE ERROR. SAW THIS BY LOOKING AT SYSLST (JSTEP010 STEP0060) SAID 'NO COMMISSION RATE RECORD FOUND'. THEN GOING TO THE HELD OUTPUT AND THEN LOOK IN SYSPDUMP FOR CURRENT (SEQUEN2) RECORD. FOUND POLICY 2453327130 AS PROBLEM. *SOLUTION: COPIED PROD FILE CL.CL$$0105.STEP0080.EXTR(0) TO BKUP FILE. DELETED POLICY 2453390320 (6 RECORDS) FROM PRODUCTION FILE USING FIRECALL. HAD OPS SUBMIT CL$$R110 FOR RESTORES. VERIFIED CC=0. HAD OPS RESTART CL$$0110 FROM TOP. RAN SUCCESSFULLY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED PROD FILE CL.CL$$0105.STEP0080.EXTR(0) TO BKUP FILE. DELETED POLICY 2453327130 (3 RECORDS) FROM PRODUCTION FILE USING FIRECALL. HAD OPS SUBMIT CL$$R110 FOR RESTORES. VERIFIED CC=0. HAD OPS RESTART CL$$0110 FROM TOP. RAN SUCCESSFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "+PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) AT LOCATION 00 +CKSN01 PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. PSW=078D1400 8C8570F2 (DECIMAL D +CKSN02 ABENDING ELEMENT CKPRTRAN EPA=0C856998 OFFSET 00075400754 +IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V5R1M0 (UK00798 2005\/02\/23) INVOKED BY IDIXDCA +IDI0082E DB2 CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQLALLOCCONNECT SQLERROR 798 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE LAST TIME WE HAD THIS ERROR IN THIS STEP WAS ON 04\/15\/2004. AT THAT TIME, THE ABEND WAS DUE TO THE DELETION OF SOME REQUIREMENTS FROM UTABLES. (TWO REQUIREMENTS WERE DROPPED FROM PRODUCTION UTABLES TODAY.) PREVIOUSLY, AN ULTIM JOB WAS RUN TO LOCATE THE OFFENDING PENDING POLICY WHICH WAS THEN DELETED. THAT ULTIM JOB IS NO LONGER IN THE TEST.CL.ULTIM LIBRARY. ADDITIONALLY, IN TODAY'S CYCLE, SEVERAL SPECIAL JOBS WERE RUN BETWEEN JOBS CL$$0010 AND CL$$0017. ",
  "SOLUTION": "WE DECIDED TO RERUN THE JOB POINTING TO THE SB VERSION OF UTABLES BEFORE THE CHANGES WERE IMPLEMENTED. SCHD.CTM.DOC(CL$$0030) CALLS FOR THE RUNNING OF CL$$R030, ****** NOTE: CL$$RC10 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL2 ******** CL$$RC10 AND CL$$R017, THEN RERUNNING CL$$0017, CL$$0018 AND CL$$0030. RUNNING CL$$R030 RESTORES THE PENDING AND AUXSEG2 FILES WHICH NEEDED TO BE DONE. CL$$RC10 RESORES CLIENT WHICH LIKEWISE NEEDED TO BE DONE. CL$$R017 RESTORES VIRTUALLY EVERYTHING ELSE WHICH WOULD UNDO THE WORK DONE BY THE SPECIAL JOBS REQUIRING THE RERUN OF THESE JOBS ALSO. SINCE THIS WAS THE FIRST STEP OF JOB CL$$0030 THAT UPDATES RECORDS AND IT BOMBED OUT ON PENDING RECORD 0620162300 WE DECIDED TO ONLY RESTORE THE PENDING FILE AND CLIENT AND NOT RUN CL$$R017 THUS AVOIDING THE RERUNNING ALL OF THE SPECIAL JOBS. THE RERUN USING THE SB VERSION OF UTABLES ENDED WITH THE SAME ABEND BECAUSE THE UTABLE CHANGES WERE INSTALLED VIA A MIGRATE PROGRAM (CL$$MIGT) BEFORE CL$$0010 MADE THE SB COPY, NOT THROUGH CL$$0018 AFTER CL$$0010 RUNS. WE RESTORED AGAIN AND THEN RAN WITH THE SA COPY OF UTABLES FROM THE PREVIOUS NIGHT'S CYCLE TO A SUCCESSFUL CONCLUSSION. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1110",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C4 - CKETRGET AT OFFSET X'466' ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CLIENT PROBLEM. ",
  "SOLUTION": "JCL STILL HAD AN OVERRIDE FROM LAST MONTH ON THE PARM DATE. SO CLIENT ABENDED. HAD PCD CHANGE DATE BACK TO USING THE PARM DATE. RESTARTED FROM TOP. JOB COMPLETED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$8503",
  "PROBLEM": "AI FILES WILL BE RENAMED BY PCD, CAUSING PROBLEM **NOTE** THE AI DATA WILL NOT BE NEEDED 5 MONTHS AFTER CONVERTING THIS TO CL JOB. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DSN=AI.TAPEBU.ARPS.MONTHLY() CHANGED TO DSN=AI.ARCV.TAPEBU.ARPS.MONTHLY() ",
  "SOLUTION": "WILL NEED TO CHANGE THIS OVER RIDE IN JCL FROM: \/\/CLARPS DD DSN=CL.CL$$0140.MTD.ARPS.REF(-0),DISP=SHR \/\/ DD DSN=CL.CL$$1190.ME.ARPS.REF,DISP=SHR \/\/ DD DSN=AI.TAPEBU.ARPS.MONTHLY(-1),DISP=SHR <-CHG \/\/ DD DSN=AI.TAPEBU.ARPS.MONTHLY(-0),DISP=SHR <-CHG TO: \/\/CLARPS DD DSN=CL.CL$$0140.MTD.ARPS.REF(-0),DISP=SHR \/\/ DD DSN=CL.CL$$1190.ME.ARPS.REF,DISP=SHR \/\/ DD DSN=AI.ARCV.TAPEBU.ARPS.MONTHLY.G0187,DISP=SHR \/\/ DD DSN=AI.ARCV.TAPEBU.ARPS.MONTHLY.G0188,DISP=SHR "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0430",
  "PROBLEM": "IN TEST REGION AFTER REGION REFRESH WAS DONE GOT ERROR IEF450I P1T9T430 STEP0030 CL$$0430 - ABEND=S000 U0999 REASON= TIME=13.55.45 -STEP=STEP0030 PGM=CKPE80AP ABENDED - COND CODE S3E7 RC=000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE U0999 INDICATES THE PROGRAM BLEW ITSELF UP. ROUTING TO THE 'ST' QUEUE AND USING A ? AND FINDING STEP0490.SYSLST INDICATES A DATE ERROR PROBLEM ON AN INPUT FILE. ANALYSIS2: LOOKED IN IDIREPRT AT THE CURRENT RECORD. THIS POLICY WAS SURRENDERED DURING CYCLE. NOT SURE IF HAS ANY BEARING. BUT WILL TRY DELETING RECORD. ENDED UP HAVING TO FIND ALL SURRENDERED POLICIES WITH A WITHHOLDING. THERE WERE TWO OF THEM... 2453169770 AND 2453400320. ",
  "SOLUTION": "IF CREATED DURING RUN DELETE DELETED: TEST.CL.CL$$0430.PEANSWRS.EXTPOLEX(0) IF CREATED ADD OVER RIDE: \/\/*OVERRIDE FOR REGION REFRESH\/INITIALIZATION \/\/STEP0030.SEQUEN2 DD DSN=CL.CL$$0420.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN.G0373V00, \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) \/\/ DD DSN=CL.CL$$0420.POLSEQ.EXTSRSL.G0373V00, \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) \/\/ DD DSN=CL.CL$$0420.POLSEQ.EXTSRPM.G0373V00, \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) RE-RUN FROM TOP, JOB FINISHED OK. SOLUTION (PRODUCTION): MADE COPY OF CL.CL$$0100.POLEX.DAILY.SORTED AND CL.CL$$0420.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN. REMOVED RECORD FOR \"CURRENT\" PROBLEM POLICY FOUND IN IDIREPRT FROM CL.CL$$0100.POLEX.DAILY.SORTED. AND RAN TEST.CL.TOOL(WAPPOLSQ) TO DELETE POLICIES FROM CL.CL$$0420.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN. BE MINDFUL OF THE GDG NUMBERS FOR THE EXTSRIN FILE. TRY TO KEEP IT MATCHED TO THE EXTSRPM AND EXTSRSL FILES. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0105",
  "PROBLEM": "IN TEST REGION AFTER REGION REFRESH WAS DONE GOT ERROR IEF450I P1T9T105 STEP0100 CL$$0105 - ABEND=S000 U0999 REASON= TIME=12.10.51 -STEP=STEP0100 PGM=CKDHXC11 ABENDED - COND CODE S3E7 RC=000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE U0999 INDICATES THE PROGRAM BLEW ITSELF UP. ROUTING TO THE 'ST' QUEUE AND USING A ? AND FINDING STEP0100.SYSLST INDICATES A DATE ERROR PROBLEM ON AN INPUT FILE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CREATED TEST.CL.TDR.CNTL(COPY0105) DELETED: TEST.CL.CL$$0100.POLEX.YTDEXT(0) AS IT WAS EMPTY RAN TEST.CL.TDR.CNTL(COPY0105) USING -3 PROD GDG TO GET CORRECT BEFORE CYCLE DATES IN THAT FILE TEST.CL.CL$$0100.POLEX.YTDEXT(0) NEXT EDITED FILE TEST.CL.CL$$0100.POLEX.DAILY.SORTED(-1) WITH SAME CYCLE DATES AS IN FILE TEST.CL.CL$$0100.POLEX.YTDEXT(0) RE-RAN IN ABENDING STEP WITH OVER RIDE FOR SORTED FILE \/\/STEP0100.SEQUEN DD DSN=TEST.CL.CL$$0100.POLEX.DAILY.SORTED(0) COMMENTED OUT RESTART & OVER RIDE FILE AFTER JOB FINISHED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$9202",
  "PROBLEM": "CC80 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED IN SYSLST AND DID A FIND ON ERR. FOUND FOUR 'ERR POS 01 (265-A) MEMBER NOT FOUND'. THESE ARE COPYBOOK MEMBERS LOCATED IN PROD.ALIS.COPYLIB. ",
  "SOLUTION": "NOTICED IN JCL THE PREVIOUS STEP HAD THE FOLLOWING: \/\/COPYLIB DD DSN=PROD.CL.COPYLIB,DISP=SHR \/\/ DD DSN=PROD.ALIS.COPYLIB,DISP=SHR HAD PCD MAKE A PERMANENT ADDITION OF THE ABOVE TO JSTEP030 AND HAD THEN RERUN JOB FROM JSTEP030. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1110",
  "PROBLEM": "S2F3 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "M724CSVL WAS OPENING AND CLOSING THE FILES FOR EVERY POLICY. WE ASSUME THAT THE NUMBER OF POLICIES NOW ON THE FILE HAS CAUSED IT TO EXCEED A THRESHHOLD IN THE SYSTEM. ",
  "SOLUTION": "ISSUE 6908. REMOVED THE DUPLICATE OPENS. ADD SYSLST TO THE PROC TO DISPLAY THE ERROR MESSAGES. NOTHING IN THE OUTPUT OF THE ABEND EXPLAINED THE DUPLICATE OPENS. DAN HUNSINGER FOUND THEM AND SUGGESTED THE CHANGE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1000",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$1000 STEP0020 ABENDED. REASON DUE TO MESSAGE: B37-04,IFG0554A,CL$$1000,STEP0020,OUTPUT THIS CAUSED STEP0080 TO FLUSH DUE TO CONDITION CODES. STEP0080 EXEC PGM=DSNUTILB,COND=(4,LT) ",
  "ANALYSIS": "STEP0020.OUTPUT HAS ONLY 320 CYL NEEDS 2000. CAN BACK-UP CL.CL$$0860.SAPPH(+0) MANUALLY AFTER INCREASING SPACE FOR CL.ME.CL$$0860.SAPPH. TEST.CL.TOOLS(REPSAPPH) USED TO MANUALLY CREATE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTARTED IN STEP0065 ON THE RESET. STEP0065 ENDED OK. JOB CONTINUED ON. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$2060",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SAW THAT THE BEGIN FILE HAD NO BEGINNING TOTAL PREMIUM VALUE FOR POLICY 5110071560. ",
  "SOLUTION": "MADE A COPY OF THE BEGIN AND END FILES, DELETED THE RECORDS FOR THIS POLICY AND RERAN JOB STARTING IN STEP0220. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0860",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$0860 - SPACE ABEND - IEC030I B37-04,IFG0554A,CL$$0860,STEP0040,SORTOF1,1241,STOR20 IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 347 SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=B37 REASON CODE=00000004 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "STEP 30 CREATES INPUT HAD SPACES SET TO SPACE=(CYL,(2000,100),RLSE) HAD OPERATOR OVER RIDE THE SPACE FOR SORT 1 & 2 IN STEP 40 TO BE SAME SPACE ALLOCATION ",
  "SOLUTION": "RE-RAN FROM ABENDING STEP WITH OVER RIDE FOR SPACE ALLOCATION FOR SORT 1 & 2 AND JOB COMPLETED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1940",
  "PROBLEM": "IN HOLD UNDER JESMSGLG IEF450I CL$$1940 STEP0010 CL$$1940 - ABEND=S0C4 U0000 REASON= TIME=17.35.15 IN HOLD UNDER SYSOUT CL$$1940 STEP0010 PARMDATE: 03-27-06 PARMTYPE: R PARMYRS: 10 CEE3204S THE SYSTEM DETECTED A PROTECTION EXCEPTION (SYSTEM COMPLE FROM COMPILE UNIT CKETRINV AT ENTRY POINT CKETRINV AT COM AT ADDRESS 0007F6E8. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKING AT IDIREPRT CL$$1940, STEP0010, DID A FIND ON CURRENT AND FOUND THE FOLLOWING INFORMATION FILE NAME . . . . . . . . . : PARMAGT DATA SET NAME . . . . . . : ACFSUBID.CL$$1940.JOB00642.D0000102. FILE ATTRIBUTES . . . . . : ORGANIZATION=SEQUENTIAL, ACCESS MODE RECFM=FIXED LAST I\/O FUNCTION . . . . : READ OPEN STATUS . . . . . . . : INPUT FILE STATUS CODE. . . . . : 10 A SEQUENTIAL READ STATEMENT WAS ATTE NEXT LOGICAL RECORD EXISTED IN THE F LOOKED AT PROGRAM FOR LAYOUT FOR PARMAGT, FOUND IT SHOULD BE CCAAAAAAAAAAX WHERE CC = 2 DIGIT COMPANY ID AAAAAAAAAA = THE AGENT ID, UP TO 10 SPACES ALLOWED X = SHOULD BE C OR SPACES (HAD JUNK IN IT) LOOKED IN CONTROL D DID J BESIDE FAILED JOB FOUND PCD CODED \/\/* THIS IS THE AGENT LIST FOR ON REQUEST TYPE RUN \/\/STEP0010.PARMAGT DD * 05SP038 0510053 COPIED TEST JCL TO UNIT AND SET UP TO POINT TO PRODUCTION RAN WITH SPACES IN FIELD X AND C IN FIELD X AND FOUND NO REPORT WOULD GENERATE FOR THESE STATE LIFE AGENTS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD OPERATOR SET UP JOB TO RUN WITH A C IN FIELD X AS I FELT IT WOULD CONFUSE THEM TO SET FIELD X TO SPACES JOB COMPLETED AND NO REPORT GOT GENERATED, AS EXPECTED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "+0710030030 108 2 AP0108 - +CKSN01 USER ABEND 0001 DETECTED. +CKUB03 CURRENT POLICY 0030320 % CL$$0100 STEP0210 JSTEP010 - ABEND=S04C U0000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE PROBLEM WAS 0710030320. THE ERROR AP0108 IS AN INDICATION OF A SCHDFL1 RECORD FOR A POLICY WHICH IS NOT ON THE POLICY MASTER FILE -CL$$POLD WAS RUN AND REMOVE 3 POLICIES BUT THE SCHDFL1 REMOVAL FAILED. CL$$POLR WAS ALSO RUN TO ADD BACK 1 OF THE 3 POLICY NUMBERS. THE SCHDF1 RESTORE FAILED FOR THE RESTORE SINCE THE SCHDF1 RECORD WAS NOT REMOVED FIRST. STEPS -DETERMINE WHY THIS HAPPENED BY LOOKING TO SEE IF THERE WERE SPECIAL JOBS IN THE CYCLE LIKE CL$$POLD. OR ANY FILEMARVEL ACTIVITY. -DETERMINE THE FULL SCOPE OF THE PROBLEM. THERE ARE NO TOOLS AVAILABLE TO DO THIS. I HAD TO RELY ON WHAT I FOUND OUT OF THE POLICY DELETE JOBS AS MY SCOPE. -CHECK THE POLICY MASTER AND SCHDFL1 FOR THE POLICIES YOU THINK OUR OUT OF SINC TO MAKE SURE THEY ARE ****** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAVE OPS RUN CL$$RC30, CL$$R060 -CLEANUP THE SCHDFL1 FOR ALL ENTRIES WHICH ARE NOT ON THE POLICY MASTER. -RESTART CL$$0100 FROM THE TOP "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC4 +IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V5R1M0 (UK00798 2005\/02\/23) INVOKED BY IDIXDCA +IDI0082E DB2 CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQLALLOCCONNECT SQLERROR 293 SQLRC=-1 {DB2 FOR OS\/390}{ODBC DRIVER} SQLSTATE=58004 ERRLOC=2:170:10 CAF \"OPEN\" FAILED USING DB2 SYSTEM:DB2P AND PLAN:DSNACLI RC=0C AND REASON=00F30040 $HASP375 P1BKG012 ESTIMATED LINES EXCEEDED IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 119 USER COMPLETION CODE=4039 REASON CODE=00000000 PROBLEM: IEF450I P1SEC012 STEP0010 CL$$0011 - ABEND=S04C U0000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOUND SQLCODE OF 811 SO KNEW IT WAS A DUPLICATE ROW. THEN I RAN TEST.CL.TOOLS(SQL$DUPA). RECEIVED DUPLICATE ROWS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "FIRECALL WAS USED TO EXPIRE THE DUPLICATE ROWS. THEN HAD CL$$0011 RESTARTED IN STEP0020. JOB WENT DOWN AGAIN, BUT WITH SQLCODE OF 100 - MISSING ROW. WENDY DETERMINED IT WAS BECAUSE CL$$POLD & CL$$POLR HAD RAN WHILE CL$$0011 WAS RUNNING AND IT HAD DELETED ONE OF THE POLICIES IT NEEDED. SO CL$$0011 WAS FORCED COMPLETE SO CYCLE COULD GET MOVING. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0035",
  "PROBLEM": "S04C 14.01.14 JOB03815 +UNABLE TO RETRIEVE STUB POOL RECORD 14.01.14 JOB03815 +- - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - 14.01.15 JOB03815 +IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V5R1M0 (UK00798 2005\/0 14.01.16 JOB03815 +IDI0082E DB2 CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQLAL 969 SQLRC=-1 {DB2 FOR OS\/390}{ODBC DRIVER} SQLSTA 969 ERRLOC=2:170:10 CAF \"OPEN\" FAILED USING DB2 969 PLAN:DSNACLI RC=0C AND REASON=00F30040 LAST ENTRY FROM SYSOUT: CONTRACT NUMBER1: 0620250850 CEE3250C THE SYSTEM OR USER ABEND U 001 R=NULL WAS ISSUED. FROM COMPILE UNIT CKABEND AT ENTRY POINT CKABEND AT COMPI AT ADDRESS 0009A4D8. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THERE WAS NO BAD SQLCODE IN THE SYSUDUMP AND BOTH POLICIES 0620250850 AND 0620250860 DISPLAYED ON THE ONLINE SCREENS. I READ IN THE BOMBLOG THAT THIS JOB SOMETIMES HAS A SO4C WHEN A POLICY IS BEING UPDATED WHILE THE JOB TRIES TO ACCESS IT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DOC INDICATES STARTING FROM THE TOP WHEN STEP0010 ABENDS SO I HAD OPS TRY IT. IT WORKED. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "SOC4 +UNABLE TO RETRIEVE STUB POOL RECORD +- - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - +IDI0001I FAULT ANALYZER V5R1M0 (UK00798 2005\/02\/23) INVOKED BY IDIXDCA +IDI0082E DB2 CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQLALLOCCONNECT SQLERROR 293 SQLRC=-1 {DB2 FOR OS\/390}{ODBC DRIVER} SQLSTATE=58004 ERRLOC=2:170:10 CAF \"OPEN\" FAILED USING DB2 SYSTEM:DB2P AND PLAN:DSNACLI RC=0C AND REASON=00F30040 $HASP375 P1BKG012 ESTIMATED LINES EXCEEDED IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 432 USER COMPLETION CODE=4039 REASON CODE=00000000 IEF450I P1BKG012 STEP0010 CL$$0011 - ABEND=S04C U0000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DID NOT FIND AN SQLCODE IN ANY OF THE DUMPS. SO ON A HUNCH I RAN TEST.CL.TOOLS(SQL$DUPA). RECEIVED A DUPLICATE ROW. ",
  "SOLUTION": "FROM THE RESULTS OF THE DUPA, I COPIED THE CLIENT_ID, LOGGED IN USING FIRECALL, WENT INTO THE CLT_ADR_RELATION TABLE IN TSO PST, PLUGGED IN THE CLIENT_ID. FOUND THE DUPLICATE ROWS AND EXPIRED THE OLDEST ROW WITH THE EFFECTIVE DATE OF THE NEWEST ROW. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB ABENDED IN STEP0020 WITH A SO4C. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "SO4C ",
  "ANALYSIS": "MORE THAN 30 POLICIES RECEIVED PROGRAM CHECKS SO AP01V ABENDS. THE DUMP POINTS TO THE 31ST POLICY. IT APPEARS THAT SOME PROCESS PRIOR TO THE 205* POLICIES HAS CAUSED THE PROBLEM. THE PROGRAM CHECKS STARTED WITH POLICY 2050002430 AND THE LAST WAS 2051000727. BEING UNCERTAIN ABOUT WHAT CAUSED THE PROBLEM, WE IDENTIFIED TWO POLICIES IN THE ERROR REGISTER PRIOR TO THE 205 NUMBERS AND DECIDED TO STOP THEM FROM PROCESSING BY CHANGING THEIR DATES IN SCHDFL1. SO WE CHANGED THE DATES FOR 0710001800 AND 0710030320. AS IT TURNS OUT THE TWO POLICIES HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH THE ABEND. IT WAS A PROBLEM IN CKULINIO CSC HAD ASSINGED SPR CK1163. SO WE THINK WE COULD HAVE JUST RERAN CL$$0100 WITHOUT CHANGING ANYTHING AND IT PROBABLY WOULD HAVE RUN. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RAN R060 AND RC30 EDITED THE SCHDFL1 DATES FOR TWO POLICIES TO BE IN THE FUTURE AND RESTARTED FROM THE TOP. 2\/2\/06 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1170"
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0015"
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0910",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB LOOPING ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB NORMALLY TAKES SECONDS. OPS CALLED, CONCERNED IT MAY BE LOOPING. JOB CANCELLED BY SYSTEM. HAD OPS RESTART IN STEP0020 AND CANCEL JOB WITH A DUMP. ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED INPUT FILE TO TEST.CL.CL$$0910.MLIR.D013006 AND DELETED POLICIES 5448762630 AND 5449041620 FROM PROD INPUT FILE. RESTARTED IN STEP0020 - JOB COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. NEED TO INVESTIGATE WHY THESE WERE LOOPING. BKG - LOOPING PROBLEM WAS FIXED WITH CL6372. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "POLICY 5770006710 ERRORS - TIME DRIVEN ERROR REGISTER AP0302 - TABLE HAS BEEN EXCEEDED FPMATV ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PROGRAM CKFPMATV, GENERATING ERROR, HAS TABLE FOR 65 SEGMENTS, THIS TABLE INDEX NEEDS TO BE INCREASED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "ISSUE CL6716 HAS BEEN CREATED BY KATHY HANNAH TO INCREASE THE TABLE IN PROGRAM CKFPMATV, BUT THIS WILL CONTINUE TO HAPPEN UNTIL IT IS FIXED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0810",
  "PROBLEM": "IEF450I CL$$0810 STEP0110 JSTEP010 - ABEND=S04C U0000 RE CURRENT RECORD IN IDIREPRT 5450007200 5450011460 - LAP 01\/26\/06 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DECIDED TO PULL OFF BAD POLICY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "SAVED FILE CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AGTPRDEX.G1090V00 AS TEST.CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AGTPRDEX.PRDG1090 THEN EDITED THE PRODUCTION FILE AND RESTARTED THE JOB IN STEP0110 PER THE RESTART INSTRUCTIONS, JOB ENDED OK. SAVED CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AGTPRDEX.G1094V00 AS TEST.CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AGTPRDEX.G1094 - LAP 01\/26\/06 01\/23\/06: NEXT DAY, MONDAY 1\/23\/06 REVIEW PROBLEM TO RESOLVE. THE PROBLEM IS THAT CKESDTBH & CKESDTB2 IS NOT INCLUDED IN THE LINK DUE TO CHANGES IN PRODUCTION FOR ISSUE 6613. PER BILL TURNER. I ADDED CKESDTBH & CKESDTB2 TO LINK FOR PGM D724AGC4 RE-LINKED IN UNIT TEST, RAN WITH COPIED PRODUCTION FILE (USING LRECL=2000) AND RAN WITH OUT PROBLEMS. LINK IS IN TEST.CL.TDR.LINKS(D724AGC4) RSW - ISSUE 6758 CREATED TO RESOLVE THIS TDR - ISSUE 6758 INSTALLED INTO PRODUCTION 2\/2\/06 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0018",
  "PROBLEM": "BATCH SYMULATION IN CL$$0018 FAILED -STEP=STEP0010 PGM=CKSYSBLB EXECUTED - COND CODE 0000 RC=000 +CKFL02 21.35.50 DPFS FILE FVDDP01 OPENED +CKFL07 21.35.50 VSAM FILE OPENS COMPLETED +CKFC1 AP FILE CONSISTENCY CHECK SUCCESSFUL +CKST09 CK4\/VS SYSTEM ON THE AIR - SSDATE=01\/20\/06 IEC020I 001-4,CL$$0018,STEP0020,SYSIPT-0002,1760,TEST46, IEC020I TEST.CL.DAH.FMBU105.DBLCH IEC020I DCB EROPT=ABE OR AN INVALID CODE, AND\/OR NO SYNAD EXI +CEE0374C CONDITION=CEE3250C TOKEN=00040CB2 61C3C5C5 00000000 WHILE RUNNING PROGRAM IGG019AQ ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CONTACTED DAN HUNSINGER, THE DCB IS INDICATING A PROBLEM WITH THE OVER RIDE FMB SCRIPT FILE. FOUND OUT IT NEEDED TO BE LRECL 80 AND WAS CREATED AS LRECL 25. USED SORT ",
  "SOLUTION": "USED SORT AND OTHER UTILITIES TO RECREATE FILE W\/ LRECL 80, JOB RE-RAN, BUT DISCOVERED THE FMB SCRIPT HAD A SYNTAX ERROR. DAN HUNSINGER RECREATED THE FILE HAD TO PLACE A HOLD ON REST OF SCHEDULE AND HAVE DAN RECREATE THE FILE WITH SYNTAX CORRECTION, THEN RE-RAN TO ABOUT 8 TRIES BUT WE GOT IT RIGHT. AFTER SUCCESSFUL EXECUTION OF FMB SCRIPT HAD PCD REMOVE THE HOLD ON REST OF THE SCHEDULE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0021",
  "PROBLEM": "+A CICS CONNECTION HAS BEEN ESTABLISHED TO CICS REGION CICSD +EXCI CALL DPL REQUEST FAILED RESP 12 REASON 414-000000000- NO CICS +EXCI CALL DPL REQUEST FAILED RESP 12 REASON 414-000000000- NO CICS STEP=STEP0010 PGM=CKDPEXTC ABENDED - COND CODE S3E7 RC=00 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CALLING CHAIN CKABEND CKVSMRDC CALLING ELEMENT CKVSMRDC RETURN 0032F8 CKVSAMIO CKDPREAD CKDPEXTC SINCE THIS PROGRAM RUNS UNDER RDC, ONLINE HAS TO BE UP FOR CL$$0021 TO RUN. AT THE TIME CL$$0021 RAN TODAY, 11:02-11:07AM, THE MAINFRAME HAD A COMMUNICATION ERROR. ONLINE WAS HOSED UP DUE TO SYSTEM\/OPPERATION(SOFTWARE). OPS ATTEMPTED TO CORRECT THE SOFTWARE PROBLEM BUT WAS UNSUCCESSFUL. ",
  "SOLUTION": "OPS WILL CORRECT THE SOFTWARE PROBLEM TONIGHT AFTER PRODUCTION IS DOWN. WE REMOVED ALL SUBSEQUENT JOBS FROM THE SCHEDULE AND FORCED CL$$0021 COMPLETE. NORMAL PROCESSING WILL CONTINUE TONIGHT. ALL POLICIES WILL BE PROCESSED THE NEXT TIME CL$$0021 RUNS ON THE FOLLOWING DAY AT 11:00 A.M. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0021",
  "PROBLEM": "+A CICS CONNECTION HAS BEEN ESTABLISHED TO CICS REGION CICSD +EXCI CALL DPL REQUEST FAILED RESP 8 REASON 203-000000000- NO CICS +EXCI CALL DPL REQUEST FAILED RESP 8 REASON 203-000000000- NO CICS STEP=STEP0010 PGM=CKDPEXTC ABENDED - COND CODE S3E7 RC=00 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CALLING CHAIN CKABEND CKVSMRDC CALLING ELEMENT CKVSMRDC RETURN 0032F8 CKVSAMIO CKDPREAD CKDPEXTC SINCE THIS PROGRAM RUNS UNDER RDC, ONLINE HAS TO BE UP FOR CL$$0021 TO RUN. AT THE TIME CL$$0021 RAN TODAY, 11:02-11:07AM, THE MAINFRAME HAD A COMMUNICATION ERROR AND ONLINE WAS HOSED UP. SO WE HAD BOUNCED CICSD AT 11:06AM. SINCE CICSD WAS DOWN AT 11:06AM, CL$$0021 WENT DOWN. ",
  "SOLUTION": "SINCE MAINFRAME OR CICSD WAS BACK UP NOW, RESTARTED CL$$0021 IN STEP0010. JOB ENDED OK. MAKE SURE +RECORDS SELECTED FOR THIS FILE ARE XXXXX GREATER THAN 0. THEY SHOULD BE GREATER THAN 0 NORMALLY. IF THEY ARE GREATER THAN 0, CL$$0021 ENDS OK, AND THE 11:00AM PAGES\/STATEMENTS JOBS RUNS, THEN NOTHING LEFT TO DO. IF RECORDS SELECTED ARE 0, THEN THE 11:00AM CL$$8XXX PAGES\/STATMENTS WON'T PRINT ANYTHING. IF THAT IS THE CASE, MAY NEED TO HAVE OPS DO AN 0003 TO FLIP THE EXTENTS AND RERUN CL$$0021, THEN RERUN THE 11:00AM CL$$8XXX JOBS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0110",
  "PROBLEM": "RECEIVED THE FOLLOWING CL ALERT EMAIL THERE WAS A PROBLEM WITH JOB CL$$0110 STEP 0060. PLEASE REVIEW SYSOUT. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "HAD TO LOOK IN JCL REPORT IN CONTROL-D FOR CL$$0110. INBETWEEN INFORMATION FOR STEP 50 AND STEP 66 IS A REPORT THAT HAD THE FOLLOWING. WE BELIEVE THIS IS WHAT WAS IN THE SYSOUT. (TOWARDS THE BOTTOM OF THE JCL REPORT.) 02 SEGMENT NOT FOUND... 3465026490 972VF COVERAGE SEGMENT NOT FOUND 12\/20\/05 CKCME010 02 SEGMENT NOT FOUND... 3465026490 972VF COVERAGE SEGMENT NOT FOUND 12\/20\/05 CKCME010 02 SEGMENT NOT FOUND... 3465026490 972VF COVERAGE SEGMENT NOT FOUND 12\/20\/05 CKCME010 02 SEGMENT NOT FOUND... 3465026490 972VF COVERAGE SEGMENT NOT FOUND 12\/20\/05 CKCME010 ",
  "SOLUTION": "FORWARDED THIS INFORMATION ON TO EVERYONE ALONG WITH CYBERLIFE_IND WHO DID NOT RECEIVE THE ORIGINAL ALERT. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "IEC141I 013-18,IGG0191B,CL$$0030,STEP0010,SYSIN,120B, PRD007,PROD.CL.CARDLIB(CLVD0030) -STEP=STEP0010 PGM=IDCAMS EXECUTED - COND CODE 0016 RC=0000 ELAP= 00:00:00.24 I\/O BLKS= 36 +0 0000000 POLICIES RELEASED TO TRADITIONAL IEF377I CL$$0030 STEP0020 JSTEP010 264 CL.COMBPEND NOT CATLGD 2 IEF377I CL$$0030 STEP0020 JSTEP010 265 CL.REQMTCOR NOT CATLGD 2 IEF377I CL$$0030 STEP0020 JSTEP010 266 CL.BILLEFT.EXTRACTS NOT CATLGD 2 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "EVEN THOUGH THIS SECOND STEP OF THE JOB HAD A CONDITION CODE OF 0016, IT CONTINUED TO RUN THROUGH THE REST OF THE STEPS. THE CARD CLVD003 HAD BEEN DELETED FROM THE PRODUCTION CARDLIB. IN THE IDCAMS STEP0010 IT DEFINED THE DATESETS TO BE DELETED: DELETE CL.BILLEFT.EXTRACTS,PURGE DELETE CL.REQMTCOR,PURGE DELETE CL.COMBPEND,PURGE WITHOUT THE CARD, THE CATALOGED DATASETS WERE NOT DELETED AND NEW UNCATALOGED DATASETS WERE CREATED. THE PROGRAM CONTINUED TO RUN USING THE OLD CATALOGED DATASETS SO ALL OF THE DATA PROCESSED WAS INVALID. ",
  "SOLUTION": "I FOUND THE CARD IN TEST AND MODEL CARDLIBS, COPIED ONE TO TEST.CL.WHH.CARDLIB AND CHANGED THE TEST DATASET NAMES TO PRODUCTION NAMES. I DELETED THE THREE UNCATALOGED DATASETS AND THE THREE GENERATION DATASETS THAT COULD BE DELETED FROM THE FIRST RUN OF CL$$0030: CL.CL$$0030.STEP0020.PFPURG.G1936V00 CL.CL$$0030.AGENT.EXTRACT.SORT.G0443V00 CL.AGCY.DAILY.INPUT.TRANS.G1762V00 ACCORDING TO SCHD.CTM.DOC, THE DB2 IMAGE COPIES OF THE POLICY DATABASE CANNOT BE CLEANED UP. DB2 KEEPS AN INTERNAL CATALOG OF THESE AND WILL NOT ALLOW RE-CREATION OF A GDG VERSION WHICH HAS BEEN REMOVED SO I DID NOT DELETE CL.BASEB.CISBMAIN.BK30.G1928V00. ****** NOTE: CL$$RC10 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL2 ******** I HAD OPS RUN CL$$R030, CL$$RC10, CL$$R017, & CL$$0017. I HAD OPS ADD THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDE TO CL$$0030: \/\/STEP0010.SYSIN DD DSN=TEST.CL.WHH.CARDLIB(CLVD0030), \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) AND RERUN FROM THE TOP. IT FINISHED WITH CC = 0000. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1110",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C7 CKDCARTH CALLED BY CKFVQUOT ",
  "ANALYSIS": "M724CSVL DISPLAYED: ERROR: 2 - 0710026650 0500-CAL INITIALIZE CKULGPRM M724CSVL CALLS CKUBINTM TO INITIALIZE CKULGPRM. THIS MESSAGE RESULTED FROM THE RETURN CODE FROM CKUBINTM NOT = ZERO. ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED CL.SA.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY TO TEST.CL.RSW.VSAM.POLICY AND USED FILE MARVEL TO DELETE POLICY 0710026650. ADDED OVERRIDE: \/\/STEP0010.VSAM1 DD DSN=TEST.CL.RSW.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY AND RERAN FROM THE TOP. THE STATUS OF 0710026650 WAS CHANGED TO DECEASED IN NOVEMBER. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0015"
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "SO4C ",
  "ANALYSIS": "POLICY 5450005720 WAS SUSPENDED AND HAD A TRANSACTION ATTEMPTING TO DO A PAYMENT REVERSAL. ",
  "SOLUTION": "EDITED THE POLICY ON THE SCHDFL1 FILE TO BE FAR INTO THE FUTURE. THIS EXAMPLE WE USED 12\/31. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0420",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$0420 WENT DOWN WITH S0C7 IN STEP 20 IN PROGRAM CKUBMVHB ",
  "SOLUTION": "I COPIED THE SA VSAM FILES FOR THE POLICY AND AUXSEG1 DELETED THE FOLLOWING POLICY 3465004990 FROM MY COPIES RERAN FROM THE TOP USING OVERRIDES FOR MY COPIES OF THE FILES. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "POLICY FOR 04\/05\/2006 = 2150632010 PROBLEM POLICY FOR 04\/05\/2006 = 2150654760 PROBLEM POLICY FOR 02\/28\/2006 = 577A282220 PROBLEM POLICY FOR 01\/18\/2006 = 2453286980 PROBLEM POLICY FOR 11\/16\/2005 = 3465092020 PROBLEM: DID FIND ON SQL IN U DUMP AND FOUND THE FOLLOWING INFO *CKVSAMIO..&....>.......4...Y.C .* * SP.3465092020...............* *..........8.2...CKCSTGETSELECT C* *ISLAR * * .N...... DSN* *T408I SQLCODE = -811, ERROR: TH* *E RESULT OF AN EMBEDDED SELECT * * STATEMENT OR A SUB* SO NEED TO FIX PENDING CLIENT INFORMATION FOR POLICY 3465092020 TABLE CLT_ADR_RELATION BEFORE 0401 RELEASE WE HAD THIS ERROR WHEN USERS WERE TRYING TO ADD A NEW ADDRESS, NOW IT OCCURS WHEN USERS ARE TRYING TO UPDATE ADDRESS INFORMATION. QUICK WAY TO FIND ALL PROBLEM ROWS RUN TEST.CL.TOOLS(SQL$DUPA). ",
  "ANALYSIS": "USING TSO PST FOUND PROBLEM ROWS 01\/18\/06 USING TEST.CL.TOOLS(SQL$DUPA) FOUND ALL PROBLEM ROWS THEN USED TSO PST UNDER FIRE CALL TO FIX THEM. CMD F == TABLE: CLADMIN.CLT_ADR_RELATION(T2) ",
  "SOLUTION": "USING TSO PST SET ALL BUT THE MOST CURRENT EFF DATE TO HIGHER HISTORY_VLD_NBR AND MADE SURE THE CIAR_EXP_DT WAS ONLY SET TO 9999-12-31 ON THE MOST CURRENT EFFECTIVE DATE ROW. AFTER EDITING ALL NECESSARY ROWS IN PST, RAN TOOLS VERSION OF 11, WHEN IT FINISHED OK HAD PCD FORCE 11 OK TO CONTINUE CYCLE. ON 1\/18\/06, RAN TEST.CL.TOOLS(SQL$DUPA) TO VERIFY NO MORE PROBLEMS, THEN HAD CL$$0011 RE-RAN FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "AFTER CL$$0014 FINISHED OK NOTHING RAN ",
  "ANALYSIS": "BILL HAD REQUESTED CL$$0015 BE CHANGED TO RUN AFTER CL$$0100. ONCE A MONTH CL$$0016 IS ADDED TO RUN AFTER CL$$0015 WITH A DEPENDANCY ON CL$$0017 TO WAIT ON IT TO FINISH OK. SO CL$$0015 WAITED ON CL$$0100 CL$$0016 WAITED ON CL$$0015 CL$$0017 WAITED ON CL$$0016 ",
  "SOLUTION": "OPERATOR CHANGED CL$$0016 TO BE DEPENDANT ON CL$$0014 ALLOWING THE SCHEDULE TO COMPLETE. IN THE MORNING RHONDA HAD US CHANGE CL$$0017 TO NO LONGER WAIT ON 16. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1025",
  "PROBLEM": "PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "NOTICED THAT CL.ME.VSAM.BASER.MORTALTY HEADER RECORD DOES NOT MATCH CL.VSAM.BASER.MORTALTY AFTER FURTHER REVIEW FOUND SYMBOLIC VRPREFX SET TO CL.ME.VSAM.BASER BUT SHOULD BE SET TO CL.VSAM.BASER. CALLED STEVE BLAZKIEWICZ AND HAD HIM PLACE A 1 TIME CHANGE TO OVER RIDE THE SYMBOLIC AND RERUN FROM THE TOP. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTART FROM TOP USING OVER RIDE FOR SYMBOLIC VRPREFX SEE ANALYSIS FOR MORE INFORMATION. FOLLOW UP: NEED TO CHANGE THIS SYMBOLIC IN THE PROC USING BLANKET ISSUE # 3242 FOR JCL MAINTENANCE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$8100",
  "PROBLEM": "CC72 ERR-G POS 49 (156-B) DEFINITION NOT PERMITTED ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DAN HUNSINGER LOOKED AT PROBLEM AND SUGGESTED POINTING THE SYSDICT TO TEST.CL.CARDLIB. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD OPS PUT IN THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDE FOR JSTEPS 30 AND 40: \/\/STEP0010.SYSDICT DD DSN=TEST.CL.CARDLIB(UDPOLICY), \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) \/\/ DD DSN=TEST.CL.CARDLIB(UDUPARMS), \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) \/\/ DD DSN=TEST.CL.CARDLIB(UDPARMDT), \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) \/\/ DD DSN=TEST.CL.CARDLIB(UDTBLTRN), \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) HAD OPS DELETE JSTEPS 10, 20, 50 AND 60 SINCE THEY RAN SUCCESSFULLY DURING THE FIRST RUN. JOB RAN OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0130",
  "PROBLEM": "0CA AT OFFSET 33A ",
  "SOLUTION": "USE TEST.CL.TOOLS(COPYCOR) TO COPY CL.BASEB.AP.COR.EXT1(0) TO TEST...D102505 DELETE POLICY 0620172690 FROM CL.BASEB.AP.COR.EXT1(0) RERUN FROM THE TOP. JOB TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$$130P) HAS BEEN CREATED THAT CAN BE RUN OVER AND OVER TO WEED OUT THE PROBLEM POLICY RECORDS, RATHER THAN HAVING OPS RERUN THE JOB IN PRODUCTION OVER AND OVER. (YOU HAVE TO CLOSE FVDCFFD DURING YOUR RERUN.) (FVDCFFD = CL.VSAM.BASEOL.CORRES) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "(RELATED TO ONLINE) IF THE POLICY IS ON THE POLICY FILE AND NOT ON THE SCHEDULER FILE, IT WILL NOT DISPLAY IN 3270. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS CASE, A RECORD WOULD NEED TO BE ADDED TO THE SCHE SCHEDULER FILE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "FILE MARVEL, THIS CAN BE ACCOMPLISHED BY LOCATING THE TWO SCHEDULE RECORDS IN WHICH THIS POLICY WOULD RESIDE BASED ON POLICY NUMBER ORDER. NEXT, REPEAT THE PREVIOUS SCHEDULE RECORD IN FILE MARVEL. THEN CHANGE THE REPEATED RECORD'S POLICY NUMBER TO BE THE POLICY NUMBER YOU ARE WORKING WITH AND CHANGE THE SCHEDULE DATE COLUMN 12-16 TO BE X'00001C001C'. THEN SAVE AND EXIT FILE MARVEL. PROBLEM: (RELATED TO BATCH CKAP01V) IF THE POLICY IS NOT ON THE POLICY FILE AND IS ON THE SCHEDULER FILE YOU WILL GET ERROR AP0108 IN CKAP01V. ANALYSIS: AN AP0108 WILL OCCUR IF THERE IS A POLICY THAT IS ON THE ON THE SCHEDULER SCHDFL1 FILE AND IT IS NOT ON THE INFORCE POLICY. THE SYSTEM IS TRYING TO READ THE INFORCE RECORD OR ACTIVITY FILE AND IT IS NOT THERE. THIS CAN OCCUR IF A POLICY IS DROPPED OFF THE INFORCE OR OR ACTIVITY AND NOT THE SCHEDULER FILE. 108 2 AP0108 - FILE I\/O PARAMETERS ARE INVALID FILENAME=FVDUNLD STATUS=1 SEVERE ERROR - RUN ABORTED FOR THIS USER SOLUTION: USING FILE MARVEL, DELETE THE POLICY'S SCHEDULE RECORD FROM THE SCHEDULE FILE. THEN SAVE AND EXIT FILE MARVEL. JOB "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0020",
  "PROBLEM": "OPERATOR CALLED WHEN CL$$0020 APPEARED TO BE IN A LOOP. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "BILL HAD OPERATOR CANCEL THE JOB WITH A DUMP. SIMILAR SITUATION OCCURRED IN THIS JOB ON 6\/9\/2004. IDENTIFIED THE BAD POLICY - THIS POLICY ALSO HAD A UW ID BEGINNING WITH J966*. ",
  "SOLUTION": "'CURRENT' POLICY WAS '0620228390' BILL COPIED CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G3538V00 TO TEST.CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G3538 THEN I DELETED THE RECORDS FOR THIS POLICY FROM THE PRODUCTION FILE VIA FILE MARVEL THROUGH FIRE CALL. I HAD PCD SET UP CL$$0020 OVERRIDES: I HAD OPERATOR RESTART JOB IN STEP0030 WITH OVERRIDE FOR GDG01='0'. --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! THE RERUN WAS GOOD. ON 10\/10\/2005, ATTEMPTED TO CONTACT THE CLERK ON THIS POLICY, BUT SHE WAS OUT. CONTACTED CARLA NEALY, AND HAD HER CHANGE THE UW ID FROM J966CLV TO J866CLV AND REORDER PAGES FOR THIS POLICY 0620228390. CHECKED WITH UNDERWRITER DEBBIE MINCEFF, AND FOUND THAT THE PML UNDERWRITER ID IS ENTERED IN WITH THE POLICY APPLICATION INFORMATION, THUS CAN BE PRONE TO INVALID ENTRIES. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB ABENDED IN STEP 20 WITH S0C1 DUE TO EMPTY ROW IN CLT_OBJ_RELATION (CISLOR). SQLCODE +100 ROW NOT FOUND FOR FETCH, UPDATE OR DELETE, OR THE IS AN EMPTY TABLE ",
  "ANALYSIS": "COULD NOT FIND SQLCODE IN SYSPDUMP, INSTEAD FOUND POLICY 5110037700 IN IDIREPRT. CALLED RHONDA, AND SHE WALKED ME THROUGH THE PROCESS AND SHOWED ME WHAT TO CHANGE IN CLIENT. THE PROBLEM IS THAT NO CLT_OBJ_RELATION RECORDS EXIST FOR THE OWNER ADR_SEQ_NBR. ",
  "SOLUTION": "USED FIRECALL TO CHANGE THE OWNER ADR_SEQ_NBR FROM 4 TO 0. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1950",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND=S000 U4038 REASON=00000001 633 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB IS A REQUEST ULTIM JOB, AND THE FOLLOWING WAS CODED INCORRECTLY IN THE JCL: \/\/* THIS IS THE AGENT LIST \/\/STEP0010.IAGENT DD * 01995 \/\/* I LOOKED AT THE PARMAGT CARDLIB, AND NOTICED THAT ALL THE ENTRIES BEGAN IN THE FIRST COLUMN. THE OVERRIDE SHOULD LOOK LIKE THIS: \/\/* THIS IS THE AGENT LIST \/\/STEP0010.IAGENT DD * 01995 \/\/* ",
  "SOLUTION": "CONTACTED OPERATOR AND ASKED HER TO MOVE THE AGENT NUMBER OVER ONE SPACE TO THE LEFT AND TO RESTART THE JOB FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0430",
  "PROBLEM": "JCL ERROR ACF01004 LOGONID ACFBCHID NOT FOUND AULHO ",
  "ANALYSIS": "HAD OPS AND PCD LOOK INTO THE PROBLEM. THIS JOB DID HAVE PROBLEMS THE NIGHT BEFORE AND A JCL CHANGE WAS DONE THEN. ",
  "SOLUTION": "THE JCL GOT CHANGED THE NIGHT BEFORE PERMANENTLY BY MISTAKE. THE PROBLEM WAS WITH THE CONTROLM AUTOEDIT VARIABLES: CKVL80PE %%PDTTTE %%PDTTTE %%CLDAT7-%%CLDAT7 AP-VSAM %%PDTTTE WAS TYPE AS %%PYEAR. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0007",
  "PROBLEM": "FOUND IN THE ABENDING STEPS SYSTSPRT SYSOUT DB2P NOT OPERATIONAL, RETRY COUNT IS ZERO OR DB2 IS ABNORMALLY ENDING. DSN IS TERMINATING ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PCD HAD PROBLEMS WITH DB2, ALL OF THESE NEEDED TO BE RE-RAN FROM THE TOP. JOBS LISTED BELOW NEED TO HAVE GDG'S DELETED BEFORE RE-RUN FROM THE TOP: CL$$0420 - SEE BOMBLOG FOR GDGS CL$$0004 - SEE RESTART DOC FOR GDGS CL$$0006 - SEE RESTART DOC FOR GDGS CL$$0007 - SEE RESTART DOC FOR GDGS BECAUSE OF THE VOLUMN OPERATIONS CONTACTED ON CALL JOBS WERE RE-RAN FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0430",
  "PROBLEM": "IN SYSOUT CL$$0430 STEP0030 FOUND THE FOLLOWING ********************************* TOP OF 1ST RECORD IS NOT A DATE RECORD TAPE2 MP CANNOT CONTINUE ******************************** BOTTOM ",
  "ANALYSIS": "BECAUSE CL$$0420 FAILED AND WAS RE-RAN EMPTY GDG'S WERE PULLED IN AND CAUSED THIS ERROR. ",
  "SOLUTION": "IN FIRE CALL DELETE THE FOLLOWING: CL.CL$$0420.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN.G0228V00 CL.CL$$0420.POLSEQ.EXTSRSL.G0228V00 CL.CL$$0420.POLSEQ.EXTSRPM.G0228V00 RE-RUN JOB FROM TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0420",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP FAILED WITH CC=12, FOUND THIS IN DUMP NEXT DAY: DB2P NOT OPERATIONAL, RETRY COUNT IS ZERO ",
  "ANALYSIS": "I COULD NOT SEE THE REAL PROBLEM UNTIL MORNING. ACTUAL PROBLEM WAS DB2 ABENDING DURING RUN. APPEARED TO BE A POSSIBLE DATE PROBLEM. ",
  "SOLUTION": "WHEN THIS JOB FAILS WE NEED TO SEE IF THE FOLLOWING GDG'S WERE CREATED DURING THE RUN AND DELETE THEM &PREFIX.CL$$0420.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN() &PREFIX.CL$$0420.POLSEQ.EXTSRSL() &PREFIX.CL$$0420.POLSEQ.EXTSRPM() FIX ANY ADITIONAL PROBLEMS AND RE-RUN FROM THE TOP ON 9\/7\/05 HAD PCD OVER RIDE ODATE, BUT FORGOT TO DELETE GDG'S WHICH CAUSED CL$$0430 TO ABEND "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0020",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB ABENDING IN SOC7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "POLICIES 3465102120 & 3465102130 WERE GETTING SOC7. ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED FILE TO TEST.CL.TDR.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G3494 EDIT PROD FILE REMOVING POLICIES LISTED ABOVE PCD RESTARTED JOB IN ABENDING STEP, USING CONTROL D RESEARCH SOC7 IN AM 9\/8\/05 ISSUE 6499\/SPR IN8686 0401 RESOLVED THIS --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0830",
  "PROBLEM": "COND CODE 99 CAUSED BY WS-TOTAL-01-AMOUNT NOT = WS-TOTAL-07-AMOUNT ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SUMMARY TOTAL OF ALL COMPANIES REPORT HAS CORRECT TOTALS OF AMOUNT AND CHECK COUNT FOR EACH COMPANY. THE TOTALS OF ALL COMPANIES IS NOT CORRECT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "ISSUE 5875 & 5876 NO ONE HAS ASKED ABOUT THESE TOTALS. THEY DO NOT APPEAR TO BE USED. HAD OPS FORCE JOB COMPLETE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0690",
  "PROBLEM": "OPERATIONS CALLED TO SAY WE WOULD NOT HAVE A CDFT FILE FROM LINDA KENTZ. THIS FILE FEEDS INTO CL$$0690. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED AT THE RESTART LOGIC FOR CL$$0690 AND FOUND WE COULD CREATE AN EMPTY FILE FROM STEP0030 TO FEED INTO CL$$0700. ",
  "SOLUTION": "USED FIRECALL TO EMPTY FILE CL.ADJUST.OUTPUT. HAD CL$$0690 FORCED COMPLETE. FOLLOW-UP AFTERWARDS THEY CAN SEND AN EMPTY CDFT FILE JOB CL$$0690 WILL RUN WITH AN EMPTY FILE. THEREFORE WE SHOULD NOT GET CALLED ON THIS IN THE FUTURE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0020",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C4 (PROTECTION EXCEPTION) CKETRLSU ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CURRENT POLICY 3465096800 CURRENT POLICY 3465104690 P1WET 12\/27\/2005 ",
  "SOLUTION": "SAVED INPUT FILE. USED FIRECALL TO REMOVE POLICY FROM CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G3474V00. RESTART JOB IN STEP0030 AS RESTART INSTRUCTIONS STATED. --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1160",
  "PROBLEM": "+INVALID USER ID PASSED TO CKTBLOCT +- - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - CL$$1160 STEP0010 CL$$1160 - ABEND=S04C CEE3250C THE SYSTEM OR USER ABEND U 001 R=NULL FROM COMPILE UNIT CKABEND AT ENTRY POINT CKABEND ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CALLING CHAIN M724TAIT M724TAIT M724CSVL M724CSVL CKBSFMUC CKBSFMUC CKTBLOCT CKTBLOCT CKABEND CKABEND CKTBLOCT CALL ALONG WITH MESSAGE FOR INVALID USER CODE CAUSED PROGRAM CHECKING LOOKING FOR WHAT ESTABLISHES USER CODE. FOUND M724CSVL WAS NOT CORRECTLY ESTABLISHING A USER CODE FOR UTABLES LOOKUPS. EVALUATION OF CRITICALITY OF JOB > WERE THERE OTHER SYSTEMS DEPENDENT ON JOB ANSWER WAS NO. THIS WAS WRONG. IND$0010 WAS HELD UP BY THIS. > DOES THIS HOLD UP ANY CYBERLIFE JOBS WHICH ARE NEED TO GET THE ON-LINE UP. NO > IS THERE DATA GOING EXTERNAL TO AUL. NO > DEFER THE JOB AND FIX IT TOMORROW ",
  "SOLUTION": "DEFERED THE JOB FOR ANALYSIS AND SOLUTION TOMORROW > WE HELD UP IND$0010 BUT THIS DID NOT HAVE NEGATIVE IMPACT ON THEIR WORK. ESTABLISH USER CODE IN PARM IN M724CSVL FOR CALL TO CKBSFMUC. PROGRAMMING CHANGES WERE REQUIRED TO FIX THE JOB. ISSUE 6411 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0820",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC-4 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS IS A CLIENT PROBLEM. HOWEVER, THE CLIENTS APPEAR TO BE OKAY. DROPPING POLICIES IS CAUSING THE NEXT POLICY TO GO DOWN. DUMPS ARE TAGGING CISLOR. ALSO, IF WE DROP POLICIES IN FRONT OF THE POLICIES ABENDING, THE ABENDING POLICIES WILL WORK. IT ACTS LIKE THE CKETRLST FLUSH IS NOT BEING DONE BUT IT IS. MADE COPY OF CL.CL$$0100.STEP0450.DACCTING(0) AND REMOVED BAD POLICIES FROM THE COPY AND SORTED THE FILE USING A MODIFIED VERSION OF THE SORT CARD FOR ISSUE CL6368 (CLS82003). HAD OPS PUT IN AN OVERRIDE TO BRING IN THE MODIFIED COPY INTO STEP0020.SEQUEN. *NOTE* NEW CODE HAD BEEN MOVED TO PRODUCTION IMPACTING THIS PROGRAM (ISSUE CL6368) ",
  "SOLUTION": "WE RAN A DUMMY FILE INTO STEP0010 TO ALLOW PROCESSING TO CONTINUE. THE NEXT DAY, WE BACKED OUT THE CODING CHANGES, COMPLETED A RUN, AND PASSED THE FILE TO ABC. THEY ARE ABLE TO ACCEPT THIS FILE DURING THE DAY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0600",
  "PROBLEM": "DST CALLED AND REPORTED BLANKS IN RECORDS FOR TRAN CODE SUFFIX, RECORD CODE, SHARE BALANCE INDICATOR. THIS IMPACTS THE DFA FILE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS WAS ON A 'LN' FUND. THERE WAS NOT TRANSLATION IN AUUDT518 FOR LOAN ACTIVITY ",
  "SOLUTION": "ALL ACTIVITY IMPACTING A LOAN FUND SHOULD BE BYPASSED "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0911",
  "PROBLEM": "THIS JOB EXPERIENCED AN ARRAY OVERFLOW. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "COPY PROGRAM DOWN TO TEST. CHANGE LIMIT ON WS-FUND-RECORDS FROM 50 TO 100. RECOMPILE AND RELINK PROGRAM INTO TEST. HAVE OPERATOR ADD AN OVERRIDE TO INCLUDE TEST.CL.PROCLIB AND RERUN JOB FROM TOP. ",
  "SOLUTION": "JOB COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. ISSUE #6393 OPENED AND MIGRATED TO PRODUCTION NEXT DAY FOR FIX. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "WE HAVE A RARE SITUATION IN PRODUCTION RELATED TO MISSING 78 STEP SEGMENTS THAT WE ARE TRYING TO TRACK AND DEBUG FOR EDB. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "IF WE GET THE FOLLOWING SHOUT \"EDB Z STUB NOT CREATED (STEP0210), CREATE BKUPS FOR DEBUG\" ",
  "SOLUTION": "NOTIFY BILL TURNER AND RHONDA WATSON SO WE CAN CAPTURE THE CYCLE MASTER FILES PRIOR TO TIME DRIVEN. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0010",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP0040 GOT JCL ERROR BECAUSE CONNECT DIRECT JOB TO COPY OMNI FILE WAS RUNNING AT SAME TIME. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "TIMING ISSUE PCD TO RESOLVE. CONNECT DIRECT SHOULD RUN BEFORE CL$$0010 ALWAYS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CHECKED FILE CL.FUND.PRICES TO MAKE SURE IT IS CORRECT. RE-RUN CL$$0010 FROM STEP0050. JOB FINISHED NORMALLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0010",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP0040 GOT JCL ERROR BECAUSE OMNI FILE HAD NOT BEEN LOADED TO THE MAINFRAME FROM THE LAN. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE SEPARATE ACCOUNTS ON CALL PERSON WAS CONTACTED TO GET PRICE FILE FROM OMNI LOADED TO THE MAINFRAME. WAS ABLE TO RE-RUN FROM TOP (AS DATA BASE FIX WAS MADE FOR ABEND IN CL$$0011 ALSO). ",
  "SOLUTION": "ONCE THE OMNI PRICE FILE WAS LOADED TO THE MAINFRAME THE JOB WAS RAN FROM THE TOP, TO GET GOOD IMAGE COPY AS CL$$0011 HAD ALSO ABENDED. NORMALLY WE WOULD HAVE RE-STARTED IN THAT STEP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB ABENDED IN STEP 20 WITH S0C1 DUE TO EMPTY ROW ROW IN CLT_OBJ_RELATION (CISLOR). SQLCODE +100 ROW NOT FOUND FOR FETCH, UPDATE OR DELETE, OR THE IS AN EMPTY TABLE ",
  "ANALYSIS": "REVIEW DUMP TO FIND POLICY # 0710019190 WITH SQLCODE 100, CISLOR. CONTACTED SANDI JEFFS MANAGER ON CALL. SANDI SAID THAT BILL TURNER HAD SIMILAR PROBLEM. THE PROBLEM IS CLIENT ONLY SHOWS SHOW PENDING CLT_OBJ_RELATION RECORDS. OBJ_SYS_ID = CK4P ALSO NEEDED OBJ_SYS_ID = CK4I WHEN WE HAVE RECORD ON POLICY MASTER VSAM. EXAMPLE OF DATA IN PRINCETON: TCH_OBJECT_KEY HISTORY_VLD_NBR CIOR_EFF_DT OBJ_SYS_ID -------CH(20)------- ---SMALLINT---- ---DATE---- --CH(4)--- 000710019190 0 2005-06-09 CK4P 000710019190 0 2005-06-09 CK4P 000710019190 0 2005-06-09 CK4P 000710019190 0 2005-06-09 CK4P ",
  "SOLUTION": "USING FIRE CALL SANDI COPIED THE CK4P RECORD AND CREATED ALL OF THE NECESSARY CK4I CLIENT RECORDS. USE LINE COMMANDS C COPY AND A AFTER AND THEN CHANGE THE CIOR_EFF_DATE TO CURRENT DATE. THE LAST ROW MAY NEED TO DO A C COPY B BEFORE AND THEN CHANGE THE CIOR_EFF_DATE TO CURRENT DATE. IF YOU GET AN (E) ERROR MESSAGE, HIT F-1 TO GET MORE INFO. TO UNDO CHANGES IF NEEDED, ENTER 'UNDO' OR 'UNDO ALL'. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0910",
  "PROBLEM": "FVDTBLS DD STATEMENT MISSING ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PROC, JCL AND PROGRAM HADN'T CHANGED. BUT JOB WAS STILL LOOKING FOR THE UTABLES FILE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD OPS PUT IN AN OVERRIDE IN THIS STEP FOR THE UTABLES FILE AND RERAN FROM STEP0020. PROBLEM: JOB LOOPING ANALYSIS: JOB NORMALLY TAKES SECONDS. THESE RUNS WERE TAKING HOURS. HAD OPS CANCEL JOB WITH A DUMP. SOLUTION: FOUND A POLICY IN SYSUDUMP THAT KEPT POPPING UP MORE THAN OTHER POLICIES. MADE COPY OF INPUT FILE CL.CL$$0910.MLIR AND REMOVED POLICY. RAN JOB IN MY UNIT TEST WORLD. JOB ENDED FINE. SINCE THE OUTPUT FILE WAS EMPTY, WENT AHEAD AND FORCED JOB OK IN PROD. POLICY WAS 5448953470. WILL INVESTIGATE AS TO WHY PROGRAM WAS LOOPING ON THIS POLICY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "+CKUB01 CEEHDLR CONDITION HANDLER SERVICE INVOKED + VSAM ERROR - FILE=FVDBLKC, INCODE=8, OUTCODE=4, R15=08, + 108 2 AP0108 - FILE I\/O PARAMETERS ARE UBMC00 + FILENAME=FVDBLKC STATUS=4 +ERROR RETURN FROM CKUBMC00 +- - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - ****** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE FVDBLKC FILE WAS EMPTY FOR UNKNOWN REASONS. TAMMY REYNOLDS REBUILT THE FILE WITH TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$$BLKC) AND TEST.CL.TOOLS(BLDBLK). RESTORE JOBS CL$$R060 AND CL$$RC30 WERE RUN. CL$$0100 WAS REUN FROM THE TOP. ****** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0010",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB SET UP TO FAIL IF THIS COMPARE STEP GET'S CC=1. TO INDICATE THE FUNDS CONTROL CARD FUNDCMPR IN UPLOAD DID NOT MATCH WITH THE FUND PRICING FILE. STEP0070 PGM=ISRSUPC EXECUTED - COND CODE 0001 RC=000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "REVIEW FILE CL.CL$$0010.ERRRPT(0) TO FIND FUND MNEMONIC ID'S OF FUNDS THAT HAVE NO PRICE. CONTACT SEPARATE ACCOUNTS ON CALL PERSON TO GET FUND PRICE FILE UPDATED AND RELOADED TO THE MAINFRAME FROM LAN. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DELETE CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES(0) PER RESTART DOC. ONCE FUND PRICES ARE LOADED AGAIN RESTART JOB IN STEP 50 PER RESTART INSTRUCTIONS. SOLUTION2: SINCE IT WAS GETTING LATE, USING FIRECALL I MODIFIED CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES(0) BY ADDING THE FUNDS THAT WERE MISSING AND USED THE PRIOR NIGHT'S PRICES. THIS WAS A DECISION MADE BY ME AND THE SEPARATE ACCOUNTS ON-CALL PERSON. HAD OPS FORCE OKAY CL$$0010. SENT AN EMAIL TO THE SEPARATE ACCOUNTS ON-CALL PERSON, CYBERLIFE PRODUCTION AND CYBERLIFE TRIAGE ALERTING THEM OF THE FUNDS MISSING AND THE INCORRECT PRICES USED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0430",
  "PROBLEM": "CC16 AT THE BOTTOM OF THE REPORT IT SHOWS... ATTENTION! ERRORS WERE SIGNALED IN THIS REPORT ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CLQPETRX IS AN ULTIM. THE REPORTS SHOWED THERE WERE ERRORS. THUS THE CC16. ",
  "SOLUTION": "THIS IS AN ISSUE WITH THE NEW ULTIM WERE A CC16 WILL GET PRODUCED IF THE REPORTS SHOWS ERRORS. THE REST OF THE JOB FINISHED FINE. FORCED JOB OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0810",
  "PROBLEM": "LOOKING IN SYSOUT JSTEP010 STEP0180 SEEING FOLLOWING ********************************* TOP OF DATA ************************** IGZ0020S A LOGIC ERROR OCCURRED. NEITHER FILE STATUS NOR A DECLARATIVE D724AGC5 AT RELATIVE LOCATION X'0D62'. THE STATUS CODE WAS 46. FROM COMPILE UNIT D724AGC5 AT ENTRY POINT D724AGC5 AT STATEMENT ENTRY OFFSET +00000D62 AT ADDRESS 0C4019D2. ******************************** BOTTOM OF DATA ************************ ",
  "ANALYSIS": "A LOGIC ERROR IS IN THE CODE IN PROGRAM D724AGC5, IS PERFORMING 8000-READ-LAPSE-FILE WITH OUT CHECKING TO MAKE SURE END OF FILE HAS NOT OCCURED. - ABEND WAS MODEL CYCLE CL$M0810, BUT THIS COULD HAPPEN IN PROD. ",
  "SOLUTION": "WORK AROUND TO RESOLVE ABEND UNTIL ISSUE # 5606 IS INSTALLED INTO PRODUCTION REMOVING THIS STEP. RESTART JOB IN ABENDING STEP. AND ADD LINE TO USE TAMMY'S LOAD LIBRARY. SEE BELOW AS EXAMPLE: \/\/CL$M0810 JOB (TCL$$,1010A),'COMMISSIONS \/ MV',CLASS=P,TYPRUN=HOLD, \/\/ REGION=0M, \/\/ RESTART=JSTEP010.STEP0190, \/\/ GROUP=CONTROLD, \/\/ MSGCLASS=J \/\/* \/\/USERPROC JCLLIB ORDER=(TEST.CL.TDR.PROCLIB,AUL1.PROCLIB) \/\/JOBLIB INCLUDE MEMBER=CL$$JOBL "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0013",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB CL$$0013 ABENDED WITH THE FOLLOWING MESSAGE OUT IAMW04 DD=VSAM3 OPEN ERROR - DATASET NOT AVAILABLE, IN USE BY JOB CL$ VSAM ERROR - FILE=VSAM3 , INCODE=1, OUTCODE=9, R15=08, ERRCODE=00A8 CKA10060: AUXSEG FILE OPEN FAILED. 9 - - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CL$$0018 WAS RUNNING WHILE CL$$0013 WAS TRYING TO RUN ",
  "SOLUTION": "RUN CL$$R013 TO RESTORE DATA SETS, THEN RUN CL$$0013 AGAIN FROM THE TOP. JOB ENDED OK. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "CONNECT DIRECT THAT COPIES FILE FROM JOB CL$$9801 FAILED. USES AUL1.PROCESS(CLTERM) TO COPY FILE DSN='CL.CL$$9801.TERM.AGENTS' TO I:\\SHARE\\ULTIM\\AGTTERM.TXT ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED FOR PATH ON THE LAN AND ONLY FOUND I:\\SHARE CREATED ULTIM FOLDER AND RE-RAN CONNECT DIRECT IT FAILED BECAUSE THE DS SERVER HAD LOST CONNECTION PER DAN DRAKE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "MANUALLY LOADED THE FILE TO THE LAN, LET DAN NOAH KNOW. DAN DRAKE WILL WORK WITH DAN NOAH AND USERS TO UPDATE THE CONNECT DIRECT PROCESS CLTERM IF FILE PATH ON LAN HAS CHANGED. (DAN NOAH SAID PATH SHOULD BE I:\\ULTIM\\AGTTERM.TXT?) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$9801",
  "PROBLEM": "ON REQUEST CLULTIM REPORT GETTING COND CODE 0016 COMPILER OPTIONS: YES,ERR ************************************************************************ * MAY 20, 2005 09:26:46 U L T I M 2004 ************************************************************************ CONSOLIDATED ERROR LISTIN CYCLE PROGRAM --STATEMENT--- ITEM COND SEG ERROR 246494 POLORPH LINE-7 00748 2 F XLFJO 246494 POLORPH SET 00897 25 F XLFJO 339593 POLORPH SET 00643 1 F XLFJO 473881 POLORPH SET 00643 1 F XLFJO THIS ULTIM CAUSES A CONNECT DIRECT TO KICK OFF TO COPY FILE DSN='CL.CL$$9801.TERM.AGENTS' CDFT8104 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ON GOING PROBLEM WITH ULTIM REPORT PER RHONDA WATSON. ",
  "SOLUTION": "PER RHONDA WATSON HAVE JOB CL$$9801 FORCED COMPLETE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$UPDF",
  "PROBLEM": "IEC030I B37-04,IFG0554A,CL$$UPDF,STEP0020,SORTWK01 FROM STEP0020 SYSOUT: RESOURCES WERE UNAVAILABLE FOR DYNAMIC ALLOCATION OF WORK DATA SETS (970C) ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SPACE PROBLEM ",
  "SOLUTION": "TRIED UPPING THE SPACE OF THE SORTOUT DATASET FROM (4000,(300,100) TO (4000,(600,200) THEN AGAIN TO (4000,(700,200). THEN TRIED UPPING THE CARDLIB CLR10130 FROM DYNALLOC=(SYSDA,2) TO DYNALLOC=(SYSDA,3). FINALLY HAD PCD CALL DASD ONCALL. THEY ADDED: \/\/SORTWK01 DD SPACE=(CYL,(200,50)), WORK \/\/ UNIT=SYSDA \/\/SORTWK02 DD SPACE=(CYL,(200,50)), WORK \/\/ UNIT=SYSDA \/\/SORTWK03 DD SPACE=(CYL,(200,50)), WORK* \/\/ UNIT=SYSDA IT RAN FINE THEN. ***P1SEC FIX. DASD PERSON HAD ME ADD FOLLOWING OVERRIDES(EMAIL BELOW) PLEASE RESTART CL$$UPDF FROM THE TOP WITH THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDE... \/\/STEP0020.SORTWK01 DD UNIT=SYSDA,SPACE=(CYL,(200,50)) \/\/STEP0020.SORTWK02 DD UNIT=SYSDA,SPACE=(CYL,(200,50)) \/\/STEP0020.SORTWK03 DD UNIT=SYSDA,SPACE=(CYL,(200,50)) ADD THE ABOVE LINES BEFORE THE SORTOUT ***END P1SEC FIX. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0035",
  "PROBLEM": "IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 929 USER COMPLETION CODE=4039 REASON CODE=00000000 ABEND=S04C U0000 REASON=00000000 932 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "D7245101 WAS EXPERIENCING A S0C7 ON POLICY 0710007900 ",
  "SOLUTION": "USED TEST.CL.TOOLS(DROP0035) TO CREATE COPY OF PENDING FILE AND DROP THE POLICY. USED AN OVERRIDE TO POINT TO THE COPY AND RERUN CL$$0035 FROM THE TOP. IT ABENDED ON 0620212330 WITH A SQLCODE 100 FOR CISLOR BUT THE POLICY COULD BE PULLED UP ONLINE. THEORIZED THAT THE POLICY WAS BEING UPDATED WHEN THE PENDING FILE WAS SNAPPED. RERAN DROP0035 TO MAKE A NEW COPY. CL$$0035 ABENDED ON THE ORIGINAL WHOLE LIFE POLICY. CHECKED DATASET AND FOUND THAT DROP0035 HAD NOT DELETED THE POLICY OFF OF THE PENDING COPY. USED FILE MARVEL TO REMOVE IT AND RERAN CL$$0035 TO A GOOD CONCLUSION. SENT EMAIL TO ECOMMERCE TO NOTIFY. 5\/2\/05 - I UPDATED DROP0035 TO ADD THE COMPANY CODE AND IT DELETED THE POLICY CORRECTLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1940",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND=S0C1 ABEND ON TRAILER GET ROUTINE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "REVIEWED IN UNIT TEST AREA AND WAS ABLE TO GET GOOD RUN BY CHANGING A PARM CARD PASSED IN JCL. OTHER WISE KEPT GETTING SOC1 ON DIFFERENT POL #'S. # 2 ANALYSIS: OK, IN THE CALLING CHAIN OF CYBERLIFE PROGRAMS USED THE PLAN DESCRIPTION FILE IS TRYING TO BE ACCESSED. THE FILE NAME GIVEN TO THE PLAN DESCRIPTION FILE IS VSAM6, WHICH IS THE FILE NAME THAT IS USED IN PROGRAM M7240CCR FOR THE INFORCE POLICY MASTER VSAM. THIS WILL NEED AN ISSUE TO BE GENERATED TO GET THE PROBLEM RESOLVED. MADE CHANGE IN UNIT TEST LAND TO USE VSAM4 FOR POLICY MASTER AND VSAM6 FOR PDF FILE AND WAS ABLE TO GENERATE THE REPORT. WILL PRINT AND SEND OUT TO USER WHO ORDERED IT. BIG THANKS TO LINDA PRAED FOR WORKING WITH ME TO RESOLVE THIS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CHANGE PARM PARMTYPE TO M INSTEAD OF R RE-RUN FROM TOP, JOB FINISHED OK. LINDA PRAED SAYS WE GET DIFFERENT DATA WHEN WE CHANGE THAT PARM. NEW SOLUTION: EDIT PROGRAM M7240CCR TO USE VSAM4 AS POLICY MASTER FILE NAME. EDIT CL$$1940 PROC TO USE VSAM4 FOR POLICY MASTER NAME, AND VSAM6 FOR PLAN DESCRIPTION FILE, WHICH WAS NOT PREVIOUSLY LISTED IN THE PROC\/JCL. RAN OUT OF MY UNIT TEST AREA AND GOT THE JOB TO WORK OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND S04C ",
  "ANALYSIS": "IF STEP0030 ABENDS, LOOK AT THE REPORT THAT IS CREATED IN STEP0040. THE CONDITION CODE ON STEP0040 IS COND=EVEN. IT RUNS AND PRINTS THE ERROR REPORT FROM STEP0030. LOOK IN CONTROL D TO FIND IT. WE FOUND THE PROBLEM POLICY HAD A 4 DIGIT AGENT CODE AND WAS CAUSING CKAGTADV TO CALL CKABEND BECAUSE THE AGENT RECORD COULD NOT BE FOUND. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DELETE THE BAD POLICY. HERE ARE THE STEPS TO DO THAT: 1) CHECK RESTART INSTRUCTIONS - CURRENTLY SAY TO RUN RESTORE CL$$R060 (IN TEST.CL.JCLLIB) ***** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** CL$$RC30 (IN TEST.CL.JCLLIB) 2) RUN DELETE JOBS (SET UP CARDLIBS OR ACTUAL JOB) CL$$PNDD (TEST.CL.JCLLIB) CL$$POLD (TEST.CL.JCLLIB) CL$$SQLB (TEST.CL.JCLLIB) DROPACT (TEST.CL.TOOLS) 3) MAKE BACKUP OF &PREFIX.CL.COMBPEND 4) MANUALLY DELETE BAD POLICY (3 RECORDS) FROM &PREFIX.CL.COMBPEND 5) RESTART CL$$0100 FROM TOP "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0007",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC4 4039 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "IN THE SYSOUT IT GAVE THE FOLLOWING MESSAGE... SECONDARY EXTENTS WERE NOT SPECIFIED OR WERE NOT AVAILABLE. THOUGHT THAT IT MAY BE JUST A TIMING ISSUE WHERE NOT ENOUGH SPACE WAS AVAILABLE AT THE TIME OF THE RUN. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RERUN JOB FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0520",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC4 +IDI0082E DB2 CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQL RETURN CODE -1 IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 194 USER COMPLETION CODE=4039 REASON CODE=00000000 TIME=00.47.36 SEQ=03483 CPU=0000 ASID=0089 PSW AT TIME OF ERROR 078D1400 85DFB3EE ILC 2 INTC 0D NO ACTIVE MODULE FOUND NAME=UNKNOWN DATA AT PSW 05DFB3E8 - 00181610 0A0D58D0 D00498EC AR\/GR 0: 80BAAE88\/84000000 1: 0001DCF8\/84000FC7 2: 00000000\/003190F0 3: 00000000\/00000000 4: 00000000\/003190F0 5: 00000000\/00000718 6: 00000000\/0C42E668 7: 00000000\/00000010 8: 00000000\/85DEF454 9: 00000000\/0031983F A: 00000000\/00318C84 B: 00000000\/05DFB318 C: 00000000\/003158B8 D: 00000000\/0031B3D8 E: 00000000\/85DEF594 F: 00000000\/00000000 END OF SYMPTOM DUMP IEF450I CL$$0520 STEP0010 CL$$0520 - ABEND=S04C U0000 REASON ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE COMBINATION OF USING \/ VS - IN THE DATE OVERRIDE AND CROSSING OVER JANUARY 31 CAUSED THIS ABEND. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RERUN JOB FROM THE TOP HAVING PCD USE AN ODATE OF FEBRUARY 1. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0004",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C4 THE SYSTEM DETECTED A DATA EXCEPTION(SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=0C7 FROM COMPILE UNIT R724AGT2 AT ENTRY POINT R724AGT2 AT COMPILE UNIT OFFSET +000021C8 AT ENTRY OFFSET +000021C8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED AT COMPILED R724AGT2 AND FOUND THE OFFSET DETERMINED THE BUSINESS PHONE NUMBER HAD GARBAGE ",
  "SOLUTION": "THIS JOB USES THE SA FILES. SO FOUND AGENT IN DUMP USED FIRECALL TO PUT ZEROS IN THE BUSINESS PHONE NUMBER. RERAN JOB FROM TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0110",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C4 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "COMMISSION RATE FILE ERROR. 01\/25\/2005 PUT IN EXPEDITER TO FIND THAT POLICY 2453275380 WAS GETTING A RETURN CODE OF '1' FROM THE READ OF THE COMMISSION RATE FILE. IT WAS TRYING TO PROCESS A CONTRACT THAT DID NOT EXIST ON THE COMMISSION RATE FILE. 8\/12\/2005 RSW TRIED DROPPING CURRENT KEY POLICY RECORD, RUNNING R110 AND RERUNNING CL$$0110. JOB ABENDED ON LATER POLICY. EVENTUALLY DETERMINED WE NEEDED TO DROP POLICIES BEFORE CURRENT KEY UNTIL WE FIND THE BAD POLICY. I SET UP A JOB WITH STEPS 0010,0050 AND 0060 AND DELETED RECORDS FROM A BACKUP OF CL.BASEB.COMMISSN.EXT I DELETED RECORDS THAT HAD VALUES THAT MATCHED THE COMM RATE FILE KEY THAT WAS BEING BUILT. I HAD COMPILED CKCMCC00 INTO MY OWN LIBRARY NON-CLIENT. THAT VERSION OF THE PROGRAM PRINTED THE KEY IN THE SYSLIST OUTPUT. THE PRODUCTION VERSION DID NOT. LATER I REALIZED THAT THE ABENDING POLICY WAS IN THE DUMP AT: BLW=000 X'0000' FOR CKCMCC00. ALSO, THE ABENDING POLICY WAS NOT THE 'CURRENT KEY' FOR SEQUEN2 IN THE DUMP. THE ABENDING POLICY WAS SEVERAL RECORDS BEFORE CURRENT KEY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "REMOVED POLICY FROM CL.BASEB.COMMISSION.EXT FILE. RESTORED FILES AND RERAN FROM THE TOP. A PROGRAM FIX WAS MADE TO CKCMCC00 (ISSUE 6032) TO RESET THE ACF-CONTRACT-SW WHEN EACH RECORD WAS READ. 8\/15\/2005 RSW FOUND THAT THE GA ON THE ABENDING POLICY DID NOT HAVE A CONTRACT ON THE DATE THE POLICY WAS ISSUED. AUL MOD CL0948 JUST FINDS A CONTRACT WITH THE SAME LEVEL, IF THERE ISN'T A CONTRACT WITH THE RIGHT DATES. SO CKCMCC00 WAS BUILDING THE COMM RATE FILE KEY WITH AN OLD CONTRACT, NOT HIS LAST CONTRACT. I CONTACTED BETTY MOOMAW IN MARKETING TO RESEARCH WHY AGENT 02567'S LAST CONTRACT WAS TERMINATED BEFORE HE STOPPED WRITING BUSINESS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "PROGRAM CHECK 2393120300 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "INVALID DATE IN 69 SEGMENT FUASOFDT-ASOF-DATE ",
  "SOLUTION": "SEE DESCRIPTION IN TEST.CL.BOMBLOG(POLRPAIR) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0600",
  "PROBLEM": "STEVE B CALLED AND SAID THE PREVIOUS ODATE WAS INCORRECT IN THE JCL FOR LAST NIGHT'S RUN. 12\/31\/2005...SHOULD'VE BEEN 12\/31\/2004 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS DATE CONTROLS THE COMPARISON OF AN AGENT'S DST EFFECTIVE DATE TO THIS PREVIOUS DATE. IF AGENT'S DST EFFECTIVE DATE > PREVIOUS DATE, TREAT THIS AGENTS AS A NEW DST USER. SINCE THE PREVIOUS DATE WAS WAY IN THE FUTURE, THIS DID NOT CAUSE A PROBLEM. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CALLED JENNIFER PEDIGO IN INDIVIDUAL MARKETING TO TO SEE IF SHE ESTABLISHED AN AGENT ON DST ON 1\/3\/2005. SHE DID NOT, SO WE'RE FINE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1130",
  "PROBLEM": "S053 IEC030I B37-04,IFG0554A,CL$$1130,STEP0020,SORTWK01,1E14,PUB +ICE097I 2 CL$$1130.CL$$1130 SORT RECOVERING FROM B37 ABEND IEC030I B37-04,IFG0554A,CL$$1130,STEP0020,SORTWK02,1E14,PUB +ICE097I 2 CL$$1130.CL$$1130 SORT RECOVERING FROM B37 ABEND IEC030I B37-04,IFG0554A,CL$$1130,STEP0020,SORTWK02,1E14,PUB +ICE097I 2 CL$$1130.CL$$1130 SORT RECOVERING FROM B37 ABEND IEE252I MEMBER IDICNF00 FOUND IN SYS2.FA.PARMLIB IEE252I MEMBER IDICNF00 FOUND IN SYS2.FA.PARMLIB IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 617 USER COMPLETION CODE=0083 TIME=07.25.06 SEQ=08721 CPU=0000 ASID=0047 # IEF450I CL$$1130 STEP0020 CL$$1130 - ABEND=S000 U0083 REASON=000 -STEP=STEP0020 PGM=SORT ABENDED - COND CODE S053 RC=0000 ELA ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SPACE PROBLEM WITH SORTWK1, SORTWK2 AND SORTWK3 IN SORT STATEMENT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "ADDED THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDE... \/\/STEP0020.SORTWK01 DD SPACE=(CYL,(200,50)), \/\/ UNIT=SYSDA \/\/STEP0020.SORTWK02 DD SPACE=(CYL,(200,50)), \/\/ UNIT=SYSDA \/\/STEP0020.SORTWK03 DD SPACE=(CYL,(200,50)), \/\/ UNIT=SYSDA RERAN FROM THE TOP. WILL BRING DOWN THE PROC AND ADD THESE LINES IN THE SORT STEP "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0420",
  "PROBLEM": "+PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) AT LOCATION 001604 IN ELEMENT CKUBMVTG IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 638 USER COMPLETION CODE=0999 REASON CODE=00000000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "AT THE TIME OF THIS ABEND, CL$$0420 WAS A NO-CALL JOB. THE LAST POLICY NUMBER RETREIVED FROM THE POLICY DB WAS 3465095850. THE IDIREPRT DUMP OUTPUT SHOWED THAT A RECORD WAS NOT FOUND ON THE FUNDVAL FILE. A U1Q1 TRANSACTION IN CICS ONLINE FOR FUND QUOTES ABENDED. WE EVENTUALLY DISCOVERED THAT THE POLICY WAS MISSING FUND ENTRIES ON THE TARGET PREMIUM SEG (58). SINCE THIS USES THE 'SA' SNAP AFTER POLICY DB, WE TRIED DELETING THE POLICY AND RERUNNING FROM THE TOP. THIS ABENDED WITH AN 0C1 RETURN BECAUSE OF DATE CONFLICTS WITH CLIENT. WE CONSULTED THE USER AND DECIDED TO NOT RERUN. ",
  "SOLUTION": "THE ATTEMPTED SOLUTION EXPOSED THE PROBLEM OF HAVING THIS AS A NO-CALL JOB AND HAS BEEN CHANGED TO 'CALL'. IF ADDRESSED DURING THE NIGHTLY CYCLE, MAKING A COPY OF THE 'SA' POLICY DB, THEN REMOVING THE OFFENDING POLICY WITH A RERUN FROM THE TOP SHOULD FIX THIS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0430",
  "PROBLEM": "S3E7 - THE STEP0030 SYSOUT DISPLAYED: ORIGINAL MASTER FILE DATE IS INVALID - DATE = 112304 DATE OF OLD MASTER MUST BE = TO START OF PERIOD (CC 10-17 OFDATE CARD) PROBABLE DATE ERROR - REFER TO SYSOUT BACKGROUND: SINCE WE DID NOT RUN CL$$0420 ON 11\/24\/04, WE ALSO DID NOT RUN CL$$0430 AND CL$$440. WE INSTRUCTED PCD TO CHANGE THE PRIOR CYCLE DATE FROM 11\/24\/04 TO 11\/23\/04. IN THE OUTPUT OF THE ABENDING JOB, PDTTTE=11\/24\/04. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "INSTRUCTED PCD TO SET THE PRIOR CYCLE DATE TO 11\/23\/04. RERAN FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0127",
  "PROBLEM": "JCL OVERRIDE FILE DOES NOT EXIST \/\/STEP0017.SORTIN DD DSN=TEST.CL.RELEASED.ERRORS.SORTED ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB CL$$SEGD WAS RUN BUT EXECUTED WRONG JOB. MANUALLY RAN TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$$ACHS) WHICH CREATED THE CORRECT FILE FOR THE OVERRIDE. RESTARTED JOB IN FAILED STEP: STEP0017 JOB RAN TO GOOD EOJ CL$$SEGD RAN 2 JOBSTEPS: STEP0010 PGM=R72SEGDL EXECUTED - COND CODE 0000 STEP0020 PGM=R72SEGDL EXECUTED - COND CODE 0000 I DID NOT PERSUE WHAT REPERCUSSIONS THIS JOB HAD ON SYSTEM. CL$$SEGD WAS SET UP TO RUN AGAINST POLICY: \/\/ICONTROL DD * 00 2453264890 38 ** \/\/ICONTROL DD * 00 2453264890 48 ** JUST AN FYI IF PROCESSING HAD BEEN SET UP CORRECTLY CL$$ACHS WOULD HAVE BEEN RENAMED CL$$SEGD TO BE RUN IN CYCLE THE NEXT DAY IT WOULD HAVE BEEN RENAMED TO CL$$ACHS. CL$$SEGD IS JUST PLACE HOLDER. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0127",
  "PROBLEM": "SB37 - MONDAY CYCLE FOR THE 15TH OF THE MONTH, PLUS THE WEEKEND. THE OPERATORS DID NOT FOLLOW THE RESTART INSTRUCTIONS AND RUN CL$$R127 BEFORE STARTING THE JOB. THE USERS HAD DATE ERRORS ON THE ERROR REPORT FOR ALL THE RECORDS THAT PROCESSED DURING THE FIRST RUN. THE RESULTING FILES AND REPORTS ONLY HAD THE RECORDS THAT DID NOT PROCESS IN THE FIRST RUN. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "1. HAD MARK WILLIAMS CLOSE CL.VSAM.ACH.AUDIT.CNTL.AIX CL.VSAM.ACH.AUDIT.CONTROL CL.VSAM.ACH.CONTROL.XREF CL.VSAM.ACH.AUDIT.ERRORS 2. RUN CL$$R127 3. DELETE THE ZERO GENERATION OF: CL.FIN.BANK.EXTS CL.FIN.BANK.AUL.EXTS CL.FIN.BANK.SL.EXTS CL.FIN.BANK.PML.EXTS CL.BASEB.ACH.AUDIT.ERROR.AFTER CL.BASEB.ACH.AUDIT.CNTRL.AFTER 4. MARYANN NOTIFIED TREASURY (TERRI SUITERS) AND HAD THEM NOT SEND THE FILES TO THE BANK AT 10:00 AM. 5. MARYANN NOTIFIED THE TEAMS THAT THEY WOULD LOSE ALL ONLINE ENTRIES IN ACHC FROM THIS MORNING. 6. RERUN CL$$0127 FROM THE TOP. 7. NOTIFIED TERRI SUITERS WHEN CL$$0127 FINISHED SO THEY COULD TRANSMIT THE FILES AT 2:00 PM. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND IN CKDCEXIN CALLED FROM CKUBRVUH. THE WORKING STORAGE IN CKUBRVUH IS BEING DESTROYED. INVALID DATA IS BEING PASSED TO CKCDEXIN CAUSING THE ABEND. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WE CANNOT RECREATE THIS PROBLEM. UNSUSPEND THE POLICIES WITH THE PROGRAM CHECKS THE NEXT DAY. THEY SHOULD PROCESS. IF THERE ARE MORE THAN 30 PROGRAM CHECKS, CKAP01V WILL ABEND. I RECOMMEND RERUNNING THE JOB. 1\/25\/05 SUSPENDED 30 POLICIES AND RAN CL$$R060 AND ******** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** CL$$RC30 AND RAN CL$$0100 FROM THE TOP. ISSUE #6031 - CORRECTION TO CKUBRVUH. INSTALLED ON 1\/26\/05 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$UVPM",
  "PROBLEM": "THE NEW VERSION OF VPPDSVSM HAS NOT BEEN INSTALLED. IT WAS IN MODL. WE INSTALLED VPPDSVSM AND RERAN CL$$UVPM THE NEXT NIGHT. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0035",
  "PROBLEM": "POLICIES 3465093030 & 3465093040 HAD BEEN DELETED USING CL$$POLD & CL$$SQLB, BUT THE PENDING VSAM RECORDS STILL EXISTED. BOTH PROGRAMS WENT DOWN TRYING TO GET CLIENT DATA ON POLICY 3465093030. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "REVIEW THE DUMP TO CONFIRM THE POLICY THAT WAS IN ERROR. ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED CL$$PNDD FROM PROD, EDITED THE JOB CARD EDITED TEST.CL.CARDLIB(CLIPNDDL), POINTED TO THAT CARD AND PRODUCTION VSAM FILES. RAN FROM FIRE CALL. HAD JOBS RE-RAN FROM THE TOP AND THE FINISHED OK. SOLUTION2: USING FIRECALL WENT INTO TSO PST AND ENTERED THE POLICY IN THE TCH_OBJECT_KEY IN THE CLT_OBJ_RELATION TABLE. SINCE THE CK4P RECORDS WERE NOT THERE WE DID AN 'R' ON EACH CK4I RECORD AND CHANGED THE CK4I TO CK4P ON EACH COPIED RECORD. RERAN JOB FROM TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1180",
  "PROBLEM": "NEXT DAY IT WAS DETERMINED TO BE A BLOCK SIZE ERROR RELATED TO ULTIM. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DETERMINED THIS WAS PRINT ONLY FOR THIS STEP. THE NEXT STEP (9090) WAS THE LAST STEP. IT CREATED A FILE FOR ABS INPUT. VERIFIED IT RAN OK IN A TEST WORLD AND THEN HAD THE OPERATOR PUT A RESTART IN THE JOB FOR STEP9090. ENDED OK. STEP9080 WAS RUN THE NEXT DAY. 12\/03\/2004 - APPEARS AS IF THE PRINT JOB IS NOW STEP 9090. THIS WOULD ALLOW FOR THAT STEP TO BE NOCALL. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0120",
  "PROBLEM": "+PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) AT LOCATION 0014FA IN ELEMENT CKBSBCII ",
  "ANALYSIS": "BAD RECORD ON CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.BILLEXTS(0). WENT TO THE BOTTOM OF SYSLST TO SEE WHAT LAST KNOWN GOOD POLICY PROCESSED (0620129120). WE FOUND THE NEXT DAY THAT THE 33 SEGMENT WAS CORRUPTED. WE HAD THE USER DELETE AND RE-ADD THE SEGMENT (OR JUST DELETE IT IF IT WAS NOT NEEDED). RSW 12\/8\/04 SYSUDUMP CL$$0120 STEP0030 105 ACFSUBID G LOCAL SYSPDUMP CL$$0120 STEP0030 106 ACFSUBID G LOCAL SYSLST CL$$0120 STEP0030 108 ACFSUBID N LOCAL SEQUEN5 CL$$0120 STEP0030 110 ACFSUBID N LOCAL IDIREPRT CL$$0120 STEP0030 155 ACFSUBID 0 LOCAL THE POLICY NUMBERS FOUND IN IDIREPRT FOR THE PREVIOUS, CURRENT, AND NEXT RECORD OF THE SEQUEN2 FILE HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH THE PROBLEM. THE OFFENDING POLICY NUMBER (0620131860) WAS FOUND IN SYSPDUMP AROUND LOCATION 8B0 OF BLW-000 FOR CKBSBCII. MANY RECORDS WERE BETWEEN GOOD AND BAD POLICIES. ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED THE FILE ABOVE TO TEST.CL.BGR.STEP0320.BILLEXTS USING TSO 3.3 AND DELETED THE BAD RECORD. HAD TO USE FILE MARVEL FOR THE DELETE BECAUSE OF SIZE. SET UP JCL AND PROC IN BASE REGION AND RAN STEP0010 THRU STEP0030. ENDED OK. KEPT A COPY OF PROD FILE TO THE BGR FILE BEFORE DELETE. THEN USED FIRECALL TO DROP THE BAD POLICY FROM THE PRODUCTION FILE. RERAN FROM THE TOP. ENDED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$Q867",
  "PROBLEM": "A SYSTEM ABEND 0CB OCCURRED IN MODULE D7240081 PROGRAM D7240081 AT OFF X'8152'. A PROGRAM INTERRUPTION CODE 000B (DECIMAL-DIVIDE EXCEPTION) IS ASSOCIA THIS ABEND AND INDICATES THAT: THE DIVISOR WAS ZERO IN A SIGNED DECIMAL DIVISION. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE PROBLEM CODE IS: CL5155 COMPUTE WK-ASSET-CAT-ALLOC-PCT-HOLD CL5155 ROUNDED = CL5155 ((WK-ASSET-CAT-ALLOC-AMT (WK-AC-IDX) \/ CL5155 WS-INV-OPT-CUMM-BAL) * 100) PROBLEM OCCURED WITH POLICY 2453313330 ",
  "SOLUTION": "BY LEANN MOSS: COPIED INPUT FILE CL.CL$$0867.IVA.OTAGTHIS(0) TO TEST.CL.LKM.CL$$0867.IVA.OTAGTHIS.P093004.BK. FILE WAS TOO BIG TO REMOVE RECORD VIA FILE MARVEL. WROTE SORT TO OMIT COND FOR THIS POLICY AND USED TEST.CL.LKM.CL$$0867.IVA.OTAGTHIS.P093004.E AS INPUT FOR RESTART IN STEP0020 SORT. JOB RAN OVER 13 HOURS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$BIND",
  "PROBLEM": "STEPS 30,50,80 & 90 RECEIVED CC8, STEP 55 RECEIVED CC4 UNSUCCESSFUL BINDS. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DSNT233I +DB2P UNSUCCESSFUL BIND FOR (STEP0030) PACKAGE = DB2P.CLCIS.XPIOCHK.() DSNT233I +DB2P UNSUCCESSFUL BIND FOR (STEP0050) PACKAGE = DB2P.CLCIS.XPIBCHK.() DSNT233I +DB2P UNSUCCESSFUL BIND FOR (STEP0080) PACKAGE = DB2P.CLAUL.R724REPE.() (BIND TO DB2P) DSNT233I -DB2S UNSUCCESSFUL BIND FOR (STEP0090) PACKAGE = DB2S.CLAUL.R724REPE.() (BIND TO DB2S) ",
  "SOLUTION": "THE FIRST TWO HAVE KNOWN PROBLEMS SINCE THE RELEASE OF 0101 AND ARE OKAY. CHECKED CL$$MOVL AND FOUND THAT R724REPE WAS NOT MOVED INTO PRODUCTION LOADLIB OR DBRMLIB. ALSO FOUND THAT R724REPE DIDN'T OCCUR IN AUL1.PROCLIB OR PROD.SCHD.JCLLIB. FORCED COMPLETE. R724REPE IS A REQUEST ONLY VERSION OF M724REPE AND APPEARS ONLY IN TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$$1090). A DBRM MOVE HAD NOT BEEN PERFORMED FOR THIS PROGRAM. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0035",
  "PROBLEM": "S04C USER COMPLETION CODE=4039 REASON CODE=00000000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOUND POLICY IN DUMP AND WAS ABLE TO BRING IT UP IN 3270. SAW THAT THE POLICY WAS JUST PUT ON SO THERE MUST'VE BEEN A CONFLICT JUST AT THE MOMENT THE JOB WAS ON THAT POLICY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTARTED JOB FROM THE TOP. FINISHED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0009",
  "PROBLEM": "NEW POLICIES DID NOT SHOW UP UNDER NAME 3465094110 & 3465094120 WERE NEW ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CHECKED TO MAKE SURE CL$$0009 RAN, IT DID SEARCHED FILE FEED TO NS FOR POLICY #'S, THEY ARE THERE CHECKED WITH PCD ON FIN$0990 RUN SUCCESS & OUR GEN USED THE JOB WAS STILL RUNNING CALLED KIM REED, GROUP RECORDS CAUSED A LOOP ",
  "SOLUTION": "KIM CORRECTED PROBLEM AND WORKED WITH PCD TO CONTINUE LOAD, JOB COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. ALL OUR RECORDS SHOULD BE THERE NOW. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0009",
  "PROBLEM": "IF CL$$0007, CL$$0008, CL$$0009 COULD NOT COMPLETE AND OUR INTERFACE TO FIN$0990 WAS BYPASSED OPS RESPONSE: OPS HAS INSTRUCTION TO REMOVE OUR FILE FROM THE FIN$0990 FEED IF ANY OF OUR 3 JOBS ABOVE EXPERIENCE A FAILURE. THEY WILL ALSO SATISFY OUR SUCCESSFUL RUN OF CL$$0009 CONDITION. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FIGURE OUT PROBLEM AND FIX ABEND POINT FIGURE OUT IF A VERSION OF THE FOLLOWING DATASET WAS CREATED IN THE ABENDING CYCLE WHICH WAS SKIPPED CL.CL$$0009.NS.SRT IF IT WAS, WE NEED TO DELETE GEN'S BACK TO THE LAST GOOD CYCLE ",
  "SOLUTION": "ONCE THE PROBLEM IS FIXED, YOU DO NOT NEED TO COMPLETE CL$$0008,0009 FROM THE NIGHT WITH THE PROBLEM. CL$$0007 NEEDS TO RUN TO SUPPORT BOOK OF BUSINESS IN THE NEXT CYCLE, THE ZERO GENERATION OF CL.CL$$0009.NS.SRT IN STEP0020, DD OLDDD MUST BE THE FILE THAT WAS CREATED IN THE LAST GOOD RUN OF CL$$0009. CL$$0007 & 0008 REQUIRE NO WORK TO DO THIS. THE WORK ABOVE WILL CAUSE NAME SEARCH TO CATCH UP TO CURRENT BY COMPARING CURRENT EXTRACT MASTER FILES TO THE LAST GOOD EXTRACT MASTER FILE. THE CORRECTION CYCLE WILL RUN AS IT NORMALLY WOULD IF THERE HAD NOT BEEN A PROBLEM. NOTE: IF WE NEEDED TO FIX THE CONDITION OF A PARTICULAR POLICY AND THE MASTER FILES WERE CORRECT ON OUR SYSTEM BUT THE CHANGE DID NOT FORCE RECORD TO NAMESEARCH BY COMPARISON, SIMPLY DELETE THE POLICY RECORD ON THE LAST HISTORY GEN AND THE CURRENT HISTORY RECORDS WILL BUILD LIKE THEY WERE NEW. JUST ABOUT ANY GLOBAL CHANGE SHOULD CAUSE THE COMPARES TO IDENTIFY IT AND SEND OVER ALL CHANGES. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "0620012340 AND 0620021380 PROGRAM CHECK IN CKDCCFIN. THE NEXT DAY 9\/7\/04, EVERY DISPLAY AND GUI ACCESS ABENDED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "RERAN TIME DRIVEN AND FOUND ABEND IN CKDCCFIN CALLED BY CKUBINTM. THE APP DATE IN THE 01 SEGMENT WAS INVALID. THE YEAR WAS 2999 ON ONE AND 3000 ON THE OTHER ",
  "SOLUTION": "USED FILE MARVEL TO CORRECT THE DATE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0020",
  "PROBLEM": "VUL POLICY 3465093310 IS ABENDING WITH A S0C7. STILL TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT IS BAD WITH THIS POLICY. IT HAS AN AIB RIDER ATTACHED, WHICH MAY NOT BE ENTERED CORRECTLY. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "I AM STILL RESEARCHING THE PROBLEM USING XPEDITER. ",
  "SOLUTION": "I COPIED CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G2969V00 TO TEST.CL.LKM.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G2969BKP THEN DELETED 3465093310 FROM THE PRODUCTION FILE USING FIRECALL ID. I HAD PCD SET UP CL$$0020 OVERRIDES: \/\/ RESTART=JSTEP010.STEP0030, AND \/\/JSTEP010 EXEC PROC=CL$$0020,GDG01='0'. THE RERUN WAS GOOD. --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0017",
  "PROBLEM": "CC04 IN STEP0020 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CHECK FOR DATE INCONSISTENCY MESSAGES "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$8140",
  "PROBLEM": "CC16 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "REPORTS GOT CREATED. BUT AT THE BOTTOM OF THE REPORT IN SYSPRT IT SHOWS: ATTENTION! ERRORS WERE SIGNALED IN THIS REPORT ",
  "SOLUTION": "THIS REPORT SHOWS ERRORS SO THIS IS NORMAL. WE FEEL THIS IS BEING CAUSED BY THE NEW ULTIM. FORCED JOB OKAY AND HAD PCD SET A CC16 OK FOR THIS STEP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0814",
  "PROBLEM": "SHOUT FOR ERROR WHILE ATTEMPTING TO UPDATE THE CLIENT_PROXY TABLE FOR POLICY 0620177110 DISPLAY IN CONTROL D STATED ERROR COPYING RECORD, RETURN CODE -803. THIS HAS BEEN HAPPENING FOR A WEEK NOW. ERROR FOR ATTEMPTING TO UPDATE A KEY FIELD ON A TABLE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WORKING WITH ROBERT BIZLEY, WE DISCOVERED THE PROBLEM WHEN WE TRY TO CREATE OUR HISTORY RECORD WE ATTEMPT TO UPDATE THE HISTORY_VLD_NBR FIELD BUT THAT IS A PART OF THE 4 FIELDS THAT MAKE UP TEH KEY TO THE NEW CLIENT_PROXY TABLE. JUST LIKE CHANGING A KEY TO A VSAM REQUIRES A DELETE OF THE RECORD WITH THE OLD KEY AND A REWRITE OF THE RECORD WITH THE NEW KEY, SO DOES DB2 REQUIRE THE OLD RECORD, WITH IT'S KEY TO BE DELETED AND THEN REPLACED WITH THE RECORD WITH THE NEW KEY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "WE NEED TO GET THE CURRENT ACTIVE RECORD WITH A 0 IN HISTORY_VLD_NBR FIELD. SAVE THE DATA IN THE RECORD TO A WORKING STORAGE AREA. GET THE MAX(HISTORY_VLD_NBR) RECORD SAVE THE MAX(HISTORY_VLD_NBR) DELETE THE 0 HISTORY_VLD_NBR RECORD. INSERT A NEW RECORD WITH SAME DATA AS THE 0 RECORD, BUT WITH AN EXPIRED DATE OF CURRENT PROCESSING DATE (CICL_EXP_DT= :WS-INPUT-DATE) AND WITH A HISTORY_VLD_NBR = MAX-HISTORY-VLD-NBR +1. THEN INSERT A NEW RECORD TO THE TABLE USING THE CURRENT DATE, A HISTORY_VLD_NBR = 0, AND THE NEW PROXY VOTE. ISSUE #5580 7\/15\/2004-RSW CL$$0814 UPDATES THE PROXY INDICATOR IN CLIENT TABLE, CLIENT_PROXY. ERROR MESSAGES FROM THIS JOB THAT BEGIN WITH THE WORD \"ERROR\" ARE PROBLEMS THAT THE USERS CANNOT RESOLVE. THE UPDATE TO THE DATABASE WAS REJECTED AND WILL NEED TO BE RE-SCANNED INTO THE PROXY DATABASE AFTER THE PROBLEM IS RESOLVED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0814",
  "PROBLEM": "DESCRIBED HERE. THREE POLICIES WITH THE SAME OWNER AND VOTES Y\/N\/Y. POLICIES 0620161610, 2453339320, 3465090970 09\/10\/2004 P1RSW THE SAME PROBLEM DESCRIBED HERE. 2453346080 9\/9\/04 Y 2453346130 9\/9\/04 N 2453346100 9\/10\/04 Y -803 IN THIS CYCLE PROBLEM: SHOUT FOR ERROR WHILE ATTEMPTING TO UPDATE THE CLIENT_PROXY TABLE FOR POLICY 0620177110 DISPLAY IN CONTROL D STATED ERROR COPYING RECORD, RETURN CODE -803. THIS HAS BEEN HAPPENING FOR A WEEK NOW. ERROR FOR ATTEMPTING TO UPDATE A KEY FIELD ON A TABLE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WORKING WITH ROBERT BIZLEY, WE DISCOVERED THE PROBLEM. WHEN WE TRY TO CREATE OUR HISTORY RECORD WE ATTEMPT TO UPDATE THE HISTORY_VLD_NBR FIELD BUT THAT IS A PART OF THE 4 FIELDS THAT MAKE UP TEH KEY TO THE CLIENT_PROXY TABLE. JUST LIKE CHANGING A KEY TO A VSAM REQUIRES A DELETE OF THE RECORD WITH THE OLD KEY AND A REWRITE OF THE RECORD W\/ A NEW KEY, SO DOES DB2 REQUIRE THE OLD RECORD, WITH IT'S KEY TO BE DELETED AND INSERT OF REC WITH THE THE NEW NEW KEY FIELD DATA. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RHONDA HAS CREATED AN ISSUE AND ASSIGNED IT TO BILL TO CORRECT THIS. SHORT TERM SOLUTION IS TO UPDATE THE CLIENT_PROXY DB2 TABLE UNDER FILE CALL USING PRINCETON PRINCETON SOFTECH TOOL. ISSUE 5580 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0040",
  "PROBLEM": "SB37 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "RESTARTED THE JOB FROM THE TOP WITH OVERRIDES FOR SPACE \/\/ STEP0115.SORTOUT DD DSN=&&TRANSRT, \/\/ DISP=(NEW,PASS,KEEP), \/\/ UNIT=SYSDA, \/\/ SPACE=(CYL,(175,50),RLSE), \/\/ DCB=(RECFM=VB,LRECL=15000,BLKSIZE=23200) JOB MADE IT PAST THIS STEP. -------- --------- ------------ ---------- ------- ------- CL$$0040 STEP0070 CKAGTPRX 08\/11\/2004 214346 P1RSW 11\/09\/2004 P1BKG 11\/24\/2004 09:42PM P1WHH PROBLEM: USER = 0999 ABEND USER ABEND 0001 ON 11\/24\/04 (SAME SOLUTION) RSW 11\/29\/04 - THE PROBLEM RECORDS HAVE X'01' AS THE USER ID IN THE ACTIVITY RECORD. IN CKAGTPRT, SUBR23000-CONV-STATE, THE CKUDT103 TABLE LOOKUP IS NOT SUCCESSFUL, BECAUSE THE USER ID DOES NOT MATCH. SO THE PROGRAM CALLS CKABEND. THE USER ID IS IN COLUMN 48. ",
  "SOLUTION": "IN FA, THE CURRENT RECORD FOR SEQUEN2 DISPLAYED A POLICY NUMBER. I DELETED THE POLICY FROM CL.VSAM.BASEOL.ACTIVITY USING TEST.CL.TOOLS(DROPACT). BACKUP NAME TEST.CL.ACTIVITY.BKUP.D081104. RESTARTED THE JOB FROM THE TOP AND IT ABENDED AGAIN WITH A DIFFERENT POLICY DISPLAYED IN CURRENT. THE NEXT RECORD IN BOTH ABENDS WAS '16336 '. SINCE CKAGTPRX IS PRINTING AGENT ACTIVITY, I DECIDED TO DROP THAT RECORD. GO INTO IDIREPRT AND DO A FIND ON SEQUEN2 AND LOOK AT THE NEXT RECORD TO DETERMINE WHICH RECORD IS CAUSING THE PROBLEM. ON 11\/09\/04 WE HAD 9 DIFFERENT AGENT NUMBERS THAT CAUSED US TO ABEND. ALL WERE DONE BY THE SAME DESK CODE. IN THE ACTIVITY FILE COL 12 IS THE POLICY\/AGENT #, COL26 IS THE DESK CODE, COL32 IS THE TRANS CODE. TO DO THAT, I RESTORED TEST.CL.ACTIVITY.BKUP.D081104 INTO CL.VSAM.BASEOL.ACTIVITY. THEN I RERAN DROPACT AND DROPPED 16336. I NAMED THE BACKUP TEST.CL.ACTIVITY.BKUP.D081104A. SOLUTION: RESTARTED THE JOB FROM THE TOP AND IT RAN SUCCESSFULLY. I INSTRUCTED THE OPERATOR THAT CONDITION CODE 8 IN STEP0010 WAS OK. THE NEXT DAY, I RERAN DROPACT AND CHANGED THE SORT 'OMIT' TO 'INCLUDE' AND CREATED A FILE WITH JUST THE 16336 RECORDS. THAT GAVE ME THE CLERK CODE AND ACTIVITY RECORDS. I CONTACTED THEM TO SEE WHY THEY WERE UPDATING CYBERLIFE ACF RECORDS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "+CKSN01 PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. PSW=078D0000 8C44B726 (OPERATIO +CKUB03 CURRENT POLICY 5770000450 +CKSN02 ABENDING ELEMENT CKETRMAP EPA=0C44B660 OFFSET 0000C4 +CKUB07 UNABLE TO CONTINUE PROCESSING - JOB ABORTING. 5770000450 WAS THE LAST POLICY NUMBER IN CL.CL$$0100.CKAP01V.DEBUG. 08\/03\/2004 POLICY = 5770000450 NUMBER IN CL.CL$$0100.CKAP01V.DEBUG. 12\/06\/2004 POLICY = 2393100650 LAST # IN CL.CL$$0100.CKAP01V.DEBUG. 12\/10\/2004 POLICY = 2393100650 LAST # IN CL.CL$$0100.CKAP01V.DEBUG. 09\/09\/2005 POLICY = 3465101550 LAST # IN CL.CL$$0100.CKAP01V.DEBUG. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "******** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** ",
  "SOLUTION": "PUT POLICY NUMBER IN TEST.CL.DATA(SUSPEND), THEN HAD OPS RUN CL$$R060, CL$$RC30, CL$$SUSP AND RESTART CL$$0100 FROM THE TOP. RSW 12\/16\/04 THE LONG TERM SOLUTION ON 2393100650: ON 12\/6\/04 PRIOR TO CL$$0100, I USED FILE MARVEL TO DELETE 69 SEGMENTS. I CHANGED THE SEGMENT ID IN: AUXSEG1 0002 RECORD FROM 69 TO 99. AUXSEG1 BF RECORD (STUB POOL) FROM 69 TO 99 (IN HEX) THE FINAL RESOLUTION ON 12\/15\/04 WAS TO ONLY CHANGE THE SEGMENT ID IN THE BF RECORD. THE SEGMENT ID SHOULD NOT BE CHANGED IN THE 0002 RECORD. THE ABEND ON 12\/10\/04 WAS BECAUSE THEY UNSUSPENDED THE POLICY BEFORE WE WERE READY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0814",
  "PROBLEM": "CC12 DB2 CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQL RETURN CODE -1 FOR SQLALLOCCONNECT TO DB2 SYSTEM DB2P CL$$0814 STEP0050 EPHWPDD OPPARMLB-BKSRVR DD IS ALREADY ALLOCATED AND WILL BE USED BY THIS TASK. $HASP375 CL$$0814 ESTIMATED LINES EXCEEDED IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 709 USER COMPLETION CODE=4039 REASON CODE=00000000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "IN THE SYSUDUMP DID A FIND ON SQL. FOUND SQLCODE = -911. THIS OCCURS WHEN ANOTHER ACTIVITY IS HITTING CLIENT AT THE SAME TIME YOUR JOB IS RUNNING. WE REALIZED OUR CL$$SQLB WAS RUNNING AT THE SAME TIME AS CL$$0814. ",
  "SOLUTION": "AT NIGHT WE REALIZED STEPS 50 AND 60 WERE NOT CRITICAL TO CYCLE. SO WE FORCED THE JOB OKAY AND FIGURED OUT THE SOLUTION THE NEXT DAY. RERAN JOB RESTARTING IN STEP0050. SINCE CL$$0814 IS FAIRLY NEW, WE REALIZE NOW THAT WHEN WE REQUEST PCD TO RUN CL$$POLD AND CL$$SQLB WE NEED TO SPECIFY CL$$0814 WILL BE DEPENDENT ON CL$$POLD AND CL$$SQLB. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0700",
  "PROBLEM": "SEPARATE ACCOUNTS REPORTED FUND AULMON (ID 19) WAS WAS OUT OF BALANCE. THE NUMBER OF UNITS REPORTED IN CL$$8002 DID NOT MATCH THE NUMBER UNITS REPORTED BY OMNI. THIS WAS REPORTED TO ME ON 6\/29. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "RAN CL$$0700, STEP0020 TO CREATE TEST.CL.RSW.CL$$0700.EXTRACT.FUNDS. I MATCHED THE RECORDS IN THAT FILE WITH CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT. I DID A FIND ON THE FUND ID IN COLUMN 81 TO MATCH THE AMOUNTS TO POLICIES. I MATCHED THE AMOUNTS AND POLICIES THAT I FOUND TO THE DIFFERENCES REPORTED IN CL$$8002. POLICY 3465089220 SURRENDERED ON 6\/23. CL$$8002 REPORTED 59.3489 UNITS IN THE PREV COLUMN AND ZERO UNITS IN THE CURRENT COLUMN. IT DID NOT DISPLAY THE DIFFERENCE IN THE DIFFERENCE COLUMN. TEST.CL.RSW.CL$$0700.EXTRACT.FUNDS REPORTED A SALE OF $42.83 WHICH IS 35.3535 UNITS AND I FOUND 35.3535 UNITS IN THE SURRENDER TRANSACTION 69 SEGMENT. THIS ACCOUNTED FOR THE DIFFERENCE IN THE BALANCE. I ALSO LOOKED AT REPORT \"BALANCE REG(AUL)\" FROM CL$$0100 TO GET THE TOTAL PURCHASE AND REDEMPTION FOR THE FUND. I COMPARED THE NUMBER OF UNITS TO THE DIFFERENCES REPORTED IN CL$$8002. ",
  "SOLUTION": "PASSED THE POLICY BACK TO VALERIE TO RESEARCH THE ACTIVITY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0814"
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0020",
  "PROBLEM": "FIGURE OUT WHY AUL TERM POLICY 0620165750 WAS LOOPING ON 6\/8\/2004 AND 6\/9\/2004. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "TO FIND SOURCE OF LOOP, I RERAN STEP WITH ONLY THE BAD POLICY AND HAD PCD CANCEL IT WITH A DUMP. SAW THE BAD EVENT WAS IN MODULE IAMACCKS. PGM CHAIN WAS D724DSLT- CKVSAMIO - IAMACCKS. DECIDED TO XPEDITE D724DSLT AND STEP THRU ALL CKVSAMIO CALLS. SUBR940-DEPT WAS CALLED TWICE, FOR THE CLERK ID AND FOR THE UNDERWRITER ID. CLERK ID WAS FINE, BUT UW ID J966RAZ WAS BAD. I CALLED CLERK TO ASK ABOUT THE UW ID THAT WAS UNFAMILIAR TO ME. SHE NOTICED IT SHOULD HAVE BEEN J866 LIKE THE OTHER PML UW IDS AND SHE CHANGED IT. I TESTED WITH J866RAZ AND THE RECORD PROCESSED NORMALLY. REPRINT WAS ISSUED AND OUTPUT SHOULD BE HERE TOMORROW MORNING. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CLERK CHANGED THE UW ID FROM J966RAZ TO J866RAZ. REPRINT TRANSACTION WAS ISSUED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0020",
  "PROBLEM": "PCD CALLED WHEN CL$$0020 RAN FOR ALMOST AN HOUR. I CHECKE Q.DA WHICH SHOWED 0 IN THE SIO COLUMN INDICATING NO INPUT OR OUTPUT. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "TO FIND SOURCE OF LOOP, I HAD PCD CANCEL THE JOB WITH A DUMP. SANDI JEFFS REMEMBERED THE UNUSUAL PROBLEM THAT WE ENCOUNTERED WITH CL$$0020 ON 04\/13\/2004 WHICH WAS A SOC7, NOT A LOOP. THE PROBLEM POLICY THEN TURNED OUT TO TO BE THE POLICY PRECEDING THE 'NEXT' RECORD IN THE IDIREPRT DUMP OUTPUT. THE 'NEXT' RECORD PRECEDES THE 'CURRENT' AND 'PREVIOUS' RECORDS IN THIS JOB'S DUMP. THE PROBLEM POLICY DOESN'T EVEN APPEAR. ",
  "SOLUTION": "'PREVIOUS' POLICY WAS '0620166590' <= SAME POLICY 'CURRENT' POLICY WAS '0620166590' <= SAME POLICY 'NEXT' POLICY WAS '0620165760' POLICY PRECEDING 'NEXT' WAS '0620165750' I COPIED CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G2857V00 TO TEST.CL.WHH.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G2857BKP THEN DELETED 0620165750 FROM THE PRODUCTION FILE VIA FILE MARVEL THROUGH FIRE CALL. I HAD PCD SET UP CL$$0020 OVERRIDES: \/\/ RESTART=JSTEP010.STEP0030, AND \/\/JSTEP010 EXEC PROC=CL$$0020,GDG01='0'. THE RERUN WAS GOOD. --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0500",
  "PROBLEM": "DB2 CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQL RETURN CODE -1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS JOB USES SB FILES. POLICY NUMBER 0620169500 DROPPED OFF CL.VSAM.BASEOL.PENDING FILE IN CL$$0030. THEREFOR PURGING THE CLIENT ROWS. SINCE THIS JOB USES CL.SB.VSAM.BASEOL.PENDING, THE RECORD WAS STILL ON THISR FILE. ONCE THE JOB TRIED TO READ THE CLIENT ROWS, THE SQL ERROR OCCURRED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "REPRO THE VSAM FILE TO TEST.CL.DJN.VSAM.PENDING BY RUNNING JOB TEST.CL.DJN.JCLLIB(DEFPEND) TO DELETE\/DEFINE THEN RAN TEST.CL.DJNTOOLS(REPROPOL). I DELETED THE BAD POLICY NUMBER IN THE COPIED FILE. THEN I OVERRIDED VSAM3 IN STEP0010 OF PROCLIB CL$$0500. RERAN THE JOB FROM THE TOP. SOLUTION: EMAIL FROM BRIAN ON 11\/30\/2004 CL$$0500 (AUTOMATED EMAILS FOR PENDING REQUIREMENTS) - THIS JOB USES THE SB VERSION OF THE PENDING FILE. POLICY 0620189890 WAS ON THE SB VERSION BUT WAS NOT ON THE REGULAR PENDING FILE. BELIEVE IT GOT REMOVED DURING THE CL$$0030 JOB, ALONG WITH THE REMOVAL OF CLIENT ROWS. THIS CAUSED AN SQL = -1 AND A SOC4. MADE A COPY OF THE SB VERSION OF THE PENDING FILE, REMOVED 0620189890 FROM COPY, HAD OPS RESTART CL$$0500 FROM TOP USING THE COPIED VERSION OF THE SB PENDING FILE ...JOB FINISHED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0010",
  "PROBLEM": "21:36:29 SNAP DATASET ( SOURCE (CL.BASEB.COMM.COMM.EXT4 21:36:29 TARGET (CL.SB.BASEB.COMM.COMM.EXT 21:36:29 ESOTERIC(SYSDA) HCPYMOD 21:36:29 REPLACE(Y) ) SIB4762E SNAPSHOT IS NOT SUPPORTED BETWEEN DIFFERENT SVAS. 21:36:30 SNAPSHOT COMPLETED, RC=8. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SOME GLITCH? WHO KNOWS? ",
  "SOLUTION": "BILL TURNER WAS WATCHING FOR A FILE CONVERSION TO RUN WHEN CL$$0010 HAD THE CC8. HE HAD SNAPPED A TEST COPY OF THIS FILE SUCCESSFULLY WITH TEST.CL.JCLLIB(SNAPTEMP AND CHANGED IT TO SNAP THE CL.SB VERSION WHILE I REBOOTED WITH FIRECALL TO SUBMIT IT. JOB RAN SUCCESSFULLY AND I HAD CL$$0010 FORCED COMPLETE. SOLUTION: THE HISTORY FILE WAS ON A TEST VOLUME. HAD TO HAVE LAVONNA NICHOLS MOVE THE FILE TO A PRODUCTION VOLUME OR ELSE WE WOULD RUN INTO THIS SAME PROBLEM FOR CL$$0060 AND 160. LAVONNA MOVED THE FILE AND I RAN THE ABOVE SNAPTEMP JOB. FORCED CL$$0010 OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "+CKSN01 PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. PSW=078D1000 8C454D8 +CKSN02 ABENDING ELEMENT CKPRTRAN EPA=0C454650 OFFSET +IDI0082E DB2 CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQL RETURN CODE -1 FOR SQLALLOCCONNECT TO DB2 SYSTEM DB2P USER ABEND CODE 0999 REASON CODE 00000000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WE HAD SEEN THIS ABEND IN TEST WHEN CERTAIN REQUIREMENTS WERE REMOVED FROM UTABLES AND THESE REQUIREMENTS WERE REMOVED FROM PRODUCTION UTABLES TWO DAYS AGO. RHONDA WATSON AND I RAN TWO ULTIM JOBS TO FIND THE NEWLY RESTRICTED REQUIREMENTS ON PRODUCTION POLICIES WE RAN TEST.CL.ULTIM(CL2SUBMS) WITH ULTIM 'CLREQTYP' AGAINST THE PENDING FILE AND 'CLREQINF' AGAINST THE INFORCE FILE. INFORCE WAS OKAY BUT PENDING HAD ONE POLICY WITH AN OFFENDING REQUIREMENT (THESE INCLUDE 04,05,11,12,23,33,47,103,117,121,126,130,209,213). THE ULTIM REPORT SEEMS TO LEAVE THE REQUIREMENT DESCRIPTION FIELD BLANK IF IT IS NO LONGER A VALID REQUIREMENT. WE FOUND THIS POLICY: 0620162650 34 ADDL FORM REQD 0620162660 23 0620162660 34 ADDL FORM REQD IN THE IDIREPRT OUTPUT, THAT IS THE CURRENT RECORD IN THE PENDING FILE. ******* NOTE: CL$$RC10 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL2 ******** ",
  "SOLUTION": "RAN RESTORE JOBS CL$$R030, CL$$RC10, & CL$$R017 PER SCHD.CT.DOC. THEN RHONDA ADDED A 5400 TRANSACTION TO CL$$0017 TO TRY TO RECEIPT THE REQUIREMENT. THIS FAILED BECAUSE OF INVALID REQUIREMENT. INSTEAD, WE TRIED TO DELETE THE PENDING POLICY USING CL$$PNDD WITH THE POLICY NUMBER IN CARD CLIPNDDL. OPS GOT THI WRONG AND TIME WAS RUNNING OUT, SO RHONDA DELETED THE POLCIY FROM THE PENDING AND AUX FILES USING FILE MARVEL. RERAN CL$$0030 FROM THE TOP. STEP0010 HAD A CC8 BECAUSE IDCAMS COULDN'T FIND THE DATASETS TO DELETE. TOLD OPS TO FORCE OKAY AND RELEASE DEPENDENCIES. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0120",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP=STEP0200 PGM=IEBGENER EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 DATA SET UTILITY - GENERATE IEB351I I\/O ERROR ,CL$$0120,STEP0200,0714,D,SYSUT1 , READ ,WRNG.LEN.RECORD,00000022000300,BSAM ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE JOB THINKS THAT THE TEMPORARY DATASET SYSUT1 DD DSN=&&BILLS, IS THE WRONG LENGTH. ",
  "SOLUTION": "AFTER DISCUSSION WITH SANDI JEFFS, WE DECIDED THAT THIS STEP THAT PRINTS LIST BILLS FROM PRINT TAPE CAN BE BYPASSED AS WE NO LONGER PRODUCE LIST BILLS. IT WAS THE LAST STEP OF THE JOB SO WE FORCED THE JOB COMPLETE TO RESTART THE CYCLE. TAMMY REYNOLDS-KELLEMS HAS DISCOVERED THAT THE PROBLEM WAS WITH THE OUTPUT FILE \/\/SYSUT2 DD SYSOUT=&SOUTA, \/\/ DCB=(RECFM=FBA,LRECL=121,BLKSIZE=6050) APPARENTLY CAUSED BY RECENT CHANGES TO OUR UNDERLYING OPERATING SYSTEMS IN OUR MAINFRAME WHICH CAUSES IBM UTILITY PROGRAM IEBGENER TO REJECT THE DCB PARAMETER. TESTS WITHOUT THE PARAMETER WORKED. A REQUEST HAS BEEN MADE TO REMOVE THIS FROM PRODUCTION. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0020",
  "PROBLEM": "+PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) AT LOCATION 0029F0 IN ELEMENT CKDPMC01 PSW = 078D0000 8000A24E IEF450I CL$$0020 STEP0030 JSTEP010 - ABEND=S000 U0999 REASON=00000000 778 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ASSUMED A BAD POLICY WAS CAUSING THE ABEND ",
  "SOLUTION": "CHECKED IDIREPRT OUTPUT FOR THE 'CURRENT RECORD' FOR FOR DD SEQUEN (CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G2780V00) AND DELETED THAT POLICY FROM THE RECORD. HAD PCD SET UP THE JCL WITH \/\/ RESTART=JSTEP010.STEP0030, AND \/\/JSTEP010 EXEC PROC=CL$$0020,GDG01='0' --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! IT TOOK SEVERAL TRIES BEFORE SANDI JEFFS FOUND THAT THE POLICY WE WANTED TO DELETE WAS THE POLICY THAT PRECEDES 'NEXT RECORD' AND DOES NOT APPEAR IN THE DUMP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0869",
  "PROBLEM": "JCL ERROR ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB JEMED FINE. THE STEPS FOR THIS JOB MAKE BACKUPS OF EACH FILE. NOTHING TOO COMPLICATED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTARTED JOB IN STEP0030. JOB ENDED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1020",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP=STEP0020 PGM=IKJEFT01 EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) AT LOCATION 000CC4 IN ELEMENT CKUBVALX ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE DUMP LOCATION OF THE ABENDING INSTRUCTION AND RELATED DATA FIELDS DID NOT MAKE SENSE. LOOKS LIKE SOME TYPE OF OVERLAY MAY BE OCCURING. ABENDING POLICY WAS 5770001560 THE CALLING CHAIN CKFPMATV CALLS CKUBVALX SOUNDED REAL FAMILIAR. DID SOME CHECKING AND FOUND THAT THIS WAS SAME PROBLEM THAT OCCURRED IN TEST LAST MONTH. THAT IS, THE POLICY HAD MORE PAYMENTS THAT WHAT OUR ACCUMATION TABLE CAN HOLD WHICH IS 208. (REFER TO EMAIL 2\/14\/04 SUBJECT: TEST CL$$0100 ABENDS) ",
  "SOLUTION": "DROPPED THIS POLICY FROM THE ME FILES ONLY USING CL$$POLD. UNCATALOGED THE FOLLOWING: CL.CL$$1020.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN.G0070V00 CL.CL$$1020.POLSEQ.EXTSRSL.G0034V00 (PARTIALLY CREATED) RERAN CL$$1020 FROM THE TOP. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0015"
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "FILE TRANSFER FOR FILE CLUCAMRA FAILED. \"OPEN FAIL FOR COPY OUTPUT\" ",
  "ANALYSIS": "OPERATORS SAID OUR MAINFRAME FILE WAS THERE BUT THE DESTINATION LAN FOLDER WAS NOT: \\\\S5\\VOL1\\USERS\\TEAM\\CAMRA\\CLTRADES.TXT ",
  "SOLUTION": "TOLD OPERATORS TO CALL SEPARATE ACCOUNTS AS WE CANNOT CREATE THEIR FOLDERS. MIKE THE OPERATOR SAID HE WOULD CALL THEM IN THE MORNING AS THE NEXT CAMRA CYCLE WAS NOT SCHEDULED TO RUN UNTIL MONDAY. MONDAY MORNING, SPOKE WITH BRIAN HOBSON. HE SAID THEIR FOLDER GOT ACCIDENTALLY MOVED. HE RECREATED THE FOLDER AND RERAN THE CDFT SATURDAY NIGHT. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$RC30",
  "PROBLEM": "SYSUT1 GOT B37 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "RAN TEST.CL.TOOLS(DB2RESET) TO RESET THE UTILITY IN STEP0040. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RAN JOB FROM TOP WITH SPACE OVERRIDE. NEXT DAY, FOUND OUT THAT A RESET IS DONE IN STEP0010 AND IT WAS NOT NECESSARYTO RUN TEST.CL.TOOLS(DB2RESET). "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP0210 WAS LOOPING ",
  "ANALYSIS": "IT HAD BEEN ONE HOUR SINCE LAST 10,000TH POLICY DISPLAY HAD BEEN REFRESHED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CANCELED CL$$0100 WITH DUMP. SUSPENDED LAST POLICY IN CL.CL$$0100.CKAP01V.DEBUG(0) *********** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** RAN CL$$R060 AND CL$$RC30 RERAN CL$$0100 FROM TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$9800",
  "PROBLEM": "+UNABLE TO RETRIEVE STUB POOL RECORD +- - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS JOB CAN BE RUN DURING THE DAY. SOMEONE MUST'VE BEEN IN A POLICY THE JOB WAS TRYING TO READ AT THAT TIME. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RERUN THE JOB FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0120",
  "PROBLEM": "IEF450I CL$$0120 STEP0030 CL$$0120 - ABEND=S000 U0999 STEP=STEP0030 PGM=CKBSBCCT ABENDED - COND CODE S3E7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FIRST LOOKED IN AT THE BOTTOM OF THE REPORT IN SYSLST TO GET A FEEL FOR WHERE IN THE LIST OF POLICIES THAT THE JOB WENT DOWN. FOUND IT WAS AROUND 0620126720. WENT INTO SYSPDUMP AND DID A SEARCH ON 06201 AND FOUND THE HIGHEST POLICY NUMBER WITH THIS PREFIX... 0620129820. ",
  "SOLUTION": "MADE A COPY OF THE LAST GEN OF CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.BILLEXTS AND CREATED A JCL AND PROC FOR CL$$0120 WITH STEPS 20 AND 30 IN THEM. DELETED 0620129820 RECORD FROM THE COPY OF THE FILE AND RAN THE JCL WITH THOSE TWO STEPS. JOB RAN CLEAN. LOGGED IN USING FIRECALL AND DELETED THE RECORD FOR THE ABOVE POLICY. RESTARTED JOB FROM THE TOP. JOB RAN CLEAN. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$D060 WAS RUN INSTEAD OF CL$$R060. OTHER SITUATIONS WHICH COULD CAUSE THIS PROBLEM IS AFTER A FAILED RUN OF CL$$0100, IF CL$$0060 WAS RUN AGAIN BY MISTAKE. ** BOTTOM LINE IS THE INTERIM BACKUPS ARE EITHER CORRUPT OR GONE. WHAT DO YOU DO? ",
  "ANALYSIS": "YOU WILL NEED TO BACKUP TO THE BEGINNING OF THE CYCLE AND START OVER. ",
  "SOLUTION": ">CLEANUP WRAP FILES - DO SOME ANALYSIS, USE FIRECALL CL.CL$$0005.AUDIT.BK(-0) CL.BASEB.ACCT.EXT(-0) CL.CL$$IVRM.AUDIT.FILE.BK(-0) THESE WERE THE FILES DETERMINED FROM THIS CYCLE >RESTORE TO BEGINNING OF CYCLE ******* NOTE: CL$$RC10 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL2 ******** HAVE OPS FORCE IN AND RUN CL$$R010\/CL$$RC10 >RE-RUN OF THE CYCLE - DO SOME ANALYSIS SINCE YOU HAVE JUST RESTORED CLIENT AND MASTER FILES - ANY JOB WHICH UPDATES CLIENT\/MASTER FILES WILL NEED TO BE RE-RUN. HAVE OPS RE-RUN IN A PROVIDED ORDER CL$$0005 CL$$0012 CL$$0015 CL$$0814 CL$$IVRM CL$$0017 CL$$0018 ONLY IF IT RAN IN RECOVERY CYCLE CL$$0020 TO RESET DPFS EXTENTS CL$$0030 CL$$0040 CL$$0060 CL$$0100 ** FROM HERE THE REST OF THE CYCLE SHOULD TAKE OFF ** THERE MAY BE ADDITIONAL JOBS ADDED TO THE CYCLE ** AFTER THIS LIST WAS WRITTEN ON 1\/21\/04. >JOBS ELECTED NOT TO RE-RUN AND WHY CL$$0001 - JUST VSAM VERIFIES CL$$0003 - NO MASTER FILES UPDATED CL$$0010 - DON'T NEED NEW IMAGE COPY OR SB'S ALREADY HAVE A GOOD PRICE FILE CL$$ABR1 - ABR1 BACKED UP SB'S WHICH DON'T CHG CL$$0014 - NO MASTER FILE UPDATES POLICY PAGES - THEY WON'T CHANGE CL$$0050 - NO MASTER FILES UPDATED CL$$0035 - NO MASTER FILES UPDATED CL$$0070 - NO MASTER FILES UPDATED "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "# IEF450I CL$$0100 STEP0490 JSTEP010 - ABEND=S000 U0999 -STEP=STEP0490 PGM=CKDHXC11 ABENDED - COND CODE S3E7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE U0999 INDICATES THE PROGRAM BLEW ITSELF UP. ROUTING TO THE 'ST' QUEUE AND USING A ? AND FINDING STEP0490.SYSLST INDICATES A DATE ERROR PROBLEM ON AN INPUT FILE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTORE USING CL$$RC30 & CL$$R060 CLEANUP TEST.CL.BASEB.ACCT.EXT(-0) ANY OCCURANCES WHICH HAPPENED IN THIS CYCLES RUN OF CL$$0100 RESTART CL$$0100 FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "+CKUB01 CEEHDLR CONDITION HANDLER SERVICE INVOKEDU0999 + 357 2 AP0357 - ALL FUNDS HAVE NOT BEEN UBMC00 +ERROR RETURN FROM CKUBMC00 +- - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - ***==================================== *** WHOLE BUNCH OF ABENDS BETWEEN ***==================================== IEF450I CL$$0100 STEP0210 JSTEP010 - ABEND=S04C U0000 REA TIME=22.53.50 # IEF450I CL$$0100 STEP0210 JSTEP010 - ABEND=S04C U0000 R ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS WAS A NON-PRICING CYCLE. THE CARD FORMAT IN THE TEST.CL.CARDLIB(FUNDBYPS) WAS INCORRECT. THE FIELD MUST BE 5 POSITIONS AND 2 ENTRIES MUST EXIST. IN THIS CASE, ONLY 4 POSITIONS HAD BEEN ENTERED. *********** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTORE USING CL$$RC30 & CL$$R060 CORRECT TEST.CL.CARDLIB(FUNDBYPS). BY ADDING A LEAD 0 RESTART CL$$0100 FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0010",
  "PROBLEM": "WAS CORRECTED BUT THE WRONG JOB WAS RUN DURING RESTORES (CL$$D060 WHICH DELETES THE SI FILES INSTEAD OF CL$$R060). A SECOND ABEND OCCURRED DUE TO THE RESTORE PROBLEM BUT WE COULD NOT RECOVER TO RESTART CL$$0100. DELETE THE FOLLOWING GDGS BEFORE RESTARTING ANY JOBS: CL.CL$$0005.AUDIT.BK(-0) CL.BASEB.ACCT.EXT(-0) CL.CL$$IVRM.AUDIT.FILE.BK(-0). RUN RESTORES - CL$$R010 & CL$$RC10. WE NEED TO RESTART THE CYBERLIFE CYCLE AT CL$$0005. FOR THIS PARTICULAR CYCLE, WE DID NOT NEED TO RE-RUN CL$$0014, CL$$0035, CL$$0050, CL$$0070, CL$$0835, CL$$0836, CL$$0845, CL$$0846, CL$$0847, CL$$0848 AND CL$$0849. THE REMAINDER OF THE JOBS RAN THROUGH CL$$0100 - REMEMBER TO HAVE THE OUTPUT FROM THE SECOND CYCLE SENT TO CONTROL-D. AT THIS POINT, THE CYCLE RESUMED RUNNING NORMALLY THROUGH CONTROL-M. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "INTEREST RATE FILE PROBLEM. NO ABEND, BUT THE FOLLOWING ERROR MESSAGE SHOWS UP ON SEVERAL JOBS ERROR REPORTS: AP0141 - INT RTE SEGMENT FOR REQUESTED PRIOR PRD CODE NOT FOUND ",
  "ANALYSIS": "INTEREST RATE FILE WAS PARTIALLY UPDATED OR UPDATED AFTER MONTH END. ACTUARIAL SOMETIMES MISSES A BUCKET OR TWO WHEN UPDATING THE INTEREST RATE FILE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAVE ACTUARIAL CORRECT THE CURRENT INTEREST RATE FILE. WE HAVE TO RERUN AFFECTED JOBS WITH THE CURRENT INTEREST RATE FILE SINCE ACTUARIAL UPDATED IT AFTER MONTH END. THE JOBS TO RERUN DEPEND ON WHAT INTEREST RATE BUCKET WAS MISSED. IT COULD BE UL RELATED OR IVA RELATED. 1. DETERMINE WHICH ME\/QE\/YE JOBS USE THE INTEREST RATE FILE. 2. DETERMINE WHICH JOBS USE CL.CL$$1020.POLSEQ* FILES BECAUSE THEY WERE CREATED WITH THE INTEREST RATE FILE THOSE JOBS WOULD HAVE TO BE RERAN TOO. 3. DETERMINE WHICH BACKUPS SHOULD BE RECREATED. ME\/QE\/YE 4. RESTORE DB2S TO DESIRED DATE. 5. COPY CL.VSAM.BASEOL.INTRATES TO CL.ME.VSAM.BASEOL.INTRATES 6. RERUN AFFECTED JOBS IN STEPS 1,2. A. PERFORM ANY NECESSARY FILE TRANSFERS 7. RERUN AFFECTED BACKUPS IN STEP 3. REFER TO THE FOLLOWING DOCUMENT FOR THE 12\/31\/03 INCIDENT: J:\\CYBERLIFE\\ISSUES LOG\\MODDOCS\\INTEREST RATE FILE PROBLEM.DOC "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0810",
  "PROBLEM": "GETTING SOC7 IN THIS STEP. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED AT DUMP FOR RECORD(S) TO DELETE. POLICIES DELETED FROM COPY OF INPUT FILE: 3360164515 3360221131 3362018889 LOOKED IN FA DUMP FOR THE INPUT FILE DDNAME WHICH WAS IAGTPRD. WHEN YOU GET A HIT, THE FIRST POLICY THAT APPEARS IS THE 'PREVIOUS RECORD'. YOU HAVE TO PAGE DOWN A LITTLE TO SEE THE 'CURRENT RECORD'. AS IT TURNS OUT, A CHANGE HAD BEEN MOVED INTO PROD THIS DAY WHICH CAUSED THE ABEND. A PERMANENT FIX IS BEING WORKED ON. ",
  "SOLUTION": "FIRST ATTEMPT TO DELETED RECORDS I GOT THE WRONG RECORDS AND DELETED FROM PRODUCTION FILE USING FIRE CALL. THEN CONTACTED BACK UP, SANDI JEFFS, TOGETHER WE RESEARCHED PROBLEM AND EVENTUALLY DROPPED THREE POLICIES FROM A COPY OF THE INPUT FILE, TO GET CLEAN UNIT TEST RUN OF JUST THIS STEP. RESTARTED IN ABENDING STEP AND USING FILE TEST.CL.TDR.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AGTPRDEX.G0566 ORIGINAL FILE WAS SAVED AS: TEST.CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AGTPRDEX.G0566 THIS IS A HARD ONE TO DEBUG AS THE DUMP OFTEN HAS SEVERAL POLICIES DUE TO THE WAY THE VSAM INPUT FILE IS READ. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1030",
  "PROBLEM": "PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) AT LOCATION 000E6A IN ELEMENT CKVA80TP ALSO RECEIVING ERROR TYPE 4039 CONTENTS OF SYSLST... CONTRACT Y H NUMBER P S LINE PAR CLASS ERROR DESCRIPTION 0620139300 2 02 I N 5 EXIT TRANSACTION MISSING 0620140400 1 01 0 N 5 UNEXPECTED ENTRY PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) AT LOCATION 000E PSW = 078D1000 8C425638 REGISTERS AT TIME OF INTERRUPT: 00-07 0C4A9E44 0002A8B0 0C4FE4B8 0C4248F8 0C4E93F8 0C4FE4B8 0C512E30 4 08-15 0C4FE088 0C4A9CF8 0C512E80 0C426F50 0C4248C4 0002A6A8 8C42539C 8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "COULD NOT GET COMPILE LISTING TO MATCHING E6A OFFSET WITH BOTH A PAN AND PDS COMPILE. NARROWED POLICIES IN THE DUMP TO 0620141260 AND 0620141270. TRIED DROPPING THEM FROM POLICY EXIBIT TRX FILE. HOWEVER ON A TEST RERUN, PROGRAM ABENDED IN A DIFFERENT SPOT. NEXT WE DROPPED BOTH POLICES FROM THE CL.CL$$1020.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN.G0067V00 FILE USING TEST.CL.WET.JCL(WAAPDRP1). TEST JOB RAN PAST 0620140400.(LAST ONE IN SYSLST) NEXT WE DROPPED JUST 0620141260 FROM CL.CL$$1020.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN.G0067V00 AND THE TEST JOB RAN PAST 0620140400.(LAST ONE IN SYSLST) CONFIRMED PROBLEM POLICY WAS 0620141260. THE POLICY WAS AN 8 WAY AGENT SPLIT AND CONTAINED 24 - 38 SEGMENTS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DROPPED JUST 0620141260 FROM CL.CL$$1020.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN.G0067V00 USING TEST.CL.WET.JCL(WAAPDRP1). 01\/30\/04: DROPPED POLICIES 0620141260 & 0620150550 ON G68. SAVED ORIGINAL IN G68 FILE (WE DID NOT HAVE TO DROP ANYTHING FROM THE TRX FILE) THE DROP CREATED TEST.CL.CL$$1020.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN.DEC31 USING FIRECALL, RENAMED CL.CL$$1020.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN.G0067V00 TO CL.CL$$1020.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN.G67 RENAMED TEST.CL.CL$$1020.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN.DEC31 TO CL.CL$$1020.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN.G0067V00 RERAN CL$$1030 FROM TOP. JOB ENDED OK. 02\/27\/04: RECEIVING ERROR 4039 NOT JUST 0C7 EA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT 717 USER COMPLETION CODE=4039 REASON CODE=00000000 TIME=03.24.46 SEQ=12904 CPU=0000 ASID=0094 DROPPED POLICIES 0620141260 & 0620150550 ON G69. SAVED ORIGINAL IN G69 FILE (WE DID NOT HAVE TO DROP ANYTHING FROM THE TRX FILE) ALSO RAN WAAPDRP1 TO TAKE OFF THE 'RL' RECORDS IN COLUMN 4. THE DROP CREATED TEST.CL.CL$$1020.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN.FEBME USING FIRECALL, RENAMED CL.CL$$1020.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN.G0069V00 TO CL.CL$$1020.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN.G69 RENAMED TEST.CL.CL$$1020.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN.FEBME TO CL.CL$$1020.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN.G0069V00 RERAN CL$$1030 FROM TOP. JOB ENDED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$4035",
  "PROBLEM": "+STUB POOL STUB FOUND ON UNENHANCED RECORD COMPLETION CODE 4039 CC=S001 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "NOT LE COMLIANT ",
  "SOLUTION": "MADE CHANGES TO LINK 'MODE AMODE(31),RMODE(ANY)'. RELINKED AND MOVED CHANGES TO PROD. RERAN JOB FROM TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$UVPM",
  "PROBLEM": "IEC030I B37-04,IFG0554A,P1DLCCPY,STEP0010,VPMODEL,0E1A,AP +IAMW13 DD=VPMODEL FILE FULL, REORGANIZATION REQUIRED DD:VPMODEL FWRITE: EDC5065I A WRITE SYSTEM ERROR WAS DETECTED. R15 VALUE = 8, REASON CODE = 28, RBA = 0, LAST OP = VSAM PUT ERROR: FWRITE(\"DD:MODEL\"...) FAILED ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FILE FULL PRETTY CLEAR. VSAM NEEDS TO BE ENLARGED ",
  "SOLUTION": "INCREASE CLDO VSAM FILE SIZE AND REBUILD VSAM. ALL MODELS IN CL.VPMS.MODELS WILL NEED TO BE RELOADED UPDATE CARDLIB CLIVPMS WITH MODEL LIST TO LOAD "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0007",
  "PROBLEM": "JCL ERROR ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CLEANUP STEP RECEIVED 'VOL ON INELIGIBLE PERMRES OR RSVD UNIT' ERROR MESSAGE. NOTICED SOME FILES TO BE DELETED WERE ON THE STOLXX VOLUMES. ",
  "SOLUTION": "LOGGED ON USING FIRECALL AND MANUALLY DELETED THE FILES FOR THAT STEP. RESTARTED JOB IN STEP0090 AND USED THE OVERRIDES GENOT='-0' AND GENIN='-1'. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "WHEN RUNNING A UNIT TEST OF CL$$0030 DURING THE DAY, ACF SECURITY FAILED AND ALLOWED DB2P TO BE UPDATED. SO WE HAD 20-30 POLICIES GO DOWN WITH EITHER A CISLOR OR CISLAR SQL100. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WE BASICALLY HAD TO KEEP RERUNNING CL$$0011 TO LIST ALL OF THE POLICIES. THEN WE ALSO HAD TO EITHER CHANGE PURG TO CK4P AND SET THE ADR_SEQ_NUM TO 0 IN CLT_OBJ_RELATION OR COPY CK4I ROWS IN CLT_OBJ_RELAT ION AND SET THE ADR_SEQ_NUM TO 0. THIS SHOULD (PROBABLY) NEVER HAPPEN AGAIN ONCE THE ACF SECURITY IS FIXED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "IEF450I CL$$0100 STEP0210 JSTEP010 - ABEND=S04C U0000 +PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C4 (PROTECTION) +CKUB03 CURRENT POLICY 2453292520 +CKSN02 ABENDING ELEMENT CKVSAMIO ON 11\/11\/2003 THE FOLLOWING MESSAGE - (SUSPENDING THIS POLICY DID NOT GET AROUND THE ABEND) +CKSN01 PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. PSW=078D1000 8C672A6A +CKUB03 CURRENT POLICY 2453292900 +CKSN02 ABENDING ELEMENT CKVSAMIO EPA=0C672768 OFFSET ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DEBUG HAS LAST POLICY AS A POLICY AFTER THIS. ATTEMPTS WERE MADE TO SUSPEND THE POLICIES IN THE DUMP UNDER BASEOL.POLICY FOR CURRENT RECORD. THESE POLICIES MATCH THE LAST POLICY IN THE DEBUG FILE. AFTER 8 POLICIES WERE ATTEMPTED THIS WAY. THE ABOVE POLICY WAS ADDED TO THE LIST ALONG WITH THE POLICY BEFORE THE ONE ABOVE, THE ADDITION OF THE MOST RECENT POLICY IN THE DEBUG FILE AND THE ONE BEFORE THE POLICY IN THE DEBUG FILE. THE JOB PROCESSED OKAY. THINGS TO CONSIDER > WHAT MOVED TO PRODUCTION RECENTLY > ANY SPECIAL JOBS RUN THAT NIGHT >CONVERSIONS >POLICY RESTORES > ANY PRIOR JOB RESTORE WORK DONE *********** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** ",
  "SOLUTION": "RUN RESTORES CL$$RC30, CL$$R060 ** ONE TIME ONLY - BEGIN ** RUN TEST.CL.TOOLS(DB2MCLTA) TO CAPTURE CLIENT ONCE THE CL$$RC30 JOB HAS COMPLETED. THIS WILL HELP WITH PROBLEM SOLVING LATER ** ONE TIME ONLY - END ** SUSPEND ALL POLICIES SUSPECTED OF HAVING OR CAUSING PROBLEMS USING CL$$SUSP. UPDATE TEST.CL.DATA(SUSPEND) MEMBER WITH ALL MEMBERS YOU WANT TO SUSPEND. RUN CL$$SUSP. REMEMBER, IF YOU RESTORE, YOU HAVE TO RESUSPEND ANY POLICIES YOU MIGHT HAVE SUSPENDED IN THE LAST ATTEMPT. CONTINUE PROCESS UNTIL YOU ARE THROUGH IT. IF YOU PASS 3 SUSPENSIONS OR 1 HOUR, GET YOUR BACKUP INVOLVED. THE BACKUP SHOULD BEGIN WORKING THE PROBLEM AND SCOPE IN PARALLEL WITH SUSPEND WORK. IF THE BACKUP IS NOT MAKING PROGRESS BY 1:00, THEY SHOULD GET ANOTHER BACKUP INVOLVED. WATCH YOUR TEST.CL.BOMBLOG(DEADLINES) SPECIAL: WE MISSED OUR DEADLINES FOR CL$$0700 - SEPARATE ACCOUNTS CONTACTED AND NOTIFIED OPERATION CONFIRMED THEY BYPASSED CYBERLIFE INPUT PROCESS VIA OMNI CL$$0004 - NOTE SENT TO ROBERT BIZLEY TO CHECK FOR SUCCESSFUL RUN OF CL$$0004 AND IF RUN OKAY LOAD ON-LINE SERVICES ALL OTHER JOBS COMPLETED ON TIME NOTIFY SUPPORT TEAMS OF PROBLEMS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "SHOUT MESSAGE INDICATING 'ACCOUNTING BATCH REJECTED IN CL$$0100'. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE 'GEN ACCT BATCH' REPORT OUT OF CL$$0100 STEP0410. IF THE BATCH THAT WAS REJECTED WAS AN 'AICWA' BATCH SEE THE INSTRUCTIONS IN TEST.CL.BOMBLOG(ACCTGPRB) FOR RESOLVING THE PROBLEM. WE WILL NEED TO FIX THE BAD ENTRY AND SEND THE FILE BACK THRU THE NEXT CYCLE. IF THE REJECTED BATCH WAS NOT AN 'AICWA' BATCH THEN WE DO NOTHING. THE USERS WILL REVIEW AND DETERMINE THE ACCOUNTING FIX NEEDED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "REJECTED ACCOUNTING BATCH THIS PARTICULAR ISSUE DOES NOT CAUSE AN ABEND. BUT WE WANTED TO DOCUMENT IT AND THE RESOLUTION IN THE BOMBLOG SINCE MOST PEOPLE LOOK HERE FIRST. WHAT HAPPENS: AN ACCOUNTING BATCH IS REJECTED IN STEP0410 OF THE TIME DRIVEN JOB. THE ERROR REPORT DOES NOT INDICATE WHY THE BATCH REJECTED. IT ONLY TAKES ONE RECORD TO BE BAD AND THE ENTIRE BATCH WILL REJECT. THERE IS NO ABEND OR BAD CONDITION CODE ON THE STEP. THE FILE THAT CONTAINS THE ACCOUNTING IS CL.BASEB.GENBATCH. IT REQUIRES SOMEONE TO PHYSICALLY SEE THE ERROR REPORT OR BE MISSING THE ACCOUNTING ENTRIES. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "IT CAN BE A BAD STATE CODE, NO ACCOUNT CODE OR AN INCORRECT ACCOUNT CODE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "SEE TEST.CL.BOMBLOG(ACCTGPRB) FOR THE FIX. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB ABENDED IN STEP 20 WITH S0C1 DUE TO DUPLICATE ROW IN CLT_ADR_RELATION (CISLAR). ",
  "ANALYSIS": "REVIEW DUMP TO FIND POLICY # 2453261320 WITH DUP ROW ",
  "SOLUTION": "EXPIRE DUPLICATE ROWS USING PST, RERUN FROM ABENDING STEP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0910",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB GOT CONDITION CODE 12, WITH S0C1 ABEND IN STEP 20. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "REVIEWED IN EXPEDITER AND FOUND POLICY # 5448915000 DID NOT HAVE SEGMENT 77 CREATED YET. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DELETE RECORD WITH POLICY # 5448915000 FROM INPUT FILE. RE-RUN USING EDITED INPUT FILE RESTARTING IN STEP 20. FOLLOW UP ISSUE WILL BE CREATED TO ADDRESS THIS SITUATION. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0837",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB HAD BEEN PROCESSING THIS STEP FROM 21.59 FOR OVER AN HOUR, STEP APPEARED TO BE LOOPING. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB STUCK IN STEP0220 ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAVE OPS KILL JOB AND RESOLVE IN AM "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$9800",
  "PROBLEM": "CC16 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "IN THE SYSLST WENT TO THE BOTTOM AND PAGED UP ONE. THIS SHOWS A CONSOLIDATED ERROR LISTING. THE STATEMENT COLUMN SHOWS A LINE NUMBER. DID A FIND ON THE LINE NUMBER AND IT SPECIFIED A LINE REGARDING THE BIRTHDATE. WENT THROUGH THE REPORT IN SYSPRT LOOKING AT THE BIRTH- DATES. CAME ACROSS A BIRTHDAY OF 00\/00\/0000. BELIEVE THERE NEEDS TO BE A VALID DATE IN THIS FIELD. LET THE SYSTEM SUPPORT TEAM KNOW OF THE CLIENT NAME IN CASE WE NEED TO GET A VALID BIRTHDATE IN THE SYSTEM FOR THIS INSURED. ANALYSIS2: SAME AS ABOVE BUT FOUND SPACES IN THE OWNER\\PAYOR (A2) FIELDS ON SEVERAL ALIS POLICIES. THIS IS VALID AS SPACES ON THIS FIELD & MEANS THE OWNER\/PAYOR IS THE SAME AS THE INSURED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "FORCED JOB OK...VERIFY THAT CDFT8114 RUNS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$BIND",
  "PROBLEM": "STEPS 30 & 50 RECEIVED CC8, STEP 55 RECEIVED CC4 UNSUCCESSFUL BINDS. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "BIND PACKAGE(CLCIS) MEMBER(XPIOCHK) OWNER(CLADMIN) QUALIFIER(CLADMIN) ) EXPLAIN(NO) DSNX200I +DB2P BIND SQL ERROR USING CLADMIN AUTHORITY PLAN=(NOT APPLICABLE) DBRM=XPIOCHK STATEMENT=1394 SQLCODE=-199 SQLSTATE=42601 TOKENS=INTO + - : <INTEGER CSECT NAME=DSNHPARS RDS CODE=0 DSNT233I +DB2P UNSUCCESSFUL BIND FOR PACKAGE = DB2P.CLCIS.XPIOCHK.() BIND PACKAGE(CLCIS) QUALIFIER (CLADMIN) MEMBER (XPIBCHK) ACTION(REP AIN(NO) OWNER(CLADMIN) DSNX200I +DB2P BIND SQL ERROR USING CLADMIN AUTHORITY PLAN=(NOT APPLICABLE) DBRM=XPIBCHK STATEMENT=1598 SQLCODE=-199 SQLSTATE=42601 TOKENS=INTO + - : <INTEGER CSECT NAME=DSNHPARS RDS CODE=0 DSNT233I +DB2P UNSUCCESSFUL BIND FOR PACKAGE = DB2P.CLCIS.XPIBCHK.() ",
  "SOLUTION": "BOTH HAVE KNOWN PROBLEMS SINCE THE RELEASE OF 0101. FORCED COMPLETE TO CONTINUE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0160",
  "PROBLEM": "4 DATASETS AUXSEG2,BILLINFO,MCSERRFL, & MCSRESFL HAD NOT CATLGD 2 PROBLEMS ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THESE FILES WERE DELETED YESTERDAY BY LAVONNA DUE TO PROBLEMS ON 7\/29\/03 IN CL$$0160. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DELETED THESE FILES AND SET-UP JOB TO RESNAP JUST THESE FILES. COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. FORCED CL$$0160 COMPLETE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0160",
  "PROBLEM": "DX FILES RECEIVED CC=8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ALTERNATE INDEX PROBLEMS AGAIN ALSO RECEIVED NOT RECATALD 2 MESSAGES. THESE FILES DID NOT CATALOG CAUSES PROBLEMS IN JOB CL$$0004. TO KNOW A FILE IS NOT CATALOGED IF YOU DO A 3;4 ON THE FILE AND IT DOESN'T SHOW UP THEN YOU MOST LIKELY HAVE A NOT CATALOGED SITUATION. IF YOU SPECIFY THE VOLUME YOU SHOULD SEE THE FILE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "FORCED JOB COMPLETE AFTER TRYING TO DEFINE THE DX FILES UNSUCCESSFULLY. IF THE DX FILES OR MCSERRFL RECEIVE THE CC=8 YOU CAN FORCE COMPLETE AND GO ON. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0004",
  "PROBLEM": "JCL ERROR ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CL.SA.VSAM FILES MISSING. PROBLEMS WITH JOB CL$$0160. HAD VSAM FILES NOT CATALOGED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CATALOGED THE POLICY, AUXSEG1, AND UTABLES FILES USING FIRECALL. RERAN JOB FROM TOP. TO KNOW A FILE IS NOT CATALOGED IF YOU DO A 3;4 ON THE FILE AND IT DOESN'T SHOW UP THEN YOU MOST LIKELY HAVE A NOT CATALOGED SITUATION. IF YOU SPECIFY THE VOLUME YOU SHOULD SEE THE FILE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$IIAM",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$IIAM ABENDED WITH A COND CODE 0008 BECAUSE THE CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG2 ALREADY IN USE, BY CL$$0006. ********************************* TOP OF DATA ************************** FDR400 REORG LOG -- FDRREORG VER 5.4\/22P -- INNOVATION DATA PROCESSIN VOLUME MESSAGE---------------------------------------------------------- ------ ----------------------------------------------------------------- CICS50 FDRR94** UNABLE TO ALLOCATE TARGET DATASET-COMP=04,CODE=0210,INFO CICS50 IKJ56225I DATA SET CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG2 ALREADY IN USE, TRY LAT CICS50 IKJ56225I DATA SET IS ALLOCATED TO ANOTHER JOB OR USER CICS50 FDRR32** BACKUP PROCESSING TERMINATED CICS50 FDRR33** BACKUP FAILED - CODE=00008,DSN=CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG2 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS HAPPENED IN MODEL CYCLE AND WAS DOCUMENTED HERE. BECAUSE WE HAVE A FEW JOBS THAT HAVE THE SAME DEPENDANCY AS CL$$IIAM THIS CAN HAPPEN. IIAM HAS TO HAVE EXCLUSIVE CONTROL WHEN IT RUNS. CL$$0006 WAS USING THE AUXSEG2 FILE IN SHARE MODE. THE JOBS WERE STARTED CLOSE TO THE SAME TIME. ",
  "SOLUTION": "WHEN OPS CALLED CL$$0006 HAD FINISHED, BUT CL$$0004 WAS RUNNING. SO I TOLD OPS TO WAIT FOR 4 TO FINISH THEN RUN IIAM FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0911",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB ABENDED WITH CONDITION CODE 50 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE PROGRAM WILL ABEND IF THE FUNDVAL RECORD IT IS SEARCHING THE CL.VSAM.BASEOL.FUNDVAL FILE FOR IS NOT THERE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPY PROGRAM TO PAN.CL.PANLIB, EDIT TO ALLOW IT TO BYPASS THE RECORD IF THE FUNDVAL COULD NOT BE FOUND COMPILE, LINK AND RUN FROM MY UNIT TEST AREA. JOB COMPLETED OK HAD OPS FORCE IT OK IN PRODUCTION. WILL RESOLVE WHY THE VALUES WERE NOT ON THE FUNDVAL FILE IN THE MORNING. 10\/28\/09: SAME PROBLEM AS ABOVE, HAD THE JOB FORCE COMPLETED SENT EMAIL TO TRIAGE.IND TO RESEARCH PROBLEM 2453471940 FUNDVAL RECORD: V 14E8 F NOT FOUND ON FUNDVAL 1 2453471940 FUNDVAL RECORD: V 14FS F NOT FOUND ON FUNDVAL 1 2453471940 FUNDVAL RECORD: V 14E4 F NOT FOUND ON FUNDVAL 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0700",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP=STEP0027 PGM=IDCAMS EXECUTED - COND CODE 0008 REPRO INFILE(INPUT) - OUTFILE(OUTPUT) REUSE IDC3302I ACTION ERROR ON CL.VSAM.BASEOL.FND1 IDC3314I **RECORD OUT OF SEQUENCE - KEY FOLLOWS: 000000 F2F0F0F3 60F0F760 F0F1F2F1 F3F1F4F1 E2E5C2E2 D9C7 LAP 000000 F2F0F0FR 60F0F360 F2F4F2F1 F3F4F0F1 C4E8D5C9 E5C2 FCC 000000 F2F0F0F7 60F1F060 F0F3F2F1 F3F7F0F3 C1D3C7C1 C1C7 IDC0005I NUMBER OF RECORDS PROCESSED WAS 20313 FCC IDC0005I NUMBER OF RECORDS PROCESSED WAS 26525 SLJ IDC3302I ACTION ERROR ON CL.VSAM.BASEOL.FND1 SLJ IDC3314I **RECORD OUT OF SEQUENCE - KEY FOLLOWS: SLJ 000000 F2F0F0F8 60F0F360 F0F3F2F1 F5F0F0F1 C1D3C2E2 C3D7 JIF IDC3302I ACTION ERROR ON CL.VSAM.BASEOL.FND1 JIF IDC3314I **RECORD OUT OF SEQUENCE - KEY FOLLOWS: JIF 000000 F2F0F0F8 60F0F660 F3F0F2F2 F3F0F5F2 C6E3C2E5 C1F1 JIF IDC0005I NUMBER OF RECORDS PROCESSED WAS 26750 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CL$$0700, OUR FUNDS TRANSMITTAL JOB GOT A SEQUENCE ERROR ON THE FOLLOWING RECORDS WHILE TRYING TO LOAD THE CL.VSAM.BASEOL.FND1 FILE. THE KEY IS 22 BYTES AND DUPLICATES ARE NOT ALLOWED. DETERMINED THAT THE RECORDS CAME FROM CL$$0690 WHICH READS THE CDFT FILE CL.ADJUST.UPLOAD THAT COMES FROM SEPARATE ACCOUNTS. 2003-07-01213141SVBSRG*0000B0000000030223 2003-07-01213141SVBSRG*0000S0000000002349 LAP 2004-03-24213401DYNIVB*0000S0000000066327 (LOADED) LAP 2004-03-24213401DYNIVB*0000S000000000 494 WET 2007-08-20213213APPIVB*0000S0000000002866 LOADED WET 2007-08-20213213APPIVB*0000S000000000 599 DID NOT LOAD FCC 2007-10-03213703ALGAAG*0000S0000000046931 LOADED FCC 2007-10-03213703ALGAAG*0000S0000000619109 DID NOT LOAD SLJ 2008-03-03215001ALBSCP*0000B0000005949581 LOADED SLJ 2008-03-03215001ALBSCP*0000S0000000296556 DID NOT LOAD JIF FROM CL.ADJUST.OUTPUT: JIF 2008-06-30223052FTBVA1*0000S000000000 051 LOADED JIF 2008-06-30223052FTBVA1*0000S0000000036582 DID NOT LOAD JIF TO CL.VSAM.BASEOL.FND1 THE PROGRAM LOADED THE 302.23 (B)UY RECORD. HOWEVER, IT DID NOT LOAD HE 23.49 (S)ALE RECORD. ",
  "SOLUTION": "WE DECIDED THAT SINCE ALL OTHER 20,313 RECORDS LOADED OK AND ALL OTHER STEPS ENDED OK, TO FORCE THE JOB OK. WE THEN SENT SEPARATE ACCOUNTS AN EMAIL TO NOTIFY THEM THEY NEED TO CORRECT AND RESEND THE RECORD THROUGH. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1000",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$1000 STEP0065 ABENDED. REASON DUE TO MESSAGE: DB2S NOT OPERATIONAL, RETRY COUNT IS ZERO ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DB2S WAS DOWN AND SHOULD BE UP. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CALLED PCD AND HAD THEM BRING UP DB2S AND RESTARTED IN STEP0065 ON THE RESET. STEP0065 ENDED OK. JOB CONTINUED ON. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1000",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP0070 ENDED WITH A JCL ERROR AND FLUSHED. THE FOLLOWING MESSAGE WAS FOUND IN JCL: CL$$1000 STEP0070 CL$$1000 DBRMLIB - DATA SET NOT FOUND I SEARCHED THE PROC AND FOUND THAT DSN DB2.DBRMLIB.DATA.DB2S DID NOT EXIST IN 3.4. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CONSULTED DAN NOAH, THEN DAVID. WE AGREED THE FILE WAS WAS NOT THERE DUE TO SOME TYPE OF ALIAS PROBLEM. THE NEW OPERATING SYSTEM Z\/OS HAD BEEN IMPLEMENTED RECENTLY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "SHORT TERM SOLUTION. POINTED TO THE VERSION SPECIFIC DBRMLIB. ADDED OVERRIDE TO POINT TO DB2.V7.DBRMLIB.DATA.DB2S AND RESTARTED IN STEP0065 ON THE RESET. JOB ENDED OK, CONTINUED ON. NEXT DAY: ROBERT BIZLEY CREATED THE PROPER ALIAS \"DB2.DBRMLIB.DATA.DB2S\" WHICH POINTS TO THE PDS \"DB2.V7.DBRMLIB.DATA.DB2S\". "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0160",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP0010 GOT CC8 ON CL..DXREGSRV. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SIB0700I 02:01:57 SNAP DATASET ( SOURCE (CL.VSAM.BASEOL.DXREGSRV SIB0700I 02:01:57 TARGET (CL.SA.VSAM.BASEOL.DXREG SIB0700I 02:01:57 VOLUME(CICS32) HCPYM SIB0700I 02:01:57 REPLACE(Y) ) SIB4622E OPEN DDN ERROR IN SIBDMOPN, RC=8. SIB0880I 02:01:57 FUNCTION DNOPEN CALLING SIBDMOPN REPORTS RC1=0 SIB4617I 02:01:57 SNAPSHOT COMPLETED, RC=8. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RAN MODIFIED VERSION OF TEST.CL.TOOLS(BLDDXR) TO POINT TO PRODUCTION FILES AND CARDLIB. THE DELE\/DEFINE IS BUILT INTO THIS JOB FOLLOWED BY THE BUILD STEP. RESTARTED CL$$0160 JSTEP020.STEP0010 JOB ENDED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0010",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP0060 GOT CC8 ON THE CL..DXLOGF,DXLGTYP,DXLMRNM AND DXLGTE. THIS PROBLEM HAS BEEN HAPPENING TEST AND MODL LAST FEW WEEKS. THIS TIME, ONLY THE DXL FILES WERE HAVING THE PROBLEM. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SIB0700I 21:47:38 SNAP DATASET ( SOURCE (CL.VSAM.BASEOL.DXLOGF SIB0700I 21:47:38 TARGET (CL.SB.VSAM.BASEOL.DXLOG SIB0700I 21:47:38 VOLUME(CICS43) HCPYM SIB0700I 21:47:38 REPLACE(Y) ) SIB4622E OPEN DDN ERROR IN SIBDMOPN, RC=8. SIB0880I 21:47:39 FUNCTION DNOPEN CALLING SIBDMOPN REPORTS RC1=0 SIB4617I 21:47:39 SNAPSHOT COMPLETED, RC=8. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RAN MODIFIED VERSION OF TOOLS JOBS BY CHANGING THE FILES AND CLDO.. CARDLIBS TO POINT TO PRODUCTION. 1. TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$$RSDX) DELETE\/DEFINE JUST DXL FILES 2. TEST.CL.TOOLS(BLDDXL) (IF DXX FILES ARE INVOLVED, YOU WOULD NEED TO RUN MODIFIED VERSION OF TEST.CL.TOOLS(BLDDXX)) 3. RESTARTED CL$$0010 IN STEP0060. 4. JOB ENDED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$RC99",
  "PROBLEM": "DATASET NOT ACCESSIBLE. DB2S.DSNDBD.CLCISDB.CISBMAIN.I0001.A001 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "VERIFIED DATASET EXISTS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTARTED JOB FROM THE TOP. JOB ENDED OK. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "ERROR ON 89 SEGMENT RETRIEVAL: 2 3465045440 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "NO 89 SEGMENTS FOUND FOR POLICY. TO VERIFY, LOG ON TO PRODUCTION AND DO A 60D7 TRANSACTION FOR THE POLICY; THERE SHOULD NOT BE ANY PEOPLE ON THE POLICY. FOLLOW THIS WITH A 6089 TRANS - NO SEGMENTS SHOULD BE DISPLAYED. IF THIS IS TRUE, CONTACT CYBERLIFE_IND WITH THE POLICY NUMBER AND TELL THEM THAT THE POLICY HAS NO PEOPLE ATTACHED TO THE PENDING SIDE. THEY WILL NEED TO DETERMINE WHAT ACTION TO TAKE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1025",
  "PROBLEM": "U0999 - DATES DO NOT MATCH - 05312003 05302003 P1JIF DATES DO NOT MATCH - 08312011 09012011 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DATES DO NOT MATCH - 05312003 05302003 THE DATES ARE COMPARING THE JCL DATE OVERRIDES TO THE 76 SEGMENT DATE ON THE VALUATION POLICY MASTER. SINCE THE VALUATION EXTRACTS CREATED ON 5\/30 AND THE OVERRIDE DATES CAME IN AS 5\/31. THIS MIS-MATCH WAS CREATED. P1JIF VALUATION EXTRACTS WERE CREATED ON (211C244C) 9\/01 SEE CL.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY 1-..+....10...+----20---+----30---+----40---+----50---+-- ---------------------------------- TOP OF FILE ---------- ..$. A0........J. 76.....<2....@ <= 0350444444444CF00000000DC444444444444444FF002124F00127 06B000000000010000000001B000000000000000760E1C4C20111C ^^^^ ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTART FROM TOP USING CYCLE DATES INSTEAD OF MONTH END DATE. USED 05302003. P1JIF RESTARTED FROM TOP; USED 09\/01\/2011. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "OC1 CKETRGET ",
  "ANALYSIS": "POLICY RESTORE WAS DONE WHICH CLEANS UP THE CLT_OBJ_RELATION\/CLT_ADR_RELATION ROWS. THE POLICY CAPTURE DATE OF 2\/28 DID NOT HAVE ANY PENDING CLIENT BECAUSE THE PENDING RECORD WAS BUILD LATER AND THE REASON THE POLICY WAS TRASHED. HOWEVER, THE PENDING RECORD SHOULD HAVE BEEN DELETED FROM THE PENDING FILE PRIOR TO THE RESTORE. IT WAS NOT. SINCE NO CLIENT EXISTED, BUT THE RECORD DID, THIS CAUSED THE ERROR. THIS STEP IS JUST A REPORT STEP AND ITS DRIVER IS THE PENDING FILE. WE SHOULD BE ABLE TO RE-CREATE THE REPORT LATER. SINCE THE REST OF THE JOB RAN TO COMPLETION, ITS 12:00 AND WE ARE ONLY IN CL$$0030. FORCE JOB AND MOVE ON. ",
  "SOLUTION": "FORCE JOB OKAY AND GET CYCLE MOVING NEXT DAY: TRIED TO RECREATE REPORT. NEED TO USE THE .SB. VERSIONS OF PENDING, BUT ROLL CHANGES HAD BEEN MADE ON CLIENT. THIS CAUSED THE SAME PROBLEM AS ABOVE. I WILL BE UNABLE TO RE-CREATE THE REPORT. RESTORES TO RE-RUN CL$$0030 WOULD HAVE OPENED UP A PRETTY BIG WORK EFFORT. IN THE END THE VALUE GAINED FROM THIS REPORT FOR ONE NIGHT, WAS NOT WORTH IT. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0860",
  "PROBLEM": "ABENDED WITH AN OC7 (DECIMAL DATA) ",
  "ANALYSIS": "BY LOOKING IN THE DUMP FOR THE WORD 'CURRENT' FOUND THE RECORD IN ERROR (POLICY 2453302240) ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. COPIED PROD INPUT FILE (G1283V00) TO TEST.CL.PSS.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT.G1283 2. DELETED ALL RECORDS FOR THIS POLICY OFF THE PROD FILE 3. DELETED THE CURRENT GENS OF OUTPUT FILES: CL.CL$$0860.OTHER.G0564V00 CL.CL$$0860.SAPPH.G0911V00 4. ASKED STEVE B. TO RESTART THIS JOB FROM THE TOP NEW JOB COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "THE ESC IO ENTRY ENDED ABNORMALLY AT 4:51 PM OPERATIONS RECEIVED A SHOUT MESSAGE AND CALLED MIB PROGRAMMER ON CALL. ERROR MESSAGES FROM ABEND: MCMSIS201 ECSESTA2 ABEND CONDITION CODE IS USER 2700 MCMSIS200 ECSESTA1 ABEND CONDITION CODE IS USER 2700 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED UP THE ERROR MESSAGES IN THE MIBCOMM BOOKS, AND FOLLOWED THE SUGGESTION. THIS DID NOT WORK FOR US, AND WE CALLED MIB HELP DESK. THEY SUGGESTED RUNNING MCMWRKFL PROGRAM TO INCREASE THE SIZE OF THE WSDS FOR CYBERLIFE'S IO. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RUN MCMWRKFL TO INCREASE THE NUMBER OF RECORDS ON THE CL.VSAM.BASOL.MIBCOMM.WSDS DATA SET. THIS JCL IS IN TEST.CL.LKM.PDS AND WILL BE MOVED TO TEST.CL.TOOLS. JCL PROVIDED FROM MIB IS FOUND IN PROD.IND.MIBCOMM.INSTALL.CNTL AND THAT IS WHAT I USED, SUBSTITUTING AUL'S FILES AND SUCH WHERE NEEDED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0012",
  "PROBLEM": "NEW FUNDS WERE JUST STARTING UP AND THE UNIT PRICES WERE NOT PROVIDED ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ON 5\/2, SEPARATE ACCOUNTS NEEDED TO GIVE US 5\/1 & 5\/2. I COULD NOT GET THIS TO WORK VIA CL$$0012. SINCE 5\/1 HAD ALREADY BEEN POSTED FOR ALL FUNDS EXCEPT THE NEW FUNDS, AN F0018 EDIT WAS GETTING IN THE WAY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "SEPARATE ACCOUNTS PUT 5\/1 ON VIA THE ON-LINE. 5\/2 CAME THROUGH IN THE CARDS ON 5\/2. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$SEGD",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB GOT USER COMPLETION CODE=4093, NEEDS REGION PARM ",
  "ANALYSIS": "USER COMPLETION CODE=4093 IS NORMALLY CAUSED BECAUSE WE DID NOT ADD THE REGION=0M PARM. LOOKING AT THE JCL IN TEST.CL.TOOLS THAT WAS THE CAUSE THIS TIME TOO. ",
  "SOLUTION": "EDIT THE JCL TO ADD REGION=0M PARM, RERUN FROM TOP CL$$SEGD ALL 05\/02\/2003 10:00PM P1BGR PROBLEM: JCL ERROR - JOB NOT EXECUTED \/\/* ACF01004 LOGONID ACFBCHID NOT FOUND AULHO ANALYSIS: MISSING \/\/*LOGONID ACFSUBID SOLUTION: EDIT THE JCL TO ADD ABOVE, RERUN FROM TOP "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0600",
  "PROBLEM": "0 UNIT PRICES ON VISION AND FANMAIL ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ON A NON-PRICING DAY CL$$0600 CAN NOT RUN AND PRODUCE A PRICE FILE ",
  "SOLUTION": "ADD THE SUSPENSION OF CL$$0600 TO THE NON-PRICING PROCEDURES. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$TRXD",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB GOT USER COMPLETION CODE=4093, NEEDS REGION PARM ",
  "ANALYSIS": "USER COMPLETION CODE=4093 IS NORMALLY CAUSED BECAUSE WE DID NOT ADD THE REGION=0M PARM. LOOKING AT THE JCL IN TEST.CL.TOOLS THAT WAS THE CAUSE THIS TIME TOO. ",
  "SOLUTION": "EDIT THE JCL TO ADD REGION=0M PARM, RERUN FROM TOP "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0901",
  "PROBLEM": "JCL ERROR - STEP FLUSHED FDRW74** ABR AUTO RECALL ABNORMALLY TERMINATED -- COMP CODE=00000378 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SPOKE WITH MARK WILLIAMS. HE SUGGEST TO JUST RESTART IN STEP0030 BECAUSE 10 AND 20 RAN FINE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CHECKED RESTARTS. RESTARTED IN STEP030. FINISHED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0901",
  "PROBLEM": "S01A ABEND=S000 U0026 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FIGURED JOB DIDN'T HAVE THE RESOURCES IT NEEDED DURING IT'S FIRST RUN. STEPS 10 AND 20 RAN FINE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CHECKED RESTARTS. RESTARTED IN STEP030. FINISHED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0020",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$0020 GOING DOWN WITH A SOC 7 IN JSTEP010.STEP0030 IN PROGRAM D724DANN ON POLICY # '2052256750' IN FILE CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G2263V00 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WE NEED TO REMOVE THE OFFENDING POLICY FROM THE INPUT FILE FOR THIS STEP. THEN RESTART IN THE ABENDING STEP TO ALLOW THE CYCLE TO CONTINUE. NOTE: HAD MORE THAN ONE BAD POLICY. --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! ",
  "SOLUTION": "FIRST FIND THE POLICY ABENDING ON - IN SYSUDUMP - DO A FIND ON YOUR INPUT FILE DD NAME (SEQUEN) MAY NEED TO DO A REFIND, BUT YOU SHOULD GET YOUR POLICY NUMBER. FOUND '2052229250' & '2052230450' (MAY NEED TO DO THIS MORE THAN ONCE) SECOND, USED JCL TEST.CL.TDR.CNTL(COPY0020) TO CREATE COPY OF CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G2263V00 (ONLY NEED TO DO THIS ONCE.) THIRD, USING THE FIRECALL ID DELETE POLICIES. (MAY NEED TO DO THIS MORE THAN ONCE) FOURTH, HAVE PCD RESTART THE JOB IN ABENDING STEP. NOTE: LOOK IN 'SCHD.CTM.DOC(CL$$0020)' FOR RESTART DOCUMENTATION ON THIS JOB. (MAY NEED TO DO THIS MORE THAN ONCE) --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! FIFTH, SEND FOLLOW UP E-MAIL INCLUDE CYBERLIFE IND, DOCUMENTATION TEAM, THE PRODUCTION SUPPORT TEAM, AND ANYONE ELSE WHO MIGHT NEED TO KNOW. (ONLY NEED TO DO THIS ONCE.) SIX, UPDATE BOMBLOG SO NEXT ON CALL PERSON WILL HAVE AN IDEA OF WHAT TO DO SHOULD THIS HAPPEN AGAIN. (ONLY NEED TO DO THIS ONCE, CAN DO THE NEXT DAY) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$BLD2",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB GOT USER COMPLETION CODE=4093, NEEDS REGION PARM ",
  "ANALYSIS": "USER COMPLETION CODE=4093 IS NORMALLY CAUSED BECAUSE WE DID NOT ADD THE REGION=0M PARM. LOOKING AT THE JCL IN TEST.CL.TOOLS THAT WAS THE CAUSE THIS TIME TOO. ",
  "SOLUTION": "EDIT THE JCL TO ADD REGION=0M PARM, RERUN FROM TOP "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0020",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$0020 GOING DOWN WITH A SOC 7 IN JSTEP010.STEP0030 IN PROGRAM D724DANN ON POLICY # '2052229250' IN FILE CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G2263V00 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WE NEED TO REMOVE THE OFFENDING POLICY FROM THE INPUT FILE FOR THIS STEP. THEN RESTART IN THE ABENDING STEP TO ALLOW THE CYCLE TO CONTINUE. NOTE: HAD MORE THAN ONE BAD POLICY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "FIRST FIND THE POLICY ABENDING ON - IN SYSUDUMP - DO A FIND ON YOUR INPUT FILE DD NAME (SEQUEN) MAY NEED TO DO A REFIND, BUT YOU SHOULD GET YOUR POLICY NUMBER. FOUND '2052229250' & '2052230450' (MAY NEED TO DO THIS MORE THAN ONCE) SECOND, USED JCL TEST.CL.TDR.CNTL(COPY0020) TO CREATE COPY OF CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G2263V00 (ONLY NEED TO DO THIS ONCE.) THIRD, USING THE FIRECALL ID DELETE POLICIES. (MAY NEED TO DO THIS MORE THAN ONCE) FOURTH, HAVE PCD RESTART THE JOB IN ABENDING STEP. NOTE: LOOK IN 'SCHD.CTM.DOC(CL$$0020)' FOR RESTART DOCUMENTATION ON THIS JOB. (MAY NEED TO DO THIS MORE THAN ONCE) --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! FIFTH, SEND FOLLOW UP E-MAIL INCLUDE CYBERLIFE IND, DOCUMENTATION TEAM, THE PRODUCTION SUPPORT TEAM, AND ANYONE ELSE WHO MIGHT NEED TO KNOW. (ONLY NEED TO DO THIS ONCE.) SIX, UPDATE BOMBLOG SO NEXT ON CALL PERSON WILL HAVE AN IDEA OF WHAT TO DO SHOULD THIS HAPPEN AGAIN. (ONLY NEED TO DO THIS ONCE, CAN DO THE NEXT DAY) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "INFORCE POLICY # '0620101520' GOT AN EMPTY ROW FOR THE CISLCA OR CLIENT_ADDRESS TRAILER GET ROUTINE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "NEED TO RUN SCOPE CHECK, FIX CLIENT_ADDRESS, AND RESTART THE CYCLE BY FORCING CL$$0011 OK AFTER THE SCOPE CHECK & CLIENT_ADDRESS FIX IS FINISHED OK. ",
  "SOLUTION": "USE WORK AROUND THAT DAN BLECK CREATED ALLOWING ME TO POINT TO THE OLD CLIENT_ADDRESS TO STOP THE EMPTY ROW, SEE 04\/04\/2003 ABEND NOTES. DUE TO THE REOCCURRING NATURE OF THIS PROBLEM, CL$$0011 WILL BE RAN OFF TO THE SIDE AROUND 3 OR 4 BY ON CALL SUPPORT PERSON(S) UNTIL THE GUI FIX FOR THIS IS IN. PROBLEM: INFORCE POLICY # '0620019500' GOT AN EMPTY ROW "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "INFORCE POLICY # '0620019500' GOT AN EMPTY ROW FOR THE CISLCA OR CLIENT_ADDRESS TRAILER GET ROUTINE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "I NEEDED TO CHECK THE SCOPE OF THE PROBLEM AND CORRECT THE MISSING ROW SITUATION BEFORE THE CYCLE COULD CONTINUE ON. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DAN BLECK HAD A SIMILAR SITUATION HAPPEN ON 3\/28\/03 HE WALKED ME THROUGH USING PRINSTON SOFTECH TO FIND THE MISSING CLT_ADR_RELATION TO CLIENT_ADDRESS. THEN I COPIED THE TWO CLT_ADR-RELATION ID FIELDS TO A CARDLIB MEMBER I CREATED. USING SPLIT SCREEN AND THE EDIT MODE OF PRINSTON I SELECTED THE CLIENT_ADDRESS FOR THE ID THAT EXPIRED THAT DAY. THEN I TYPED AN R ON THAT ONE ROW TO REPEAT IT. THEN I COPIED THE NEW CLT_ADR_RELATION ID AND PASTED IT INTO THE ROW I JUST CREATED. THEN I SHIFTED OVER TO THE USER ID FIELD AND TYPED MY P1TDR ID IN THAT FIELD. THEN USING A VERSION OF CL$$0011 I RAN JUST THE POLICY I HAD CORRECTED. IT FINISHED WITH GOOD CONDITION CODES. THEN I RAN THE SCOPE CHECK WHICH RAN ABOUT AN HOUR AND AFTER IT FINISHED WITH GOOD CONDITION CODES I CALLED OPS TO FORCE 11 OK AND THUS CONTINUE ON WITH THE CYCLE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$Q867",
  "PROBLEM": "GETTING BUFFER OVER FLOW ",
  "ANALYSIS": "AT FIRST THE JOB WAS RESTARTED, THEN DAN BLECK NOTICED THE BUFFER OVER FLOW WAS OCCURRING THIS MEANS THAT D7240150 HAD TO BE FIXED AND MOVED UP BEFORE THIS JOB COULD RUN ",
  "SOLUTION": "PROGRAM D7240150 FIXED, MIGRATED TO PRODUCTION, JOB RESTARTED FROM THE JOB "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1130",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$1130 ABENDED WITH JCL ERROR TRYING TO CLEANUP FILES IN THE FIRST STEP ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CL$$1130 HAD FILE FIXED USING FIRE CALL ",
  "SOLUTION": "CL$$1130 RE-RAN AFTER FIXING CL$$1130 STEP0010 IEFBR14 05\/01\/2003 07:30AM P1BKG BRIAN HAD MARK WILLIAMS DELETE THE FILE AND RERUN MARK ASSIGNED THIS TO LAVONNA NICHOLS TO RESOLVE PER RHONDA "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0035",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC7 ABEND IN CKDCINEX, CALLED BY D7245101 ON VUL PENDING RECORD 3465078640. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "A DECISION WAS MADE TO FORCE THIS JOB OK THINKING A PARTIAL FEED TO ONLINE SEVICES IS ACCEPTABLE SINCE WE COULD HOPEFULLY RESOLVE THE ABEND PROBLEM THE NEXT MORNING IN TIME FOR THE NEXT MID-DAY RUN OF CL$$0035 AT 11:00AM THE NEXT DAY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DETERMINED THE NEXT DAY THAT AN INVALID NOTIFY DATE IN A REQUIREMENT (80) SEGMENT WAS CAUSING THE ABEND. HAD THE SEGMENT DELETED AND RE-ADDED AND THAT CORRECTED THE INVALID DATE. ALSO FOUND OUT THAT A PARTIAL FEED TO ONLINE SERVICES IS NOT ACCEPTABLE. IN THE FUTURE WE SHOULD USE THE FOLLOWING WORKAROUND... ==> RUN TEST.CL.TOOLS(DROP0035) AND FOLLOW THE INSTRUCTIONS IN THIS JOB. THIS WORKAROUND COULD BE USED TO SKIP SPECIFIC PENDING RECORDS IN CL$$0035 FOR ANY REASON (ANY ABEND). SEND E-MAIL TO ECOMMERCE IND\/AUL TO LET THEM KNOW THAT PROBLEMS OCCURRED AND WHAT POLICY NUMBER(S) WERE DROPPED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0860",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$0860 - JCL ERROR PROBLEM CL$$1020 - SPACE PROBLEM CL$$Q866 - DEFER RUNNING JOB TO LATER IN WEEK CL$$Q867 - DEFER RUNNING JOB TO LATER IN WEEK CL$$2010 - DID EMERGENCY FIX FOR BUFFER OVER FLOW CL$$2040 - DID EMERGENCY FIX FOR BUFFER OVER FLOW CL$$2060 - DID EMERGENCY FIX FOR BUFFER OVER FLOW ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SEVERAL QUARTER END JOBS FAILED WITH THE BUFFER OVER FLOW PROBLEM. PROBLEM HAD TO BE EMERGENCY FIXED, MIGRATED TO PRODUCTION & JOBS RE-RAN ",
  "SOLUTION": "BUFFER OVER FLOW PROBLEM FIXED, FOR CL$$2010, 40, 60 CL$$0860 WAS JUST RE-RAN? JCL SPACE BUMBED UP FOR CL$$1020 & RE-RAN CL$$Q866 & 7 DEFERRED "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "TWO PENDING POLICIES GOT AN EMPTY ROW FOR THE CISLCA OR CLIENT_ADDRESS TRAILER GET ROUTINE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CHECKED THE SCOPE OF THE PROBLEM AND CORRECT THE MISSING ROW SITUATION. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DAN BLECK HAD A SIMILAR SITUATION HAPPEN ON 3\/28\/03 HE WALKED ME THROUGH USING PRINSTON SOFTECH TO FIND THE MISSING CLT_ADR_RELATION TO CLIENT_ADDRESS. THEN I COPIED THE TWO CLT_ADR-RELATION ID FIELDS TO A CARDLIB MEMBER I CREATED. USING SPLIT SCREEN AND THE EDIT MODE OF PRINSTON I SELECTED THE CLIENT_ADDRESS FOR THE ID THAT EXPIRED THAT DAY. THEN I TYPED AN R ON THAT ONE ROW TO REPEAT IT. THEN I COPIED THE NEW CLT_ADR_RELATION ID AND PASTED IT INTO THE ROW I JUST CREATED. THEN I SHIFTED OVER TO THE USER ID FIELD AND TYPED MY P1TDR ID IN THAT FIELD. THEN USING A VERSION OF CL$$0011 I RAN JUST THE POLICY I HAD CORRECTED. IT FINISHED WITH GOOD CONDITION CODES. THEN I RAN THE SCOPE CHECK WHICH RAN ABOUT AN HOUR AND AFTER IT FINISHED WITH GOOD CONDITION CODES I CALLED OPS TO FORCE 11 OK AND THUS CONTINUE ON WITH THE CYCLE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0155",
  "PROBLEM": "SPACE, THE FINAL FRONTIER. DYNAMIC ALLOCATION FAILED; RC=4, REASON=4714041D, SMSCODE=00. IKJ56245I DATA SET CL.SA.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG1 NOT ALLOCATED, NOT ENOUGH IKJ56245I USE DELETE COMMAND TO DELETE UNUSED DATA SETS 23:34:09 SNAPSHOT COMPLETED, RC=8. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB TRIED TO SNAP A COPY OF CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG1 WHICH OCCUPIES 887 CYLINDERS ONTO VOLUME CICS52 WHICH HAD 805 CYLINDERS OF FREE SPACE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "I CHECKED THE CICS* PACKS WITH QW FOR FREE SPACE AND FOUND 1611 CYLINDERS ON CICS28. I MADE A COPY OF PROD.CL.CARDLIB(CLH0155) ON TEST.CL.WHH.CARDLIB AND CHANGED THE TARGET VOLSER TO CICS28. I HAD OPS PUT IN AN OVERRIDE IN THE JCL TO POINT TO THIS CARD IN JSTEP020: \/\/STEP0010.SYSIN DD DSN=TEST.CL.WHH.CARDLIB(CLH0155), \/\/ DISP=SHR I HAD OPS RUN CL$$D155 AND THEN RESTART CL$$0155 IN JSTEP020.STEP0010. THIS RUN ENDED WITH A CC 12 WITH THIS MESSAGE: THE ARGUMENT TO FATTR DID NOT POINT TO A VALID OPEN FILE. IT WAS GETTING LATE, SO I TRIED TO CONTACT DAN NOAH. FAILING THAT I CONTACTED DAN BLECK. HE NOTICED THAT THE OVERRIDE POINTED TO CARDLIB MEMBER CLH0150 INSTEAD OF CLH0155 WHICH DIDN'T EXIST. HE DECIDED THAT CL$$0155 HAD RUN TO A SATISFACTORY CONCLUSSION AND ANTICIPATING THE SAME PROBLEM IN CL$$0160, CAME UP UP WITH A NEW PLAN OF ACTION. I CREATED A NEW COPY OF CLH0160 IN MY PERSONAL PDS CARDLIB AND CHANGED THE VOLSER TARGET FOR CL.SA.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG1 FROM VOLUME(CICS52) TO ESOTERIC(SNAP). I HAD OPS PUT AN OVERRIDE IN CL$$0160 SIMILAR TO THE ONE IN CL$$0155 (EXCEPT WITH THE CORRECT CARDLIB MEMBER) AND HAD OPS FORCE COMPLETE CL$$0155. AT 3:01 THE CYCLE KICKED OFF AND COMPLETED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0125",
  "PROBLEM": "SYSIN CARDLIB DATA SET NOT FOUND. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE NEW PROC FOR CL$$0125 HAD &PREFIX.CARDLIB(CL724010) (CL.CARDLIB(CL724010)) INSTEAD OF &CPREFIX.CARDLIB(CL724010) (PROD.CL.CARDLIB(CL724010)). ",
  "SOLUTION": "BRIAN GIBSON CORRECTED THE PROC IN THE STAGING LIBRARY AND HAD DAN HUNSINGER SIGN OFF THE MOVE TO PRODUCTION. I CHECKED THE JCL AND TOLD OPS TO RERUN FROM SORT STEP0034. INSTEAD, THEY STARTED IN STEP0040. IT ABENDED WHEN IT REACHED STEP0120 WHICH USES THE OUTPUT STEP0034. I SET UP JCL TO RUN JUST STEP0034 UNDER FIRECALL. AFTER THREE UNSUCCESSFUL ATTEMPTS, I REMOVED THE ACF \"COMMENT\" (\/\/*LOGONID ACFSUBID) AND IT RAN FINE. I HAD OPS CONTINUE THE RERUN FROM STEP0120 WHICH ENDED WITH GOOD CONDITION CODES. NOTE: WHILE \"\/\/*LOGONID ACFSUBID\" MAY LOOK LIKE A COMMENT, SMELL LIKE A COMMENT, AND QUACK LIKE A COMMENT IT IS ACTUALLY A TRIGGER TO START ACF WHICH WILL PREVENT ANY JOB SUBMITTED BY AN INDIVIDUAL FROM RUNNING. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C1 - OFFSET 00031C +CKSN01 PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. PSW=078D2000 8B12DB16 (OPER +CKSN02 ABENDING ELEMENT CKETRGET EPA=0B12D7F8 OFFSET 00031C IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT USER COMPLETION CODE=0999 REASON CODE=00000000 TIME=19.32.53 SEQ=11937 CPU=0000 ASID=003B ",
  "ANALYSIS": "RAN SQL$DUPA. FOUND NO DUPLICATE ROWS IN CLIENT. LOOKED FOR 'SQL' IN THE LE DUMP (SYSPDUMP) WITH NO SUCCESS. CALLED DAN NOAH. HE LOOKED FOR BAD CLIENT DATA WHILE I RAN TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$$0011) STARTING WITH THE PENDING AND INFORCE POLICIES IMMEDIATELY AFTER THE ABENDING POLICIES. EACH OF THE NEXT FIVE PENDING POLICIES ABENDED AS DID MORE INFORCE POLICIES. DAN CALLED DAN BLECK WHO RECALLED THAT HE HAD CHANGED THE PARMDATE CARD DURING THE DAY AND NOT RESTORED IT. IN THE MEANTIME, THE CYCLE HAD STARTED AND CL$$0012 HAD ENDED WITH AN ABEND. NOTE: THE NEW LE ABEND SPLITS THE OCCURANCES OF THE STRING 'SQL' BETWEEN TWO LINES. DO A FIND ON 'SQ' INSTEAD TO FIND THE SQL RETURN CODE. A FIND OF 'CISL' WILL ALSO WORK. ",
  "SOLUTION": "WE RAN CL$$R012 TO RESTORE CL$$0012 AND RAN SCHD1551 TO RECREATE THE PARMDATE CARDS. THEN WE RAN TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$$0011) FROM THE BEGINNING. WHEN THE PENDING POLICIES ALL HAD PROCESSED SUCCESSFULLY, I CANCELLED THE JOB. WE HAD OPS FORCE COMPLETE CL$$0011 AND HAD THEM RERUN CL$$0012 FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0004",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC4 - U4039-8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WENT TO 'ST' SCREEN. LOOKED IN ABENDAID DUMP. SAW CKETRGET WAS PROBLEM AT 31E. THIS IS A CLIENT PROBLEM. WENT TO VSAM3 IN DUMP TO FIND POLICY. POLICY LISTED UNDER CURRENT RECORD. 3361174300. USED TSO PST TO DIAGNOSE CLIENT PROBLEM. FOUND DUPLICATE CISLAR CL$$0011 HAD GONE DOWN AND WAS NOT COMPLETED. THAT IS HOW THIS CASE GOT PAST OUR EVALUATION TOOLS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "FIX CLIENT PROBLEM AND RESTART JOB FROM THE TOP. **NOTE** THIS JOB USE TO CONTINUE ITS RUN AND REQUIRE DATASET CLEANUP. THIS PROCESS WAS IMPROVED VIA THE CHANGE IN THE STEP FROM IKJEFT01 TO IKJEFT1B. THE IKJEFT1B CAUSES THE FOLLOWING STEPS TO FLUSH. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1051",
  "PROBLEM": "IDC3302I ACTION ERROR ON CL.OFFSITE.HISTORY.ARCHIVE.G003 IDC3321I ** OPEN\/CLOSE\/EOV ABEND EXIT TAKEN IDC31467I MAXIMUM ERROR LIMIT REACHED. IDC0005I NUMBER OF RECORDS PROCESSED WAS 21223635 IDC3003I FUNCTION TERMINATED. CONDITION CODE IS 12 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DEFAULT IS SIX VOLUMES OUTPUT AND JOB MUST HAVE EXCEEDED THAT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "\/\/ VOL=(,,,25), AFTER \/\/ LABEL=EXPDT=99000, IN PROC. MOVED PROC TO PRODUCTION AND RERAN JOB FROM TOP "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$2080",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C7. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE ABENDING FIELD IN M724WHL3 IS 05 WS-WORK-TARGET-PREM PIC S9(9)V99. IT REACHES THIS STATEMENT WITH LOW VALUES IN IT: ADD WS-WORK-TARGET-PREM TO WS-TOTAL-TARGET-PREMIUM. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DAN NOAH CHANGED THE WORKING STORAGE DEFINITION TO 05 WS-WORK-TARGET-PREM PIC S9(9)V99 VALUE ZEROE MOVED LOADLIB TO PRODUCTION AND RERAN CL$$2080 FROM TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC-7 CALLING CKDCINEX IN STEP0090. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WAS THE CURRENT KEY FOR DD SEQUEN. DECIDED TO DROP PENDING POLICY 0620106980. ******* NOTE: CL$$RC10 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL2 ******** ",
  "SOLUTION": "CL$$R030, CL$$RC10, & CL$$R017 RESTORES BE RAN RESTORES ENDED OK. DROPPED PENDING POLICY FROM BASEOL PENDING AND AUXSEG2 USING FILE MARVEL. RERAN CL$$R017 FROM TOP. JOB ENDED OK. RERAN CL$$0030 FROM TOP. JOB ENDED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0600",
  "PROBLEM": "CC50 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ATTEMPT TO LOOKUP A FUNDVAL PRICE FAILED. THIS WAS DUE TO A CHANGE IN THE KEY TO THE FUNDVAL FILE DURING THE 0101 RELEASE CONVERSIONS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "TWEEK PROGRAM TO GET UNUSED AREAS OF KEY IN PROGRAM TO BE LOW-VALUES INSTEAD OF SPACES. THIS IS THE CHANGE THAT IMPACTED THE FILE. -RESTARTS- RUN CL$$R600 FOR RESTORES RESTART FROM TOP WITH SYMBOLIC VOPREFX='CL.SA.VSAM.BASEOL' **NOTE**SYMBOLIC CHANGE ONLY NEEDED IF ON-LINE IS UP. THIS AVOIDS IMPACT OF TODAYS ACTIVITY "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$POLR",
  "PROBLEM": "IEC030I B37-04,IFG0554A,CL$$POLR,MDB2PROC,PSDFCTRL,0E19,STOR7 TEST.CL.DB2MOVE.PROD.RESTORE.CONTROL -STEP=MDB2PROC PGM=PDPMMAIN EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 RC=000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CONTROL FILE RAN OUT OF SPACE. I WAS ABLE TO SEE THIS FROM THE JESMSGLG PART OF THE EXECUTION JCL I LOOKED IN THE PSDFRPRT PART OF THE EXECUTION JCL TO SEE IF IT LOOKED LIKE ANY UPDATES HAD BEEN DONE. THE REPORT DID NOT SHOW ANY ROW UPDATES. I USED FILE MARVEL AND CHECKED THE POLICY MASTER TO SEE IF THE POLICY WAS THERE. IT WAS NOT. THIS TOLD ME MY RESTARTS WOULD BE JOB FROM THE TOP. EVEN IF THERE WERE SOME UPDATES, RESTARTS WOULD BE JOB FROM THE TOP, I JUST WOULD HAVE RECEIVED A CC4 FOR REPLACE ATTEMPT WHEN NO REPLACE OPTION WAS CHOSEN. ",
  "SOLUTION": "=3.2, IMAGE THE CONTROL FILE, DELETE THE CONTROL FILE, CREATE A NEW CONTROL FILE WITH A LARGER SIZE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0120",
  "PROBLEM": "S3E7 ABEND=S000 U0999 I\/O ERROR WHILE WRITING VSAM2 FILE. JOB ABORTED. I\/O RETURN CODE - 2 KEY = 023012370100905 01 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS PROBLEM IS RELATED TO THE 0101 RELEASE WHICH IS NOT IN PRODUCTION YET. HOWEVER I WANTED TO DOCUMENT THIS PROBLEM AS IT OCCURRED WHILE RUNNING A TEST CYCLE WITH FULL PRODUCTION DATA. THIS PROBLEM IS TELLING US THAT THE STEP ABENDED BECAUSE OF DUPLICATE KEYS. THE INPUT FILE TO THIS STEP0220 IS \/\/SEQUEN. IT WAS NOT OBVIOUS TO ME UNTIL I LOOKED AT THE FILE FOR THE ABOVE KEY. THERE WERE 2 RECORDS WITH THE SAME KEY. IN LOOKING AT THE 2 POLICIES INVOLVED ONE HAD A 33 SEG FOR A CHECKING ACCOUNT AND THE OTHER POLICY HAD A 33 SEG WITH THE SAME ACCOUNT HOWEVER IT WAS DESIGNATED AS A SAVINGS ACCT BOTH USING THE SAME BILL CONTROL#. THE REASON THE RECORDS DID NOT COMBINE WAS BECAUSE THE ACCOUNT TYPES WERE DIFFERENT. IT TURNS OUT THIS WAS AN ADMINISTRATIVE ERROR. ONE POLICY WAS CHANGED HOWEVER THE OTHER WAS NOT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "IN ORDER TO GET THE JOB TO RUN, I COPIED THE INPUT FILE &PREFIX.CL$$0100.STEP0320.BILLEXTS(0) AND DELETED ONE OF THE DUPLICATE RECORDS. THEN RESTARTED THE JOB AT THE TOP WITH THE CHANGED FILE AS AN OVERRIDE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1030",
  "PROBLEM": "CC S001 ABEND=S000 U0001 REASON=00000000 # ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED IN DUMP AND FOUND 3 POLICY NUMBERS. ONE WAS ONLY LISTED 5 TIMES, ONE 4 TIMES AND THE LAST 12 TIMES. THE ONE LISTED 12 TIMES WAS THE HIGHEST IN NUMBER AND WAS THE LAST LISTED IN THE DUMP - 2453218490. LOOKED AT THE INPUT FILE FOR STEP0030, CL.CL$$1020. POLSEQ.EXTSRIN.G0055V00 AND SAW THAT THE RECORD FOR THIS POLICY DIDN'T LOOK ANYTHING LIKE THE OTHER POLICIES. EACH POLICY HAD MULTIPLE RECORDS. THIS POLICY ONLY HAD ONE AND IT DIDN'T LOOK TO BE IN THE RIGHT FORMAT. FIGURED THIS MUST BE THE PROBLEM RECORD. ",
  "SOLUTION": "MADE COPY OF THE INPUT FILE. COULD NOT DELETE THE RECORD USING EDIT IN 3.4 OR FILE MARVEL. HAD TO DELETE USING A WAAP DROP JOB, TEST.CL. BKGTOOLS(WAAPDRP1). BE AWARE THAT THIS IS A VB FILE, SO IN YOUR JOB THE STARTING COLUMN FOR THE POLICY NUMBER IS +4. USING FIRECALL, DELETED THE LAST GEN OF THE INPUT FILE. THEN RENAMED THE OUTPUT FILE FROM THE WAAP DROP JOB TO THE LAST GEN OF THE INPUT FILE. (THE FILE YOU JUST DELETED.) HAD OPS RERUN JOB FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0835",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C4 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "POL# 2052246540 HAD 2 DIFFERENT SETS OF INPUT RECORDS ONE FOR 979CAP000 PLAN & ONE FOR 919FPA400 PLAN ",
  "SOLUTION": "1) REPRO CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR(0) TO TEST FILE 2) CHECKED PROD 3270 TO SEE WHICH PLAN VALID IT WAS 919FPA400 3) MARYANN FOUND OUT THIS WAS A REISSUE 4) REMOVED BAD GROUP OF RECORDS 3) CALLED PCD (X1409) TO RERUN CL$$0835 FROM THE TOP JOB ENDED OK "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "DST FILES DID NOT TRANSMIT ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CHECKED CONTROL-D TO MAKE SURE CL$$0600 RAN OKAY. CHECKED LOG(=Q.I; LOG; FIND CDFT1120 UNTIL YOU FIND THE FOLLOWING: STEP01 COPY CDFT1120( 610) SNODE=AULCD.PC4390 180 FROM CL.CL$$0600.DST.AMP.FILE TO PC4826VM3 OUTBOUND FANMAIL AULAM09.TXT COMPLETED 00000000\/SCPA000I A GROUP OF 6 FILES TO BE DOWNLOADED SUCCESSFULLY IF ALL LOOKS OKAY SO FAR. CHECK DATE IN DOWNLOAD FILES. THE HEADER SHOULD HAVE THE DATE DST EXPECTED TO RECEIVE(COL 22-29 CCYYMMDD) ALL 6 FILES HAVE THIS. YOU SHOULD BE SAFE CHECKING ANY ONE OF THEM. IF THAT LOOKS GOOD, CALL PCD AND SEE IF NSFT0002 RAN FROM THE PGP SERVER. THIS LOADS FILES FROM OUR PGP SERVER TO DST'S AUL DIRECTORY. IF THIS IS OK, CHECK WITH LEE(JESSE) COONE TO SEE IF HE CAN RESEND THE FILES. IF HE IS NOT AVAILABLE HAVE PCD RE-RUN CDFT1120 AND NSFT0002. LEE WILL BE ABLE TO RESEND WHAT WAS ALREADY DOWNLOADED ON THE PGP SERVER. SO, LEE IS THE DESIRED DIRECTION **NOTE** THE FILES DOWNLOADED VIA CDFT1120 GET REPLACED EACH NIGHT. THEY CAN BE RECOVERED FROM THE TAPE BACKUP AT THE END OF THE JOB, BUT ITS A BUNCH OF WORK. SO, SAME DAY RESOLUTION IS BEST. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0601",
  "PROBLEM": "+IGZ035I THERE WAS AN UNSUCCESSFUL OPEN OR CLOSE OF FILE PROGRAM 'D724DSTH' AT RELATIVE LOCATION X'0DB2'. STATUS NOR AN ERROR DECLARATIVE WERE SPECIFIED. STATUS CODE WAS '35'. IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT USER COMPLETION CODE=1035 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "MISSING DDNAME IDSSNUM FOUND DDNAME OF OVERRIDE WHICH SHOULD HAVE BEEN DDNAME IDSSNUM. THIS DID NOT SHOW UP IN TESTING BECAUSE ALL XJCL HAD AN OVERRIDE FOR IDSSNUM. WHEN WE MOVED TO PRODUCTION, THE IDSSNUM WE REMOVED, WHICH IS EXACTLY WHAT IS SUPPOSE TO HAPPEN. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CORRECTED STEP NAME FROM OVERRIDE TO IDSSNUM. RESTARTED CL$$0601 FROM THE TOP WITH FORCED ODATE OF MONTH END 12\/31\/2002. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0600",
  "PROBLEM": "CC40 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "NEW PRODUCT STARPOINT WAS MOVED TO PRODUCTION ALL TABLES AND PDF WENT UP BUT FUNDS WERE NOT ADDED TO THE FUNDVAL. THIS CREATES A CRITICAL ERROR IN THE PROGRAM LOGIC ",
  "SOLUTION": "ALTERED THE PROGRAM LOGIC TO ALLOW CONTINUED PROCESSING EVEN IF A PLAN HAS BEEN TURNED ON FOR DST(AUUDT503) AND THE PDF HAS VARIABLE FUNDS, BUT THE FUNDVAL DOES NOT REFLECT THE FUND. REPORT THE SITUATION, BUT GO AHEAD AND BUILD THE REST OF THE PRICING RECORDS. MOVED PROGRAM CHANGE TO PRODUCTION "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0012",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOK AT DATASET CREATED CL.CL$$0012.FUNDS.ERROR.REPORT SEE WHAT IT TELLS YOU ABOUT ABEND ",
  "SOLUTION": "DIAGNOSE PROBLEM FROM SYSOUT FILE "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0012",
  "PROBLEM": "U040 PROGRAM ABEND ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PARMDATE AND THE CONTROL CARD ON THE FUNDS FILE DO NOT MATCH ",
  "SOLUTION": "FIGURE OUT IF THE FUNDS FILE IS IN ERROR OR THE PARMDATE "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$IAAM",
  "PROBLEM": "CC8 FOR CL.VSAM.BASEOL.UTABLES UNABLE TO ALLOCATE TARGET DATASET, ALREADY IN USE, BACKUP PROCESSING FAILED ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE UTABLES FILE WAS AT 16 CYLS WITH 3 EXTENTS LOOKS LIKE SOMETHING ELSE WAS RUNNING AT THE SAME TIME ",
  "SOLUTION": "TOLD OPERATOR TO FORCE COMPLETE THE JOB, HOPEFULLY IT WILL REORG AGAIN NEXT CYCLE "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0810",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC7 OCCURED ON FIELD AGPREX-ANNUALIZED-PREM CONTAINED LOW-VAULES FOR POLICY 5110036840. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DECIDED TO PULL OFF BAD POLICY, MULTIPLE RECORDS PER POLICY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "SAVED FILE CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AGTPRDEX.G0282V00 AS TEST.CL.SLJ.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AGTPRDEX.D1115 THEN EDITED THE PRODUCTION FILE AND RESTARTED THE JOB IN STEP0110. GOOD EOJ. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0810",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC7 OCCURED ON FIELD WS-SEQ-ID CONTAINED LOW-VAULES FOR POLICY 5770001100. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DECIDED TO PULL OFF BAD POLICY, MULTIPLE RECORDS PER POLICY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "SAVED FILE CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AGTPRDEX.G0625V00 AS TEST.CL.LAP.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AGTPRDEX.D0324 THEN EDITED THE PRODUCTION FILE AND RESTARTED THE JOB IN STEP0110. GOOD EOJ. RSW - ISSUE 3543 WILL RESOLVE THIS "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0810",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC7 OCCURED ON FIELD WS-SEQ-ID CONTAINED LOW-VAULES FOR POLICY 5770001100. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DECIDED TO PULL OFF BAD POLICY. THERE WERE 3 RECORDS FOR THIS POLICY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "SAVED FILE CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AGTPRDEX.G0648V00 AS TEST.CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AGTPRDEX.D0426 THEN EDITED THE PRODUCTION FILE AND RESTARTED THE JOB IN STEP0110. I ADDED OVERRIDES TO STEP0200 SORTIN AND STEP0210 IINPUT TO USE THE ZERO GENERATION OF CL.D724AGC2.TRANS2 INSTEAD OF GENOT, +1. GOOD EOJ SOLUTION: SAVED FILE CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AGTPRDEX.G0648V00 AS TEST.CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AGTPRDEX.D0524 THEN EDITED THE PRODUCTION FILE AND RESTARTED THE JOB IN STEP0110. I DID THE ABOVE SOLUTION. BUT THE PROC HAD CHANGED AND THE ONLY OVERRIDE NEEDED IS THE ONE FOR STEP0200 SORTIN. CHECK THE RESTARTS. RSW - ISSUE 3543 WILL RESOLVE THIS "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "CDFT FAILED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE CDFT CREATES A NEW FILE EVERY TIME. IT FAILS IF THE PRIOR FILE HAS NOT BEEN DELETED. NOT SURE IF THAT WAS THE PROBLEM OR NOT, BUT IT IS A POSSIBILITY. WITH THE 12\/05\/02 ABEND WE DECIDED TO CHANGE THE DEPENDENCIES OF THE TRANSFER TO OCCUR AFTER CL$$ABR2 SO WE DON'T CONFLICT WITH PML'S CYCLE. THIS PROBLEM SEEMS TO BE OCCURING IN RELTAION TO THE TIME CHANGE SINCE 10\/31. ",
  "SOLUTION": "YOU CAN DEFER TO THE NEXT BUSINESS DAY. GO AHEAD AND HAVE OPS RERUN CDFT1010. IF OK, THEN NOTHING ELSE HAS TO BE DONE. IF NOT, YOU MIGHT GET DRAKE OR DOREEN CLOMSTAD AT PML INVOLVED. THIS CAN BE DEFERRED TO THE NEXT DAY BECAUSE THE PML CYCLE IS ALWAYS A DAY BEHIND OURS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "CKUB01 SYSTEM MACRO, TO TRAP PROGRAM INTERRUPTS AB5A9- S0C4 ABEND AT 033750 IN IDARMTBL, IL=0, R15=844102F8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "AFTER LOOKING AT CL.CL$$0100.DEBUG TO FIND THE LAST POL# AND REVIEWING THE SYSTEM DUMPS AND MESSAGES OUT IT APPEARS THAT THE SYSTEM WAS TRYING TO SNAP POLICY NUMBER '3465074440' AND CONTINUE PROCESSING, BUT IT ABENDED INSTEAD. NO CLUE WHY IT WAS TRYING TO SNAP ON THAT POLICY OR WHY IT ABENDED INSTEAD. IT ALSO APPEARS THAT THE JOB WAS NOT GETTING MUCH CPU AND SO IT WAS RUNNING VERY SLOW, WHICH EXPLAINS THE TIME OF THE ABEND. THE JOB WAS STARTED AT A NORMAL TIME, BUT HAD BEEN TRYING TO PROCESS FOR ABOUT TWO HOURS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAVE OPS RUN R060 AND RC30. ONCE THOSE JOBS ARE DONE, RUN CL$$0018 TO SUSPEND POLICY '3465074440'. IF CL$$0018 APPEARS TO HAVE WORKED OK, HAVE OPS RUN CL$$0100 FROM THE TOP. OPS DID NOT KNOW HOW TO EDIT AND RUN CL$$0018 AFTER TEST.CL.DATA(SUSPEND) WAS UPDATED WITH POLICY. SO DAN BLECK RAN THAT UNDER FIRECALL. RE-RUN APPEARED TO BE DOING BETTER AS PREVIOUS RUN WAS NOT GETTING CPU AND SO IT RAN MUCH LONGER THAN NORMAL. BUT THEN CL$$0100 WENT DOWN IN THE SAME STEP WITH THE SAME ABEND ON POLICY #'3465075630' WENT THROUGH THE SAME STEPS: RUN R060 & RC30, SUSPEND POLICIES BY RUNNING CL$$0018 UNDER FIRECALL. THEN RE-RUN CL$$0100 FROM TOP. THIS TIME IT WORKED BUT WE WERE VERY CLOSE TO THE TIME WHEN WE CAN NOT GET FUNDS PROCESSED. SO WILL RESOLVE PROBLEM WITH TWO POLICIES AND REASON 100 WAS NOT GETTING CPU IN THE AM. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0848",
  "PROBLEM": "S0CB ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ON 12\/2 SAME PROBLEM, SAME POLICY. THIS HAPPENED A FEW DAYS AGO IN THE TEST CYCLE. APPARENTLY THERE IS A FIELD THAT IS NOT GETTING POPULATED WHICH IS CAUSING DIVISION BY ZERO. THE POLICY INVOLVED NEEDS TO BE REMOVED FROM THE INPUT FILE BEFORE THE JOB WILL RUN CLEAN. ",
  "SOLUTION": "THE INPUT FILE, 'CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR.G2034V00' WAS COPIED TO 'TEST.CL.TDR.BASEB.DPFSEXTR.G2034 POLICY '2453217880' WAS DELETED FROM 'CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR.G2034V00' AND JOB WAS RE-RAN FROM THE TOP. AN ISSUE WILL BE CREATED FOR THIS PROBLEM, BY PAT SOUTH. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$2100",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ALTHOUGH THERE WERE A LOT OF POLICIES IN THE DUMP, I FOUND ONE THAT WAS REPRESENTED MANY TIMES. THE RECORDS FOR THIS POLICY NEEDS TO BE REMOVED FROM THIS INPUT FILE AND THEN RESTART JOB IN STEP0110. ",
  "SOLUTION": "THE INPUT FILE, CL.CL$$1020.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN, IS HUGE. MAKE A COPY OF THE INPUT FILE AND THEN USE A WAAP TO DELETE THE RECORDS RELATED TO THE PROBLEM POLICY FROM YOUR COPY. PUT IN AN OVERRIDE IN STEP0120.IPOLEXIB FOR YOUR MODIFIED FILE AND THEN RESTART IN STEP0110. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1020",
  "PROBLEM": "OC7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ISL POLICIES WERE CAUSING PROBLEMS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DELETED THE RECORDS OF THE POLICIES FROM THE CL.ME.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY FILE USING FIRECALL. USING FIRECALL I ALSO DELETED THE FILES CREATED FROM THE 1020 JOB, CL.CL$$1020.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN AND EXTSRSL. RERAN JOB FROM THE TOP. (DAN BLECK FOUND THE BUG IN CKUBRVUH CAUSING THIS PROBLEM. FIXED PROBLEM AND IS MOVING FIX INTO PRODUCTION TONIGHT.) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0836",
  "PROBLEM": "-STEP=STEP0140 PGM=DLSBATCH ABENDED - COND CODE CC 8 -STEP=STEP0200 PGM=DLSBATCH ABENDED - COND CODE CC 8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "STEP0140: THE MESSAGE REGARDING THE TEXT PIECE NOT FOUND IN DLSTEXT OCCURRED FOR BOTH OF THE POLICIES THAT HAD ERRORS - TEXT PIECE T200110111658351 NOT FOUND IN DATABASE DLSTEXT. STATE LIFE TERM PAGES, COMPANY-CD: 05, CONTRACT-NUM: 5110033500 STATE LIFE TERM PAGES, COMPANY-CD: 05, CONTRACT-NUM: 5110033560 STEP0200: TEXT PIECE T200202081520311 NOT FOUND IN DATABASE DLSTEXT. TERM 2002 POLICY PAGES, COMPANY-CD: 00, CONTRACT-NUM: 0620087010 ",
  "SOLUTION": "SOME CHANGES WERE MADE IN THE DLS PRODUCTS TO CORRECT A TYPING ERROR IN THE GUARANTEE NOTICE FOR CALIFORNIA. THESE 3 POLICIES THAT HAD ERRORS WERE FROM CA, AND THAT HELPED IDENTIFY THE PROBLEM. WHEN A MESSAGE LIKE THIS OCCURS, IT MEANS THE MAINFRAME DLS TGEFF DBASE IS OUT OF SYNC WITH THE LAN DLSTEXT.MDB. TO RESOLVE THE PROBLEM, I DID THESE STEPS:(1) UPDATE THE PRODUCT VERSION IN DDMEDIT AND (2) RUN THE MAINTAIN BATCH JURISDICTION TASK IN DDMADMIN. THIS SECOND STEP SYNCHRONIZES THE DATABASES. THE JOB WAS THEN RESTARTED AND RAN FINE. TO PRINT THE 3 POLICIES THAT HAD ABENDED, USE CL$$0836 IN TEST.CL.LKM.JCLLIB WITH THE OVERRIDES NECESSARY FOR THE STEPS YOU WANT TO RUN. I COPIED THE PROD FILES, DELETED ALL RECORDS EXCEPT THE ONES WE NEED TO REPRINT, THEN ADDED OVERRIDES IN THIS PDS MEMBER TO RESTART IN STEP0080, RUN STEP0090, THEN ONLY RUN THE STEPS FOR THE PRODUCTS NEEDED. IN THIS CASE, I ONLY RAN THE STATE LIFE TERM AND THE AUL TERM STEPS. ALL OF THE PAGES FROM THE ORIGINAL RUN WERE FINE. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND=S000 U1015 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS STEP CREATES THE NOTIFICATION REGISTER REPORT. DECIDED TO RERUN CL$$0100 BUT SKIP STEP. FIGURE OUT WHICH POLICY IS CAUSING THE PROBLEM WHEN WE GET IN IN THE MORNING AND RERUN THE STEP OFF TO THE SIDE IN ORDER TO GET THE REPORT OUT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAVE OPS RUN R060 AND RC30. ONCE THOSE JOBS ARE DONE, HAVE OPS RERUN CL$$0100 FROM THE TOP WITH THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDE TO SKIP STEP0710: \/\/JSTEP010 EXEC PROC=CL$$0100,COND.STEP0710=(0,LE) EMAIL KATHY'S TEAM TO LET THEM KNOW THAT THERE WILL BE NO DELIVER OF THE NOTIFICATION REGISTER REPORT UNTIL WE FIGURE OUT THE PROBLEM POLICY AND RUN THE STEP ON OUR OWN. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0836",
  "PROBLEM": "CC8 INDICATES DLSBATCH FAILED ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SYSPRINT PROVIDES A BUNCH OF INFORMATION FOR THIS STEP THAT YOU ARE GOING TO CARE ABOUT. LOOK FOR TRIGGER 1. ONCE YOU GET THE POLICY NUMBER ANALYSIS: SC RECORD TERM 2002 POLICY PAGES, COMPANY-CD: 05, CONTRACT-NUM: 5110023520 ",
  "SOLUTION": "THE POLICY 5110023520 IS FOR SC, AND SOUTH CAROLINA HAS NOT APPROVED THE 15SLT20P PLAN. THEY SHOULD NOT HAVE RECEIVED ANY PAGES FOR THIS. POSSIBLY, THE SERVICE REP OVERRODE THE 171 ERROR? SC IS NOT LISTED FOR *L263 WHEN I CHECKED THE CKAPTB65 TABLE IN PRODUCTION. (NOTE: *THIS IF THE FORM NUMBER AND TO LOCATE WHAT IT SHOULD BE FIRST LOG ONTO 3270 AND TYPE '60D1,POLNBR; NEWCO=05;.' TO BRING UP SCREEN WITH FORM NUMBER ON IT; THEN LOCATE FORM IN CKAPTB65 TABLE TO SEE IF STATE HAS BEEN APPROVED) ALL OF THE OTHER POLICIES SHOULD HAVE PRINTED JUST FINE. NO RERUN NEED BE DONE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0060",
  "PROBLEM": "CC8 WITH SB37 ON SNAP DATASET ",
  "ANALYSIS": "3.4 WITH SHIFT LEFT SHOWED THE DATASET WITH THE CC8 WAS AT 16 EXTENTS. EVALUATION OF THE PACK SPACE VIA QW SHOWED THERE WAS STILL AMPLE PACK SPACE ",
  "SOLUTION": "RUN CL$$D060 THE RE-RUN CL$$0060 "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "WHETHER TO SEND ANOTHER PML EXTRACT FILE WHEN PML WAS NOT OPEN FOR BUSINESS FRIDAY 7\/5\/2002 AND WE WERE. A CYCLE WAS RUN AND THE TRANSFER WAS PUT ON HOLD. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WE ARE WAITING FOR COMMUNICATION FROM OUR PML CONTACT WHO IS DOREEN KLOMSTAD. HER PHONE NUMBER CAN BE FOUND IN THE PHONE# MEMBER OF THIS PDS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$2040",
  "PROBLEM": "LOOPING PROBLEM REACHED 1 HOUR CPU LIMIT. TIMED OUT. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED AT LAST RECORD IN SYSOUT TO FIND PROBLEM POLICY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HARD CODED BAD POLICY IN CKUBIRSE TO BE SKIPPED. DO A FIND ON 'DISPLAY' TO FIND AREA WHERE SKIPS ARE LOCATED. MOVED PROGRAM TO PRODUCTION AND RERAN. USED BLANKET ISSUE CL3145. ISSUE 7239 WAS CREATED FOR POLICY 2052258060. WAM "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$836",
  "PROBLEM": "# CL$$0836 STEP0200 CL$$0836 - ABEND -STEP=STEP0200 PGM=DLSBATCH ABENDED - COND CODE CC 8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "NJ RECORD (STATE, PRODUCT\/PLAN, CONTRACT-NUM MAY VARY) TERM 2002 POLICY PAGES, COMPANY-CD: 00, CONTRACT-NUM: 0620079530 ",
  "SOLUTION": "THE POLICY 0620079530 IS FOR NJ, AND NEW JERSEY HAS NOT APPROVED THE TERM2000 PLAN. THEY SHOULD NOT HAVE RECEIVED ANY PAGES FOR THIS. POSSIBLY, THE SERVICE REP OVERRODE THE 171 ERROR? NJ IS NOT LISTED FOR T2000 WHEN I CHECKED THE CKAPTB65 TABLE IN PRODUCTION. ALL OF THE OTHER POLICIES SHOULD HAVE PRINTED JUST FINE. NO PRODUCTION RERUN NEED BE DONE. THE DOCUMENTS TEAM WILL NEED TO REPRINT THE STD PAGES FOR THE POLICY IN ERROR AND DELIVER TO COMPLIANCE, WHO WILL MAKE THE NEEDED CHANGES FOR THE UNAPPROVED STATE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0120",
  "PROBLEM": "# IEF450I P1DJN120 STEP0030 CL$$0120 - ABEND=S0C7 U0000 REASON=000 -STEP=STEP0030 PGM=CKBSBCCT ABENDED - COND CODE S0C7 RC=0000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "BAD RECORD ON CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.BILLEXTS(0). WENT TO THE BOTTOM OF SYSLST. DETERMINED THAT THE BAD POLICY WAS THE NEXT RECORD. ",
  "SOLUTION": "REPROED THE FILE ABOVE TO TEST.CL.DJN.CL$$0100.STEP0320. BILLEXTS AND DROPPED THE BAD RECORD. SET UP JCL AND PROC IN 'DJN WORLD' AND RAN STEP0010 THRU STEP0030. ENDED OK. TOOK ANOTHER BACKUP OF CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.BILLEXTS(0). THEN USED FIRECALL TO DROP THE BAD POLICY FROM THE PRODUCTION FILE. RERAN FROM THE TOP. ENDED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$836",
  "PROBLEM": "# IEF450I CL$$0836 STEP0200 CL$$0836 - ABEND=S000 U4038 REASO -STEP=STEP0200 PGM=DLSBATCH ABENDED - COND CODE SFC6 RC=000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "TX RECORD IS BAD TERM 2002 POLICY PAGES, COMPANY-CD: 00, CONTRACT-NUM: 0620073940 ",
  "SOLUTION": "DROP TX RECORD FROM CL.DLS.SLTCUST.SORT.AULTERM RESTARTED IN STEP0160 OPS HAD TO CLOSE CL.VSAM.DLS.SLTCUST MANULLY "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0155",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC 1 ABEND STEP0020 PGM=IKJEFT01 EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 POLICY REQUEST DATE DEPT\/DESK MESSAGE 00-2051013918 10\/16\/84 948MS I\/O ERROR ENCOUNTERED 00-2051013918 10\/16\/84 610LO I\/O ERROR ENCOUNTERED 10\/30\/203 00-2453005500 08\/21\/95 610CF I\/O ERROR ENCOUNTERED ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED AT DUMP. DETERMINED I\/O CODE WAS A 2, DUPLICATE WRITE ERROR. HAD TO COMPILE SOURCE TO PDS DUE TO 20 BYTE PAN AUDIT. NOTICED THAT DURATION ON 66 SEG WAS 209 175, WHICH= 34 MONTHS. HOWVER, THE ONLINE HISTORY FILE CONTAINED DURATIONS 1 TO 209. SO THE 66 SEG IS OUT OF SYNC WITH THE ONLINE HISTORY FILE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "TEMP SOLUTION AT NIGHT. RAN CL$$R0155 CHANGED CARD IN CL$$0160 TO CLHDIHST FORCED CL$$0155 OK. NEXT DAY, EVALUATE DUMP AND EXPEDITOR & CONTACTED CYBERLFE SUPPORT TEAM. WE FOUND THAT: -THIS IS ONE OF THE 6 POLICIES THAT RAN WITHOUT UNIT PRICES DUE TO OPERATOR ERROR THE MONTH BEFORE WHEN THE OPERATORS FORCED OUR CYCLE TO RUN W\/O UNIT PRICES. -THE COMPLEX CHANGE PROCESS SOMEHOW GOT HOSE UP. -RESTORED POLICY PRIOR TO COMPLEX CHANGE -RE-DID COMPLEX CHANGE P1LAP 6\/5\/03 -DOUBLE CHECK POLICY NUMBER TO SEE IF IT MATCHES POLICY LISTED ABOVE -I HAD RESTORE RUN, DELETED PROBLEM POLICY FROM FILE CL.CL$$0100.STEP0290.HISTREQ(0) AND HAD JOB RERUN. JOB RAN WITHOUT FURTHER PROBLEMS. I DIDN'T CHANGE CL$$0160 AND IT RAN WITHOUT PROBLEMS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0155",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP ENDED WITH CC 8 DUE TO NOTCAT2 ON CL.SA.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FILES NEEDED CLEANED UP. ",
  "SOLUTION": "TEMP SOLUTION- -RAN CL$$D155 -RESTARTED CL$$0155 JSTEP020.STEP0010 -JOB ENDED OK THE SAME ABEND\/NOT CAT2 THEN OCCURED IN CL$$0160 APPLIED SIMILAR TEMP SOLUTION -RAN CL$$D160 -RESTARTED CL$$0160 JSTEP020.STEP0010 -JOB ENDED OK NEXT DAY, DETERMINED THAT THE REAL PROBLEM WAS THAT VOLUME ASSIGNMENT OF THE TARGET WAS NOT THE SAME AS THE SOURCE DATASET. I HAD CHANGED THE TARGET VOLUME IN STAGE BECAUSE THE CAPACITY OF CICS52 WAS LOW. IN SNAP, THE SOURCE AND TARGET VOLUMES HAS TO BE THE SAME. PERM SOLUTION-CHANGED THE TARGET VOLUME BACK TO CICS52 IN PROD.CL.CARDLIB(CLH0155) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0836",
  "PROBLEM": "CC12 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SAW THAT IN THE FILE CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT CREATED IN CL$$0020 THERE WERE SIX RECORDS FOR THE SAME POLICY -- 3 FOR A 55 TRANSACTION (NEW ISSUE) AND 3 FOR A 53 TRANSACTION (REPRINT). THERE SHOULD ONLY BE 3 RECORDS PER POLICY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "LOGGED IN UNDER FIRECALL AND DELETED THE 3 RECORDS WITH THE 55 TRANSACTION. RERAN CL$$0020 WITH A RESTART IN STEP0030 WITH AND OVERRIDE OF 0 GEN. THEN RERAN CL$$0836 FROM THE TOP. --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! LET THE PRODUCTION PERSON IN KATHY'S AREA KNOW THAT THE USERS MAY BE GETTING DUPLICATE PAGES. HAVE THEM THROW AWAY THE PAGES FROM THE PREVIOUS RUN. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$IIAM",
  "PROBLEM": "FAILED BECAUSE BKUP VERSION OF FILE ALREADY EXISTED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "HAVE OPS CALL DASD ON-CALL PERSON. ",
  "SOLUTION": "THE DASD ON-CALL PERSON SUPPORTS CL$$IIAM AND THE CL$$ABR JOBS. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "CDFT1010 FAILED DUE TO 'FILE ALREADY EXISTS' ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PMLCOM FILE TRANSFER FAILED. IN ORDER TO FIND OUT WHICH MAINFRAME FILE WAS INVOLVED LOOKED IN AUL1.PROCESS(PMLCOM) AND FOUND THAT IT WAS THE CL.CL$$0110.PML.COMSSN() FILE FOR PML. CALLED DOREEN KLOMSTAD AT PML 701-277-2414. AFTER SPEAKING WITH HER FOUND THAT THEY ALREADY RECEIVED THE FILE ONCE TODAY, VERIFIED BY THE HEADER DATE IN THE FILE. CALLED PRODUCTION CONTROL AND FOUND THAT THEY WERE SETTING UP A NEW JOB USING A PREVIOUSLY USED JOB THAT WAS ONCE USED FOR THE TEST TRANSFER OF THE PML COM FILE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "FORWARDED THE TICKET TO DAN DRAKE, NO FURTHER ACTION ON MY PART. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0035",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$0035 CC12 FAILED DUE TO CLIENT PROBLEMS WITH THESE 3 CASES 2052215750, 2052215760, 2052215770. THERE WAS NO CLT OBJ RELATION FOR THESE CASES FOUND BY RUNNING SPUFI (SQL$LVL1). FAULT HISTORY FILE ENTRY SUPPRESSED DUE TO: DUPLICATE FAULT OR END PRO MODULE D7245000, CSECT CKETRGET, OFFSET X'45A': ABEND S0C1 (OPERATION D7245000 D7245000 D7245000 P+F8C E+F8C D7245000 D7245101 D7245101 P+41B8 E+41B8 D7245000 CKETRGET CKETRGET P+45A E+45A * 2...CKCSTGET* *SELECT CISLOR * * * * * * ....* *.... DSNT404I SQ* *LCODE = 100, NOT* * FOUND: ROW NOT* * FOUND FOR FETCH* ",
  "ANALYSIS": "BAD POLICIES WERE IDENTIFIED PRIOR TO THE CYCLE HOWEVER THERE WERE ORIGINALLY 4, SO JOB CL$$PNDD WAS SET UP THINKING THAT ALL 4 POLICIES COULD BE DROPPED. TURNS OUT THE JOB IS SET UP TO ONLY DROP ONE POLICY PER EXECUTION. THE FIRST POLICY WAS DROPPED HOWEVER THE OTHERS WERE NOT. SO DAVID DID SOME MAGIC WITH THE DB2TOOL TO GET SOME KIND OF AN OBJ RELATION SETUP TO KEEP CL$$0035 FROM ABENDING. THE JOB RAN AT 11:00AM SUCCESSFULLY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "LATER SUBMITTED A REQUEST TO RUN CL$$PNDD AFTER CL$$0010 AND BEFORE CL$$0017 TO DROP THE BAD RECORDS. USED JOB CL$$PNDD IN TEST.CL.TOOLS AS A MODEL. SOLUTION 01\/29\/2013: 62XX NOR CKAP34V PRINT WILL WORK IN THIS CASE. REVIEW CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG2 AND DO A FIND ON '89' TO LOCATE THE BEGINNING OF 89 SEGMENTS AND NOTE THE DIFFERENT KIND OF FLC PERSON CODES 89..20... 89..10..... INCLUDE THE TWO DIGIT FLCSEQ-SEQUENCE AFTER THE PERSON CODES. NOTICED THERE WERE 5 ROLES 3000 2000 1000 0001 0002 THEN CHECK DB2 PST CLT_OBJ_RELATION AND SEEN THERE WERE ONLY 4 OBJECT RELATIONS AND ONE OCCURENCE FOR 0001. CMD F == TABLE: CLADMIN.CLT_OBJ_RELATION(T1) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0865",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$0865 ABENDED WITH AN OC1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "IN LOOKING AT THE DUMP FOR THE ABENDING POLICY, I WAS LOOKING AT THE PROBLEM POLICY AS THE 'CURRENT' RECORD ON THE UL.SORTED FILE. AS IT TURNS OUT THE BAD RECORD WAS REALLY THE 'PREVIOUS' RECORD. SO, I HAD THE WRONG POLICY NUMBER. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CREATED A COPY OF THE PRODUCTION INPUT FILE CL.ML$$0860.UL.SORTED. THEN DELETED THE BAD POLICY RECORDS FROM THE COPY OF THE FILE. SUBMITTED A JCL OVERRIDE FORM WITH THE OVERRIDE: \/\/STEP0010.IINPUT01 DD DSN=TEST.CL.SLJ.CL$$0860.UL.SORTED.D0304C JOB RESTART FROM THE TOP. HAVE SET UP JOB CL$$0865 IN TEST.CL.TOOLS TO RUN A PRODUCTION VERSION OF JUST STEP0010 WITH A DIFFERENT INPUT FILE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$IIAM",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$MIIAM ABENDED WITH A COND CODE 0008 BECAUSE THE MODL.CL.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY FILE WAS IN USE FDR400 REORG LOG -- FDRREORG VER 5.3\/52P -- INNOVATION DATA PROCESSIN VOLUME MESSAGE ------ ----------------------------------------------------------------- APL006 FDRR30 BACKUP STARTED DSN=MODL.CL.VSAM.BASEOL.SYSSTAT APL006 FDRR31 BACKUP ENDED DSN=MODL.CL.VSAM.BASEOL.SYSSTAT APL006 FDRR30 RELOAD STARTED DSN=MODL.CL.VSAM.BASEOL.SYSSTAT APL006 FDRR31 RELOAD ENDED DSN=MODL.CL.VSAM.BASEOL.SYSSTAT APL007 FDRR94** UNABLE TO ALLOCATE TARGET DATASET-COMP=04,CODE=0210,INFO APL007 IKJ56225I DATA SET MODL.CL.VSAM.BASEOL.POLICY ALREADY IN USE, TRY APL007 IKJ56225I DATA SET IS ALLOCATED TO ANOTHER JOB OR USER APL007 FDRR32** BACKUP PROCESSING TERMINATED APL007 FDRR33** BACKUP FAILED - CODE=00008,DSN=MODL.CL.VSAM.BASEOL.POL ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE FILE WAS NO LONGER IN USE, THE RESTARTS WERE REVIEWED. THEN DAVID COLVILLE WAS CONSULTED. DAVID ADVISED THAT SINCE THE JOB DID NOT PROCESS THE FILE IT COULD BE RAN AGAIN FROM THE TOP. IF THE JOB FAILS WITH A SC07 WE WOULD NEED TO CALL MIKE GEORGE TO GET THE DATA BASE RESET SO THE JOB COULD BE RAN. IN THAT CASE THE FILE COULD BE CORUPT AND THE CYCLE MAY NEED TO BE RE-RAN FROM CL$$0100. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0810",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$0810.STEP0060 ABENDED WITH A SOC4, S30A, D724AGC2 CALLING CKETRLST. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED IN BOMBLOG, SEEN THAT IT WAS OK TO DROP A BAD POLICY AS WE DID IT BEFORE IN THIS STEP. LOOKED IN THE DUMP. THIS ONE WAS TRICKY BECAUSE THERE WAS NO CURRENT RECORD. I BELIEVE THE SOC4 OVERWROTE STORAGE ON THAT. THE ONLY POLICY # IN THE DUMP WAS 3465033410. SET UP A TEST JOB WITH A TEST FILE. DROPPED THAT POLICY AND IT STILL ABENDED. THE POLICY BEFORE 3465033410 SHOWED UP IN THE NEXT RUN'S DUMP. AFTER A 3RD ITERATION OF DROPS AND NO LUCK, I REALIZED THAT THE BAD POLICY WAS THE ONE AFTER 3465033410.(NOT THE ONE IN THE DUMP) THE BAD POLICY WAS 3465033450. THIS POLICY HAD 160 RECORDS. I'M GUESSING THAT IT PROBABLY EXCEEDED AN INDEX AND OVERWROTE WORKING STORAGE . I DROPPED 3465033450 FROM MY TEST JOB AND THE JOB ENDED OK. ",
  "SOLUTION": "WORKAROUND SOLUTION. COPIED CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AGTPRDEX(0) TO TEST.CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AGT DROPPED 3465033450 FROM TEST.CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AGTPRDEX.D0125 CHECKED OUTPUT FILE FROM FIRST PRODUCTION RUN. IT WAS NOT CATALOGED SO NO CLEANUP NECESSARY. CHECKED GENIN AND GENOUTS. NO ADJUSTMENTS NEEDED. CHECKED RESTARTS. CALLED OPS AND HAD THEM RESTART IN STEP0060 WITH AN OVERRIDE TO MY TEST FILE \/\/STEP0060.IAGTPRD DD DSN=TEST.CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AGTPRDEX.D0125 JOB ENDED OK AND THE AGCY JOBS KICKED OFF. PERMAMENT SOLUTION: NEXT DAY, DEBUGGED D724AGC2 AND FOUND THAT THE INITIAL READ OF CKVSAMIO ON THIS POLICY WAS OVERWRITING WORKING STORAGE. THE SIZE OF THE RECORD WAS +11945, BUT CKFRECRC ONLY HAD ROOM FOR 10,000. PART OF THE WORKING STORAGE THAT WAS OVERWRITTEN WAS APINMAX-RECORD +14000 APINTRLR-TRAILERS +1000 WHICH NOW HAD NEGATIVE NUMBERS INSTEAD OF POSITIVE. THE CKVSAMIO READ DIDN'T ABEND, BUT CKETRLST DID WITH NEGATIVE NUMBERS. TO FIX, INCREASE SIZE OF FILLER UNDER CKFRECRC FROM 10,000 TO 13,977. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0014",
  "PROBLEM": "B37-04 SPACE PROBLEM TRYING TO CREATE DD OOUTPUT ",
  "ANALYSIS": "TRIED BUMPING SPACE 3 TIMES AND STILL GOT B37. ** USE THIS ",
  "SOLUTION": "DJN 2\/6\/02 SOLUTION: HAVE OPS CANCEL WITH A DUMP TO FIND THE LOOPING POLICY NUMBER. DROP THE POLICY NUMBER AND RERUN. DO NOT CREATE EMPTY DATA SETS TO FEED TO CL$$0017. IT IS IMPORTANT TO PROCESS ALL VARIABLE PAYMENTS IN ORDER TO AVOID GAIN\/LOSS. VARIABLE CONTRACTS HAVE A POLICY NUMBER PREFIX OF '24' OR '34'. ** END-SOLUTION SOLUTION: DECIDED PROGRAM WAS PROBABLY LOOPING AND WRITING DATA OVER AND OVER. CREATED A DUMMY FILE TO FEED INTO CL$$0017 CL.CL$$0014.ARPS.EXT() FORCED CL$$0014 OK FOR NOW WITH THE INTENTION OF CORRECTING THE PROBLEM NEXT DAY & DOUBLING UP ON ARPS INPUT IN CL$$0014. CYCLE CONTINUED ON. NEXT MORNING, FOUND OUT WE MADE A MISTAKE: WE FORCED CL$$0014 OK BUT THERE ARE 2 FILES THAT COME OUT OF CL$$0014: ARPS AND CBS. WE SHOULD HAVE CREATED A DUMMY FILE FOR CL.CL$$0014.CBS.EXT() AS A RESULT OF CL$$0014 NOT RUNNING, CL$$0017 RAN WITH THE PRIOR NIGHTS FILE FOR CBS. FORTUNATELY, ALL BUT 2 CBS RECORDS ERRORED OUT. SO JEAN WAS ABLE TO BACK OUT THOSE TWO RECORDS. THIS PUTS US IN A POSITION TO RUN DOUBLE INPUT FOR CBS AS WELL. TO FIX THE CYCLE: COPIED THE CURRENT ARPS FILE TO A TEST FILE. DROPPED THE BAD POLICY RECORD FROM THE TEST FILE PUT IN OVERRIDES FOR TONIGHT TO RUN TWO ARPS FILES ARPS.CL.PAYMENTS(0) TEST.CL.ARPS.PAYMENTS.D0123 PUT IN OVERRIDES FOR TONIGHT TO RUN TWO CBS FILES TO FIX THE CYCLE: CBS.CL.PAYMENT.EXTRACTS(0) CBS.CL.PAYMENT.EXTRACTS(-1) JOBS RAN OK THAT NIGHT. TO FIX THE LOOP: DAVID IS WORKING ON PGM D724FMB1. DAVID FOUND THAT IF THE PREMIUM PAYMENT IS 0.00, THE PGM LOGIC IS NOT SET UP TO HANDLE THAT. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$BIND",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP0055 AND STEP0070 GOT A CC 8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE JOB SYSOUT ERROR STATES UNAVAILABLE RESOURCE. CL$$BIND CANNOT RUN IF ANOTHER JOB IS RUNNING THAT IS USING DB2. IN THIS CASE, CL$$0004 WAS RUNNING SO CL$$BIND GOT ERRORS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "AFTER CL$$0004 WAS DONE, RESTART CL$$BIND FROM TOP. CL$$BIND ENDED OK. TO PREVENT FUTURE OCCURENCES, WE'VE ADD A CONDITION ON CL$$BIND TO RUN ONLY IF CL$$0004 IS NOT RUNNING. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$RBR5",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP0010 PGM=FDRABR ABENDED - COND CODE S378 FDR111** VOL=STOR57,DSN=CL.ME.CL$$0860.SAPPH FDR111** NUMBER OF TRACKS NECESSARY=03261 FDR111** EXTENT CYL=0677 TRK=0013,CYL=0895 TRK=0003 FDR326** RESTORE ENDED WITH NO DATA SETS RESTORED VOL=STO WAS TRYING TO RESTORE DB2 WD99 TO RERUN A YEAR END JOB AND GOT THIS MESSAGE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THERE IS NOT ENOUGH SPACE ON STOR57 TO RESTORE THIS FILE TO. FROM MARK WILLIAMS... THE DATA SET WILL NOT BE RESTORED. SCRATCH THE PRE-ALLOCATED DATA SET. IN MOST CASES, SIMPLY RE-RUN THE RESTORE AND FDR WILL ALLOCATE THE DATA SET PROPERLY. IN SOME CASES YOU MAY NEED TO PRE-ALLOCATE THE DATA SET WITH THE ALLOCATIONS SHOWN (FOR EXAMPLE, FDR CANNOT ALLOCATE AN UNMOVABLE DATA SET WITH MORE THAN ONE EXTENT). IF YOU GET THIS MESSAGE FOR A DATA SET ALLOCATED BY FDR (NOT PRE-ALLOCATED), CONTACT INNOVATION FOR ASSISTANCE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "SINCE THE JOB I AM TRYING TO RERUN DOES NOT USE THE SAPPH FILE, I AM FORCING CL$$RBR5 OK. IF THE FILE IN QUESTION WAS NEEDED FOR THE RERUN JOB AND THERE WAS NOT ENOUGHT SPACE, TRY DELETING THE FILE AND RERUNNING CL$$RBR5. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP=STEP0290 PGM=IKJEFT01 EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 THE SYSLST DISPLAY 'I\/O ERROR ON INFORCE FILE' DUMP YIELDED: THE NEXT SEQUENTIAL INSTRUCTION TO BE EXECUTE PROGRAM CKABEND WAS AT DISPLACEMENT 000000CE. CKAP02 CKUBATSP DISP 00001912 CALLS CKABEND ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS STEPS STRIPS OFF ACTIVITY RECORDS. LOOKING IN CKUBATSP, WE COULD SEE TWO PLACES WHERE THE ERROR COULD BE CREATED. IT WAS ON THE OPEN OR CLOSE PARAGRAPHS, BUT WE DID NOT HAVE THE EXACT IO CODE. NEXT WE DETERMINED THAT THE ABENDING SEQUEN RECORD WAS A 'DU' RECORD FOR POLICY 2052015190. THIS POLICY WAS ALSO ONE THAT GOT DELETED THROUGH CL$$POLD TONIGHT. BUT APPARENTLY, SOME ACTIVITY GOT ON THE ACTIVITY FILE AND CKUBATSP TRIED TO READ THE POLICY RECORD FOR 2052015190. ",
  "SOLUTION": "TO GET THROUGH THE CYCLE, *********** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** RUN CL$$R060, CL$$RC30 DROP RELATED ACTIVITY FROM CL.VSAM.BASEOL.ACTIVITY FOR POLICY 2052015190. RESTART CL$$0100 FROM TOP. TO AVOID THIS IN THE FUTURE, WE PLAN TO MAKE THE POLICY DELETES, CL$$POLD, A POST CYCLE EVENT FROM NOW ON. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "CKUB08 PROGRAM CHECKS EXCEED LIMIT - JOB ABORTING ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS ERROR DID NOT ACTUALLY OCCUR, BUT WE CAME REAL CLOSE IN THE 12\/31\/2001 CYCLE, WHEN THE HARD CODED PROGRAM CHECK LIMIT (OF 20) IN CKUB01V WAS ALMOST EXCEEDED WHEN WE HAD 19 PROGRAM CHECKS RELATED TO YEAR END RMD PROCESSING (THAT ISSUE WAS RESOLVED ON 1\/7\/2002). THE PROGRAM CHECK LIMIT WAS INCREASED FROM 20 TO 30 ON 1\/2\/2002. THIS IS HARD CODED IN ASSEMBLER PROGRAM CKUB01V, WHICH IS IN THE CKAP01V LOAD MODULE. THE FIELD IN CKUB01V IS CALLED PCLIMIT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "IF THIS ERROR IS ENCOUNTERED, DETERMINE IF THE ABEND IS RELATED TO A CHANGE THAT CAN BE BACKED OUT. ANOTHER POTENTIAL OPTION TO CONSIDER IS INCREASING THE PROGRAM CHECK LIMIT AND RERUNNING 100. SUSPENSION OF PROGRAM CHECKING POLICIES COULD ALLOW YOU TO GET BY THIS PROBLEM. BUT, SOME ACTIVITY TYPES HAPPEN EVEN THROUGH A POLICY IS SUSPENDED. BUT THE SUSPENDING APPROACH SHOULD BE TRIED BEFORE INCREASING THE LIMITS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0070",
  "PROBLEM": "CC12 IAMW09 DD=VSAM1 OPEN ERROR - FILE ALLOCATED BUT NOT CREATED -STEP=STEP0030 PGM=IDCAMS EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 RC=0000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WAS ABLE TO LOOK AT CL.VSAM.BASER.BILLDUE2 IN 3.4. BUT IN FILE MARVEL IT SAID THE FILE WAS EMPTY. DAN B DID A LISTCAT ON THE FILE AND IT SHOWED THE FILE WAS NOT LOADED. DID RESEARCH ON THE FILE IN CL$$0120 FROM THE NIGHT BEFORE'S CYCLE. IT SHOWED AN IAMW39 ERROR BUT DIDN'T ERROR OUT WITH AN ABEND. FOUND THERE'S A BUG IN PROGRAM CKBSMPLD WHICH DOESN'T CAUSE AN ERROR FOR THIS PROBLEM WHICH APPEARED TO BE A SPACE ISSUE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "TEMPORARY WORKAROUND...COPIED CL.SB.VSAM.BASER.BILLDUE TO CL.VSAM.BASER.BILLDUE AND BILLDUE2. FORCED OK JOB SINCE THE REST OF THE STEPS EXECUTED. NEXT DAY DAN B REDEFINED BILLDUE AND BILLDUE2 WITH 15% CI AND CA FREESPACE WITH THE IAM RELEASE=NO PARM. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0864",
  "PROBLEM": "CC12 SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=0C7 REASON CODE=00000000 TIME=00.00.41 SEQ=12990 CPU=0000 ASID=00AC PSW AT TIME OF ERROR 078D0000 00355FB0 ILC 6 INTC 07 ACTIVE LOAD MODULE ADDRESS=003553C8 OFFSET=00000BE8 NAME=W0900300 DATA AT PSW 00355FAA - F8227003 D20D94F0 7005960C GPR 0-3 00355D44 00355A78 00000000 00000078 GPR 4-7 00279B50 8027E7E0 00355468 8027E7E0 GPR 8-11 00355948 003568E2 003553C8 00355BF0 GPR 12-15 00355A80 00355740 50355F8C 0025A178 END OF SYMPTOM DUMP IEC130I SYSABOUT DD STATEMENT MISSING +IGZ043I A 'SYSABOUT' ERROR OCCURRED. THE ABEND INFORMATION MAY BE INCOMPLETE. +IGZ057I AN ABEND WAS INTERCEPTED BY THE COBOL RUN-TIME ABEND HANDLER. IT IS DESCRIBED BY A CORRESPONDING IEA995I MESSAGE. +IGZ062I THE FP REGISTERS AT ENTRY TO ABEND WERE FPREG 0 - '421A81BD 85B26473 .26506798130085780 E 02' FPREG 2 - '00000000 00000000 .00000000000000000 E 00' FPREG 4 - '00000000 00000000 .00000000000000000 E 00' FPREG 6 - '00000000 00000000 .00000000000000000 E 00' -STEP=STEP0010 PGM=IKJEFT01 EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 RC=0000 ELAP= 0 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CL$$0004 WENT DOWN DURING LAST NIGHT'S CYCLE. THIS INFO IS TIED TO THIS ISSUE. THE AGENT TIED TO THE POLICY IN THE DUMP HAD A BAD TRAILER. ",
  "SOLUTION": "KRISTI DELETED THE BAD TRAILERS IN AUTO ISSUE AND CYBERLIFE AGENT FILES. RERAN THE JOB FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0836",
  "PROBLEM": "CC3000 +************************************************************ +AB61A-INSUFFICIENT MEMORY REMAINING FOR #XAAINTR TO CONTINUE +************************************************************ -STEP=STEP0140 PGM=DLSBATCH EXECUTED - COND CODE 3000 RC=0000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "REGION SIZE SET TOO LOW ",
  "SOLUTION": "REGION=8M IN JOB CARD OF JCL. CHANGED TO REGION=0M. PRIOR TO JUST RERUNNING FROM THE TOP, CHECK TO SEE IF PRIOR STEPS DID PRINT. IF THEY DID, YOU MAY WANT TO RESTART IN STEP0140. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0015",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC4 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "STEP0030 AND 0040 DID NOT EXECUTE. THE REST OF THE JOB RAN FINE. THEREFORE, MUST BE A PROBLEM WITH A GSYS AGENT RECORD. ",
  "SOLUTION": "AS LONG AS PRIOR STEPS RAN FINE, HAVE OPS FORCE JOB OK. THE NEXT MORNING HAVE WENDY MEDLEY LOOK AT THE JOB. SHE'LL BE ABLE TO FIND THE AGENT RECORD CAUSING THE PROBLEM AND THEN WORK WITH SHARON JONES TO GET IT FIXED. ALSO, THE NEXT TIME WE GET A CLEAN RUN OF CL$$0015, THE MISSED NIGHT'S UPDATES WILL GET PICKED UP AND WE'LL BE UP TO DATE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0004",
  "PROBLEM": "CC12 IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=0C7 REASON CODE=00000000 TIME=20.46.44 SEQ=12676 CPU=0000 ASID=00AC PSW AT TIME OF ERROR 078D0000 000E3FB0 ILC 6 INTC 07 ACTIVE LOAD MODULE ADDRESS=000E33C8 OFFSET=00000BE8 NAME=W0900300 DATA AT PSW 000E3FAA - F8227003 D20D94F0 7005960C GPR 0-3 000E3D44 000E3A78 00000000 0000005A GPR 4-7 0008E180 8008F188 000E3468 8008F188 GPR 8-11 000E3948 000E48E2 000E33C8 000E3BF0 GPR 12-15 000E3A80 000E3740 500E3F8C 0006E0B0 END OF SYMPTOM DUMP IEC130I SYSABOUT DD STATEMENT MISSING +IGZ043I A 'SYSABOUT' ERROR OCCURRED. THE ABEND INFORMATION MAY BE INCOMPLETE. +IGZ057I AN ABEND WAS INTERCEPTED BY THE COBOL RUN-TIME ABEND HANDLER. IT IS DESCRIBED BY A CORRESPONDING IEA995I MESSAGE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE AGCY ACF IS NOT SET UP PROPERLY FOR THE AGENT BEING PROCESSED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CURRENTLY THE JOB IS SET UP SO THAT THE REST OF THE JOB WILL EXECUTE. THIS WILL CREATE BOGUS FILES WHICH WILL NEED TO BE DELETED THROUGH FIRECALL. THEY ARE: CL.CL$$0004.DIRECT.SORT.GXXXXV00 CL.CL$$0004.POL.DIR.GXXXXV00 CL.CL$$0004.PO..PLN.GXXXXV00 LEAVE THE JOB AS NOT OK. THIS WILL CAUSE THE CDFT TO NOT RUN. FIND THE POLICY IN THE DUMP THAT IS CAUSING THE PROBLEM. THE NEXT MORNING LOOK UP THE POLICY AND FIND THE AGENT ATTACHED TO IT. I HAD KRISTI LOOK AT THE AGENT RECORD. SHE NOTICED THAT THERE WAS A BAD TRAILER IN BOTH THE AUTO ISSUE AND CYBERLIFE AGENT FILE. SHE DELETED THE TRAILERS. CALLED KRISTA FARRER TO LET HER KNOW SHE WOULD NOT BE RECEIVING THE FILES FROM THAT NIGHT'S CYCLE. THE NEXT CLEAN RUN OF CL$$0004 WILL BRING IN FILES THAT WILL GET THEM UP TO DATE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0836",
  "PROBLEM": "CC 3000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "IN SYSPRINT FOR STEP 140 IT SHOWS INSUFFICIENT VIRTUAL MEMORY. DON'T LET THAT THROW YOU. THIS IS IN REGARDS TO THE DUMP BEING SO LARGE. SHIFT TO THE RIGHT TO FIND WHAT POLICY RECORD THE JOB WENT DOWN ON. THIS IS SHOWN ON THE 'TRIGGER' LINE. ALSO THE TRIGGER NUMBER PERTAINS TO THE RECORD NUMBER THAT IS CAUSING THE PROBLEM IN FILE CL.DLS.SLTCUST.GXX. ",
  "SOLUTION": "MAKE A COPY OF THE LATEST CL.DLS.SLTCUST.GXX. DELETE THE RECORD THAT IS CAUSING THE PROBLEM AND RERUN THE JOB FROM THE TOP. BE AWARE AS TO WHETHER THE VUL POLICY PAGES PRINTED OR NOT. IF THEY DID AND YOU RERUN FROM THE TOP, YOU WILL GET THOSE PAGES AGAIN. IF THE VUL FILE WAS EMPTY, THEN RERUNNING FROM THE TOP WILL NOT AFFECT ANYTHING. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0810",
  "PROBLEM": "CKABEND ENVOKED GIVING A SO01 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DID FIND ON 'IAGTPRD' IN DUMP. FOUND CURRENT RECORD AND IDENTIFIED THE POLICY NUMBER. CURRENT RECORD HAD LOW VALUES WHERE THE PLAN SHOULD BE(COL 31). LATER ANALYSIS: THIS IS AN ENHARENT RIDER WHICH SHOULD NOT BE INCLUDED IN THIS PROCESSING. KRISTI IS GOING TO COORDINATE A TICKET TO GET THIS FIXED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DROP ALL POLICIES WITH LOW VALUES IN THE PLAN POSITION RESTART PER RESTARTS IN STEP0060. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0015",
  "PROBLEM": "LOOPING ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CANCELLED CL$$0015 WITH A DUMP. HAD OPS RUN CL$$R015. AFTER CL$$R015 FINISHED OK, FORCED CL$$0015 OK. LOOK AT THE PROBLEM THE NEXT DAY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0004",
  "PROBLEM": "GOT A SOC 7 DUE TO THE AGCY ACF FILE BEING CORRUPT. THE OPERATORS ALREADY HAD THIS FIGURED OUT BY THE TIME I WAS CALLED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "COULD RERUN FROM THE TOP FOLLOWING RESTART INSTRUCTIONS SINCE THE OPERATORS SAID THE ACF FILE WAS FIXED ",
  "SOLUTION": "RERAN FOLLOWING RESTART INSTRUCTIONS "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "IN TEST AND MODL, WE HAVE HAD THE FOLLOWING ERROR: + 356 2 AP0356 - FILE DATES ARE INCONSISTENT UBMC00 + I=08062001H=08062001F=NOTREAD A=NOTRE +- - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - -STEP=STEP0210 PGM=IKJEFT01 EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 RC=000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE BLOCK CONTROL FILE WAS RUN WITH A WRONG DATE \/\/**************************************************************** \/\/* R E B U I L D B L O C K C O N T R O L F I L E . \/\/**************************************************************** \/\/* IF YOU RUN THIS JOB BEFORE THE CYCLE, USE LAST CYCLE DATE \/\/* IF YOU RUN THIS AFTER THE CYCLE, USE CURRENT CYCLE DATE ",
  "SOLUTION": "RUN CL$$R060 *********** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** RUN CL$$RC30 RUN CL$$UBLK WITH LAST CYCLE DATE(SINCE CYCLE HASN'T COMPLETED YET) CALL PCD AND RERUN CL$$0100 FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0020",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC-4 IEC130I **552DCL DD STATEMENT MISSING +**552DCL - FILE COULD NOT BE OPENED ",
  "ANALYSIS": "BAD POLICY - NOT SURE WHAT IS CAUSING ",
  "SOLUTION": "FORCE JOB OKAY "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0020",
  "PROBLEM": "+INVALID USER ID PASSED TO CKTBLOCT ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PROGRAM ISSUE INVOLVING USER ID ",
  "SOLUTION": "FORCE JOB OKAY "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0820",
  "PROBLEM": "CODE 1035 A FILE ATTRIBUTE MISMATCH WAS DETECTED. FILE 'REPORT-FILE' IN PROGRAM 'D724ABC1' HAD A RECORD LENGTH OF '63' AND THE FILE SPECIFIED IN THE ASSIGN CLAUSE HAD A RECORD LENGTH OF '108'. THERE WAS AN UNSUCCESSFUL OPEN OR CLOSE OF FILE 'IRPTFL' IN PROGRAM 'D724ABC1' AT RELATIVE LOCATION X'0E58'. NEITHER FILE STATUS NOR AN ERROR DECLARATIVE WERE SPECIFIED. THE I-O STATUS CODE WAS '39'. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "APPARENTLY, AN ISSUE WAS PARTIALLY INSTALLED. EITHER A PROC WENT UP WITH OUT THE PROGRAM OR VICE VERSA. THE REASON IS D724ABC1 IS EXECUTED IN STEP0040 AND STEP0060. THE RECORD LENGTH IN STEP0040 MATCHES THE PROGRAM. THE RECORD LENGTH IN STEP0060 DOES NOT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "SINCE STEP0060 IS THE LAST STEP AND IT IS JUST AN ONB REPORT, WE WILL HOLD THIS JOB, BECAUSE THE ABC EXTRACTS WERE CREATED. HAD OPS SATIFY ALL THE CL$$0820 CONDITIONS ON THE JOBS THAT DEPENDED UPON CL$$0820 SO THEY WOULD KICK OFF. THE NEXT DAY, WE CREATED D724ABC2 AND MODIFIED PROC CL$$0820 AS A TEMP FIX. THIS WAS MOVED TO PRODUCTION AS A TEMP FIX UNTIL THE ISSUE CAN FULLY MOVE UP. APPARENTLY, THERE IS ANOTHER ISSUE TIED TO THIS THAT CAN'T GO UP YET. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0004",
  "PROBLEM": "SB-37, CC 20, ON COMPARE UTILITY. \/\/DELDD DD DSN=&ENVO.CL$$0004.SUPERC.POLDIR, ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DETERMINED THE FILE WAS BIGGER. THIS JOB IS PRETTY NEW AND NEEDS SOME ADJUSTMENTS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CHECKED RESTARTS. INDICATED IT WAS STEP RESTARTABLE. -SINCE THE JOB RAN TO THEN, I HAD TO PERFORM CLEANUP OF DATASETS USING FIRECALL. DELETED CL.CL$$0004.POLDIR.INS DELETED CL.CL$$0004.POLDIR.DEL DELETED CL.CL$$0004.DIRECT.INS -ADDED CARD, \/\/ RESTART=CL$$0004.STEP0050, -ADDED GENIN,GENOT OVERRIDES \/\/CL$$0004 EXEC PROC=CL$$0004,GENIN='(-1)',GENOT='(-0)' -ADDED 2 SPACE OVERRIDES \/\/STEP0050.DELDD SPACE=(CYL,(20,5),RLSE) \/\/STEP0070.DELDD SPACE=(CYL,(20,5),RLSE) AS PRECAUTION RERAN AND JOB ENDED OK. WE WILL UPDATE PROC TOMMORROW FOR SPACE ADJUSTMENTS. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0012",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$0060 DID NOT KICK OFF BECAUSE THE CL$$0012 ERROR REPORT CONTAINED ERRORS. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CHECKED THE CONTROL-M, U OPTION TO VIEW THE ERROR RPT. SEV ERROR DESCRIPTION ___________________________________ 2 FF0058 - UNIT-VALUE REQUIRED PULTCC NEXT, WE BROWSED CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES.G0570V00 AND FOUND THE PULTCC WAS THERE, BUT IT HAD A ZERO PRICE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "SEPARATE ACCOUNTS FED A ZERO PRICE FOR PULTCC TONIGHT. THE CONTROL\/D CL$$0012 ERROR REPORT CHECK HELD UP THE CYCLE AS IT SHOULD. WE GOT THE CORRECT PRICE FROM LINDA. SHE WILL RESEARCH WHY THERE PROCEDURES FAILED. WE MADE A COPY OF THE FILE THEN WENT IN THROUGH FIRECALL AND EDITED THE FILE DIRECTLY. WE EDITED THE UNIT PRICE INPUT FILE, RAN R012, THEN RERAN 12 AND THE CYCLE TOOK OFF. THE RECOVERY WENT VERY SMOOTHLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0820",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB WAS LOOPING. ENDED WITH AN ABEND S322 (TIMED OUT). ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PROGRAM LOGIC IN R7242000 (CALLED BY D724ABC) CAUSED LOOP. ",
  "SOLUTION": "FIXED PROGRAM BY COMMENTING OUT IN D724ABC ANY CALL TO R7242000. **** IMPORTANT MESSAGE REGARDING CL$$0820 **** THERE IS A 5:00AM DEADLINE ON THIS JOB. IF UNABLE TO FIX A PROBLEM WITH THIS JOB AND YOU ARE COMING UP ON THE 5AM DEADLINE: 1. CONTACT DAN BLECK AND OR DAVID COLVILLE 2. SUBMIT THE JOB USING A DUMMY INPUT FILE 3. EMAIL THE FOLLOWING USERS MAKING THEM AWARE OF THE PROBLEM AND THAT THERE WILL BE AN EMPTY ABC INTERFACE FILE FROM CL: JEFF TATUM LINDA KEINTZ MARY KAY MORGAN ERIN GARRETT CYBERLIFE_IND (KATHY HANNAH) 4. ONCE THE PROBLEM IS FIXED AS SOON AS POSSIBLE, CONTACT CORPORATE ACCOUNTING (NORA ARBOGAST) TO INCORPORATE THIS INTERFACE FILE INTO JOB ABC$0004. CONTACT JEFF TATUM, ERIN GARRETT AND THE ABC ON-CALL PERSON WITH FILE NAME. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "CC 12 IN STEP0200 THE ABENDING PROGRAM WAS CKABEND WITH A U0001 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "AFTER LOOKING AT THE DUMP AND THE MAIN MODULE WAS ABLE TO DETERMINE THAT POLICY 2052209770 WAS NOT FOUND ON THE POLICY MASTER FILE ",
  "SOLUTION": "AFTER DISCUSSING WITH DAVID SINCE THIS WAS A NEW ABEND, WE DECIDED TO DROP THE PENDING, AUXSEG2, AND ACTIVITY RECORDS FOR THIS POLICY ******* NOTE: CL$$RC10 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL2 ******** RAN RESTORE JOBS CL$$R030, CL$$RC10, CL$$R017 THEN DROPPED THE PENDING AND AUXSEG2 RECORDS RAN DROPACT FROM TEST.CL.TOOLS TO DROP ACTIVITY THEN RERAN CL$$0017 AND RESTARTED CL$$0030 FROM TOP AFTER MORE RESEARCH WE WERE ABLE TO DETERMINE THAT THE POLICY SHOULD HAVE BEEN ISSUED HOWEVER THE TIMING OF THE ISSUE TRANSACTION COOINCIDED WITH AN ONLINE PROBLEM THAT WE HAD DURING THE DAY. SOMETHING PREVENTED THE POLICY FROM ACTUALLY BEING ISSUED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$2080",
  "PROBLEM": "IAMW09 DD=INFILE OPEN ERROR - FILE ALLOCATED BUT NOT CREATED -STEP=STEP0060 PGM=IDCAMS EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 RC=0000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CL.VSAM.BASEOL.WHOLESALE WAS EMPTY. APPARENTLY THE JOB WAS NOT TESTED IN MODL BEFORE IT MOVED TO PRODUCTION. THE PRODUCTION AND MODL FILE SHOULD HAVE BEEN POPULATED WITH THE DATA THAT WAS IN THE TEST FILE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPY THE TEST.CL.VSAM.BASEOL.WHOLESALE TO CL.VSAM.BASEOL.WHOLESALE RERAN JOB FROM THE TOP. JOB ENDED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "DUMP +CKUB01 SYSTEM MACRO, TO TRAP PROGRAM INTERRUPTS, +IGZ015I A RECURSIVE CALL WAS ATTEMPTED TO A PROGRAM THAT WAS STIL ACTIVE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "VERY TOUGH DUMP TO GO THROUGH. LOOK AT CL$$0100.DEBUG FILE TO GET PROBLEM POLICY NUMBER. THE LAST POLICY IN THE FILE IS THE PROBLEM. WE NEED TO SUSPEND THIS POLICY TO GET THE CYCLE GOING AND LATER FIGURE OUT WHAT IS WRONG. *********** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** ",
  "SOLUTION": "RUN RESTORES CL$$RC30 AND CL$$R060. SETUP OUR SUSPEND JOB USING CL$$0018 TO POINT TO TEST.CL.DATA (SUSPEND). RUN CL$$0018 ONCE RESTORES ARE COMPLETE THEN RESTART CL$$0100 FROM THE TOP. REPEAT THIS PROCESS IF ANOTHER POLICY HAS THIS PROBLEM. IF YOU ENCOUNTER 2 POLICIES, GET YOUR BACKUP INVOLVED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0866",
  "PROBLEM": "CC12 SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=0C7 REASON CODE=00000000 TIME=01.59.18 SEQ=03033 CPU=0000 ASID=00AF PSW AT TIME OF ERROR 078D1000 00064532 ILC 6 INTC 07 ACTIVE LOAD MODULE ADDRESS=00057DF0 OFFSET=0000C742 NAME=D7240150 DATA AT PSW 0006452C - F84443BD 43BDF258 DCD82AEE GPR 0-3 00279433 00000000 00279028 002A7028 GPR 4-7 002A8028 5005C69A 002764A4 40000000 GPR 8-11 0027A028 002D4028 00057F00 00063C78 GPR 12-15 00057E70 00274E80 002764A4 00000000 END OF SYMPTOM DUMP IEC130I SYSABOUT DD STATEMENT MISSING +IGZ043I A 'SYSABOUT' ERROR OCCURRED. THE ABEND INFORMATION MAY BE INCOMPLETE. +IGZ057I AN ABEND WAS INTERCEPTED BY THE COBOL RUN-TIME ABEND HANDLER. IT IS DESCRIBED BY A CORRESPONDING IEA995I MESSAGE. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "TROUBLED POLICY WHICH WAS FOUND IN THE DUMP. REST OF THE STEPS IN THE JOB RAN. THEREFORE, THE POLICIES IN THE FILE PRIOR TO THE TROUBLED POLICY DID GET PROCESSED AND PRINTED (AND WILL THEN GET DELIVERED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "MADE A COPY OF CL.$$0860.VUL.SORTED. DELETED THE TROUBLED POLICY, ALONG WITH ALL POLICIES PRIOR OUT OF THE COPIED FILE. PUT IN AN OVERRIDE IN JOB: \/\/STEP0010.IINPUT01 DD DSN=TEST.CL.DJN.CL$$0860.VUL.SORTED RERAN JOB FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0867",
  "PROBLEM": "SB37 IEC030I B37-04,IFG0554A,CL$$0867,STEP0030,OTAGCUST,0733,STOR27,CL.CL +IGZ034I THE FILE WITH SYSTEM-NAME 'OTAGCUST' COULD NOT BE EXTENDED. SECONDARY EXTENTS WERE NOT SPECIFIED OR WERE NOT AVAILABLE. THE LAST WRITE WAS AT OFFSET X'F9E2' IN PROGRAM 'D7240080'. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "=Q.DA PROBLEM WITH CL.CL$$0867.OTAGCUST AND OTAGAGNT ",
  "SOLUTION": "PUT IN THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDE: \/\/STEP0020.SORTIN DD DSN=CL.CL$$0867.IVA.OTAGTHIS(-0),DISP=SHR \/\/STEP0030.OTAGCUST DD SPACE=(CYL,(1500,200),RLSE) \/\/STEP0030.OTAGAGNT DD SPACE=(CYL,(1500,200),RLSE) RESTART JOB IN STEP0020 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1070",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DO A FIND ON SQL. THIS IS A SQLCODE=100 ROW NOT FOUND PROBLEM ON CISLOR. EXAMINATION OF DB2 SHOWS THE ROWS BUT DATED WITH 3\/31. WE ARE RUNNING WITH PARMDATE 3\/30. ONCE PARDATE BECAUSE 3\/31 OR LATER, THIS JOB WILL RUN OKAY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "WAITED UNTIL 8:30 MONDAY UNTIL THE PARMDATE CHANGES HAD JOB RUN FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1110",
  "PROBLEM": "CC12 ABEND CODE 878 IN DB2 REASON 10 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "QUICK REF INDICATED THIS IS A REGION SIZE PROBLEM. HAD OPS RE-SUBMIT TO SEE THE PROCESS WORK. THE JOB RAN A LITTLE AND THEN REQUEUED TO HOLD POSITION. THEN THE JOB DIED WITH A REGION ERROR. CHECKED JOB FOR A REGION CARD...IT HAD THE MAX. ADJUSTED THE THE REGION CARD TO 8M AND THE JOB DIED WITH 80A. AGAIN A REGION PROBLEM. TRIED REMOVING JOB UNDER DB2 AND REMOVED BUFNO REFERENCE AND CHANGED BLOCK TO SMALL BLOCKING TO REDUCE REGION NEEDS. THIS WORKED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "SETUP A TEMPERARY PROC TO REMOVE THE DB2 UMBRELLA, REMOVE BUFNO REFERENCE AND REDUCE FILE BLOCK SIZE. THIS ALLOWED THE JOB TO RUN....NOW NEED TO FIGURE OUT WHY THE REGION IS BEING USED UP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$2060",
  "PROBLEM": "CC12 - LOGIC ERROR ON OEXTRACT ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SYSOUT SAYS THERE IS A DATE ERROR. LOOKED IN PROGRAM AND DATE EXPECTED IS MM-DD-CCYY BUT JCL WAS PROVIDING MM-DD-YY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "PUT IN OVERRIDE TO USE CORRECT DATE FORMAT "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "CC12 IN STEPO020 DUE TO SOC7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PROGRAM CKPRTRAN WAS THE ABENDING PROGRAM. IT HAS NOT BEEN CHANGED SINCE 99. DATA FIELD AT DISPL 705 FROM BEGIN OF BLW 00 CONTAINS 'C30C' FOR POLICY 060021920. DJN 060031060. DJN 0620036810. DJN 0620101010. NOTE: THE BAD POLICY WAS THE ONE AFTER THE CURRENT POLICY IN THE DUMP. DJN 11\/26\/02 ******* NOTE: CL$$RC10 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL2 ******** ",
  "SOLUTION": "RAN RESTORES CL$$R030, CL$$RC10 AND CL$$R017. DROPPED BAD PENDING RECORD AND RECORDS FROM AUXSEG2 USING FM. RAN A JOB TO DROP THE ACTIVITY FROM THE ACTIVITY FILE TEST.CL.TOOLS(DROPACT). NEED TO ALSO RERUN CL$$0017. THEN HAVE CL$$0030 RESTARTED FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "NOT CAT 2'S ON THREE FILES CL.BASEB.AP.BATCH.EXT2 NEXT USED IN STEP0910 CL.BASEB.COMMISSN.EXT USED IN JOB CL$$0110 CL.BASEB.POLEX.EXT NEXT USED IN STEP0510 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOUND THAT CARDLIB MEMBER CLL10110 HAD BEEN CHANGED AND WAS POINTING TO MODL.* FILES INSTEAD OF PRODUCTION FILES TO BE DELETED IN THE FIRST STEP. DETERMINED THAT THE CORRECT FILES COULD BE CATALOGED AND 2 OF THE FILES REPROED TO MAKE THEM AVAILABLE FOR THE NEXT NIGHT'S CYCLE. DAN BLECK CREATED JOB TEST.CL.TOOLS(DMBFIX1) TO REPRO 2 OF THE FILES FOR THE NEXT CYCLE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "FORCE COMPLETED THE JOB AND CATALOGED THE FILES AND CHANGED THE CARDLIB THE FOLLOWING MORNING. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0160",
  "PROBLEM": "CC8 ON SIBBATCH OF CL$$SNAP PROC JSTEP020 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DUPLICATE DATA SET NAME FOR TAXREC FILE BECAUSE THE CARDLIB WAS SET UP FOR THE TEST FILE INSTEAD OF PROD CARDLIB MEMBER CLH0160 ",
  "SOLUTION": "FORCE COMPLETED THE JOB AND FIX TO CARDLIB WAS MADE THE FOLLOWING MORNING. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "0001 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "POLICY 2453100290 MATURED IN LAST NIGHT'S NON-PRICING CYCLE. THIS CAN NOT BE FIXED THE SAME NIGHT. IT TOOK MOST OF THE NEXT MORNING TO FIX. ISSUE CL2882. ",
  "SOLUTION": "1) HAVE OPS OVERRIDE THE FOLLOWING: STEP0950: FROM &PREFIX.CL$$0100.OFFDE2&GENOT TO &PREFIX.CL$$0100.OFFDE2(0) AND STEP0970: FROM &PREFIX.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT&GENOT TO &PREFIX.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT(0) 2) RESTART CL$$0100 IN STEP0910 JOB ENDED OK "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0835",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DUPLICATE GROUP OF RECORDS IN FILE CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR(0) ",
  "SOLUTION": "1) REPRO CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR(0) TO TEST FILE 2) REMOVED FIRST GROUP OF DUPLICATE RECORDS 3) CALLED PCD TO RERUN CL$$0835 FROM THE TOP WITH OVERRIDE IN STEP0020.SORTIN DD DSN= TEST FILE JOB ENDED OK "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0010",
  "PROBLEM": "CC8 HISTORY FILE SNAP FAILED ",
  "ANALYSIS": "REQUESTED VOLUMES WERE OFF LINE NO ONE COULD GET THE VOLUMES BACK ON-LINE ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED THE CARDLIB USED IN CL$$B010 FOR FDR\/ABR. ALTERED THE CARDLIB TO BACKUP THE PRODUCTION VERSION OF THE HISTORY FILE INSTEAD OF THE SNAP VERSION. HAD CL$$B010 KICKED OFF. WHEN THE CL$$B010 WAS COMPLETE, THEN WE FORCED OKAY THE CL$$0010 SO THE REST OF THE CYCLE COULD RUN. YOU HAVE TO WATCH RECOVERIES WITH THIS APPROACH. YOU CAN NOT REALY ON SNAP RESTORES FOR THE DATASETS YOU COPIED TO FDR\/ABR STRAIGHT FROM PRODUCTION DATASETS. YOU WILL HAVE TO RESTORE THOSE FROM THE FDR\/ABR TAPES. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0690",
  "PROBLEM": "CDFT1079 ABENDED WITH A BUFFER FULL MESSAGE. -FILE SIZES FROM LAN AND CDFT JOB NOT MATCHING LAN FILE WAS LARGER THAN 80 CHARACTERS ********************************************************* ** THE ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOR THIS ISSUE STILL APPLIES, BUT THE ** ** ACTION WE WANT TO TAKE HAS CHANGED ** ** LINDA'S AREA SHOULD BE CONTACTED TO FIX THE FILE ** ** IF THIS PROBLEM IS DIAGNOSED *PHONE LIST IN BOMBLOG** ********************************************************* LAST NIGHT THE CDFT FOR CL$$0690 REGISTERED A \"BUFFER FULL\" MESSAGE. THIS WAS THE RESULT OF AN ENTRY IN THE PC FILE FROM SEPARATE ACCOUNTS BEING 86 BYTES WHEN THE RECORD LENGTH OF THE MAINFRAME IS SET AT 80. ANALYSIS: MARK WILLIAMS SAID THAT A BUFFER FULL USUALLY MEANS THE FILE CREATED ON THE PC SIDE IS BIGGER THAN THE CDFT SETUP DEFINITION FOR THE MAINFRAME SIDE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "SEE NOT ABOVE FIRST SINCE CL.ADJUST.UPLOAD WAS EMPTY, AND WE KNEW THAT CL$$0690 COULD RUN WITH AN EMPTY FILE, WE LET CL$$0690 RUN AS IS WITH THE EMPTY FILE. ALL WE HAD TO DO WAS TO FORCE THE CDFT690 CONDITION AS BEING SATISFIED. THEN LET SEPARATE ACCOUNT FIX TOMMORROW. LINDA KIENTZ WAS MADE AWARE OF THIS AND COULD SEE IN THE PC FILE WHERE THE MISTAKE WAS MADE. SHE'S SAID SHE'S GOING TO FIX THE PROBLEM ON HER END AND APPEND TODAY'S ENTRIES TO YESTERDAY'S. THEREFORE, TONIGHT'S UPLOAD WILL HAVE TODAY'S AND YESTERDAY'S ENTRIES. BUT THAT'LL BE NO PROBLEM. HAVING A BLANK FILE IN CL$$0690 FOR TODAY IS ALSO NO PROBLEM. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0860",
  "PROBLEM": "FIXED INTEREST RATE PLANS FOR IVA NOT UPDATED ",
  "ANALYSIS": "NEED TO EVALUATE THE ABOVE JOBS TO SEE IF THEY ARE IMPACTED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "NEEDED TO RUN CL$$0860,CL$$1010,CL$$2010. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$4000",
  "PROBLEM": "JOBS IN WAIT STATE ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOBS TO KICK OFF CL$$4000 ARE NOT SCHEDULED TO RUN DURING THE SAME CYCLE CL$$4000 ARE RUNNING ",
  "SOLUTION": "RELEASE JOB TO RUN. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$4020",
  "PROBLEM": "PRINTER LOST REPORTS ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB IS RESTARTABLE FROM THE TOP WITH NO INTERVENTION ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAVE OPS RUN THE JOB FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC-1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WENT INTO DUMP. DID A FIND ON SQL. THIS BROUGHT ME TO AN SQL CODE = -811. THIS IS A DUPLICATE ROW. I PAGED DOWN 2 PAGES AND FOUND THE POLICY NUMBER WITH THE PROBLEM ALSO THE TABLE WHICH HAD THE PROBLEM. THIS IS CIS.....IN THIS CASE IT WAS CISLTX. THIS IS A DUPLICATE TAX ROW ENTRY. I ALWAYS CHECK THE POLICY OWNER FIRST FOR THESE DUPLICATES BECAUSE I THINK THEY ARE THE ONLY RELATIONSHIP WE SETUP THE TIN ON. I RAN SPUFI FOR SQL$LVL1 WITH THE POLICY NUMBER. I CUT THE CLIENT_ID FOR THE OWNER AND THEN PROCEDE TO SQL$LVL2. I ONLY POPULATE THE CLIENT_ID FOR THE TAX TABLE LOOKUP. THEN I SEE IF I HAVE 2 ROWS WHICH ARE NOT EXPIRED, WITH HISTORY OF 0. THE SEQUENCE DOES NOT MATTER IN THIS SQL. WHAT MATTERS IS WHAT CKCSTGET PROGRAM IS LOOKING UP IN THE SQL FOR CISLTX. THERE WERE 2 DUPLICATE ROWS FOR THIS TAX ID. ",
  "SOLUTION": "ONCE I PINNED DOWN THE CLIENT_ID WITH THE DUPLICATE TAX ROWS. I USED THE SEQUENCES, HISTORY VALID, AND CLIENT_ID TO PICK UP THE UNIQUE ROWS I WANTED TO EXPIRE. THE ROW TO LEAVE AVAILABLE IS THE ROW WITH THE MOST RECENT EFFECTIVE DATE. IF THERE IS MORE THAN ONE...COMPARE THEM AND APPLY YOUR BEST GUESS AS TO WHICH ONE THE USER PROBABLY WANTED TO HAVE ACTIVE. THEN APPLY INFORMATION TO SQL$FIXT. I BELIEVE THIS IS OBVIOUS HOW TO FILL OUT. EXPIRE DATE SHOULD BE SET TO TODAYS DATE. CHECK THE FIRST SELECT TO MAKE SURE THESE ARE THE ROWS YOU WANT. CHECK TO MAKE SURE YOU ONLY UPDATED THE NUMBER OF ROWS YOU INTENDED. CHECK THE SECOND SELECT TO MAKE SURE EXPIRATION DATE CHANGED AND THE ROWS OTHERWISE LOOK THE SAME AS THE FIRST SELECT. THEN PF3 AND COMMIT THE CHANGE. THEN GO INTO TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$$0011) AND RUN A SPECIFIC POLICY RUN FOR THE POLICY YOU FIXED, CHANGE YOUR COUNTER SO ONLY A COUPLE OF POLICIES PRINT... THATS THE 999999 TO 0000005. IT IS RECOMMENDED TO DO A FULL RE-RUN OF CL$$0011 ONCE THE REPAIR HAS BEEN DONE. THIS IS TO MAKE SURE NO NEGATIVE IMPACT HAS BEEN DONE ON SOME OTHER POLICY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0848",
  "PROBLEM": "CC 8\\STOP 8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "( 150) <SC,201, \/SC,202, \/SC,203, \/SC,204, \/SC,205, THE ABOVE LINE IN THE FT06F001 USUALLY DENOTES DUPLICATE LINES. WENT INTO THE CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR FILE AND NOTICED ONE POLICY'S EXTRACTS WERE IN THERE TWICE FOR TWO DIFFERENT PLANS. SO WE BROUGHT UP THE POLICY IN 3270 TO SEE WHAT PLAN THIS POLICY ACTUALLY HAD; SVAQ01 VS FVAQ01. NOTE: THESE DUPLICATE POLICY RECORDS WILL CREATE RECORDS IN THE OTAG FILE WITH A POLICY NUMBER OF 00. ",
  "SOLUTION": "MADE A COPY OF CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR, LOGGED ON USING FIRECALL, DELETED THE SVAQ01 SECTION FOR SPECIFIC POLICY IN CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR, THEN HAD OPS RERUN CL$$0848 FROM THE TOP. JOB RAN CLEAN. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC1 ABEND IN CKETRGET, LOAD MODULE CKUNVPRT ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB ABENDED WHILE TRYING TO PRINT A POLICY WHICH HAD NUMEROUS 75 SEGMENTS. NOT SURE WHY THERE ARE SO MANY 75 SEGMENTS. IT MAY BE TRYING TO PRINT ALL OF THE HISTORY 75 SEGMENTS. IT MAY BE LOOPING AND FINALLY ABENDING. ??? ",
  "SOLUTION": "FORCE THE JOB OK ONCE WE SAW THAT ALL OF THE OTHER STEPS EXECUTED, WITH THE EXCEPTION OF 720 AND 730. THESE STEPS WILL ALWAYS BE FLUSHED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$9101",
  "PROBLEM": "SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=0C1 REASON CODE=00000001 TIME=07.55.13 SEQ=10167 CPU=0000 ASID=00C7 PSW AT TIME OF ERROR 078D2200 0014BEDC ILC 2 INTC ACTIVE LOAD MODULE ADDRESS=00149848 OFFSET NAME=D724COV DATA AT PSW 0014BED6 - 478032AA 000058F0 D05895F2 GPR 0-3 00000494 0011FAD0 00000028 5214BC32 GPR 4-7 00166B68 00160400 00000001 001601B8 GPR 8-11 00000001 0016F028 0016F978 0016FB54 GPR 12-15 001498C8 0014C690 00160284 0016F9E0 END OF SYMPTOM DUMP IEC130I SYSABOUT DD STATEMENT MISSING +IGZ043I A 'SYSABOUT' ERROR OCCURRED. THE ABEND INFORMA INCOMPLETE. +IGZ057I AN ABEND WAS INTERCEPTED BY THE COBOL RUN-TIME IT IS DESCRIBED BY A CORRESPONDING IEA995I MESS -STEP=STEP0010 PGM=IKJEFT01 EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 R ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DID A SEARCH ON SQL IN DUMP AND FOUND CODE=100 (ADDRESS ROW MISSING). FIGURED SINCE THE JOB STARTED SO LATE, 6AM, A USER CAME IN AND MADE CHANGES WHILE THE JOB WAS RUNNING. ",
  "SOLUTION": "WAITED UNTIL THE PARMDATE JOB RAN AT 8:30 TO ADVANCE THE DATE TO TODAY'S DATE. THEN HAD OPS RERUN THE JOB FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "WAS TOLD CDFT1066 FINISHED OK AND HAD A CC OF 0 BUT A SHOUT MESSAGE CAME UP STATING THE CL ON-CALL PERSON NEEDED TO BE CALLED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "BY THIS TIME ONLY ABR1 AND 2 WERE RUNNING. ALL OF OUR OTHER CL$$ JOBS RAN WITH NO PROBLEMS AND FINISHED OK. WENT INTO MR3 AND SAW THAT CDFT1066 FINISHED OK. ONE THING THAT I DIDN'T DO BUT NEEDS TO BE DONE IS TO VERIFY THAT THE FILE TO BE DOWNLOADED WAS CREATED. IN THIS INSTANCE, IT WAS WITH NO PROBLEMS. IF YOU WONDER WHAT FILES ARE CREATED AND DOWNLOADED\\ UPLOADED, CHECK OUR \"AUL CYBERLIFE JOBS - TIME DRIVEN\" (CYBRJOB.DOC). ",
  "SOLUTION": "AT THIS POINT EVERYTHING LOOKED AS IF IT WENT SMOOTHLY. SO I LOOKED TO SEE WHO WAS ON-CALL FOR CDFT. I TOLD OPS TO CALL THEM. COME TO FIND OUT THE NEXT MORNING, THE S2 SERVER WAS DOWN. BOTTOM LINE IS...IF EVERYTHING APPEARS TO HAVE RUN SMOOTHLY, ASK OPS IF THERE IS SOMETHING ELSE WHICH MAY BE HINDERING THE UPLOAD OR DOWNLOAD SUCH AS THE S2 SERVER BEING DOWN. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0860",
  "PROBLEM": "CC12 - AN INVALID EBCDIC DIGIT STRING ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SINCE I HAD SEEN THIS IN MODL AND DURING THAT CYCLE I FOUND I WAS ABLE TO DROP A POLICY AND MOVE ON. I BEGAN TRYING THIS APPROACH. USING TEST.CL.DLCJCL CL$$0860. I BROUGHT IN A FILE "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0130",
  "PROBLEM": "SB37 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "NEED TO INCREASE SPACE. THIS IS A NON-CALLABLE BUT IS IN THE MAINSTREAM ALSO. SINCE I WAS HERE, I WENT AHEAD AND FIXED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "PUT IN OVERRIDE TO INCREASE SPACE IN THE FOLLOWING STEP0050.SEQUEN2 STEP0060.SORTOUT THEN RESTART THE JOB FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "SB37 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "NEED TO INCREASE SPACE. I CHOOSE TO LET THE JOB FINISH NATURALLY BEFORE I BEGAN RESTORES. *********** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** ",
  "SOLUTION": "RUN CL$$R060, CL$$RC30 PUT IN OVERRIDE FOR THE FOLLOWING STEP0050.OUTPUT STEP0060.SORTOUT STEP0250.SORTOUT STEP0280.SORTOUT STEP0290.SEQUEN2 STEP0300.SORTOUT RAN CL$$0100 FROM THE TOP IDEALLY A JOB SHOULD BE SETUP HERE TO CLEANUP THE FOLLOWING DATASET 'CL.BASEB.ACCT.EXT'. THIS IS A FILE WHICH WRAPPS IN CL$$0100. IN THIS CASE I DETERMINED THE RESULT WAS THE SAME. I DID NOT REMEMBER THE PIECE UNTIL I WAS DEEP IN MY RE-RUN..SO I LET IT FINISH AND COMPARED THE OUTPUT RESULTS FROM BOTH RUNS AND THEY MATCH. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "SB37 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "INCREASE SPACE. HAD TO FIGURE OUT HOW TO RESTART. ",
  "SOLUTION": "PUT IN OVERRIDE FOR SPACE INCREASE TO THE FOLLOWING STEP0192.QSAM1, STEP0193.SORTOUT ******* NOTE: CL$$RC10 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL2 ******** RESTORE CL$$R010, CL$$RC10. RERUN THE FOLLOWING CL$$0012, CL$$0015, CL$$0017, CL$$0018, CL$$0030 ALL FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0125",
  "PROBLEM": "CC8 ON - STOP 8 ON EMITTER STEPS ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SEE IF THE PROBLEM WAS GLOBAL, WE RAN A TEST JOB CL$$0835 TO SEE IF IT GOT THE SAME PROBLEM. IT DID. -FOUND IN THE EMITTER FT06F001 A MESSAGE INDICATING A CONFIGURATIONS FILE ERROR. LOOKING IN THE JCL THERE IS A FILE CALLED XICS.COMPUSET.CONFIG(AULXICS) THERE WAS A VERSION DATED THE DAY PRIOR CALLED XICS.COMPUSET.CONFIG(AULXICSO). THE DATE OF THE ORIGINAL MEMBER WAS ALSO YESTERDAY. THIS WAS AN INDICATION OF A CHANGE. THIS WAS DONE BY LAVONNA.NICHOLS -TO TEST THE AULXICSO MEMBER, A COPY OF CL$$0835 WAS BROUGHT DOWN INTO TEST. THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDE WAS ADDED \/\/ CONFIG='AULXICSO', AFTER EACH REFERENCE OF \/\/STEP0100 EXEC COMPUSET, THEN CL$$0835 WAS RUN FROM THE TOP. THE STOP 8 WENT AWAY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "WORKED WITH LINDA KELLEY TO HAVE THEM FIGURE OUT WHAT NEEDED TO BE DONE. THEY REPLACED THE OLD MEMBER AND ALL THE ABOVE JOBS WERE RESTARTED FROM THE TOP. FOR CL$$0125, WE CHANGED THE PARMDATE BACK TO THE DATE OF THE RUN. THIS IS BECAUSE AFTER 8:00AM, THE DATE CHANGED. THEN WHEN THE RUN WAS COMPLETE, WE CHANGED IT BACK TO TODAYS DATE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0070",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC7 ABEND IN CKDCCFEX ",
  "ANALYSIS": "AN ERROR WAS WRITTEN OUT INDICATING THAT THE POLICY WAS NOT FOUND FOR 0620216980 ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED FILE CBS.CL.PAYMENTS.G0419V00 AND DELETED THE RECORD FOR THAT POLICY. RESTARTED JOB WITH AN OVERRIDE AT STEP0060. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0040",
  "PROBLEM": "COND CODE 12 OPEN ERROR FILE IN USE ",
  "ANALYSIS": "APPEARS THAT CL$$0035 HAD NOT FINISHED WHEN 0040 STARTED AND HAD AHOLD OF THE AGENT FILE ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTARTED CL$$0040 FROM THE TOP. GOOD EOJ "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1040",
  "PROBLEM": "JCL ERROR CL$$1040 STEP0020 CL$$1040 OUTPUT - SPACE REQUESTED NOT AVAILABLE ",
  "ANALYSIS": "STOR PACKS DID NOT HAVE ENOUGH SPACE ",
  "SOLUTION": "CHANGE SYMBOLIC DISK='SYSDAL'. PUT IN OVERRIDE TO SET PARMDATE TO CORRECT CYCLE DATE \/\/STEP0010.SYSUT1 DD DSN=PROD.CL.CARDLIB(PARMPREV) RESTARTED JOB FROM THE TOP. THE OVERRIDE IS ONLY NEEDED BECAUSE PARMDATE HAS CHANGED TO THE NEXT BUSINESS DAY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0866",
  "PROBLEM": "JCL ERROR CL$$0866 STEP0020 CL$$0866 OTAGCUST - SPACE REQUESTED NOT AVAILABL ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED AT STOR* PACKS THROUGH QUICKREF. THE OUTPUT FILE FROM THE PROBLEM STEP WAS LOOKING FOR 500 CYL NO STOR* PACKS HAD 500 CONTIGUOUS CYL'S AVAILABLE ",
  "SOLUTION": "CHANGE SYMBOLIC DISK='SYSDAL'. RESTARTED JOB FROM THE TOP. THIS CHANGE WAS RECOMMENDED BY MIKE GEORGE, HE DOES NOT WANT US TO GO CRAZY WITH THIS. IF WE CAN AVOID THIS CHANGE, WE SHOULD. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0035",
  "PROBLEM": "IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=0C7 REASON CODE=00000007 TIME=12.47.11 SEQ=04860 CPU=0000 ASID=0029 PSW AT TIME OF ERROR 078D3000 0006CF4E ILC 6 INTC 07 ACTIVE LOAD MODULE ADDRESS=00054248 OFFSET=000 NAME=D7245000 DATA AT PSW 0006CF48 - FD30D3A0 9131F332 A36ED3A0 GPR 0-3 000867B0 000869A8 3025F392 3025F30B GPR 4-7 000BD528 00000000 0025F3A9 40000000 GPR 8-11 00261028 0006A578 0025F028 0006CA02 GPR 12-15 0006A550 00086608 5006CF32 00000000 END OF SYMPTOM DUMP +IGZ057I AN ABEND WAS INTERCEPTED BY THE COBOL RUN-TIME ABEN IT IS DESCRIBED BY A CORRESPONDING IEA995I MESSAGE. -STEP=STEP0010 PGM=IKJEFT01 EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 RC=00 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CKULMPIF IS AN INTERFACE TO THE MODE PREMIUM CALCULATION ELEMENT CKULMPRM. IT IS SUPPOSE TO HANDLE BOTH STANDARD AND SPECIAL FREQUENCY MODES. BUT IT HAS A PROBLEM WITH SPECIAL FREQUENCY MODES. THE POLICY THIS JOB BOMBED ON HAD A BILLING MODE OF \"EVERY 4 WEEKS\". ",
  "SOLUTION": "IN PRODUCTION, THE USERS ARE NOT ABLE TO SELECT THESE SPECIAL FREQUENCIES. THEREFORE, WE SHOULDN'T RUN INTO THIS PROBLEM IN PRODUCTION. WE ASKED PERMISSION TO DROP THIS POLICY SO IT WON'T BOMB THIS JOB THE NEXT TIME WE RUN CYCLE. DROPPED THE POLICY. THE E-COMMERCE EXTRACT WAS NOT NEEDED FROM THIS CYCLE, SO WE DIDN'T RERUN THIS JOB. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1050",
  "PROBLEM": "EXCESSIVE WALL CLOCK TIME SOME MESSAGES INDICATING TAPE DRIVES REQUIRED ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB WAS RUNNING JUST FINE. BELIEVE THERE WAS A BOTTLENECK WITH THE TAPE DRIVES. ",
  "SOLUTION": "JOB CAN BE TERMINATED TO ALLOW CICSD TO COME UP AS LONG AS WE ARE IN STEP0020. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC-7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "AF TRANSACTIONS IN THE ACTIVITY FILE RELATED TO THE 53 SEGMENT. THE PROGRAM EXPECT A BEFORE AND AFTER PICTURE ON EACH RECORD OF THE 53 SEGMENT. SO, ON A GIVEN RECORD YOU SHOULD SEE TWO 53 SEGMENTS. IF YOU DO NOT, DROP THE TRANSACTION WHICH DOES NOT HAVE THE TWO 53 SEGMENTS. CHECK ALL U1AW AND U1AT TRANSACTIO NS. ANOTHER PROBLEM WAS WITH A 26AC NOT HAVING ANY SEGMENT RECORD INFORMATION AT ALL. DROP THOSE ALSO. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DROP IDENTIFIED PROBLEM RECORDS OUT OF THE COPY OF CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT(0). RESTART IN STEP0970 WITH OVERRIDE FOR SORTIN BEING YOUR FIXED RECORD. IF YOU ENCOUNTER ADDITIONAL PROBLEMS OR TIME GETS AWAY FROM YOU(YOU DON'T WANT TO GO PAST 1\/2 HOUR ON THIS ISSUE)......HAVE OPS FORCE JOB OK AND HAVE THE CYCLE MOVE ON. THIS PROBLEM CAN BE ANALYZED AND FIXED THE NEXT DAY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0035",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC-7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PROGRAM COULD NOT HANDLE TRANSLATION FOR SEG SEQ PAST 09. WE HAD ONE SHOW UP WITH 10. HAD TO ALTER DEFINITION OF SEG SEQENCE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DID NOT RE-RUN THE JOB. THE PROBLEM WAS FIGURED OUT THE NEXT DAY AND THE CATALOGUED FILES FROM THE FAILED PRODUCTION RUN WERE ALREADY PICKED UP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0866",
  "PROBLEM": "CC8 - STOP 8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE FOLLOWING MESSAGE IN THE FT06F001 INDICATES DUPLICATE POLICIES IN THE DPFS FILE ( 1634) <SC,201, \/SC,202, \/SC,203, \/SC,204, \/SC,205, \/SC,206, \/SC ",
  "SOLUTION": "SPLIT THE CL.BASEB.DPFSEXTR FILE INTO 2 FILES. 1 CONTAINING ALL POLICIES DELETING THE DUPLICATE ENTRY THE OTHER CONTAINING THE DUPLICATE ENTRIES. RUN CL$$0849 FROM THE TOP TWICE, ONCE WITH EACH FILE \/\/STEP0020.SORTIN DD DSN=***YOUR DATASET NAME**** "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0865",
  "PROBLEM": "SB37 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "COMPUSET SPACE WAS INADEQUITE FOR QUARTERLY STATEMENT PRODUCTION ",
  "SOLUTION": "INCREASED SPACE FOR CSSOUT TO 12000 CYL. LONG TERM SOLUTION IS TO SPLIT FILES BY LOB. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0865",
  "PROBLEM": "S322 TIME OUT ERROR ",
  "ANALYSIS": "NO TIME CARD ON JOB WHICH ONLY ALLOWS 1 HOUR OF CPU JOB NEEDS MORE THAN 1 HOUR ",
  "SOLUTION": "ADDED TIME CARD FOR 2 HOURS "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "CC12 IEC036I 002-18,IGC0005E,CL$$0030,STEP0020,SEQUEN,0835, ",
  "ANALYSIS": "RECORD TRYING TO BE WRITTEN WAS LARGER THAN THE LRECL DEFINED. THIS WAS A FLAT FILE VERSION OF THE PENDING FILE WHICH WAS CAUSING THE PROBLEM. MAXIMUM RECORD SIZE IS 10,000 BYTES. SINCE THIS IS A VB FILE. THE REAL MAX IS 10,004. THE JCL ONLY ALLOWED 10,000 IN THE LRECL. THE RECORD TRYING TO BE WRITTEN WAS 9997 + 4 BYTES FOR VB = 10,001. LARGER THAN OUR LRECL. ",
  "SOLUTION": "THIS JCL SHOULD BE CODED WITH LRECL=10004. 1)RELOAD THE FOLLOWING VSAM FILES ACTIVITY, PENDING, POLICY, AUXSEG1, AUXSEG2 IN THE FUTURE THERE WILL BE A CL$$R030 JOB. ******* NOTE: CL$$RC10 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL2 ******** 2)RUN CL$$RC10 TO RESTORE CLIENT 3)RUN CL$$0017 AGAIN TO APPLY FMB AGAINST THE POLICY 4)PUT IN OVERRIDE FOR INCREASED LRECL \/\/STEP0020.SEQUEN DD DCB=(RECFM=VB,LRECL=10004,BLKSIZE=23200) 5)RESTART CL$$0030 FROM THE TOP "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0035",
  "PROBLEM": "IN LPARB TESTING, WE GOT THE FOLLOWING RUN TIME SYNTAX ERROR: P1WET035 STEP0005 CL$$0035 ORATING - VOL ON INELIGIBLE PERMRES OR RSVD UNIT P1WET035 STEP0005 CL$$0035 - STEP WAS NOT EXECUTED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PACK IS NOT IN MAIN STORAGE GROUP, SYSDA. ",
  "SOLUTION": "QUICK JOB FIX: ADD SYMBOLIC TO POINT SYSDA TO SYSALLDA. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND=SB37 IEF450I CL$$0100 STEP0930 JSTEP010 - ABEND=SB37 U0000 REASON=00000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SPACE PROBLEM WITH CL.BASEB.CISBMAIN.BK00.G0516V00 ",
  "SOLUTION": "DUE TO THE ABEND ON A STEP REGARDING DB2, NEED TO RE- START IN STEP0920 IN ORDER TO RESET DB2. SO, I HAD OPS PUT IN A RESTART=JSTEP010.STEP0920 AND 3 OVERRIDES: \/\/STEP0930.SYSCOPY DD SPACE=(CYL,(250,20),RLSE) \/\/STEP0950.SORTIN DD DSN=CL.CL$$0100.OFFDE2(-0) \/\/STEP0970.SORTIN DD DSN=CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT(-0) THE OVERRIDES FOR STEPS 0950 AND 0970 ARE NECESSARY BECAUSE THESE FILES HAD ALREADY BEEN CREATED IN STEPS PRIOR TO 0930 FROM THE FIRST TIME THE JOB RAN WHEN IT ABENDED. THE HINT IS THE (SHR, KEEP,KEEP) IN THE DISP. ALL OTHER GENERATION FILES IN STEPS AFTER 0920 ARE NEW AND THEREFORE CAN USE THE SYMBOLIC FOR (+1). DAN DRAKE INCREASED SPACE FOR ALL BASEB.CISBMAIN FILES TO (200,20) IN JOBS 0010, 0030, 0100 AND 0150. THIS PROBLEM SHOULDN'T HAPPEN AGAIN FOR A WHILE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0125",
  "PROBLEM": "CC 12 806 ERROR FROM A DYNAMIC PROGRAM CALL ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE NAMES OF 4 PROGRAMS IN WORKING STORAGE WERE GETTING WIPED OUT BECAUSE OF LOGIC THAT MANIPULATED THE SRVAGENT-ADDRESS FIELD, WHICH OCCURS 5 TIMES. A 6TH OCCURANCE WAS BEING MOVED INTO THIS AREA, THUS WIPING OUT THE FOLLOWING FIELD IN WORKING STORAGE (THE PROGRAM NAMES FOR DYNAMIC CALLS). BKG ",
  "SOLUTION": "ADDED A 6TH OCCURANCE TO PREVENT THE PROGRAM NAMES IN WORKING STORAGE FROM BEING WIPED OUT. BROUGHT THE CHANGE INTO PRODUCTION IMMEDIATELY AND THEN HAD OPS RUN CL$$0125 FROM THE TOP. (THIS SOLUTION WAS NEXT DAY). DJN SOLUTION: ADDED A 7TH OCCURANCE TO PREVENT THE PROGRAM NAMES IN WORKING STORAGE FROM BEING WIPED OUT. BROUGHT THE CHANGE INTO PRODUCTION IMMEDIATELY AND THEN HAD OPS RUN CL$$0125 FROM THE TOP. (THIS SOLUTION WAS NEXT DAY). LAP SOLUTION: ADDED A 6TH OCCURANCE TO PREVENT THE PROGRAM NAMES IN WORKING STORAGE FROM BEING WIPED OUT. (PREVIOUS UPDATE (CL2309) HAD BEEN REMOVED BY CL4544.) RAN CL$$0125 FROM THE TOP FROM TEST; COPIED UPDATES UP NEXT DAY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0110",
  "PROBLEM": "OPEN ERROR - DATASET NOT AVAILABLE, IN USE BY JOB CICSD ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE CICSD REGION HAD BEEN BROUGHT UP DURING CYCLE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD OPS CHANGE THE SELECT LINE IN CL$$RSTR TO RESTORE CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AGTFIN, THEN RUN CL$$RSTR. AFTER CL$$RSTR WAS DONE, HAD OPS RESTART CL$$0110 FROM THE TOP. ONCE CL$$0110 WAS DONE, IT FINISHED WITH CC 8 IN STEP0010. THIS IS CAUSED BY THE JOB NOT BEING ABLE TO DELETE FILES THAT AREN'T THERE. THIS IS OKAY. HAD OPS FORCE OKAY CL$$0110 TO HAVE CYCLE CONTINUE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "S001 FORCED ABEND +- - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - ",
  "SOLUTION": "FOR THE NIGHT: RUN STEP0001 OF TEST.CL.TOOLS(EMPTYFLS) TO CREATE AN EMPTY FILE FOR AGCY0020, THEN HAVE THE JOB FORCE COMPLETED AND CYCLE STARTED UP. NEXT DAY: LOOK IN DUMP FOR 'CURRENT'. GET CURRENT POLICY NUMBER. PULL A COPY OF CL.COMBPEND. CALL IT TEST.CL.XXX.COMBPEND.#MMDD WHERE XXX IS YOUR INITIALS. MAKE ANOTHER COPY AND ADD .GOOD TO THE END. GO INTO THE GOOD VERSION AND DELETE YOUR BAD POLICY. THEN YOU CAN TAKE A COPY OF TEST.CL. DLCJCL(D724AGC1). THIS JOB CAN BE TWEEKED TO RUN THE NECCESSARY PIECES TO TEST YOUR NEW FILE AND CREATE A NEW FILE YOU WILL NEED TO RUN THRU TONIGHTS PRODUCTION CYCLE SO WE DO NOT HOLD UP PRODUCTION ANY LONGER. WHEN THE RUN IS SUCCESSFUL TAKE THE 'TEST.CL.XXX.CL$$0030.AGTSTAT' FILE AND HAVE PCD PUT THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDE INTO CL$$0030. \/\/STEP0160.SORTIN DD \/\/ DD DSN=TEST.CL.XXX.CL$$0030.AGTSTAT,DISP=SHR NOTIFY KRISTI ABBOTT WHAT POLICY HAS A PROBLEM AND SHE WILL BE ABLE TO PUT UP MANUAL NUMBERS. ALSO, LET HER KNOW THAT THE REST OF THE FILE WILL FEED INTO PRODUCTION TONIGHT. LET HER KNOW THAT THE FOLLOWING REPORT FOR TONIGHT WILL CONTAIN LAST NIGHTS NUMBERS AND TONIGHTS NUMBERS. WHILE LAST NIGHTS VERSION OF THIS REPORT HAS LAST NIGHTS NUMBERS ALSO. 'AGENTS PRODUCTION REPORT' "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0017",
  "PROBLEM": "CC 12 MESSAGES FROM JOB LOG: +CKFC1 AP FILE CONSISTENCY CHECK SUCCESSFUL +CKST09 CK4\/VS SYSTEM ON THE AIR - SSDATE=05\/18\/00 IEC130I SYSPDUMP DD STATEMENT MISSING +CKSN01 PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. PSW=078D0600 8009FE46 +CKSN02 ABENDING ELEMENT IGZESPM EPA=0009F5C8 OFFSET 000 +CKSN03 CALLING ELEMENT UNKNOWN EPA=8009F548 SYSLST PRINT LINES: -INPUT- 0001 CKSN01 PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. PSW=078D0600 8009FE46 (PRO CKSN02 ABENDING ELEMENT IGZESPM EPA=0009F5C8 OFFSET 00087E 0-7 00000190 0009FA02 09772000 40404040 0853D938 40404040 8005 8-15 000B8CC0 00000000 000B8CC0 000A05C8 8009F5C8 000B8020 8009 CKSN03 CALLING ELEMENT UNKNOWN EPA=8009F548 0-7 00000190 0009FA02 09772000 40404040 0853D938 40404040 8005 8-15 000B8CC0 00000000 000B8CC0 000A05C8 8009F5C8 000B8020 8009 -INPUT- QUIT *** GENERATED BY CKAITEST *** . . . << REPEATED UNTIL 10 PROGRAM CHECKS OCCURRED >> . . A NORMAL CL$$0017 FMB CYCLE SHOULD START OFF WITH THE FOLLOWING SYSLST PRINT LINES: ***** TERMINAL SWITCH TO CNT0 -INPUT- 0001 CKST09 CK4\/VS SYSTEM ON THE AIR - SSDATE=05\/18\/00: ! 34 CYBERLIFE ON THE AIR ! -INPUT- 0000; ID:AUL; PASS:BATCH; . ! 03 SIGN-ON COMPLETED ! NEXT DAY CYBERLIFE ON-LINE DID NOT COME UP ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOUND A CONVERSION PROGRAM HAD CORRUPTED THE HIGH VALUES RECORD OF THE POLICY\/PENDING FILES. THE LENGTH SB '1F' IN HEX LENGTH. CHECK BOTH THE CYBERLIFE LENGTH AND THE ACTUAL RECORD LENGTH. ",
  "SOLUTION": "FOUND GOOD RECORD IN BASE SYSTEM. COPIED THE RECORD OFF TO THE SIDE. TWEEKED IT TO HAVE THE PRODUCTION DATES AND SWITCHES SET. DELETED THE BAD HIGH VALUES RECORD FROM THE PRODUCTION FILE USING FIRE CALL AND DID A KEY TO KEY MOVE UNDER FIRE CALL TO MOVE IN THE REPAIRED RECORD. DID THIS FOR BOTH POLICY AND PENDING FILES. (KEY TO KEY MOVE JOB TEST.CL.DLCTOOLS(REPROKEY)). "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0130",
  "PROBLEM": "B37 - SPACE PROBLEM ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SEQUEN2 RAN OUT OF SPACE. LOOK AT WHERE SEQUEN2 FEEDS AND SEE IF THERE ARE OTHER SPACE INCREASE REQUIREMENTS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DOUBLE PRIMARY SPACE NEEDS ON SEQUEN2(300 TO 600) LOOK AT WHERE SEQUEN2 FEEDS AND SEE IF THERE ARE OTHER INCREASE SPACE REQUIREMENTS. THERE ARE INCREASE SOUTOUT FROM 300 TO 600 PRIMARY BLOCKS. RESTART CL$$0130 FROM THE TOP. DON'T WORRY THAT THE ACTIVITY FILE HAS BEEN RE-INITIALIZED FROM LAST NIGHT. THERE IS NO DATA BEING EXTRACTED FROM HERE ANYWAY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0860",
  "PROBLEM": "LOOPING IN PROGRAM. CHECK FOR Q.DA SIO'S. YOU SHOULD GET SOME CPU PROCESSING. FOR THIS STATMENT JOB AND THE AMOUNT OF PROCESSING NEEDED FOR PROJECTIONS, YOU HAVE TO WATCH THE SIO'S COME THROUGH FOR ABOUT 5-10 MINUTES TO MAKE SURE WHETER OR NOT YOU ARE GETTING ANY. IF NOT, CANCEL THE JOB. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SINCE OUTPUT FILE WAS CATLG,CATLG LOOKED AT LAST POLICY RECORD GENERATED IN FILE CL.CL$$0860.OTAGTHIS(-0). THIS IS YOUR SUSPECT POLICY. IEBGENER 2 VERSIONS OF CL.CL$$0860.SAPPH(-0). TAG FILE AS TEST.CL......#MMDD.BAD AND TEST.CL.....#MMDD.GOOD IN THE BAD FILE, DELETE ALL BUT THE POLICY WHICH LOOKS TO BE THE PROBLEM. IN THE GOOD FILE KEEP ALL BUT THE BAD POLICY. SET UP A RUN FOR CL$$0860.STEP0030 USING PRODUCTION DATASETS AND THE IINPUT01 POINTING TO THE BAD DATASET VERSION(TEST.CL.DLCJCL(CL$$0860)). IF THIS LOOPS, MOST LIKELY THIS IS THE PROBLEM POLICY. IF NOT, CONTINUE TO TEST TO FIND THE PROBLEM POLICY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "ONCE YOU HAVE THE PROBLEM POLICY AND HAVE SET IT ASIDE FROM THE FILE YOU WANT TO CONTINUE RUNNING WITH, USE THE FOLLOWING RESTARTS: RESTART=CL$$0860.STEP0030 \/\/STEP0030.IINPUT01 DD DSN=TEST.CL......#MMDD.GOOD,DISP=SHR \/\/STEP0040.SEQUEN DD DSN=TEST.CL.....#MMDD.GOOD,DISP=SHR "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0866",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC-7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOUND LAST POLICY WAS CAUSING PROBLEM BY LOOKING AT DUMP. RICK RESEARCHED PROBLEM POLICY AND FOUND THE POLICY WAS EXCEDING AN INTERNAL ARRAY SIZE REQUIREMENT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "STRIPPED THE LAST POLICY FROM THE CL$$0860.OTAGTHIS FILE AND HAD PCD RESTART FROM THE TOP. TO STRIP THE POLICY I COPIED THE PROD VERSION TO A TEST VERSION, STRIPPED THE POLICY AND PUT IN AN OVERRIDE TO STEP0010 INPUT FILE TO PICK UP THE EDITED FILE. RICK INCREASED THE ARRAY SIZE TO ALLOW THE PROBLEM POLICY TO BE FULLY PROCESSED. HE THEN COMPLETED THE PROBLEM POLICY PROCESS IN TEST USING PRODUCTION PAPER AND DELIVERED TO THE USERS. THE PROGRAM CHANGE WAS TO D7240080. THIS WILL BE TESTED AND MOVED TO PROD. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "PENDING POLICY 3465000040 WAS ABENDING ON 60D1 SCREEN ONLY. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED AT SEGMENTS REFERENCED IN THE PROGRAM. EVENTUALLY FOCUSED ON THE 33 BILLING INFO SEG. IT WAS HOSED, OVERLA LAYED WITH 67 SEGMENT INFO. ",
  "SOLUTION": "SINCE THE PENDING REC IS DELETED 2 YEARS FROM ISSUE AND THIS POLICY IS 1 YR 8 MONTHS OLD, DO NOTHING. THIS WAS ONE OF THE FIRST POLICIES WE PUT ON THE SYSTEM AND NO TELLING WHAT WE DID WRONG. LATER KATHY TOLD ME THAT SHE WAS GOING TO GO AHEAD AND DELETE THE PENDING RECORD AS THEY DID NOT NEED IT. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0012\/CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$0012 ENDED OK, BUT THE LITERAL 'NO ERRORS DETECTED' WAS NOT FOUND IN THE REPORT BY CONTROL-D. AS A RESULT, CL$$0100 WAS WAITING FOR THIS CONDITION TO START. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CHECKED CL$$0012 REPORT AND FOUND THAT THERE WERE INVALID DATE MESSAGES ON EACH FUND. 2 FF0018 - INPUT DATE RANGE INVALID LAST VALUATION DATE NOT LESS THAN LOW DA THE DATE RANGE IN CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES(0) WAS 03102000 03132000 THIS WAS THE PROBLEM. THE DATE RANGE SHOULD BE: 03112000 03132000 ",
  "SOLUTION": "USING FIRECALL, EDITED CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES(0) TO CORRECT THE DATE RANGE TO 03112000 03132000. RAN CL$$R012 FROM TOP RAN CL$$0012 FROM TOP FORCED CL$$010=2TO START ALL JOBS ENDED OK. MORE IMPORTANTLY, THE LITERAL, 'NO ERRORS DETECTED' WAS IN THE REPORT OUT OF CL$$0012. ACTION ITEM-WE NEED TO PUT SHOUT IN CL$$0012 SO THAT IF THIS CONDITION IS NOT MET, WE ARE CALLED RIGHT AWAY, RATHER THAN 11:30 WHEN CL$$0100 ISN'T RUNNING. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0127",
  "PROBLEM": "B37-04 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FILE DID NOT HAVE A UNIT=&DISK(SYSDA). FILE SPACE WAS OK. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RAN RESTORE JOB CL$$R127. OVERIDE TO ADD UNIT=&DISK AND RERAN CL$$0127 FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0860",
  "PROBLEM": "S322 U0000 (TIME OUT ERROR) ",
  "ANALYSIS": "BAD POLICY IN FILE CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT(0) CAUSED A LOOP AND TIMED OUT. POLICY ON WAIVER WILL CAUSE THIS TO LOOP. THERE IS AN ISSUE TO FIX THIS BUT WE WILL HAVE THIS PROBLEM UNTIL IT IS FIXED. TO TELL IF IT IS A POLICY ON WAIVER, YOU MUST LOOK AT THE POLICIES STATUS. IF IT IS A '32', THEN THIS WILL LOOP. BAD POLICY: 3361180682 ",
  "SOLUTION": "RERAN CL$$0860 FROM TOP. AFTER SIO STAYED AT ZERO INDICATING THE LOOP, CALLED PROD. CONTROL AND CANCEL JOB W\/ A DUMP. CREATED A BATCH JOB TEST.CL.DJNTOOLS (CL$$0860) WHICH WILL RUN FIRST TO STEPS. COPIED FILE ABOVE INTO A TEST FILE. RAN MY BATCH JOB THEN CANCELED WHEN I REACHED THE LOOP. LOOKED IN TEST JOB FILE TEST.CL.DJN.CL$$0860.SAPPH.XXXXXXXX AND THE LAST POLICY LISTED MATCHED ONE OF THE POLICIES IN THE DUMP. I DELETED THE POLICY IN TEST.CL.DJN.CL$$0100.AUDIT.XXXXXXX AND RERAN THE TEST JOB FROM THE TOP. JOB FINISHED FINE. WENT INTO FIRECALL AND DELETED THE POLICY IN CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT(0) AND HAD OPS RERUN FROM TOP NOTES: HOLD JOB SCHD1551 BEFORE 8:30 SO PARMDATE IS NOT UPDATED. AFTER CL$$0860 FINISHED OK, RELEASE JOB SCHD1551 BEFORE 11AM TO UPDATE PARMDATE. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "+CKUB01 SYSTEM MACRO, TO TRAP PROGRAM INTERRUPTS, +CKSN01 PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. PSW=078D1200 8860FC +CKUB03 CURRENT POLICY 3465002260 +CKSN02 ABENDING ELEMENT CKUBMVCH EPA=0860D6D0 OFFSE +IGZ015I A RECURSIVE CALL WAS ATTEMPTED TO A PROGRAM THA ACTIVE. IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT USER COMPLETION CODE=1015 TIME=13.45.09 SEQ=21481 CPU=0000 ASID=0028 PSW AT TIME OF ERROR 078D1200 8009CE9A ILC 2 INTC ACTIVE LOAD MODULE ADDRESS=00087600 OFFSET NAME=IGZCPCO DATA AT PSW 0009CE94 - 00181610 0A0D47F0 C0E84820 GPR 0-3 80000000 800003F7 000003F7 0023283C GPR 4-7 000A30F0 887ACED0 00232973 00232970 GPR 8-11 8006263C 887ACED0 0001B644 0008C448 GPR 12-15 8009CDC2 000A30A8 8009CE1E 887C4B30 END OF SYMPTOM DUMP -STEP=STEP0210 PGM=IKJEFT01 EXECUTED - COND CODE 001 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE POLICY NUMBER WHICH APPEARS ABOVE IS OF NO USE. THERE IS A POLICY PRIOR TO THIS ONE WHICH IS CAUSING THE JOB TO ABEND. PROBLEM IS THAT THERE IS NO QUICK WAY OF KNOWING EXACTLY WHICH ONE IT IS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "OPEN TEST.CL.CKAP01V.DEBUG.GXXXXV00 USING 3.4. MAX TO THE BOTTOM TO FIND THE POLICY WHICH THE JOB STOPS ON. (THIS IS NOT THE BAD POLICY.) TRY DELETING THE 2ND, 3RD, 4TH OR 5TH POLICY PRIOR. THIS CAN BE DONE ALL AT ONCE OR ONE AT A TIME TO TRY AND NARROW DOWN EXACTLY WHICH POLICY IS THE BAD ONE. DELETING THE POLICIES WILL HAVE TO BE DONE IN TEST.CL.VSAM.BASEOL. POLICY, AUXSEG1, ACTIVITY, AND HISTORY. IF WHEN TRYING TO DO THE PROCESS OF ELIMINATION, YOU MUST RUN *********** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** CL$$R060, CL$$RC30 AND CL$$0018 EACH TIME BEFORE YOU RERUN CL$$0100. ONCE YOU'VE FOUND THE BAD POLICY AND HAVE DELETED IT FROM POLICY, AUXSEG1, ACTIVITY, AND HISTORY, RUN *********** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** CL$$R060, CL$$RC30, CL$$0018, AND THEN CL$$0100 FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "B37-04 S0C1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SEQUEN DD RAN OUT OF SPACE IN STEP0020 WHICH CAUSED STEP0090 TO ALSO ABEND. NO NEED TO RUN RESTORE JOBS SINCE ALL THE STEPS AFTER STEP0090 FLUSHED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DOUBLED THE PRIMARY AND SECONDARY SPACE AND RERAN CL$$0030 FROM THE TOP. NO RESTORES. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$BIND",
  "PROBLEM": "CC8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "2 BAD PROGRAMS IS BIND. THIS IS COMMON. NEED TO PULL THE PROGRAMS OUT OF THE JOB. ",
  "SOLUTION": "FORCED OK "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0127",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC-7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "A DATE RECORD ON THE CL.VSAM.ACH.AUDIT.CONTROL FILE WAS NOT POPULATED. THIS IS A VSAM FILE THE USERS DO DIRECT ENTRY ON IN ORDER TO CROSS CHECK THE ACCURACY OF ACH TRANSACTIONS TRYING TO GO OUT THE DOOR. CL$$0120 GENERATES CYBERLIFES ACH TRANSACTIONS THOSE TRANSACTIONS COME INTO CL$$0127 AND GET CHECKED AGAINST THE CL.VSAM.ACH.AUDIT.CONTROL FILE TO MAKE SURE THE DRAFT IS TAKING PLACE WHEN THE USERS WANT IT TO. IF THE DATE OF THE DRAFT DOES NOT MATCH THE DATE IN THE CL.VSAM.ACH.AUDIT.CONTROL FILE, THEN THE DRAFT WILL ERROR AND THE DRAFT TRANSACTION WILL GO TO THE ERROR FILE. THE USERS WILL THEN BE ABLE TO REVIEW THE DRAFT AND DECIDE WHAT TO DO WITH IT. HOW DID I KNOW THIS WAS A DATE PROBLEM. I COMPILED THE PROGRAM AND TRACKED DOWN THE LAST EXECUTED STMT AND THE FIELD WITH THE PROBLEM AND COULD THEN SEE THE PROBLEM WAS RELATED TO A DATE FROM THE CL.VSAM.ACH AUDIT.CONTROL FILE....I THEN LOOKED AT THE RECORD THRU FILE MARVEL IN THE AUDIT CONTROL FILE AND COULD SEE THE NAME HAD LOW-VALUES AND SOME OTHER FIELDS WERE NOT POPULATED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "PLUG IN ANY OLD DATE...BUT NOT TODAYS DATE INTO THE CL.VSAM.ACH.AUDIT.CONTROL FILE, THIS WILL CAUSE THE TRANSACTION TO ERROR AND WILL GIVE THE USERS A CHANCE TO REVIEW THE DRAFT. IF WE PLUG IN TODAYS DATE THE DRAFT MIGHT GO OUT THE DOOR INCOMPLETE. SO, BEFORE THE FILE FIX COULD BE DONE, WE HAVE TO RUN CL$$R127 THEN FIX THE FILE, THEN RESTART CL$$0127 FROM THE TOP. LONG TERM SOLUTION: MAKE A PROGRAM CHANGE TO FORCE A DATE INTO THE DATE FIELD IF IT IS BLANK SO THE DRAFT WILL ERROR AND THE USERS CAN FIX IT....THIS WILL STOP THE PROGRAM FROM ABENDING. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "S322 - TIME OUT ERROR ",
  "ANALYSIS": "A TIME OUT IS CAUSED WHEN THE CPU FOR A PROCESS EXCEEDS THE TIME CARD ON THE JOB. DEFAULT IS 1 HOURS. NEEDED TO FIGURE OUT WHAT POLICY IS LOOPING. SO, *********** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** I HAD OPS RUN CL$$R060\/CL$$RC30. GO INTO 3.4 AND VIEW CL.CL$$0100.CKAP01V.DEBUG.GXXXXV00. THE LAST POLICY IS THE ONE THAT HAS THE PROBLEM. ******** OLD METHOD BEFORE THE DEBUG FILE (SKIP) ***** I HAD THEM RESTART CL$$0100 FROM THE TOP ONCE THE RESTORES WERE COMPLETE. I WATCHED THE JOB. ABOUT 15 MINUTES LATER...IT BEGAN TO LOOP. I HAD OPS CANCEL THE JOB WITH A DUMP. I HAD OPS RUN THE RESTORES AGAIN WHILE I EXAMINED THE DUMPS. USING THE LAST ENTRY ON THE TIME DRIVEN ERROR REGISTER I COULD SEE WE WERE AT LEASE INTO THE 3465 POLICY BLOCKS SO, IN THE DUMP, I DID A FIND ON 3465 AND THE FIRST POLICY I ENCOUNTERED.....TURNED OUT TO BE THE PROBLEM.. ****************************************************** UPDATED TEST.CL.DATA(SUSPEND) TO USE IDENTIFIED POLICY. AFTER THE RESTORES WERE DONE, WENT INTO FIRECALL AND RAN TEST.CL.TOOLS(SUSPEND). THIS SHOWS THE STATUS OF THE POLICY BEFORE THE SUSPEND...SUSPENDS IT AND SHOWS THE STATUS OF THE POLICY AFTER. IF THE POLICY SUSPENDS OKAY AND WAS NOT SUSPENDED PRIOR TO THIS PROCESS......YOU ARE OKAY TO START CL$$0100 FROM THE TOP. IN THIS CASE, THE POLICY IN QUESTION WAS ALREADY SUSPENDED. THIS LEFT DOUBT IN OUR MINDS THAT WE HAD THE CORRECT POLICY. SO, WE PUT DISPLAYS IN CKAP01V TO SHOW US EACH POLICY THAT WAS BEING PROCESSED. RAN CL$$0100 AND WHEN IT LOOPED CANCELLED IT....IT TAGGED THE SAME POLICY THAT WAS ALREADY SUSPENDED AS BEING THE PROBLEM. WE HAD NOT CHOICE BUT TO DROP THE POLICY. HAD OPS RUN THE RESTORES,,,,AGAIN.....AFTER ALL WAS RESTORED, WENT IN AND DROPPED THE POLICY FROM ACTIVITY, POLICY, AUXSEG1....BECAUSE IT WAS A FAIRLY NEW POLICY...DID NOT DROP FROM THE HISTORY. THIS WORKED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "ALOT OF GUESS WORK. SOME TRIAL AND ERROR. WATCH THE CLOCK....DON'T GO PAST 1:00AM WITHOUT GETTING SOMEONE ELSE INVOLVED TO HELP...UNLESS YOU ARE SURE WHAT YOU ARE DOING IS GOING TO WORK. TWO HEADS ARE BETTER THAN ONE. TIPS: -DON'T WORRY ABOUT THE SYSPDUMP. THIS IS FOR THE SYSTEM MANAGED CHECK ROUTINES. -THE SYSUDUMP MIGHT HAVE POLICY NUMBERS IN IT THAT HAVE NOT EVEN BEEN PROCESSED YET. WE NEED TO IMPROVE THIS ISSUE WITH SOME KIND OF POLICY PROCESSING AUDIT TRAIL. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC-1 CC12 THIS PROBLEM WAS ON THE POLICY MASTER NOT THE PENDING FILE. THIS MEANS DROP IS NOT DESIREABLE. WE NEED TO SEE IF WE CAN FIX. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DID A FIND ON SQL IN DUMP AND SAW SQL=100. THIS IS AN INDICATION THAT THERE IS A PROBLEM WITH CLIENT RETRIEVAL. A 100 MEANS NO ROW FOUND. IF YOU PAGE DOWN YOU WILL SEE DATA THAT LOOKS LIKE THE FOLLOWING CKETRGET...................M..MQ ......89..B.......�............. 00 .. ....YNH000.....S$.3360190783. ..........................2...CK CSTGETSELECT CISLCA THIS GIVES ME THE POLICY NUMBER WITH THE PROBLEM AND WHAT CLIENT TABLE HAD THE PROBLEM(CISLCA). I LOOKED IN CKCSTGET IN PAN.CL.PPANLIB AND DID A FIND ON CISLCA. I DID REFINDS UNTIL I CAME UPON THE SQL DOING THE SELECT FOR THESE DATA ELEMENTS. THIS SQL GIVES ME THE TABLE NAME THE RETRIEVAL FAILED ON(IE: CLIENT ADDRESS). I TOOK THE POLICY NUMBER INTO =DB2(OPTION D TO POINT TO DB2P). I PULLED UP UNDER OPTION 1 THE SQL TEST.CL.DLCJCL(SQL$LVL1). I PLUG IN THE POLICY NUMBER 3360190783 AS FOLLOWS:TCH_OBJECT_KEY = '003360190783' THIS WILL RETURN ROWS FROM THE CLT_OBJECT_RELATION. GET THE CLIENT_ID AND THE ADR_SEQ COMBINATIONS FROM THE RETURN ROWS. THIS INFORMATION YOU WILL USE IN THE NEXT QUERY. PF3 OUT OF THIS QUERY AND PULL UP SQL$LVL2. PAGE DOWN TO THE TABLE SELECT CLADMIN.CLT_ADR_RELATION_V. AND FILL OUT THE CLIENT_ID = TO YOURS...DON'T WORRY ABOUT THE ADR_SEQ..YOU WILL GET ALL ADR_SEQ RELATED TO THE CLIENT_ID AND YOU CAN FIND THE ONE YOU MATCH. FROM THIS RESULT, GET THE ADR_ID. YOU WILL USE THIS IN THE NEXT YOU ROW....IF NOT...YOU PROBABLY HAVE YOUR PROBLEM. IF SO, CHECK EFFECTIVE AND EXPIRATION DATES. IF THE CYCLE DATA IS OUTSIDE OF THE EFF\/EXP DATE, THAT IS THE PROBLEM IF ALL LOOKS GOOD...TAKE YOUR NEXT CLIENT_ID AND CHECK EACH OF THEM UNTIL YOU FIND THE PROBLEM. WHAT I FOUND WAS THAT FOR THE CLIENT_ID\/ADR_SEQ WHICH PROVIDED ME AN ADR_ID.....THE ADR_ID DID NOT EXIST WHEN I RAN SQL$LVL3. I THEN WENT BACK TO SQL$LVL2 AND CHANGED THE CLADMIN.CLT_ADR_RELATION_V SELECT TO PULL ALL ROWS WHICH REFERENCED THE MISSING ADR_ID. THIS WILL LET ME KNOW IF OTHER POLICIES ARE IMPACTED BY THIS MISSING CLIENT ADDRESS. THERE WERE NO OTHER POLICIES IMPACTED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "SINCE I DO NOT HAVE AN ADDRESS FOR THE ABOVE DEFINED CLIENTS. I AM GOING TO CHANGE THE CLIENT_ID\/ADR_SEQ TO HAVE AN ADDRESS I KNOW EXISTS. THE USERS WILL BE ABLE TO FIX THIS TO THE CORRECT ADDRESS TOMORROW. I USED SQL$FIX2 TO RUN 3 QUERIES. THE FIRST ONE IS A SELECT, THE SECOND ONE IS A CHANGE AND THE THIRD ONE IS A SELECT AGAIN. THE FIRST QUERY SHOWS ME THE PROBLEM ROWS, THE SECOND ONE WILL CHANGE THE DATA ON THE CLT_ADR_RELATION TO THE NEW ADR_ID THAT EXISTS AND THE THIRD QUERY WILL ALLOW ME TO SEE THE ROWS WHICH USE THE NEW ADR_ID. NONE OF THIS IS CHANGED UNTIL YOU PF3 AND DO A COMMIT....IF YOU HAVE DOUBT ABOUT THE RESULTS, MAKE SURE YOU DO A ROLLBACK WHEN YOU EXIT THE QUERY. IF THE RESULTS ARE AS EXPECTED....YOU CAN EXIT AND COMMIT. TIPS: THIS IS A GOOD IDEA TO MAKE THE CHANGE AFTER THE CLIENT BACKUPS HAVE BEEN TAKEN CL$$0010 IF YOU MESS SOMETHING UP, A RESTORE CAN BE DONE TO RECOVER. - ALSO, IF YOU RUN YOUR UPDATE QUERY WITH THE UPDATE PORTION COMMENTED OUT, IT WILL GIVE YOU SOME GUIDELINES ON WHAT ROWS ALREADY EXIST BEFORE YOU ATTEMPT AN UPDATE AND IS VERY HELPFUL TO DETERMINE IF YOU ONLY IMPACTED WHAT YOU INTENDED TO IMPACT. - ALSO, I CHOOSE TO RE-RUN CL$$0011 AFTER THIS OPERATION TO MAKE SURE I HAVE NOT HAD NEGATIVE IMPACT ON OTHER POLICIES. - CAUTION CAN PAY OFF ON CLIENT ISSUES. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0120",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC 7 ABEND IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=0C7 REASON CODE=00000007 TIME=12.29.28 SEQ=23893 CPU=0000 ASID=0028 PSW AT TIME OF ERROR 078D0000 88505972 ILC 6 INTC ACTIVE LOAD MODULE ADDRESS=085006B8 OFFSET NAME=CKBSFMCT DATA AT PSW 0850596C - FA549112 D249940F 9112960F GPR 0-3 08655DD4 08655E78 085404B8 086A5028 GPR 4-7 0869D028 00000000 086A6028 00000000 GPR 8-11 08540640 0869C028 08504BBC 08504DCA GPR 12-15 08504BB0 08655C30 88505850 00000000 END OF SYMPTOM DUMP ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOUND THE SAME PROBLEM IN THE BOMBLOG WHICH LED ME TO LOOK AT THE TRANSIT ROUTING NUMBER. I OPENED THIS JOB IN Q.ST AND AT THE BOTTOM IS SEQUEN5 WHICH SHOWED A POLICY WITH THE TR NUMBER OF 2222. ",
  "SOLUTION": "WENT INTO TEST.CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.BILLEXTS AND DID A SEARCH ON THE POLICY NUMBER. FOUND 2222 AND EDITED IT WITH A VALID TR NUMBER. SAVED AND RERAN CL$$0120 FROM THE TOP. HAD KATHY HANNAH'S AREA CHANGE THE POLICY'S TR NUMBER ONCE TEST WAS BACK UP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$RC30",
  "PROBLEM": "ORIGINAL PROBLEM OCCURED WITH CL$$0100.STEP1000, WHICH WAS A PREVIOUSLY DOCUMENTED PROBLEM RELATED TO AUTO TRX REGISTER. THIS HAPPENS WHEN A 53 SEG IS DELETED AND 57 REMAINS OR VICE VERSA. IF YOU HAVE ONE YOU NEED TO HAVE BOTH. SO, ALL WE NEEDED TO DO WAS FOLLOW THE DOCUMENTED RESTARTS: SKIP STEP FOR TONIGHT AND FIGURE OUT LATER. RUN CL$$R060 *********** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** RUN CL$$RC30 WITH CORRECT GDG OVERRIDE RUN CL$$0100 WITH FOLLOWING STEP OVERRIDE ON THE EXEC CARD TO SKIP THE STEP. (ALSO PUT COMMA AFTER EXEC) \/\/ COND.STEP1000=(0,LE) R060 ENDED OK, BUT RC30 ABENDED WITH A B37-04 SPACE PROBLEM. THIS CREATED A NEW PROBLEM. WHEN A DB2 UTILITY ABENDS, THE DB2 UTILITY NEEDS TO BE RESET TO BY OUR DB2 ADMINISTRATOR ON CALL. CALLED TIM NOONE. HE RESET THE UTILITY. I UPPED THE SPACE ON SYSUT1 FROM (50,10) TO (100,20) AND RERAN RC30. HOWEVER, THE JOB ABENDED AGAIN. FORTUNATELY, TIM WAS ONLINE AND RESET THE UTILITY AGAIN. THE JOB ABENDED BECAUSE AT ABEND TIME, THE WORK DATASETS ARE CATALOGUED AND THE MOD OPTION IS USED IN THE DISP...SO THE NEXT RUN OF THE JOB CAUSES THE NEW WORK TO APPEND TO THE PRIOR RUN. SO, WE WERE OUT OF SPACE BEFORE WE STARTED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SEVERAL ATTEMPTS, TIM PITCHED IN AND STARTED DELETING LEFTOVER\/HANGING SORTWKXX FILES WHICH WERE ADDING TO THE SIZE OF THE FILE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DELETING THE RETAINED SORTWKXX FILES AND UPPING THE SPACE ON SYSUT1, RC30 ENDED OK. NEXT WE RAN CL$$0100 WITH SKIP OVERRIDE IN PLACE. WE LATER DETERMINED TO RESTART RC30... DAN BLECK HAS AN OVERRIDE FROM STEVE KLOTZ TO RESET THE DATABASE ACTIVITY SO WE DON'T HAVE TO CALL THE DBA(IE: TIM NOONE OR STEVE KLOTZ). LOOK AT TEST.CL.DLCTOOLS( DB2RESET). MAKE SURE YOU POINT AT DB2P AND REFERENCE THE STEPNAME THAT HAD THE PROBLEM. TO CONFIRM YOU HAVE THE THE CORRECT NAME TO RESET...LOOK IN THE SYSOUT ON THE STEP THAT WENT DOWN ... THE NAME IS AFTER THE UTILID= STATEMENT. THEN THE OVERRIDE TO INCREASE SPACE CAN BE PUT IN AND WILL RUN SUCCESSFULLY. THIS JOB MIGHT HAVE TO BE RUN UNDER FIRECALL....WE HAVE NOT TRIED IT IN PRODUCTION YET. THERE IS AN ASSIGNED PROJECT TO IMPLEMENT AND IMPROVE THE WAY WE HANDLE THIS ISSUE TODAY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC 1 ON BOTH PENDING AND POLICY WITH AN SQL CODE -811. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SOMEONE ATTACHED ANOTHER ADDRESS TO 2543202530 ON WEDNESDAY AND AP APPARENTLY DID NOT DETACH THE OLD ADDRESS. ANYWAY, WE HAD A DUPLICATE ADDRESS ROW ERROR LAST NIGHT. I DROPPED 3 DUPLICATE ROWS EFFECTIVE 12-22-1999(INSURED, OWNER, PAYOR). DAVID, THE RESULTS OF THE SPUFI I RAN TO DELETE THE ROWS CAN BE VIEWED IN TEST.CL.SPUFI.OUTPUT. IF THEY MESS WITH THIS POLICY TODAY I WOULD RECOMMEND RUNNING A RECORD PRINT TO MAKE SURE THE CLIENT ROWS ARE OK. MAYBE SOMEONE SHOULD GO DOWN AND MAKE SURE THEY ARE DOING THE ADDRESS CHANGE WITH THE RIGHT PROCEDURE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "AFTER ROWS WERE DROPPED, WE RAN CL$$0011 OUT OF TEST.CL.JCLLIB. JOB ENDED OK, SO WE FORCED CL$$011 AS ENDED OK IN PRODUCTION. CYCLE CONTINUED ON. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0860",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP=STEP0030 PGM=IKJEFT01 EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=0C7 REASON CODE=00000007 TIME=23.16.14 SEQ=02951 CPU=0000 ASID=0096 I DIALED IN THIS MORNING TO CHECK ON SOMETHING AND NOTICED THAT CL$$0860 WAS DOWN. WE PROBABLY RECEIVED THE NON-CALL EMAIL VIA NOTES. I TOOK A LOOK AT IT AND SAW THAT IT WAS A PROBLEM WE HAVE SEEN BEFORE. THIS IS A DOCUMENTED ISSUE. IF NO '50' RECORD COMES THRU IT ABENDS IN D7240150. I DROPPED THE OFFENDING EXTRACT AND SET UP A JOB TO RERUN STEP0030 UNDER MY ID (SUBMITTED VIA FIRECALL), P1DMB860, SUBMITTED AROUND 6:30AM. SINCE IT IS PRODUCING STATEMENT EXTRACTS FOR 3 DAYS (SAT - MON) I WANTED TO GET IT RESTARTED EARLY. THE RERUN GETS MORE COMPLICATED AFTER THE PARMDATES CHANGE LATER THIS MORNING. IF SOMEONE CAN KEEP AN EYE ON MY JOB AND CHECK IT WHEN IT GETS DONE, AS LONG AS IT GETS A CONDITION CODE ZERO IN STEP0030 YOU CAN CALL OPS OR PCD AND THEM FORCE CL$$0860-ENDED-OK IN CONTROL\/M. THAT WILL RELEASE 865, 866 AND 900. ",
  "SOLUTION": "JOB ENDED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0830",
  "PROBLEM": "-STEP=STEP0060 PGM=IKJEFT01 EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 RC IKJ56644I NO VALID TSO USERID, DEFAULT USER ATTRIBUTES US ACF0C038 ACF2 LOGONID ATTRIBUTES HAVE REPLACED DEFAULT US READY DSN SYSTEM(DB2P) MAXIMUM NUMBER OF DB2 USERS REACHED. YOUR RETRY COUNT IS READY RUN PROGRAM(D724CDS4) PLAN(CLCISBCH) INVALID KEYWORD, PLAN(CLCISBCH) READY END READY END ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PROGRAM AND JOB HAD NOT BEEN RECENTLY CHANGED. I DID A JOB SCAN, JOB WAS FINE. I CHECKED ALL FILES THAT WERE CREATED, THEY ALL LOOKED FINE. CHECKED WITH DAVE. MESSAGE APPEARS TO BE A DB2 MANAGEMEN SYSTEM TYPE MESSAGE. MAXING OUT ON # USERS COULD BE A CONFLICT WITH CYBERTEK AND PAYROLL. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTART JOB FROM TOP. JOB ENDED OK. I TALKED TO TIM NOONE TODAY ABOUT THE PRODUCTION PROBLEM WITH THE USER LIMITATION. OUR DATABASE ENVIRONMENT WAS SET UP TO ONLY ALLOW 5 BATCH JOBS ACCESS TO DB2 AT A TIME. THIS WOULD BE COMPETITION BETWEEN US AND CYBORG(PAYROLL). TIM SAID HE CAN EXPAND THIS EASILY THIS WEEKEND DURING THE RE-CYCLE OF DB2. HE IS GOING TO GROW THIS TO 20. HE DOES NOT FEEL THIS WILL HAVE ANY NEGATIVE EFFECTS TO RESPONSE AND SUCH. THIS SHOULD GET RID OF THIS PROBLEM FOR US. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "THE BASE SYSTEM STATEMENT EXTRACT PROGRAM LOOPED. THE JOB STEP EVENTUALLY TIMED OUT AND CANCELLED WITHOUT A DUMP. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS IS TO DOCUMENT WHAT HAPPENED LAST NIGHT... THIS IS TO DOCUMENT WHAT HAPPENED LAST NIGHT... ... CL$$0100.STEP0690 LOOPED, JOB CANCELLED WITHOUT A DUMP. THIS IS THE BASE SYSTEM STATEMENT EXTRACT PROGRAM. ... CL$$R060, RC30, R012, 0012 (NOTE R012 & 0012 NOT NECESSARY) ... 100 RERAN, THIS TIME STEP0690 CANCELLED WITH A DUMP. ... 4:00 AM - DECIDED TO FORCE 100 OK IN ORDER TO GET THE CYCLE DONE AND FEED INTERFACING SYSTEMS. ... HELD 860, 865, 866 ... RELEASED 810, 820, 830, 845, 850 SINCE THEY WERE WAITING ON CL$$IIAM WHICH WAS WAITING ON CL$$ABR1, WHICH WAS NOT EXPECTED TO FINISH BEFORE 5:30 AM. THIS ALLOWED INTERFACING SYSTEMS TO PROCEED. ... I CREATED A CL$$0100 PROC ON TEST.CL.PROD.PROCLIB THAT BASICALLY CONTAINS ALL STEPS AFTER THE STATEMENT EXTRACT STEPS IN 100 EXCEPT THE LAST TWO STEPS, WHICH PRINT THE ERROR REGISTER BY TEAM ID. WE CAN'T RUN STEP0950 BECAUSE IT USES A TEMP FILE OUT OF STEP0210 RUNNING THE REMAINDER OF 100 ALLOWED THE REMAINING REPORTS TO AND THE DB2 IMAGE COPIES TO BE CREATED. ... HAD OPS PUT IN AN OVERRIDE TO RUN THE 100 JOB MENTIONED ABOVE. ... RELEASED CL$$ABR2, WHICH WAS WAITING ON 900. ",
  "SOLUTION": "IN THE SHORT RUN, THE ABOVE ANALYIS DESCRIBES HOW WE GOT THROUGH THE CYCLE. 07:37AM ... I FOUND POLICY 3361332964 IN THE DUMP. ... I DROPPED IT FROM THE INPUT TO CL$$0100.STEP0690 AND RAN STEP0690 WITH A TEST JOB (USING PROD FILES). ... I THEN RENAMED THE OUTPUT STATEMENT EXTRACT FILE TO THE PRODUCTION DSN USING FIRECALL. ... I CALLED PCD AND TOLD THEM TO REMOVE THE HOLD FROM 860, 865 AND 866. 860 IS RUNNING NOW. IN THE LONG RUN, WE HAVE MADE A PROC CHANGE TO MOVE STEPS0680-0700 FROM CL$$0100 TO THE END OF CL$$0860. THESE STEPS WERE DETERMINED NON-CRITICAL AND SHOULD NOT HOLD UP CL$$0100 FROM COMPLETING. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "A POLICY WAS ADDED TO THE PRODUCTION WORLD BY MISTAKE WE NEEDED TO REMOVE ALL REMENENCE OF THE POLICY ",
  "SOLUTION": "A HOLD ON CL$$0012\/CL$$0015\/CL$$0020 .ALLOW BACKUPS TO HAPPEN(CL$$0010) THEN DELETE THE POLICY FROM THE FOLLOWING FILES CL.VSAM.BASEOL.PENDING AUXSEG1 POLICY AUXSEG2 ACTIVITY DPFS1\/DPFS2\/DPFS3 .RELEASE OUR HOLD ON CL$$0012\/CL$$0015\/CL$$0020 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0126",
  "PROBLEM": "B37 - SPACE ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE OUTPUT DATASET IN STEP0040 NEEDED TO HAVE THE SPACE PARAMETER INCREASED ",
  "SOLUTION": "I GAVE OPS AN OVERRIDE TO DOUBLE THE PRIMARY SPACE \/\/STEP0040.OXREFILE DD SPACE=(8900,(400,40),RLSE) I ALSO TOLD THEM TO RESTART IN JSTEP010.STEP0040. THEY TRIED TO USE THE CONTROL-R AND IT FAILED TWICE. THEY HAD TO ADD RESTART=JSTEP010.STEP0040, TO THE JOB CARD TO GET THE JOB TO RUN "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0060",
  "PROBLEM": "TAPE DRIVE FAILURE ",
  "ANALYSIS": "NONE ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTART JOB FROM THE TOP "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "CC12 USER COMPLETION CODE=0001 +CKUB01 SYSTEM MACRO, TO TRAP PROGRAM INTERRUPTS, + A 357 2 AP0357 - ALL FUNDS HAVE NOT BEEN VERIFIED UBMC00 +- - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED AT CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES(-0) TO SEE IF I COULD SEE ANYTHING WRONG WITH THE DATES. NOTICED THAT THE DATES WERE SET UP FOR A 1 DAY CYCLE WHEN ON MONDAY, THEY SHOULD BE SETUP FOR SATURDAY THRU MONDAY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "BEGAN RESTORES OF CL$$0060....WHILE THAT WAS RUNNING *********** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** I LOOKED UP THE GDG NEEDED FOR CL$$RC30 RESTORES. GAVE INSTRUCTIONS TO HAVE CL$$RC30 RUN WITH CORRECT GDG AFTER CL$$0060 WAS DONE. I THEN GAVE INSTRUCTIONS TO RUN CL$$RSTR TWICE. EACH TIME I HAD THEM OVERRIDE THE SELECT STATEMENT TO THE FOLLOWING: SELECT DSN=CL.VSAM.BASEOL.FUNDVAL SELECT DSN=CL.VSAM.BASER.DATECNTL THESE RESTORES ARE OUT OF CL.CL$$0010.ACF(-0). I COULD HAVE DONE THIS IN 1 JOB SUBMISSION BY HAVING BOTH THESE SELECTS ADDED...BUT I WANTED TO KEEP THINGS AS SIMPLE AS I COULD. IT IS IMPORTANT TO RUN THE RESTORES OUT OF CL$$0010 AFTER THE RESTORES OUT OF CL$$0060. I THEN WENT INTO FIRECALL AND PULLED UP CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES(-0) TO FIX THE DATES. COL 15 HAS A DATE MMDDCCYY AND COL 23 HAS A DATE MMDDCCYY. THE FIRST RECORD NEEDS COL 15 TO BE THE CURRENT CYCLE DATE. ALL THE RECORDS FOLLOWING NEED TO HAVE COL 23 AS THE CURRENT CYCLE DATE. THE CURRENT CYCLE DATE CAN BE FOUND IN PROD.CL.CARDLIB (PARMDATE). FOR RECORDS 2.....END IN COLUMN 15, WE NEED TO HAVE 1)1 DAY CYCLE - CURRENT CYCLE DATE 2)ALL OTHER CYCLES - DAY AFTER THE LAST DATE WE POSTED FUND VALUES. YOU CAN TELL THIS BY LOOKING IN THE CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES(-1) TO SEE WHAT THE CURRENT DATE IS IN COL 15 ON 1ST RECORD. THEN ADD 1 DAY. AFTER ALL RESTORES ARE DONE... RE-RUN CL$$0012...WHEN THAT IS DONE RE-RUN CL$$0100. *NOTE* LOOK FOR A JOB CALLED CL$$R012. IF THIS EXISTS *********** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** YOU CAN RUN IT AFTER CL$$0060\/CL$$RC30 TO DO THE RESTORES FOR RE-RUNNING CL$$0012. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0040",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC-4 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOUND THE MESSAGE 'INVALID USER ID PASSED TO CKTBLOCT'. RAN TEST.CL.TOOLS(DROPACT1) TO PULL OFF POLICY ACTIVITY FILE AND RERAN FROM THE TOP. STILL ABENDED ONE ACTIVITY RECORD WAS STILL HANGING. MANUALLY DELETED RERAN FROM THE TOP. COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. MIBX TRANSACTION WAS THE CAUSE. TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$T004B) CAN BE USED TO RUN THE FILE INSTEAD OF RUNNING IN PROD. W MEDLEY-DAVIS 10\/10\/06 ANALYSIS: FOUND THE MESSAGE 'INVALID USER ID PASSED TO CKTBLOCT'. FOUND THAT WE HAD 2 RECORDS WITH BAD. RAN A WAAPD TO PULL OFF THE MESSED UP RECORDS FROM THE ACTIVITY FILE AND RERAN FROM THE TOP. S JEFFS 12\/24\/02 DID A FIND IN THE DUMP ON SEQUEN2 TO GET CURRENT AND PRIOR RECORD. THE POLICY NUMBER WAS THE SAME ON BOTH. RAN TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$T0040) TO CREATE MY FLAT FILE FOR INPUT TO STEP0120. I THEN WAS ABLE TO GO INTO TEST.CL.CL$T0040.TRANSRT AND DELETE THE SUSPECT POLICY...THEN UNCOMMENT THE RESTART TO STEP0120 SO YOU RUN THE CHANGED FILE THROUGH STEP0120. YOU CAN CONTINUE THIS PROCESS UNTIL YOU GET ALL THE BAD POLICIES CLEARED OUT. IN THIS PARTICULAR NIGHTS PROCESSING, CL$T0040 WAS DYING ON A BUNCH OF POLICIES. FIRST A BUNCH OF IVA THEN SOME UL STARTED SHOWING UP...I WAS ONLY 500 TRANSACTIONS INTO A 10,000 TRANSACTION FILE...THERE MUST BE SOMETHING ELSE GOING WRONG. I CHECKED DATES, I CHECKED FOR PROC CHANGES OR PROGRAM CHANGES...NONE I THEN DROPPED ALL TRANSACTIONS DOWN TO THE LAST POLICY I HAD DETERMINED I NEEDED TO DROP. I LEFT THE TRANSACTION THE LAST RUN HAD TOLD ME I NEEDED TO DROP. THE JOB WORKED. SO, THE POLICIES BEING TAGGED AS BAD IN THE DUMP WERE NOT THE PROBLEM. I RE-RAN CL$T0040 FROM THE TOP WITH THE RESTART COMMENTED BACK OUT. THEN I DROPPED ALL TRANSACTIONS DOWN TO THE FIRST POLICY I HAD TO DROP. THE JOB WORKED. ALL THIS TELLS ME THERE IS SOME TRANSACTION THAT HAS GARBAGE LEFT OVER AND IS IMPACTING POLICIES ON DOWN IN THE FILE. I RE-RAN CL$T0040 FROM THE TOP AGAIN...NO RESTART. BEGAN DROPPING GROUPS OF RECORDS FROM THE TOP OF TEST.CL.CL$T0040.TRANSRT AND RUNNING CL$T0040 IN STEP0120....UNTIL THE ABENDS STOPPED..THEN I KNEW THE PROBLEM TRANSACTION WAS IN THAT GROUP. THEN SHRINK THAT GROUP UNTIL YOU ISOLATE THE TRANSACTIONS. IN MY CASE....IT WAS 1000 TRANSACTION ON POLICY AUTO AUTO IS A POLICY THE SYSTEM USES TO RESERVE OR CONTROL THE ASSIGNMENT OF THE NEXT POLICY NUMBER THROUGH THE AUTOMATIC POLICY NUMBER ASSIGNMENT PROCESS. ANALYSIS: 11\/30\/2009 DID A FIND IN THE DUMP ON SEQUEN2 TO GET CURRENT. ALSO HAVE 4 SPACE PROBLEMS (OPS HANDLED THESE) ",
  "SOLUTION": "USING FIRECALL, RAN TEST.CL.TOOLS(DROPACT1) TO DROP THE CURRENT RECORD FOR 2052384790. LATER FOUND 2 MORE RECORDS AND DELETED THEM ALSO RECORDS = 2052385100 & 3465115850 NOTE;;;;; JOB TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$T0040) IS NOT 0801 READY (SEE SOLUTIONS BELOW). SOLUTION: ONCE I HAD THE TRANSACTIONS I NEEDED TO DROP. PUT A HOLD ON CL$$0040...I KNEW IN ADVANCE THIS PROBLEM WAS GOING TO HAPPEN....GO INTO CL.VSAM.BASEOL.ACTIVITY AND DELETE THE TRANSACTIONS YOU NEED TO. THEN LET CL$$0040 GO...IF THE CL$$0040 WAS ALREADY DOWN..YOU CAN RE-START FROM THE TOP AND LET OPS KNOW THAT THEY WILL GET A CC8 IN STEP0010. SOLUTION: 12-08-06 RAN TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$T0040) TO CREATE FILE TEST.CL.CL$T0040.TRANSRT TO INPUT AS DD SEQUEN2 IN STEP0120. DELETED THE OFFENDING POLICY AND RESTARTED CL$$0040 IN STEP0120 WITH THE DD OVERRIDE. NO CLEAN UP WAS NEEDED. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0860",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC-7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB IS NON CALLABLE....SO, I GOT THIS FIRST THING IN THE MORNING. FIRST THING I DID WAS LOOK IN CL.JOBS.ON.SCHEDULE TO SEE WHAT JOB WAS DOWN. I THEN WENT TO THE DUMP FOR THE JOB AND MAXED TO THE BOTTOM. THEN PAGING UP, I FOUND THE CURRENT AND PREVIOUS RECORDS PROCESSED FOR IINPUT DD NAME. I KNEW IT WOULD BE ONE OF THESE 2 POLICIES WHICH CAUSED THE PROBLEM. I RAN AN IEBGENER TO MAKE 2 COPIES OF THE PRODUCTION FILE. ONE I COULD WORK WITH AND ONE I COULD HAVE AS A FULL BACKUP IN CASE I WANTED TO GO BACK TO IT LATER. I DROPPED THE POLICY TAGGED AS PREVIOUS FIRST OUT OF MY BACKUP FILE. I THEN RAN A JOB I HAVE SETUP TEST.CL.DLCJCL(CL$$0860) WITH THE FILE I DROPPED THE RECORD FROM AS INPUT....THERE ARE MANY OTHER CHANGES REQUIRED TO THIS JOB TO RUN IT AGAINST PRODUCTION...IT IS SETUP FOR TEST. THIS RUN WORKED. THE PROBLEM POLICY HAD PRODUCED MULTIPLE '01' TYPE RECORDS IN COL '26' OF THE FILE...IT SHOULD ONLY HAVE 1 '01' RECORD TYPE. THE FILE TO DROP FROM IS CL.CL$$0100.STEP0690.SAPPH(-0) ",
  "SOLUTION": "WENT INTO PRODUCTION AND DROPPED THE POLICY WHICH WAS DETERMINED TO BE THE PROBLEM IN THE ABOVE PROCESS. DROP FROM CL.CL$$0100.STEP0690.SAPPH(-0) 2453204070. HAD THE JOB RESTARTED FROM THE TOP. NOTIFIED KATHY HANNAH OF POLICY DROP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0126",
  "PROBLEM": "CC12 IDC3302I ACTION ERROR ON CL.VSAM.ACH.CONTROL.XREF IDC3314I **RECORD OUT OF SEQUENCE - KEY FOLLOWS: 000000 F4F0F0F1 F0F2F5F1 F9F9F9F1 F0F0F7F3 F4F6F5F0 F0F7F5F5 F0 IDC31467I MAXIMUM ERROR LIMIT REACHED. IDC0005I NUMBER OF RECORDS PROCESSED WAS 28567 IDC3003I FUNCTION TERMINATED. CONDITION CODE IS 12 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE MAXIMUM ERROR LIMIT REACHED TELLS ME THAT THE VSAM BEING LOADED WAS NOT COMPLETELY LOADED BEFORE THE IDCAMS ENDED. THE RECORD OUT OF SEQUENCE IS MOST LIKELY A DUPLICATE RECORD. THE KEY IS 7 DIGIT CONTROL #, DATE CCCCMMDD, 10 DIGIT POLICY #, 2 DIGIT SEQUENCE. THE RECORD OUT OF SEQUENCE ABOVE WILL GIVE YOU THE POLICY NUMBER WHICH IS HAVING THE PROBLEM...ALSO THE CONTROL # CAN BE USED TO TRACK THE RECORDS. IF YOU LOOK AT CL.CL$$0120.STEP0090.FM01FM02(-0), YOU CAN FIND THE CONTROL # OR POLICY AND SEE HOW MANY RECORDS EXIST IF IT EXCEDES 99, THEN THE SEQUENCE IS GOING TO GO OVER THE 2 DIGIT SEQUENCE NUMBER. ",
  "SOLUTION": "I HAD CL$$0126\/CL$$0127 HELD AND HAD THE DEPENDENCIES SATISFIED ON CL$$0150 SO THE CYCLE COULD CONTINUE. SOME OF THE SIDE EFFECTS OF HOLDING THESE JOBS 1)THEY MUST COMPLETE PRIOR TO 10:30AM THE NEXT DAY TO SUPPORT THE BANK FILE 2)CICS USES MOST OF THE ACH VSAM FILES 3)OUR USER CONTACT FOR THE HOLD UP IS LINDA.WILLIAMS(1430). IN THIS PROBLEM, THERE WERE 174 BILLING PERIODS ALL GENERATED AT ONCE. THE POLICY WAS BILLED OUT TO 2014 BY MISTAKE. IT WAS DECIDED TO DROP THE BILLING TRANSACTIONS. WE DROPPED ALL REFERENCES TO THE CONTROL NUMBER(4001025) FROM CL.CL$$0120.STEP0090.FM01FM02(-0). WE ALSO DROPPED REFERENCES TO THE CONTROL # FROM CL.ACH.BANK.EXTS(-0) WE RESTARTED CL$$0126 IN JSTEP010.STEP0020 WITH SYMBOLIC GENOT='(-0)'. THEN CL$$0127 TOOK OFF. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0150",
  "PROBLEM": "SB37 - SPACE S04E - DUPLICATE UTILID FOUND IN SYSUTIL ",
  "ANALYSIS": "3.4 ON CL.BASEB.CISBMAIN...SHIFT LEFT WILL SHOW YOU TRKS ALLOCATED AND % OF TRACKS USED. IT ALSO SHOWS HOW MANY EXTENTS YOU ARE IN. THE MAX EXTENTS ARE 16....IF YOU ARE EVEN CLOSE TO THIS NUMBER WITH A HIGH % OF USAGE....SPACE IS THE PROBLEM. THIS CASE IS UNUSUAL BECAUSE OF THE DATABASE BEING INVOLVED. ONCE YOU START A DB2 TASK....DB2 EXPECTS THAT TASK TO BE COMPLETED BEFORE YOU CAN START ANOTHER ONE. THIS FORCES A DB2 ADMINISTRATOR TO GET INVOLVED THE TASK IN DB2 MUST BE CLEANED OUT. TRYING TO RESTART THE JOB WITHOUT HAVING THE LAST TASK CLEANED UP WILL RESULT IN A S04E ERROR. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CALL THE DB2 SUPPORT PERSON. HAVE THEM CLEAN UP THE TASK IN DB2 FOR CL$$0150.....THEN RE-RUN CL$$0150 FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "OPERATOR CALLED THIS MORNING AND SAID THAT CDFT5017 DOWNLOAD ABENDED. CDFT5017(CDFT1065) DOWNLOADS THE FILE OUT OF CL$$0730. SO I GOT THE FOLLOWING INFO FROM Q.LOG ******** CONNECT:DIRECT FILE TRANSFER FAILED ********* FILE XFER BETWEEN - AULCD.MVS.CORP AND - AULCD.SAA6 FAILED REQUESTOR=CDXNET DSN=CDFAIL CDFT5017 CLUCAMRA FAILED LUNAME=L430 LOGOFF COMPLETED, CONNID=151 ,LUADDR=X'08871220' STEP01 COPY CDFT5017( 85) SNODE=AULCD.SAA6 426 FROM CL.CL$$0730.CAMERA.FILE TO S1 VOL1:USERS TEAM CAMRA CLTRADES.TXT #### COMPLETED 00000008\/SVSI010I DSN=CDFAIL CDFT5017 CLUCAMRA FAILED NOTIFY CL ONCALL PROGRAMMER CONNECT:DIRECT FILE TRANSFER FAILED ********* 427 ******** CONNECT:DIRECT FILE TRANSFER FAILED ********* ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CAROL THE OPERATOR SAID THAT CDFT5017 CLUCAMRA FAILED TRYING TO LOAD CL.CL$$0730.CAMERA.FILE. I COULD NOT FIND CDFT5017 IN SCHEDULE. SPOKE WITH STEVE. HE SAID THE OPERATORS HAD JUST GOT THAT JOB TO END-OK. SO IT WAS A TECHNICAL SYSTEM PROBLEM ON THE CDFT\/OPERATOR SIDE. THE ONLY CDFT JOB SHOWING ON SCHEDULE WAS CDFT1065. SO I LOOKED IN Q.LOG, AND FOUND THE MSG THAT CAROL WAS REFERRING TO ABOVE. NEXT, I CALLED STEVE BACK. HE SAID DAN DRAKE WAS JUST TELLING HIM HOW THIS JOB WAS AN EXCEPTION. THE JOB IS CDFT1065 TO DOWNLOAD THE CAMERA FILE, BUT IT WILL SHOUT CDFT5017 WHEN IT GOES DOWN. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DON'T NEED TO DO ANYTHING SINCE THE OPERATORS GOT THE JOB TO RUN. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC-7 SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=0C7 REASON CODE=00000007 IEF450I CL$$0100 STEP1000 JSTEP010 - ABEND=S0C7 U0000 RE STEP=STEP1000 PGM=CKAP08 ABENDED - COND CODE S0C7 RC= A DATA EXCEPTION WAS CAUSED BY DATA REFERENCED AT DISPLACEMENT AD0 FROM THE START OF BLW CELL 01 (X'1') THE FIELD CONTAINS X'4040'. REFER TO THE DATA DIVISION MAP IN THE PROGRAM LISTING... ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS STEP PRINTS THE AUTOMATIC TRX REGISTER. COMPILED PROGRAM TO SEE IF I COULD TRACE FIELD QUICKLY, BUT WAS NOT APPARENT SO CONSULTED WITH DAVID. AFTER BOUNCING THINGS BACK AND FORTH, WE FOUND THAT -THE INPUT FILE WAS CATALOGUED IN A PREVIOUS STEP0320, WHICH MEANT WE COULD RECREATE THE PROBLEM TOMMORROW. -THIS STEP DID NOT UPDATE IN ANY FILES. **** ",
  "SOLUTION": "(NEW SOLUTION SINCE 02\/15\/00) FORCE OK. SEND POLICY NUMBER TO KATHY H. FROM THE DUMP. SOLUTION: DECIDED TO SKIP STEP FOR TONIGHT AND FIGURE OUT LATER. RAN CL$$R060 *********** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** RAN CL$$RC30 WITH CORRECT GDG OVERRIDE RAN CL$$0100 WITH FOLLOWING STEP OVERRIDE ON THE EXEC CARD TO SKIP THE STEP. (ALSO PUT COMMA AFTER EXEC) \/\/ COND.STEP1000=(0,LE) ALL 3 JOBS ENDED OK, CYCLE CONTINUED ON. THE NEXT MORNING, COMPILED PROGRAM. DUMP GAVE NEXT INSTRUCTION LOCATION TO BE 4234, WHICH REFERS TO LINE 007462 IN CODE. 007456 SUBR2510-NEW-PAYEE. 007458 ADD +1 TO WS-PAY-SUB. 007460 IF WS-PAY-SUB > FAUNUMPY-NUMBER-OF-PAYEES OF 007461 NEW-AUTO-TRANS-SEG 007462 1 GO TO SUBR2520-PRINT-AWD-PAYEE. TRACED LOCATION TO A FIELD FAUNUMPY-NUMBER-OF-PAYEES USING EXPEDITOR AND NOTED POLICY 2453201040 WAS THE ONE IN QUESTION. CHECKED WITH KATHY, SHE SAID JEAN PRICE WAS HAVING PROBLEMS WITH THIS ONE. THEY WERE TRYING TO REMOVE A DOLLAR COST AVERAGING U1AT TRX THAT WAS PUT ON THE POLICY. THEY HAD ALREADY DELETED THE 53 SEG, BUT ALSO NEEDED TO DELETE THE 57 SEG. WELL TODAY, THEY JUST DELETED THE 57 SEG BECUASE THEY SAID THEY LEARNED THAT 53 AND 57 SEG WORK TOGETHER AND MUST EITHER BE THERE OR NOT. CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT.G0342V00 AF. ...%2 U1AT1...%..:;...%22453201040 129KW...*2...%2.... O......53.. AF. ...%2 U1AT1...%.......%22453201040 129KW...*2...%2.... O......53.. IN SHORT, THE 53 SEGMENT WAS NOT THERE AND OUR PROGRAM ASSUMES IT SHOULD BE. THE PROGRAM EXECUTES UNTIL IT ENCOUNTERS ITS FIRST COMPARE OR COMPUTE WHICH HAPPENED TO BE: IF WS-PAY-SUB > FAUNUMPY-NUMBER-OF-PAYEES FAUNUMPY-NUMBER-OF-PAYEES CONTAINED '4040' SO HOPEFULLY, THE SEGMENT DELETES MADE BY JEAN TODAY WILL TAKE CARE OF THIS PROBLEM TONIGHT. CHECKED WITH KATHY. SHE SAID NO NEED TO PRINT THIS REPORT AS SHE DID NOT THINK THE USERS REVIEWED IT. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "ENDED CC 0, BUT OPERATORS GOT A SHOUT MESSAGE THAT THE UPLOAD FAILED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS JOB, CDFT1038, UPLOADS CYUBLOD.TXT FROM THE LAN TO THE MAINFRAME DSN, CL.BKUP.FUND.PRICES. WHEN THE JOB IS SUCCESSFUL, IT CREATES A MESSAGE\/CONDITON, CDFT-TO-CL$$0012-OK. THIS CONDITION HAS TO BE MET FOR FOR CL$$0010 AND CL$$0012 TO RUN. IF THE LAN FILE IS NOT THERE, CDFT1038 WILL END CC 0, BUT OPERATORS WILL GET A SHOUT MESSAGE TELLING OF FAILED UPLOAD, AND THE CDFT-TO-CL$$0012-OK WILL NOT BE GENERATED. SINCE THIS FILE IS NEEDED FOR THE CYCLE TO RUN, THE WHOLE CYCLE WAS ON HOLD. CONFIRMED WITH JERRY AND MARK WILLIAMS THAT THE REAL PROBLEM WAS MISSING THE LAN INPUT FILE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CONTACT DAN SCHLUGE AND TOLD HIM OF MISSING PRICE FILE. HE WENT TO AUL AND CREATED FILE. ONCE DAN WAS FINISHED CREATING THE FILE, I HAD DAN NOTIFY OPERATIONS AT X-1451 TO RESTART CDFT1038. JOB ENDED OK WITH NO SHOUT MESSAGE. CYCLE CONTINUED ON. LESSON HERE IS THAT IF A CDFT... JOB GOES DOWN, 9 TIMES OUT OF 10, THE CAUSE WILL BE MISSING INPUT. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0846",
  "PROBLEM": "STOP 8 OR CC 8 TAG FILE ERRORS <PR 166 MI> <PR 167 MI> ERRONEOUS TAGS ",
  "ANALYSIS": "MODL\/PROD CONFLICT WITH PGM CHANGES BEING MOVED IN RELATED TO ISSUE#1523 ",
  "SOLUTION": "1. EDIT 'CL.VSAM.RECORDS' USING FIRECALL. 2. CHG ALL 'PR166 AZ' ' ' CHG ALL 'PR166 FL' ' ' CHG ALL 'PR166 IN' ' ' CHG ALL 'PR166 MI' ' ' CHG ALL 'PR166 MS' ' ' CHG ALL 'PR166 TN' ' ' CHG ALL 'PR166 XX' ' ' CHG ALL 'PR167 AZ' ' ' CHG ALL 'PR167 FL' ' ' CHG ALL 'PR167 IN' ' ' CHG ALL 'PR167 MI' ' ' CHG ALL 'PR167 MS' ' ' CHG ALL 'PR167 TN' ' ' CHG ALL 'PR167 XX' ' ' 3. RUN CL$$0845 AND CL$$0846 FROM THE TOP. PERFORMED THESE THREE STEPS AND BOTH JOBS ENDED-OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0900",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB ABENDED IN MIDDLE OF NIGHT WITH APPARENT HARDWARE ERROR. OPERATORS RESTARTED FROM TOP, BUT ABENDED AGAIN. *TMS009 IEC501A M 0AB7,026807,SL,,CL$$0900,STEP0020.CL$$ IEC023I 237-04,IFG0552R,CL$$0900,STEP0020,SORTIN-0005,0A IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=237 REASON CODE=00000004 STEP=STEP0020 PGM=SORT ABENDED - COND CODE S237 RC STEP=STEP0030 PGM=IDCAMS FLUSHED - COND CODE 0000 RC STEP=STEP0040 PGM=IDCAMS FLUSHED - COND CODE 0000 RC ",
  "ANALYSIS": "TRIED RESTARTING IN STEP0030 SINCE THE FILES WERE CREATED IN STEPS 10 AND 20(EVEN THOUGH THEY RAN TWICE). I UNCATALOGED THE FILE CREATED IN STEP0010 AND RESTARTED IN STEP0030. JOB STILL ABENDED. REASON: THE FILE(TAPE) WHICH WAS BAD WAS CREATED IN IN STEP0020. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RATHER THAN RESTART MID-STREAM, WE UNCATALOGED THE FILES THAT WERE CREATED (+1) IN STEPS 10 AND 20. RERAN JOB FROM THE TOP. JOB ENDED OK. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0020",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC4 ABEND ",
  "ANALYSIS": "POLICY RECORDS IN MODL.CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT WERE OUT OF ORDER. THREE LINES OF THREE POLICIES WERE MIXED TOGETHER. WHEREAS THE REST OF THE POLICIES' THREE LINES ARE GROUPED TOGETHER. ",
  "SOLUTION": "ORDER THE MIXED LINES SO THEY ARE GROUPED TOGETHER. CHANGE GDG01 FROM +1 TO 0 AND RESTART IN STEP0030. --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0070",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND S000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "+IGZ002I 'P1BKG070,STEP0005,0E32,D,BATCHIN ,GET ,WRNG.LEN.RECORD,000000B1000200,QSAM' +IGZ043I A 'SYSABOUT' ERROR OCCURRED. THE ABEND INFORMA INCOMPLETE.' +IGZ057I AN ABEND WAS INTERCEPTED BY THE COBOL RUN-TIME IT IS DESCRIBED BY A CORRESPONDING IEA995I MESS IEF450I P1BKG070 STEP0005 JSTEP010 - ABEND=S000 U1002 RE TIME=12.41.12 PROBLEM WITH THE SYSTEM READING FILES AS BEING 42 CHARAC WHEN THEY ARE ACTUALLY SETUP TO BE 50. NOTICE \"WRNG.LEN RECORD\" ABOVE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "EDIT THE FOLLOWING FILES WITH THE CYCLE END DATE, SKIP JOB 70 AND MOVE ON. TEST.CL.CBS.BATCH.G0XXXXXX TEST.CL.ARPS.BATCH.G0XXXXXX TEST.CL.LOCKBOX.BATCH.G0XXXXXX "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "THIS JOB WENT DOWN TONIGHT WITH A SOC1 ON THE PENDING FILE WITH A MISSING ROW. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "IDENTIFIED TWO BAD PENDING RECORDS: 3465018160 3465018170 ",
  "SOLUTION": "DROPPED RECORDS FROM PENDING, AUXSEG2, AND ACTIVITY FILE. RESTARTED CL$$0011 FROM TOP. JOB ENDED OK. CYCLE CONTINUED ON. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0125",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB ENDED OK, BUT OUTPUT WAS COMING OUT ON 2 PAGES PER BILL INSTEAD OF ONE PAGE OF FRONT AND BACK. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DECIDED TO RERUN JOB TO ELIMINATE POSSIBLE PRINTER PROBLEM. IF THIS IS NOT THE PROBLEM, THEN WE'D LOOK AT THE COMPUSET SIDE, BECAUSE WE HAD NOT MADE ANY RECENT CHANGES TO CL$$0125. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RERAN THE JOB FROM TOP. JOB ENDED OK AND OUTPUT CAME OUT RIGHT THIS TIME EXCEPT ONE BILL. WHAT WAS HAPPENING ON THE FIRST RUN WAS THAT THE PRINTER FEEDER WAS FEEDING 2 SHEETS THROUGH INSTEAD OF 1. CORRECTED THE ONE BILL BY USING THE COPY MACHINE AND DELIVERED REST OF OUTPUT TO BUZZ 610. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C7 IN STEP 260 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED AT RESTART INSTRUCTIONS IN SCHD.CTM.DOC. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CREATE DUMMY FILE OF CL.AGCY.DAILY.INPUT.TRANS(+1) FORCE COMPLETE JOB OKAY SO CYCLE CAN CONTINUE "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0070",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC-7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "EMPTY FILE COMING INTO STEP0005 FROM STEP0003 ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTART IN STEP0007 AND PUT IN OVERRIDE TO DUMMY OUT THE INPUT FILE TO STEP0007. RESTART=JSTEP0010.STEP0007 \/\/STEP0007.SORTIN DD DUMMY,DCB=(RECFM=FB,LRECL=80, BLKSIZE=8000) LONG TERM SOLUTION: FOUND THAT ULTIM WHEN IT PUTS OUT AN EMPTY FILE, DOES NOT SPECIFY THE DSORG. NEED TO HAVE DSORG=PS IN THE DCB TO BUILD THIS. ADDED THIS TO THE OUTPUT FILE IN STEP0003. THIS PROBLEM SHOULD NOT HAPPEN AGAIN. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC-7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DON'T KNOW WHY THIS ABENDED. REALIZED I WAS NOT GOING TO FIGURE IT OUT THAT NIGHT..SO, I HAD TO GET AROUND IT. THE POLICY WAS 3465016160. ",
  "SOLUTION": ">>>>>>>> SHORT TERM SOLUTION TO GET US GOING >>>>>>>> BE SURE TO LOOK AT LONG TERM SOLUTION AFTER STEPS 1-9 ******* NOTE: CL$$RC10 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL2 ******** 1) RUN BACKUPS CL$$R010 AND CL$$RC10. IN CL$$RC10, STEP0020 AND STEP0030 NEED TO BRING IN THE MOST RECENT VERSIONS OF THE GDGS. 2) AFTER THE BACKUPS HAVE COMPLETED, RERUN CL$$0012 RESTARTING AT STEP0010 AND OVERRIDE 'GENIN' TO EQUAL 0. 2) AFTER CL$$0012 HAS COMPLETED, RERUN CL$$0015 RESTARTING AT STEP0020 AND OVERRIDING 'GENOT' TO EQUAL 0. 3) AFTER CL$$0015 IS COMPLETE, RUN CL$$0017 FROM THE TOP. 3.5)USE FIRECALL TO CREATE AN EMPTY DATASET TO FEED TO THE AGENCY SYSTEM. 4) AFTER CL$$0017 IS COMPLETE, SETUP CL$$0030 WITH COND.STEP0165=(0,LE), THIS WILL STOP STEP 165 FROM RUNNING....BUT WILL ALLOW THE REST OF THE JOB TO RUN. THIS ENTRY IS CODED JUST AS YOU WOULD A SYMBOLIC OVER RIDE...THEN RE-START CL$$0030 FROM THE TOP. 5)NEXT DAY...COPY THE FILE CL.COMBPEND TO YOUR VERSION 6)DROP THE PROBLEM POLICY 7)RUN STEPS 150,160,165 FROM CL$$0030 BRINGING IN YOUR VERSION OF THE DATASET TO CREATE A FILE 8)GET THIS FILE DOUBLED UP WITH TONIGHTS PRODUCTION TO FEED TO AGCY0020..EITHOR JEFF CAN OVERRIDE TO BRING IN OR WE HAVE TO SET UP A COLLAPSE. 9)LET CHARITY KNOW THE POLICY YOU DROPPED SO SHE CAN GET THAT POLICY CODED INTO THE AGCY SYSTEM >>>>> LONGER TERM SOLUTION 1)WE MOVED THE PROGRAM D724AGC1 TO THE LAST STEP IN THE JOB. THIS WAY WHEN IT GOES DOWN....WE CAN CREATE AN EMPTY FILE TO FEED TO AGCY AND FORCE COMPLETE THE JOB CL$$0030..AND THE CYCLE CAN CONTINUE WITHOUT ANY RESTORES OR RE-RUNS. WE CAN THEN FIX THE PROBLEM THE NEXT DAY USING STEPS 5-9 ABOVE. STEP 165 MOVED TO STEP0260.... "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0040",
  "PROBLEM": "SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=0C4 REASON CODE=00000010 EARLIER TONIGHT WE HAD A PROBLEM WITH CL$$0011, SO LOOKING IN THE DUMP FOR THIS JOB, WE FOUND POLICY 3465009730 AS THE CULPRIT. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE ACTIVTY IS HOSED UP FOR THIS POLICY. WILL PROVE BY RUNNING A TEST WITH CL$T0040. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RAN TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$T0040). ONCE THE SEQ FILE WAS CREATED, I RAN THE 3 STEP WAAPDSUT TO DROP ACTIVITY FROM THE TEST SEQ FILE. RESTARTED CL$T0040 IN STEP 0120. TEST JOB ENDED OK. IN PRODUCTION RAN THE 3 STEP WAAPDSUT TO DROP ACTIVITY FOR POLICY 3465009730. RESTARTED CL$$0040 FROM THE TOP. PROD JOB ENDS CC8 IN STEP0010. NOTE: STEP0010 WILL END IN A CC8 ON THE RERUN. THIS IS OK. MAKE SURE ALL OTHER STEPS END CC0. TELL OPERATOR TO FORCE CL$$0040 OK SO OTHER JOBS WILL KICK OFF. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "THE POLICY PORTION OF THE PRINT ROUTINE ABENDED WITH A SOC1. SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=0C1 REASON CODE=00000001 STEP=BATCHTSO PGM=IKJEFT01 EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 RC= ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WE WERE GIVEN A HEADS UP EARLIER THAT DAY PRODUCTION POLICY 3465009730 WAS HAVING PROBLEMS IN THAT THEY COULD NOT UNLOCK IT. LOOKING IN THE DUMP, THIS POLICY NUMBER CAME UP FIRST. ALSO IN THE DUMP, WE WERE GETTING SQL ERROR -811, WHICH IS A SIGN OF A DUPLICATED ROW. RAN A SPUFI TEST.CL.DLCJCL(SQL$LVL1) AND FOUND THAT TWO ROWS HAD A RLT_TYP_CD OF 0001. SO WE NEED TO EXPIRE ONE OF THE ROWS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "FIRST, PUT A HOLD CL$$0030 RAN A SPUFI TO EXPIRE MOST RECENT ROW. WE DECIDED TO KEEP THE OLDEST ROW. RAN CL$$0011 FROM TOP AGAIN. ENDED OK. RELEASED CL$$0030 TO RUN. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0120",
  "PROBLEM": "VSAM ERROR - - FILE=VSAM3 , INCODE=4, OUTCODE=4, R15=08, ERRCODE=006C USER COMPLETION CODE=0001 IEF450I CL$$0120 STEP0130 CL$$0120 - ABEND=S000 U0001 REAS STEP=STEP0130 PGM=CKDELBDB ABENDED - COND CODE S001 RC=00 LBDB004 - VSAM3 RECORD WRITE FAILURE, RUN TERMINATED ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE LBDXXX TYPE MESSAGES WE'VE SEEN BEFORE, BUT THIS ONE WAS DIFFERENT THAN LAST TIME AND IT OCCURED ON A DIFFERENT FILE, THE BILLPMNT. SINCE, THIS JOB HAS ABENDED BEFORE IN THIS STEP, I FOLLOWED SAME RESTARTS AS DOCUMENTED PREVIOUSLY KNOWING WE'D NEED TO FIX THE NEXT BUSINESS DAY. -DEFERRED CL$$0120 AND RELEASED DEPENDENCIES ON CL$$0125 CL$$0126 CL$$0130 CL$$0140 ALSO NOTED THAT THE VSAM CODE 6C MEANS: RECLEN > MAXIMUM ALLOWABLE VALUE, RECLEN=0, OR LESS THAN KEYLEN + KEY OFFSET IN RECORD ",
  "SOLUTION": "THE NEXT DAY, WE DECIDED TO TRY AND INCREASE THE RECORD SIZE IN THE DEL\/DEFINE FROM 4700 TO 7000. WE RAN A TEST RUNNNING STEP0110 TO 0130 WITH THE NEW DEL\/DEFINE SETTINGS BOR BILLPMNT AND IT WORKED. SO TO CORRECT IN PRODUCTION: CLOSED LISTBILL AND BILLPMNT FILES DEL\/DEFINED BILLPMNT WITH NEW RECORDSIZE SETTINGS DEL\/DEFINED LISTBILL WITH NORMAL DEL\/DEFINE PROD CARD. RESTORED FROM BILLPMNT FROM BACKUPS OUT OF CL$$0010 RESTORED FROM LISTBILL FROM BACKUPS OUT OF CL$$0145 FROM THE PREVIOUS NIGHT. RAN CL$$0120 FROM THE TOP LOGGED AS ISSUE CL1397 -WE WILL NEED TO UPDATE TEST AND MODL DEL\/DEF BILLPMNT FILE. -CHANGED TEST AND MODL DEL\/DEF CARDLIBS TO MATCH PROD, AND IN THE PROCESS OF REDEFINING AND REPROING BACK OUT TO MATCH PRODUCTION. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0060",
  "PROBLEM": "IEC210I 214-10 ON OUT3 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE NUMBER OF BLOCKS PROCESSED, WHICH IS DETERMINED BY THE POSITION OF THE TAPE, DOES NOT MATCH THE NUMBER OF BLOCKS SPECIFIED IN THE DCB. ",
  "SOLUTION": "1) RERAN JOB CL$$0060 FROM THE TOP. EVERYTHING TURNED OUT FINE. I DID NOT MODIFY ANYTHING. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC-7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DID A FIND ON CURRENT IN THE DUMP. POLICY NUMBER WAS 3465012250. DAN BLECK DETERMINED TO GO AHEAD AND DROP THE PROBLEM POLICY OFF OF THE ACTIVITY, PENDING, AND AUXSEG2 FILES. THE USERS WHERE HAVING A PROBLEM ISSUEING THE POLICY. ******* NOTE: CL$$RC10 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL2 ******** ",
  "SOLUTION": "1) RUN BACKUPS CL$$R010 AND CL$$RC10. IN CL$$RC10, STEP0020 AND STEP0030 NEED TO BRING IN THE MOST RECENT VERSIONS OF THE GDGS. 2) AFTER THE BACKUPS HAVE COMPLETED, RERUN CL$$0015 RESTARTING AT STEP0020 AND OVERRIDING 'GENOT' TO EQUAL 0. 3) AFTER CL$$0015 IS COMPLETE, RUN CL$$0017 FROM THE TOP. 4) AFTER CL$$0017 IS COMPLETE, USE FM TO PULL THE RECORD OFF OF THE CL.VSAM.BASEOL.ACTIVITY, PENDING, AND AUXSEG2 FILES. 5) RERUN CL$$0030 FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0016",
  "PROBLEM": "CC12 - IEC030I B37-04 OUTDD1 DD DSN=&PREFIX.CL$$0016.S0010.SEQUEN SYSUT2 DD DSN=&PREFIX.CL$$0016.STEP0020.FILE ",
  "ANALYSIS": "OUTDD1 FILE RAN OUT OF SPACE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "STEP 1 - RUN CL$$RAGT FROM THE TOP. STEP 2 - ONCE CL$$RAGT IS COMPLETE, RERUN CL$$0015 FROM STEP0020 AFTER HAVING THE OPERATOR OVERRIDE ALL OF THE 'GENOT'S TO EQUAL '0'. STEP 3 - ONCE CL$$0015 IS COMPLETE, RERUN CL$$0016 FROM THE TOP AFTER HAVING THE OPERATOR OVERRIDE THE OUTDD1 FILE IN STEP0010 AND SYSUT2 FILE IN STEP0020 WITH THE NEW INCREASED SPACE VALUES. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0127",
  "PROBLEM": "CC8 - IDCAMS KEY OUT OF SEQUENCE IDC3302I ACTION ERROR ON CL.VSAM.ACH.AUDIT.ERRORS IDC3314I **RECORD OUT OF SEQUENCE - KEY FOLLOWS: 000000 F1F9F9F9 F0F4F2F8 F4F0F0F0 F0F8F5 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS IS REALLY A DUPLICATE KEY. THE KEY IS THE THE FIRST 15 POSITIONS AND THE SORT IN THE PRIOR STEP ORDERS THE FILE ON THE FIRST 15 POSITIONS. SO, UNLESS THE SORT KEY LENGTH CHANGES...THIS WILL ALWAYS BE A DUPLICATE KEY. IF THERE IS JUST ONE OR TWO RECORDS WHICH POSED THIS PROBLEM....CONTINUE WITH THE CYCLE. UNLESS WE HAVE SOME KIND OF A MASS OUTBREAK...WE CAN DEAL WITH THE PROBLEM THE NEXT BUSINESS DAY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "POSITION 33 FOR A LENGTH OF 2 IS AN ERROR CODE. AN '05' IN THIS FIELD INDICATES A BILLING DATE ERROR AND IS CORRECTABLE BY THE USERS. WE JUST NEED TO LET THE REGION KNOW THE FOLLOWING INFORMATION: REGION CODE IN POS 11 FOR LENGTH OF 4 BILLING DATE IN POS 25 FOR LENGTH OF 8 ERROR RECORD IN POSITION 9 FOR LENGTH OF 7 POLICY NUMBER FROM THE ACH.AUDIT.CONTROL FILE .....LOOKUP THE AUDIT CONTROL USING THE 7 DIGIT ERROR CODE. THIS INFORMATION IS PROVIDED TO THE REGION BY A BUSINESS ANALYST. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC-4 OR SOC-1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "COULD SEE THIS WAS AN OLD POLICY WHICH HAD WORKED THE NIGHT PRIOR. COULD SEE IN THE DUMP BY DOING A FIND ON SQL THAT IT WAS AN SQL 100 WHICH IS A MISSING ROW. THEN PAGE DOWN 1 OR TWO PAGES TO SEE A CIS... REFERENCE THIS WILL TELL YOU WHAT TABLE HAD THE PROBLEM. IF YOU LOOK IN CKCSTGET IN PANVALET, YOU CAN DO A FIND ON THE CIS... REFERENCE AND SEE WHAT TABLE WAS MISSING. IN THIS CASE THE CLIENT ADDRESS WAS MISSING CISLCA. BY RUNNING FOR THE ABENDING POLICY, TEST.CL.DLCJCL(SQL$LVL1) WITH POLICY SPECIFIED AND USING THE CLIENT_ID AND ADDRESS SEQUENCE FOR EACH CLIENT, I THEN WENT INTO TEST.CL.DLCJCL(SQL$LVL2) IN PARTICULAR I WAS INTERESTED IN THE CLT_ADR_RELATION TABLE SINCE THIS TAKES ME TO THE CLIENT_ADDRESS ROW. I PLUGGED INTO TEST.CL.DLCJCL(SQL$LVL2) THE CLIENT_ID AND SEQUENCE TO GET THE ADR_ID, THEN I PLUG THIS INTO TEST.CL.DLCJCL(SQL$LVL3) AND THE ADDRESS WAS MISSING. ",
  "SOLUTION": "FOUND ANOTHER ADDRESS TO ATTACK THIS POLICY TO. MODIFIED SQL$FIX2 TO DISPLAY AND UPDATE THE DESIRED ROWS. THEN RAN CL$$0011 AGAIN. REPORTED THE PROBLEM SO THE USERS COULD GET THE ADDRESS STUFF CORRECTED. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC-4 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOUND 13 POLICIES WITHOUT CLIENT PIECES. USED CL$$0011 SKIP RECORD TECHNIQUE TO NARROW DOWN WHICH POLICIES HAD THE PROBLEM. THEN RAN A JOB TO REPRO OUT THE PENDING\/AUXSEG2\/ACTIVITY FILES. DROPPED ALL REFERENCES TO THE 13 POLICIES. USED FIRECALL TO RELOAD ",
  "SOLUTION": "RAN A JOB TO REPRO OUT THE PENDING\/AUXSEG2\/ACTIVITY FILES. DROPPED ALL REFERENCES TO THE 13 POLICIES. USED FIRECALL TO RELOAD. RAN CL$$0011 AGAIN. SEE.....TEST.CL.TOOLS(REPOTPN) REPRO DOWN ALL 3 FILES (REPINPN) REPRO BACK ALL 3 FILES 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC-4 +UNABLE TO RETRIEVE STUB POOL RECORD +- - - - > JOB TERMINATED BY CKABEND < - - - - IEF450I P1BGR012 STEP0020 CL$$0011 - ABEND=S04C U0000 REASON=0000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOUND POLICY POLICY FILE WAS 2453306150 AND THE AUXSEG1 FILE WAS 2453306170 RERUN CKAP01V ON THAT POLICY AND IT RAN OK. SUBMITTED CL$$0011 FOR THE FULL FILE AGAIN. CANCELLED IT AFTER IT EXCEEDED THE CPU TIME OF THE ABEND. OPERATOR CALLED LATER WHEN CL$$0011 WAS RUNNING DURING THE CYCLE BECAUSE IT WAS RUNNING A LONG TIME. DID NOT TAKE ACTION. IT COMPLETED NORMALLY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RAN A JOB TO REPRO OUT THE PENDING\/AUXSEG2\/ACTIVITY FILES. DROPPED ALL REFERENCES TO THE 13 POLICIES. USED FIRECALL TO RELOAD. RAN CL$$0011 AGAIN. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0130",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC-4 SOC4 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED IN DUMP TO SEE IF I COULD LOCATE A POLICY NUMBER FOUND MANY POLICY NUMBERS. I MADE A LIST, THEN I RAN A JOB WHICH KEPT THE DATASETS(TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$$0130)) I LOOKED IN THE FILE CORRLETR TO SEE WHAT THE LAST RECORD WRITTEN WAS. THEN I LOOKED IN THE CORRSORT TO SEE WHAT THE NEXT RECORD AFTER THE LAST WRITTEN RECORD WAS. THEN I TRACKED BACK THE POLICY TO SEE IF IT IS IN THE CL.BASEB.AP.COR.EXT1(-0) OR THE CL.REQMTCOR. POLICY: 3465028990 12\/16\/04 THE RECORD WAS IN CL.REQMTCOR FROM CL$$0100 ANALYSIS2: LOOK IN IDIREPRT AND DO A SEARCH ON CURRENT. THE POLICY THAT POPS UP THE MOST IS PROBABLY THE PROBLEM POLICY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DELETE THE POLICY WITH THE BAD CORRESPONDENCE REQUEST IN PRODUCTION BY USING FIRECALL. I RECOMMEND A BACKUP OF THE FILE FIRST USING AN IEBGENER. TEST.CL.TOOLS(COPYCOR) IS SET TO COPY THE FILE. YOU HAVE TO CLOSE FVDCFFD DURING YOUR RERUN. FVDCFFD = CL.VSAM.BASEOL.CORRES RESTART THE JOB FROM THE TOP. NOTE: PRODUCTION WILL NOT STOP RUNNING, THIS JOB HAS NOTHING DEPENDENT ON IT. THE ACTIVITY FILE WILL BE RE-INITIALIZED IN CL$$0150...BUT WE DON'T THINK THERE ARE ANY COORESPONDENCE REQUESTS AVAILABLE TO THE ACTIVITY FILE. NOTE: I HAVE HAD THE SAME PROBLEM POLICY TWICE NOW IN THE APRIL 2000 ABENDS. (3465028990) DJN 12\/20\/04 THE PROBLEM ON 12\/17 AND 12\/20 AND POSSIBLY OTHER TIMES RSW IS THAT A COUNTER IN CL.VSAM.BASEOL.CORRES HAS REACHED 99999. THE COUNTER IS SBSUSAGE-USAGE-COUNTER IN CKSRECBS, WHICH ENDS UP BEING AROUND COLUMN 73 IN THE CORRES FILE. EACH CORRESPONDENCE RECORD HAS A COUNTER OF HOW MANY TIMES THAT LETTER HAS BEEN CREATED. WE NEED TO RUN CKCBRORG WITH THE RESETUSE OPTION TO RESET THE COUNTERS. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0847",
  "PROBLEM": "CC8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "TAG PROBLEM ",
  "SOLUTION": "FIX THE VSAM.RECORDS FILE. RUN CL$$0845 IN TEST.CL.TOOLS RUN CL$$0846 IN TEST.CL.TOOLS FOR STATE 'MO' MOVE IN CORRECTION TO VSAM RECORDS. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0120",
  "PROBLEM": "USER COMPLETION CODE 0001 AT THE BOTTOM OF SYSLST LBDB010 - TABLE AREA EXHAUSTED, RUN TERMINATED ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ABEND AID WAS TURNED OFF. HOWEVER, THE PROGRAM GAVE ME AN ERROR MESSAGE. LBDB010 - TABLE EXHAUSTED. DID A FIND ON OCCUR AND FOUND ONLY 1 INTERNAL TABLE. IT WAS SET AT 35..INCREASED IT TO 55 AND TRIED AGAIN. DID NOT WORK. FOUND THE VSAM MAXIMUM RECORD LENGTH NEEDED TO BE INCREASED. THE FOLLOWING IS WHAT YOU GET WHEN THE VSAM MAXIMUM RECORD LENGTH NEEDS TO INCREASE VSAM ERROR - FILE=VSAM3 , INCODE=4, OUTCODE=4, R15=08, ERRCODE=6C LBDB004 - VSAM3 RECORD WRITE FAILURE, RUN TERMINATED ",
  "SOLUTION": "WE NEED TO KEEP THE CYCLE MOVING. SO, SINCE WE WENT DOWN IN STEP0130, WE CAN BYPASS THIS JOB HAVE OPERATIONS RELEASE THE CL$$0120 DEPENDENCIES ON THE FOLLOWING JOBS: CL$$0125 CL$$0126 CL$$0130 CL$$0140 THIS WILL ALLOW THE CYCLE TO COMPLETE UNTIL WE CAN FIX THE PROBLEM. NEXT DAY SOLUTION: INCREASE INTERNAL TABLE IN CKDELBDB\/CKDELBDU. THIS CAN BE FOUND BY LOOKING AT CL1136. THERE IS AN OCCURS AREA UPDATE AND A TABLE MAX EDIT. IN THE CKDELBDU MODULE THERE IS AN INCREASE REQUIRED TO FT-CLEAR. THE NUMBER OF BYTES OF THAT FIELD AND THE FIELD BEFORE IT MUST ADD UP TO THE SIZE OF THE OCCURS. A COMPILE WILL SHOW YOU THE SIZE OF THE OCCURS. THEN COMPILE AND LINK THESE GUYS. THE NEXT THING THAT MIGHT NEED TO HAPPEN IS TO INCREASE THE MAXIMUM RECORD LENGTH FOR THE VSAM. USE DEFVLSBP(CLDOLSB IF IAM) FOR DELETE\/DEFINE. REPRO OUT WHAT IS IN THE CURRENT BILLPMNT FILE, DELETE\/DEFINE, THEN RELOAD WITH WHAT YOU BACKED UP. YOU CAN RESTART CL$$0120 FROM THE TOP. TO DETERMINE HOW BIG TO MAKE THE MAXIMUM RECORD LENGTH, ADD 125 + (56 * NUMBER OF OCCURS) + 4 AND THEN SOME. I'M THINKING THERE MIGHT BE SOME FILES TO CLOSE IF YOU FIND OUT WHAT THEY ARE REPLACE THIS COMMENT WITH THAT INFORMATION. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0040",
  "PROBLEM": "S200 WITH A REASON 311 IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=200 REASON CODE=00000311 TIME=23.32.14 SEQ=04702 CPU=0041 ASID=0029 PSW AT TIME OF ERROR 078C2000 00FF5A2C ILC 4 INTC 11 NO ACTIVE MODULE FOUND NAME=UNKNOWN DATA AT PSW 00FF5A26 - C00FB20A F0005840 20145830 GPR 0-3 009F95C0 F4002000 F4002000 00000C58 GPR 4-7 009F95C0 00FF59FA 80000080 00FB2800 GPR 8-11 00E16F40 00FFDF00 009C7270 7F733000 GPR 12-15 00000C60 00028330 00FF5A04 00E16A80 END OF SYMPTOM DUMP IEC914I 119-04,CL$$0040,STEP0120, IEF450I CL$$0040 STEP0120 JSTEP010 - ABEND=S200 U0000 REASON=00311 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED THESE MESSAGES UP IN QW AND THOUGHT THEY WERE TELLING ME THIS JOB NEVER GOT STARTED. THE DUMP WAS NOT VERY HELPFUL...I BELIEVE ABENDAID WAS TURNED OFF. AFTER ABOUT 1\/2 HOUR, I CALLED SANDI. SHE SAID LETS JUST TRY IT AGAIN. THIS JOB CAN BE RUN FROM THE TOP AS MANY TIMES AS YOU NEED....SO, WE DID....THEN I COULD SEE THAT THE JOB WAS ACTUALLY PROCESSING RECORDS BECAUSE OF SIO'S IN THE STEP AND CPU. THIS PUT ME BACK ON TRACK FOR AN ACTIVITY PROBLEM. I BEGAN DROPING ACTIVITY FOR NEW POLICIES. SANDI DID A FIND IN THE IN THE DUMP FOR 3465 AND GOT A HIT. WE TRIED DROPPING THAT POLICY AND IT WORKED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "LOOK THOUGH THE DUMP FOR 336 OR 3465 AND TRY TO FIND A POLICY NUMBER. RUN TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$T0040) TO CREATE YOUR ACTIVITY FLAT FILE..THEN X ALL WITH YOUR POLICY NUMBER IN FILE MARVEL IN POSITION 12, THEN DEL ALL X. THEN SAVE AND TRY TO RUN CL$T0040 WITH RESTART IN STEP0030, IF THIS WORKS YOU HAVE ISOLATED THE PROBLEM AND YOU NEED TO DROP THE POLICY FROM THE VSAM PRODUCTION ACTIVITY FILE. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0110",
  "PROBLEM": "U0001 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THERE WAS A VSAM ERROR MESSAGE OF IEC070I 102-204 THIS PROBLEM WAS TAGGED AS BEING THE AGTFIN. THERE WAS ALSO A WRITE ERROR INDICATED IN THE SYSLST. MESSAGES INDICATED SOME KIND OF SPACE RELATED ERROR. I CHECKED FOR A REGION CARD...THERE WAS NONE. I CHECKED DISK PACK VOLUME SPACE...THERE WAS PLENTY. I CHECKED A LSTCAT ON THE VSAM AND FOUND IT TO BE AT 123 EXTENTS. SINCE EXTENTS ONLY GO TO 126, THIS SEEMED LIKE MY BEST GUESS. TURNS OUT TO BE CORRECT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "BUILT MY OWN CARDLIB DEFVAFAP FROM PRODUCTION. INCREASED THE SPACE PARAMATER. RAN AN IDCAMS TO EXECUTE THE DEL\/DEF UNDER FIRECALL. BUILT AN IDCAMS RELOAD JOB TO LOAD CL.AGTFIN.DALY(-0) TO CL.VSAM.BASEOL. AGTFIN WITH REUSE. RESTARTED CL$$0110 AT THE TOP. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0860",
  "PROBLEM": "APPEARED THAT THE JOB WAS LOOPING, SO IT WAS CANCELLED. HOWEVER, IT WAS NOT CANCELLED WITH A DUMP. WERE ABLE TO DETERMINE FROM THE DISPLAYS IN THE PROGRAM WHAT POLICY IT WAS ON. IT RAN FOR OVER 3 1\/2 HOURS. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CAN LOOK AT THE SYSOUT FILE AND SEE WHAT THE LAST POLICY NUMBER DISPLAYED WAS. IN THIS CASE IT WAS A UL POLICY RECENTLY CONVERTED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CREATED A COPY OF FILE CL.CL$$0100.STEP0690.SAPPH(0) AND PULLED THAT POLICY OFF, THERE ARE MULTIPLE RECORDS PER POLICY. THEN CREATED A PROC WITH THAT FILE AS INPUT FOR IINPUT01 AND CHANGED THE PARMDATE TO POINT TO MY PDS, SOMETIMES THE PARMDATE CARD GETS UPDATED EARLY IN THE MORNING. RESTART 860 AT THE TOP. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0900",
  "PROBLEM": "# IEF450I CL$$0900 STEP0020 CL$$0900 - ABEND=S000 U0046 REASO IEF234E K 0AB2,027765,PVT,CL$$0900,STEP0020 TMS014 IEF234E K 0AB2,027765,PVT,CL$$0900,STEP0020 -STEP=STEP0020 PGM=SORT ABENDED - COND CODE S02E RC=000 IEF404I CL$$0900 - ENDED - TIME=04.06.55 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SORT EXEEDED MAX # RECORDS ALLOWED. JEFF, PLEASE ADVISE. SEEMS LIKE WE WILL NEED TO USE A DIFFERENT UTILITY TO CREATE THE ACCUMULATED BACKUP FILE. DO THE REPRINT JOBS ASSUME A SORTED FILE IN? WE NEED TO DO SOMETHING FOR TONIGHT AND CORRECT LAST NIGHT'S FILE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "UPDATED PROD.CL.CARDLIB(CL086605) SORT FIELDS=(25,4,CH,A,21,4,CH,A,1,20,CH,A) OMIT COND=(01,10,ZD,LT,2) OPTION FILSZ=E16000,DYNALLOC=(SYSDA,5) DEBUG ABEND 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0120",
  "PROBLEM": "TWO PROBLEMS: 1. SOC7 2. VSAM ERROR IEC161I 052(009)-084,CL$$0120,STEP0220CL$$0120,VSAM2,,, IEC161I CL.VSAM.BASER.BILLDUE2,CL.VSAM.BASER.BILLDUE2.DAT IEC161I CATALOG.AREA1 + VSAM ERROR - FILE=VSAM2 , INCODE=0, OUTCODE=9, R15=08, IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=0C7 REASON CODE=00000007 TIME=01.40.16 SEQ=03423 CPU=0000 ASID=009D IEF450I CL$$0120 STEP0220 CL$$0120 - ABEND=S0C7 U0000 RE TIME=01.40.19 # IEF450I CL$$0120 STEP0220 CL$$0120 - ABEND=S0C7 U0000 -STEP=STEP0220 PGM=CKBSMPLD ABENDED - COND CODE S0C7 R VSAM ERROR-FILE=VSAM2, INCODE=0, OUTCODE=9, R15=08, ERRCODE=00A8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CL$$0120.STEP0220 ABENDED WITH A S0C7. I THINK WE HAVE SEEN THIS IN THE TEST AND\/OR MODL REGIONS BEFORE. AFTER ASSESSING THE IMPACT WE DECIDED TO CONTINUE THE CYCLE. THE BILLDUE2 FILE IS GETTING A VSAM ERROR ON THE OPEN OUTPUT. THIS CAUSES ERROR MESSAGES TO BE WRITTEN. SINCE THUIS OCCURS IN 'START UP' PROCESSING A FIELD IS NOT YET INITIALIZED (MAX LINES - NORMALLY POPULATED FROM CKUDCBR0) THAT CAUSES THE S0C7. THIS NEEDS TO BE CORRECTED BEFORE CYCLE TONI I GAVE UP LAST NIGHT WHEN THE PAN JOBS WOULD NOT LET ME COPY THE PROGRAM DOWN TO APPLY A FIX. DAN NOAH, PLEASE FIX THIS. LATER IT WAS DETERMINED THAT THE VSAM ERROR A8 MEANT THAT A FILE WAS NOT AVAILBLE. BY CROSS REFERENCING WHERE THE BILLDUE2 FILE WAS USED, WE WERE ABLE TO DETERMINE THAT IT WAS USED IN CL$$120 AND CL$$130. A CLOSER LOOK AT THESE TWO JOBS REVEALED THAT THEY RAN AT THE SAME TIME CAUSING A CONTENTION PROBLEM. ",
  "SOLUTION": "BY RUNNING CL$$0120 SEPARATELY IN TEST(W\/O CL$$0130 RUNNING), WE FOUND OUT THAT THE JOB ENDED OK. PUT IN NEW JOB DEPENDENCY TO MAKE CL$$0130 RUN AFTER CL$$0120. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "SPACE PROBLEM DURING TIME DRIVEN AFTER 2ND UL CONVERSION. IEC030I B37-04,IFG0554A,CL$$0100,BATCHTSO,SEQUEN2,0BDF,PU IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=B37 REASON CODE=00000004 -STEP=BATCHTSO PGM=IKJEFT01 EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 RC IEC130I FVDSEG1 DD STATEMENT MISSING + VSAM ERROR - FILE=FVDSEG1, INCODE=6, OUTCODE=8, R15=08, -STEP=STEP0880 PGM=CKPRBLD EXECUTED - COND CODE 0000 RC ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CL$$0100.STEP0870.SEQUEN2 RAN OUT OF SPACE. SINCE DB2 STEPS DO NOT BOTHER TO STOP RUNNING THE REST JOB FINISHED OK. THIS STEP BUILDS A CROSS REFERENCE FILE WHICH IS LOADED TO THE VSAM.BASEOL.POLCRF.INFORCE FILE. I BELIEVE THIS FILE IS USED FOR FIELDLINK,A BASE SYSTEM FACILITY WE DO NOT USE. THE FILE IS NOT USED IN ANY OTHER PLACES IN THE CYCLE OTHER THAN BACKUPS\/RESTORES. OTHER PLACES IN THE CYCLE OTHER THAN BACKUPS\/RESTORES. IT IS REBUILT EVERY NIGHT. WE ELECTED TO FORCE 100 WITH AN ENDED-OK CONDITION AND KEPT RUNNING. ",
  "SOLUTION": "WE NEED TO BUMP THE SPACE TO (27998,(600,100),RLSE) IN STEPS 870, 880, & 890. THAT SHOULD HANDLE ABOUT 300,000 RECORDS. LATER WE MAY WANT TO CONSIDER REMOVING THE STEPS THAT MAINTAIN THIS FILE FROM THE CYCLE. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$UINT",
  "PROBLEM": "IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT USER COMPLETION CODE=0005 TIME=21.32.37 SEQ=16832 CPU=0000 ASID=005B PSW AT TIME OF ERROR 078D1000 0000825A ILC 2 INTC 0 ACTIVE LOAD MODULE ADDRESS=00006000 OFFSET= NAME=ICEMON END OF SYMPTOM DUMP IEF450I CL$$UINT STEP0010 JSTEP010 - ABEND=S000 U0005 REA TIME=21.32.40 JOB05612 *# IEF450I CL$$UINT STEP0010 JSTEP010 - ABEND=S000 U00 IDC0002I IDCAMS PROCESSING COMPLETE. MAXIMUM CONDITION ICE000I J --- CONTROL STATEMENTS\/MESSAGES ---- 5740-SM SORT FIELDS=(1,14,BI,A,16,2,BI,A,22,4,BI,A, 15,1,BI,D,26,2,BI,A,40,4,BI,A 38,2,BI,A) FILSZ=E5000,DYNALLOC=(SYSDA,4) $ ICE005A M STATEMENT DEFINER ERROR ICE052I J END OF DFSORT ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DEFINER ERROR POINTS TO BAD STATEMENT OR SYNTAX PROBLEM. BY COMPARING ANOTHER PROD SORT CARD I WAS ABLE TO DETERMINE THAT THE SORT CARD WAS MISSING A COMMA IN BETWEEN COMMANDS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CREATED TEST.CL.CARDLIB(CLSUINTR) AND CORRECTED THE ERROR. HAD PCD RESTART IN STEP0010 WITH THE CARD OVERRIDE. STEP0005 HAD ALREADY CREATED THE TAPE BACK UP. JOB ENDED-OK. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0015",
  "PROBLEM": "IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=0C4 REASON CODE=00000011 TIME=23.15.08 SEQ=13813 CPU=0000 ASID=002A PSW AT TIME OF ERROR 078D0000 0000E450 ILC 2 INTC 1 ACTIVE LOAD MODULE ADDRESS=00006AD8 OFFSET= ",
  "ANALYSIS": "NOT SURE WHAT PROBLEM WAS, DECIDED TO DEFER. I DIDN'T THIS TIME, BUT NEXT TIME I DEFER, MAKE SURE WE RESTORE THE ACF SO THAT WE DON'T HAVE A PARTIALLY UPDATED FILE. THE NEXT DAY, WE DETERMINED THAT THE PROGRAM(BEING A COMPILED WITH COBOL1) ERRORED OUT WITH THE IAM VERSION OF THE ACF. IAM WAS JUST RECENTLY IMPLEMENTED. WE ALSO DETERMINED THAT THE COMPILE AND LINK IN PRODUCTION WERE QUESTIONABLE DUE TO SIZE AND THE FACT THERE WASN'T A PROD.CL.LINK(D7241010). WE ALSO DETERMINE THAT SOURCE HAD COMPILE ERRORS WITH MANY LINES MISSING PERIODS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "UPDATED SOURCE, RECOMPILED USING COBOL2 AND LINK USING OUR SYSTEM STANDARD PROCEDURES FOR CYBERTEK PROGRAMS. WE RERAN THEN JOB USING AN IAM VERSION OF ACF. JOB ENDED OK. FOR TONIGHT'S CYCLE, WE WILL RUN ANOTHER CL$$0015 BEFORE CL$$0015 WITH RESTART IN STEP0030 AND PICK UP THE (-1) OF AI.TAPEBU... 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0830",
  "PROBLEM": "IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=878 REASON CODE=00000010 TIME=22.38.34 SEQ=10758 CPU=0041 ASID=0091 EA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT USER COMPLETION CODE=1035 IEF450I CL$$0830 STEP0080 CL$$0830 - ABEND=S000 U1035 REA ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LACKING REGION CARD ",
  "SOLUTION": "ADDED REGION=0M TO JOB AND RESTARTED FROM TOP. JOB ENDED-OK. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1030",
  "PROBLEM": "IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT USER COMPLETION CODE=0001 TIME=22.19.17 SEQ=05337 CPU=0000 ASID=0032 PSW AT TIME OF ERROR 078D1000 88502B46 ILC 2 INTC 0 ACTIVE LOAD MODULE ADDRESS=08500668 OFFSET= NAME=CKPE80AP DATA AT PSW 08502B40 - 00181610 0A0D5850 D04C1255 GPR 0-3 80000000 80000001 000052E4 88502A9A GPR 4-7 0851DAE4 00000000 00000000 00FDA488 GPR 8-11 0856D028 0851DB28 08573028 08502BC0 GPR 12-15 0851DB10 08502BC0 88502B18 00000000 END OF SYMPTOM DUMP ",
  "ANALYSIS": "USING ST QUEUE I WAS ABLE TO VIEW SYSLST AND SEE AN ERROR MSG: SPECIFIED RUNDATE INCONSISTENT WITH LAST RUNDATE OF 76 CONTROL RECORD(HEADER ON POLICY FILE). HINT: ALWAYS CHECK THE DATES AT TOP OF CURR AND PREV SEQ POLICIES FILES: CURR: CL.CL$$1020.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN(0) PREV: CL.CL$$1020.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN(-1) THE DATES IN THESE FILES MUST MATCH THE DATES IN PARMDAT5. TAKING A CLOSER LOOK I WAS ABLE TO DETERMINE: CL.CL$$1020.POLSEQ.EXTSRIN(0) WAS CREATED AS AN EMPTY FILE WITH NO DATA AND NO DATE RECORD. HOWEVER, CL$$1020 HAD ENDED CC-0. SO, I RAN A TEST JOB OF CL$$1020 USING PRODUCTION FILES\/CARDLIBS AND WAS ABLE TO CAPTURE THE SYSLST TO HOLD QUEUE. THE ERROR MESSAGE WAS: SPECIFIED RUNDATE INCONSISTENT WITH LAST RUNDATE OF 76 CONTROL RECORD(HEADER ON POLICY FILE). SO, BASCICALLY, CL$$1020 RAN WITH AN INVALID PARMDAT4 DATE. IT RAN WITH 01311999 AND SHOULD HAVE BEEN 02011999. SINCE PARMDAT4 CHANGED, PARMDAT5 HAS TO BE CHANGED AS WELL ",
  "SOLUTION": "UNCATALOG\/DELETE CURRENT EMPTY FILE RERAN CL$$1020 FROM TOP WITH OVERRIDE TO PICKUP CORRECT DATE CARD. RERAN CL$$1030 FROM TOP WITH OVERRIDE TO PICKUP CORRECT DATE CARD. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0820",
  "PROBLEM": "IEW4000I FETCH FOR MODULE CKCSSGI1 FROM DDNAME JOBLIB F CSV031I LIBRARY ACCESS FAILED FOR MODULE CKCSSGI1, RETURN +CKLD01 - LOAD OF CKCSSGI1 UNSUCCESSFUL IEW4000I FETCH FOR MODULE CKCSSGI2 FROM DDNAME JOBLIB F CSV031I LIBRARY ACCESS FAILED FOR MODULE CKCSSGI2, RETURN +CKLD01 - LOAD OF CKCSSGI2 UNSUCCESSFUL IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=80A REASON CODE=00000010 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "80A INDICATES LACKING VIRTUAL STORAGE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "ADDED REGION=0M TO JOB CARD. RERAN FROM TOP. JOB ENDED-OK. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC-1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DID A FIND ON SQL IN THE DUMP. FOUND AN 811 WHICH IS A DUPLICATE ROW. DID A FIND ON BASEOL.PENDING TO FIND THE PROBLEM POLICY. 3465004690. RAN AN SQL TO VIEW THE CLT_OBJ_RELATION TABLE FOR WHO WAS ATTACHED TO THIS POLICY. THE SQL CAN BE FOUND IN 'TEST.CL.DLCJCL(SQL$LVL1)' THERE IS A WHOLE SERIES OF SQLS CALLED SQL$LVL1,SQL$LVL2, SQL$LVL3. THESE ARE DESIGNED TO EMULATE CKCSTGET WHICH IS USED BY CKAP34V. THIS PROBLEM USUALLY IS RELATED TO THE DATA IN THE RESULTS FROM SQL$LVL1. LOOK FOR DUPLICATE RLT_TYP_CD THIS REFLECTS THE PERSON ASSOCIATED TO THE POLICY AND IF THEY ARE THE 1ST OR SECOND OR THIRD...ECT...ECT OF THIS PERSON TYPE ASSOCIATED TO THE POLICY. SO, THE CODE IS 4 POSITIONS WITH PERSON CODE AND SEQUENCE. 00=PRIMARY INSURED 10=OWNER 20=PAYOR 30=BENEFICIARY...ECT....ECT IF THERE IS A DUPLICATE RELATIONSHIP SUCH AS 2001 SHOWS UP TWICE...WE NEED TO EXPIRE THE OLD ROW. ",
  "SOLUTION": "TO EXPIRE THE OLD ROW. MODIFY SQL 'TEST.CL.DLCJCL(SQL$FIXP)'. THIS SQL HAS 4 STEPS TO IT. 1)SHOW ALL CLT_OBJ_RELATION ROWS FOR POLICY 2)LIMIT TO ROW YOU WANT TO EXPIRE 3)EXPIRE THE ROW 4)SHOW ALL ROWS AGAIN SO YOU CAN SEE EXPIRED ROW COMMENT OUT THE 3RD SQL UNTIL EVERYTHING ELSE IS SET UP. FOLLOW THE DIRECTIONS IN THE SQL WHEN YOU ARE CONVINCED YOUR SQL IS WORKING AND YOU UNCOMMENT THE UPDATE PIECE...DON'T FORGET YOU HAVE TO DO A COMMIT WHEN YOU EXIT THE SQL REVIEW SCREEN TO GET YOUR CHANGE TO TAKE...ROLLBACK WILL CAUSE YOUR CHANGE NOT TO TAKE EFFECT. SINCE YOU HAVE TO RESTORE CLIENT ANYWAY, YOU CAN TRY THE CORRECTION AND TEST WITH CL$$0011 OR EQUIVALENT. ----------------------------------------- CL$$R010 HAS TO BE RUN TO RESTORE FILES ******* NOTE: CL$$RC10 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL2 ******** CL$$RC10 HAS TO BE RUN TO RESTORE CLIENT THEN YOU HAVE TO EXPIRE THE ROW THEN RUN CL$$0011 OR EQUIVALENT - MAKE SURE CLEAN THEN RESTART CL$$0030 FROM THE TOP ----------------------------------------- 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0125",
  "PROBLEM": "CC 12 ON COMPUSET STEPS ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FILE WAS EMPTY COMING INTO COMPUSET. COMPUSET DOES NOT LIKE EMPTY FILES. ",
  "SOLUTION": "A NEW STEP STEP0040 TO EVALUATE THE INCOMING FILE TO COMPUSET AND IF IT IS EMPTY...RETURN A CC12 SO THE COMPUSET STEPS WILL FLUSH. ALSO, HAD CONTROL-M UPDATED TO SAY A CC12 IN STEP0040 IS OKAY.... 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0110",
  "PROBLEM": "SPACE B37 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "AND COMM.COMM.EXT2 FILE SIZES WERE TO SMALL. THESE ARE FIXED FLAT FILES AND THE DATA IS REPROED INTO THEM EACH NIGHT WITH A REUSE. THEY WERE SIZED FOR 65 RECORDS. THEY RECEIVED 258 RECORDS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "THE OLD FILES. RECREATE THEM IN A LARGER SIZE. RESTART THE JOB IN STEP0170. THIS LOADS THE FILES. THE RESTORE JOB WILL NEED TO BE UPDATED TO REFLECT THE ENLARGEMENT AS IT CREATES THESE FILES FROM SCRATCH. THE FILES WERE ENLARGED TO ALLOW 300 RECORDS AS BASE. BILL TURNER UPDATED THE RESTORE JOB. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP0020 RETURNED A CC OF 12 WITH AN SB37 ON THE SEQUEN FILE AND THE NEXT 6 STEPS EXECUTED UNTIL STEP0090 ABENDED WITH A SOC1. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "REAL PROBLEM WAS THE SB37 (SPACE) IN STEP0020, THE OTHER STEPS SHOULD NOT HAVE EXECUTED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "TRIED HAVING THE OPERATOR PUT IN AN OVERRIDE TO BUMP UP THE SPACE ON THAT FILE, BUT BECAUSE OF THE DB2 PROC THE OVERRIDE DID NOT WORK. LUCKILY GERRY REESE WAS THERE AND HAS UPDATE ACCESS TO THE AUL1.PROCLIB, SO HE MADE THE SPACE CHANGE TO THE PRODUCTION PROC. WE RESTARTED THE JOB AT THE BEGINNING AND IT RAN FINE. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$R700",
  "PROBLEM": "SPECIAL HOLIDAY RUN OF TCI TO GENERATE A $0 FILE WHEN THE MARKETS ARE OPEN AND AUL IS CLOSED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "NEED TO REQUEST THESE 3 JOBS TO RUN. CL$$R730 ",
  "SOLUTION": "1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0040",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP0120 RECEIVED A OC4. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOLLOWED STEPS DOCUMENTED ON 11\/17\/98 FOR THE SAME PROBLEM. DUMP POINTED TO 3465004120 RAN TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$T0040) TO LOOK AT THE SORTED ACTIVITY FILE, TEST.CL.CL$T0040.TRANSRT. WE THOUGHT THE PREVIOUS POLICY BEFORE 4120 WOULD HAVE AN IMBALANCE OF PO'S AND PN'S. IN THIS CASE, POLICY 4110 WAS GOOD AND 4120 WAS THE POLICY WITH THE IMBALANCE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "MANUALLY DELETED 3465004120 ACTIVITY FROM TEST.CL.CL$T0040.TRANSRT RESTARTED CL$T0040 IN STEP0120. JOB ENDED OK, WHICH PROVED THAT DROPPING 4120 WOULD SOLVE THE PROBLEM. CONSULTED SANDI: FROM HERE, WE BOTH AGREED THAT DROPPING THE ACTIVITY FOR 3465004120 USING 3-STEP WAAPDSUT WAS NECESSARY. PERFORM THE 3 STEP DROP PROCEDURE ON ACTIVITY FILE. RESTARTED CL$$0040 FROM TOP. JOB ENDED OK. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0040",
  "PROBLEM": "B37 ON STEP0340 SEQUEN6 IEC030I B37-04,IFG0554A,CL$$0040,STEP0340,SEQUEN6,0B23,PUB004 IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=B37 REASON CODE=00000004 TIME=22.09.39 SEQ=10313 CPU=0000 ASID=0029 PSW AT TIME OF ERROR 075C1000 80E719FA ILC 2 INTC 0D NO ACTIVE MODULE FOUND NAME=UNKNOWN ",
  "ANALYSIS": "RAN OUT OF SPACE FOR AGENT BACKUPS. OCCURS 3 TIMES IN THE PROC CL$$0040. ",
  "SOLUTION": "SHORT TERM: PUT IN TEMP OVERRIDE TO INCREASE PRIMARY ALLOCATION. INCREASE (150,150) TO (300,300) LONG TERM: CHANGED CL$$0040 AGNT BKUP STEPS TO HAVE THE FOLLOWING SPACE ALLOCATION. \/\/ SPACE=(23200,(2300,1000),RLSE,,ROUND), 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0040",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP0120 RECEIVED A OC4. THE DUMP INDICATES A PROBLEM AT DISPLACEMENT 3EA2 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WOW THIS IS MESSY. STEP 1 IS TO FIGURE OUT WHAT POLICY IS CAUSING THE PROBLEM. LOOK IN THE DUMP AT BLW=0 DISPLACEMENT 202. THERE SHOULD BE A POLICY THERE. THIS IS THE POLICY WHICH PROBABLY ABENDED BUT NOT NECCESSARILY THE POLICY WHICH CAUSED THE PROBLEM. IN ALL LIKELY HOOD, THE POLICY IMMEDIATLY IN FRONT OF THIS POLICY CAUSED THE PROBLEM. THIS IS NOT TO BE CONFUSED WITH THE POLICY RIGHT IN FRONT OF THIS POLICY IN THE ACTIVITY FILE, THE FILE GOING INTO STEP0120 IS SORTED. THERE IS A TOOL IN TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$T0040) WHICH COULD BE USED TO CATALOG THE SORTED DSN TO DETERMINE WHAT POLICIES ARE IN FRONT OF THE ONE WHICH ABENDED. ONE THING TO WATCH FOR IN YOUR NEWLY CATALOGUED SORTED ACTIVITY FILE, LOOK FOR POLICY RECORD TYPE 'C'(1ST POSITION OF RECORD) THESE SHOULD BE FOLLOWED BY 3-'PO', 3-'PN', AND AN OPTIONAL 'Z' RECORD TYPE. THE KEY IS IF YOU SEE AN UNEVEN NUMBER OF 'PO' TO 'PN' RECORDS...THESE ARE SUSPECT. THEN IT IS A MATTER OF DROP AND RUN UNTIL YOU ISOLATE THE PROBLEM POLICY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DROP THE RECORDS FROM THE ACTIVITY FILE FOR THE PROBLEM POLICY. 1- RAN JOB REPRO IN TEST.CL.TOOLS TO CREATE SEQ ACT FILE 2- RAN JOB DROPREC IN TEST.CL.TOOLS FOR THE POLICY (FIRECALL)3- RAN JOB REPACT TO RELOAD THE CHANGED ACTIVITY FILE TO PRODUCTION. THIS JOB WAS RUN UNDER FIRECALL. 4- RESTARTED THE JOB FROM THE TOP SUCCESSFULLY NOTE: STEP0010 GETS A CC8 DUE TO TWO DATA SETS THE JOB COULD NOT FIND TO DELETE. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0120",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP0180 ABENDED WITH CC 8, OUT OF SEQUENCE ERROR IDCAMS SYSTEM SERVICES REPRO INFILE (QSAM1) OUTFILE (VSAM1) REUSE IDC3302I ACTION ERROR ON CL.VSAM.BASEOL.LISTBILL IDC3314I **RECORD OUT OF SEQUENCE - KEY FOLLOWS: 000000 D200C4F3 F4F6F540 40404040 40198C34 3C000000 1C IDC0005I NUMBER OF RECORDS PROCESSED WAS 3 IDC0001I FUNCTION COMPLETED, HIGHEST CONDITION CODE WAS 8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE LISTBILL FILE ONLY HAD 3 RECORDS IN IT WHICH LOOKED LIKE A HEADER RECORD AND 2 GARBAGE RECORDS. SPOKE WITH DAVID, HE SAID LISTBILL ISN'T TECHNICALLY IN YET. SO I DECIDED TO EDIT THE LISTBILL FILE. ..K.C3465 ........0..........INITLOAD....212305 ..K.U ........0.......... .......... ..K.U ........0.......... .......... ",
  "SOLUTION": "MADE A BACKUP OF LISTBILL FILE: TEST.CL.WET.LISTBILL.D1116 UNDER FIRECALL, I DELETED THE LAST TWO RECORDS. RERAN JOB FROM TOP-JOB ENDED OK. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0040",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP0120 RECEIVED A SOC7. THE PENDING POLICY WAS 3465003720. LOAD: CKOA02 PGM: CKOAMPSE CALLED CKDCCFIN <- DOWN IN THIS MODULE ",
  "ANALYSIS": "EARLIER TODAY, DAVID DETERMINED THE PENDING RECORD HAS THE FOLLOWING PROBLEMS: 1. REQUESTED ISSUE DATE = 11\/01\/1199 2. PAID TO DATE = 01\/01\/1200 NOTE: THE ABENDING PROGRAM CKOAMPSE ABENDED WHEN CALLING DATE ROUTINE, CKDCCFIN, AT DISPLACEMENT 0B6. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DECIDED TO DROP THE RECORDS FROM THE ACTIVITY FILE FOR THAT POLICY. 1- RAN JOB REPRO IN TEST.CL.TOOLS TO CREATE SEQ ACT FILE 2- RAN JOB DROPREC IN TEST.CL.TOOLS FOR THE POLICY (FIRECALL)3- RAN JOB REPACT TO RELOAD THE CHANGED ACTIVITY FILE TO PRODUCTION. THIS JOB WAS RUN UNDER FIRECALL. 4- RESTARTED THE JOB FROM THE TOP SUCCESSFULLY NOTE: STEP0010 GETS A CC8 DUE TO TWO DATA SETS THE JOB COULD NOT FIND TO DELETE. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0040",
  "PROBLEM": "STEP0120 RECEIVED A SOC4. THE PENDING POLICY WAS 3465003720. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SPENT TIME LOOKING AT THE POLICY TO SEE IF WE WERE MISSING AN AGENT RECORD SINCE WE JUST IMPLEMENTED THE AGENT DELETE JOB. THAT DID NOT APPEAR TO BE THE PROBLEM. NOT SURE WHAT THE CAUSE OF THE ABEND WAS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DECIDED TO DROP THE RECORDS FROM THE ACTIVITY FILE FOR THAT POLICY. 1- RAN JOB REPRO IN TEST.CL.TOOLS TO CREATE SEQ ACT FILE 2- RAN JOB DROPREC IN TEST.CL.TOOLS FOR THE POLICY 3- RAN JOB REPACT TO RELOAD THE CHANGED ACTIVITY FILE TO PRODUCTION. THIS JOB WAS RUN UNDER FIRECALL. 4- RESTRATED THE JOB FROM THE TOP SUCCESSFULLY EXCEPT FOR A CC-12 IN STEP0360 WHICH WE HAVE BEEN GETTING. WE ARE GOING TO ADD A DEL\/DEFINE STEP FOR THE ACF PRIOR TO STEP0360 TO RESOLVE THIS PROB. A CC8 OCCURED IN STEP0010. THIS IS OK. THIS STEP TRIED TO REMOVE DATASETS WHICH HAD NOT BEEN RECREATED SINCE WE DID NOT DO A COMPLETE RUN ON THE ABENDING RUN. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0040",
  "PROBLEM": "IDCAMS SYSTEM SERVICES TIME: REPRO - INFILE(VSAM2) - OUTFILE(SEQUEN) IDC3302I ACTION ERROR ON SYS98308.T204301.RA000.CL$$0040.AGNTBKUP.H01 IDC3309I ** RECORD X'0059C500F8' NOT WRITTEN. LENGTH INVALID IDC0005I NUMBER OF RECORDS PROCESSED WAS 36804 IDC0001I FUNCTION COMPLETED, HIGHEST CONDITION CODE WAS 8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DID A HEX SEARCH IN FILE MARVEL FOR X'0059C500F8'. THE BAD AGENT # IS 8157103, WHICH HAS A PARTIAL RECORD. ",
  "SOLUTION": "SINCE ONLY 1 RECORD WAS NOT COPIED TO THE SEQ FILE IN STEP0360, I LET THE CYCLE CONTINUE ON. STEPS 0370 AND 0380 ALREADY RAN WITH CC ZERO. TOLD OPERATOR TO CONTINUE ON WITH NEXT JOB IN CYCLE. WE WILL HAVE TO LOOK AT ACF TOMMORROW AND REBUILD IF NECESSARY. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0015",
  "PROBLEM": "IEF257I CL$$0015 STEP0020 CL$$0015 OUTDD1 - SPACE REQUESTED NOT AVAILABL IEF453I CL$$0015 - JOB FAILED - JCL ERROR - TIME=21.28.00 # IEF272I CL$$0015 STEP0020 CL$$0015 - STEP WAS NOT EXECUTED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "I ENTERPRETED AS NOT ENOUGH SPACE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RAN A LISTCAT ON CL.VSAM.BASEOL.AGENT -USED THESE SETTINGS TO DO SPACE CALC FROM TSO MAIN MENU: E SPACE CALC IT SUGGESTED A CERTAIN AMOUNT OF CYL OR TRKS. I DECIDED TO USE (20,10) CYLINDERS. SET UP A TEST JOB AND TESTED WITH NEW SETTINGS. TEST JOB ENDED OK. REQUESTED A RESTART IN STEP0020 WITH 2 OVERRIDES: -STEP0020.OUTDD1 SPACE=(CYL,(20,10),RLSE) -STEP0030.IUPDATES DD DSN=CL.CL$$0015.ACF.UPDATES(0), DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) RESTARTED JOB AND JOB ENDED IN CC12, NOT OK. HOWEVER, THE JOB RAN THROUGH TO THE END, WHICH MEANT THE UPDATES WERE APPLIED. CYCLE WAS STILL ON HOLD. TO START OVER, I DID: -USED FIRECALL TO DELETE CL.BEFORE.UPDATE.ACF TO AVOID NOT CAT 2. -HAD PCD RUN CL$$RAGT WITH OVERRIDE TO USE CL.AGENT.DALY(0) AS INPUT. -RERAN CL$$0015 WITH RESTART IN STEP0020 WITH 2 OVERRIDES MENTIONED EARLIER. -JOB ENDED OK. WERE NOT SURE WHY OVERRIDES DID NOT WORK FIRST TIME. I LATER FOUND OUT THAT THE REAL PROBLEM WAS MOST LIKELY THAT THE SYSTEM COULD NOT GET ENOUGH CONTIGUOUS TRKS, WHICH MEANT I SHOULD HAVE LOWERED THE TRKS. IN ANY CASE, THE CYL OVERRIDE WAS ONE WAY TO ALLOW THE SYSTEM TO GET THE REQUIRED SPACE. SINCE WE HAVE A BACKUP OF ACF IN CL$$0010, WE MAY GET RID OF THE STEP0020 BACKUP IN CL$$0015. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0017",
  "PROBLEM": "CC=12 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED IN SYSPRINT FOR STEP0020 TO SEE WHICH VSAM FILE HAD RECEIVED THE ERROR. IT WAS THE LISTBILL FILE. I LOOKED AT THE FILE THROUGH FILE MARVEL AND FOUND THE FILE TO BE EMPTY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "WE NEED TO INTIALIZE THE FILE BY RUNNING TEST.CL.TOOLS(PBLDELB). THEN HAVE OPS TAG CL$$0017 AS OK AND MOVE THE CYCLE FORWARD. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0017",
  "PROBLEM": "CC=80A ",
  "ANALYSIS": "REGION CARD MISSING ",
  "SOLUTION": "WHEN EXAMINING THIS. NOTICED REST OF CYCLE HAD CONTINUED. SO, WE DID NOT RUN THIS JOB. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0866",
  "PROBLEM": "STOP 8 OR CC 8 IN COMPOSE STEP ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOUND TAG ERRORS. THIS LOOKS TO BE DUE TO CHANGES WITH TAG FILES MOVED TO PRODUCTION BUT THE PROGRAMS DID NOT MOVE TO PRODUCTION. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DELAYED HANDLING OF THE ISSUE. RE-CREATED THE RUN OUT OF TEST. USING TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$$0860) THEN TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$$0866). 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0866",
  "PROBLEM": "PRINTED ON INCORRECT PAPER ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED AT PROC FOR WRAP FILES AND TO SEE IF INPUT DATASETS EXIST. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DELETE CL.CL$$0866.OTAGAGNT(-0) DELETE CL.CL$$0866.OTAGCUST(-0) DELETE CL.CL$$0866.BKUPSTMT.HIST(-0) RESTART FROM THE TOP. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0865",
  "PROBLEM": "PRINTED ON INCORRECT PAPER ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED AT PROC FOR WRAP FILES AND TO SEE IF INPUT DATASETS EXIST. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DELETE CL.CL$$0865.OTAGAGNT(-0) DELETE CL.CL$$0865.OTAGCUST(-0) RESTART FROM THE TOP. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0840",
  "PROBLEM": "PRINTED ON THE WRONG PAPER...NEEDED A RE-RUN ",
  "ANALYSIS": "EXAMINED JCL FOR WRAP AROUND FILES AND TO MAKE SURE INPUT FILE WAS STILL THERE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DELETE CL.CL$$0840.OTAGCON(-0) DELETE CL.CL$$0840.CONARCH(-0) RE-START JOB FROM THE TOP. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0846",
  "PROBLEM": "TAG FILE ERRORS - STOP 8 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FIRST LOOKED IN THE JES FOR ERROR MESSAGES ABOUT COMPUSET FILES NOT BEING AVAILABLE....THIS DID NOT SHOW UP. SO, I LOOKED IN THE OUTPUT FROM THE STEP THAT HAD THE STOP 8 AND FOUND REFERENCE TO TAG FILE ERRORS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CONTINUE WITH THE CYCLE. HOLD CL$$0846. TURN THIS OVER TO A COMPUSET EXPERT NEXT BUSINESS DAY. FOUND THE POLICY PAGES PRINTED OK. THIS COULD JUST BE A WARNING MESSAGE. 10\/19\/98 FOUND STYLE FILE CHANGES HAD BEEN MADE BUT THE PROGRAM WAS STILL IN TEST. RAN THE STUFF THOUGH TEST USING TEST.CL.TOOLS(CL$$0845). THEN FOR THE INDIVIDUAL STATES WHICH HAD TAG PROBLEMS, RAN TEST.CL.TOOLS (CL$$0847) CHANGING THE STATE CODE IN 3 PLACES. THIS CAN BE DONE FOR STATES IN CL$$0846 OR CL$$0847. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0040",
  "PROBLEM": "CC 8 - INVALID LENGTH ERROR ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PROBLEM CAME FROM NOT RUNNING CL$$0015 STEP0030 IN THE PREVIOUS CYCLE. SOMEHOW AN INCOMPLETE AND INVALID RECORD WAS PUT UP PROBABLY FROM THE PROGRAM IN STEP0040. I WAS ABLE TO ISOLATE THE AGENT WITH THE PROBLEM BY DOING A HEX FIND USING THE KEY PROVIDED BY IDCAMS ON THE VSAM AGENT FILE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "I LET THE CYCLE MOVE FORWARD SINCE THERE DID NOT APPEAR TO BE ANY OTHER SIDE EFFECTS. THE NEXT BUSINESS DAY, I DETERMINED WHERE THE ERROR OCCURED AND REBUILT THE ACF FROM THE BACKUP PRIOR TO THE PROBLEM CYCLE AND RUNNING CL$$0015 STEPS 30\/40 UP TO CURRENT DATE. THEN I SET UP CL$$RAGT TO RE-BUILD AND RE-LOAD THE CORRECTED ACF FILE JUST PRIOR TO THE NIGHTLY CYCLE. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0015",
  "PROBLEM": "NOT ENOUGH SPACE AVAILABLE - CAUSED A JCL ERROR ",
  "ANALYSIS": "OPERATIONS HAD ALREADY DOWNSIZED THE SPACE REQUEST WHEN THEY CALLED ME...THEY JUST WANTED TO KNOW WHERE TO RESTART. I DIALED IN AND LOOKED... ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTART IN STEP0040 WHERE THE JOB WENT DOWN. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "CC0012 - USER COMPLETION CODE 0001 THERE WAS A FUND FILE MAINT ERROR OUT OF THIS STEP THAT SAID 'AP0357 - ALL FUNDS HAVE NOT BEEN VERIFIED FOR USER, SEVERE ERROR - RUN ABORTED FOR THIS USER'. ERROR MSG FOUND IN STEP0210 SYSLST. TO GET MORE INFO YOU LOOK AT STEP0100 SYSLST. STEP0100 IS WHERE FUND FILE MAINT TAKES PLACE-CKFFMAIN. THERE WERE MSGS FOR EACH FUND THAT SAID 'UNIT-VALUE REQUIRED'. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WE WERE TRYING TO PROCESS FOR A 3 DAY WEEKEND, IT APPEARED THAT NOT ALL UNIT VALUES HAD BEEN ENTERED. WE COULD NOT DETERMINE FROM THE REPORTS WHAT THE LAST VALUATION DATE WAS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DAN TALKED TO DAN SCHLUGE, IT WAS DECIDED THAT WE WOULD USE OUR BATCH INPUT CARDS FOR THE UNIT VALUES, GOING WITH THE VALUES THAT HAD BEEN ENTERED ONLINE. SO I CREATED A TEST.CL.CARDLIB(FUNDS) MEMBER THAT CONTAINS ALL PRODUCTION FUNDS AND UPDATED THE VALUES TO BE WHAT WAS PRINTED ON THE REPORT OUT OF STEP0100 SEQUEN2 UNIT VALUE-I. WE DECIDED TO USE A DATE RANGE OF 9\/5\/98 TO 9\/8\/98. IT DID NOT LIKE THAT DATE RANGE AND SO I TRIED 2 OTHER ATTEMPTS USING 9\/6-9\/8 AND 9\/4-9\/8. AFTER ALL THE ATTEMPTS FAILED, DAN DETERMINED WE PROBABLY NEEDED TO IGNORE WHATEVER ONLINE UPDATING OCCURED DURING THE DAY, SO WE LOADED THE FUND VAL FILE FROM AFTER THE LAST CYCLE. USED OUR BATCH CARDS DATED 9\/5 THRU 9\/8 AND IT WORKED. FOR RESTARTING THE JOB, FIRST WE RAN CL$$R060 WITH *********** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** AN OVERRIDE FOR THE FUNDVAL FILE, THEN RAN CL$$RC30 WITH THE CORRECT G0000V00 NUMBERS, THEN RESTARTED CL$$0100 FROM THE TOP WITH AN OVERRIDE FOR STEP0080. SORTIN DD DSN=TEST.CL.CARDLIB(FUNDS). 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0100",
  "PROBLEM": "S222 (EXCEEDED 1 HOUR OF CPU TIME) THE SYSTEM DEFAULT FOR CPU TIME FOR A JOB IS 1 HOUR. AN S222 IS ISSUED (WITHOUT A DUMP) WHEN THIS LIMIT IS EXCEEDED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "MR STATISTICS. AVERAGE CPU TIME WAS 15 MIN. *********** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** DECIDED TO RELOAD FILES (CL$$R060 & CL$$RC30) AND RERUN, THIS TIME WATCHING THE CPU TIME AND SIO COUNTS IN THE SDSF QUEUES, AND TO REQUEST THE JOB TO BE CANCELLED WITH A DUMP TO HOPEFULLY FIND A POLICY NUMBER. THE RERUN REVEALED THE JOB WAS IN FACT LOOPING. SIO COUNTS WENT TO ZERO AND CPU TIME DOUBLED AFTER 15 MINUTES IN STEP0210. JOB WAS CANCELLED WITH A DUMP. A POLICY NUMBER WAS FOUND IN THE DUMNP THAT MATCHED THE LAST POLICY NUMBER ON THE TIME DRIVEN ERROR REG. AS WELL AS THE POLICY NUMBER IN AN EMAIL DISCUSSING THE PROBLEMS WITH THIS POLICY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DROPPED THE POLICY RECORD. ABENDED LATER IN CL$$0100 BECAUSE THE ACTIVITY WAS NOT DROPPED. AT THAT POINT WE RAN OUT OF TIME AND HAD TO SCRAP THE CYCLE. IF THIS EVER HAPPENS AGAIN (LOOP IN CKAP01V) I WANT TO TRY TO SUSPEND THE POLICY VIA FMB (CL$$0018). TO SUSPEND A PROD POLICY, RUN TEST.CL.TOOLS(SUSPEND) AFTER RESTORING THE MASTER FILES TO THE PRE-CL$$0100 *********** NOTE: CL$$RC30 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL4 ******** STATE. RUN CL$$0060 AND CL$$RC30 WITH CORRECT GDG. THEN RUN CL$$0018 WITH OVERRIDE TO SUSPEND. THEN RE-RUN CL$$0100 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0700",
  "PROBLEM": "BOTH STEPS ENDED IN CC12. STEP=STEP0010 PGM=STOUTL EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 STEP=STEP0010 PGM=STOUTL EXECUTED - COND CODE 0012 CMU007S - VSAM ALLOCATE\/OPEN FAILED FOR VCF FILE, RC=252 RSN=00000004 ERC=021000 CMU013I - UTILITY COMPLETED, HIGHEST RETURN CODES ARE, THIS UTILITY 12, ",
  "ANALYSIS": "BOTH STEPS ENDED IN CC12. WE CONSULTED WAYNE MCSPADDEN, MAILBOX TECH SUPPORT. HE THINKS THERE WAS A CONFLICT OF RUNNING CL$$0700 AT THE SAME TIME HIS MAILBOX JOBS (CMFT0050 AND CMFT0100). CL$$0700(THE WHOLE CL SCHEDULE) WAS DELAYED TONIGHT BECAUSE BILL WAS DOING THE UL TEAMID CONVERSION. AS A RESULT CL$$0700 RAN ABOUT 9:00PM WHICH IS THE TIME MAILBOX USUALLY RUNS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTARTED THE JOB IN JSTEP020.STEP0010 BECAUSE THIS IS A MULTI-PROC PROC, JSTEP030.STEP0010 WAS ALSO RAN. AS A RESULT, BOTH CC12 WERE RESET TO 0 AND THE AMERICAN AND FIDELITY FILE WERE SENT TO THE MAILBOX. ALSO, WE WILL BE PUTTING A NEGATIVE DEPENDENCY ON CL$$0700, SO THAT IT DOES NOT RUN AT THE SAME TIME AS CMFT0050 AND CMFT0100. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0840",
  "PROBLEM": "THE JOB ENDED-OK WITH ALL STEPS CONDITION 0. HOWEVER, REESE CALLED AND SAID THE PRINTER DID NOT PRINT THE LAST PAGE ON THE PROPER FORM. CAN WE RERUN THE JOB TO GET THE CORRECT OUTPUT? ",
  "ANALYSIS": "SINCE NO OTHER JOBS DEPEND ON CL$$0840, AND PER ROUGH DRAFT OF RESTART INSTRUCTIONS, WE CAN RERUN FROM THE TOP. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD REESE RERUN THE JOB FROM THE TOP. SINCE THE LAST STEP WAS RAN TWICE, GDG CL.CL$$0840.CONARCH(+1) WAS CREATED TWICE. TO REMEDY, USING FIRECALL, =3.2, 'U' UNCATALOG, CL.CL$$0840.CONARCH.G0029V00, THE EXTRA FILE WAS DELETED. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0847",
  "PROBLEM": "REGION WAS DOWN WHICH CAUSED JOB TO HAVE A PROBLEM. OPERATIONS JUST WANTED RESTART INSTRUCTIONS. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "NONE ",
  "SOLUTION": "RESTART JOB FROM THE TOP. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$UIAF",
  "PROBLEM": "S005 ABEND ",
  "ANALYSIS": "AT FIRST IT LOOKED LIKE A SYSTEM ERROR, BUT IT ALSO SAID SYNTAX ERROR. WITH SANDI'S HELP, SHE DETERMINED IT WAS SPACING PROBLEM ON THE CARDLIB. THE DATA IN A SORT CARD MUST START IN COLUMN 2, NOT COLUMN 1. ",
  "SOLUTION": "I COPIED THE CARD TO TEST.CL.CARDLIB(CLS01010), EDITED IT AND HAD THE OPERATOR PUT AN OVERRIDE IN TO POINT TO THIS CARD AND RESTART FROM THE TOP. JOB ENDED OK. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0011",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC1 ABEND ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOUND THE POLICY NUMBER BY LOOKING AT THE PRINTOUT FROM THE STEP. THE LAST POLICY NUMBER SHOWING ON THE REPORT IS USUALLY THE PROBLEM CASE. THIS PROBLEM IS SIMILAR TO THE ONE REPORTED FOR JOB CL$$0030 SOC1. AFTER THAT PROBLEM WE ADDED THE EXECUTION OF CL$$0011 TO OUR NIGHTLY CYCLE TO CATCH THESE PROBLEMS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DID THE FOLLOWING 1- FM THE PENDING FILE TO DELETE THE BAD POLICY\/S UNDER FIRECALL 2- FM THE AUXSEG2 FILE TO DELETE THE BAD POLICIES UNDER FIRECALL 3- CREATE ACTIVITY FILE COPY TEST.CL.TOOLS(REPRO) 4- RUN WAAPD AGAINST ACTIVITY FILE COPY TEST.CL.TOOLS(DROPREC) 5- RELOAD NEW ACTIVITY FILE UNDER FIRECALL TEST.CL.TOOLS(REPACT) 6- RUN CKAP34V TO BE SURE NO MORE PROBLEMS TEST.CL.TOOLS(CKAP34V) 6.5-PUT A HOLD ON CL$$0015 OR NEXT JOB AFTER CL$$0011 IN THE CYCLE 7- RUN CL$$0011 FROM THE TOP TO MAKE SURE OKAY 8- HAVE CL$$0010 RUN AGAIN TO BACKUP CORRECTED FILES 9- RELEASE THE JOB WHICH HAD THE HOLD IN STEP 6.5 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0020",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC-7 IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=0C7 REASON CODE=00000007 TIME=19.28.08 SEQ=03994 CPU=0000 ASID=002F PSW AT TIME OF ERROR 078D2000 8005735A ILC 6 INTC 0 ACTIVE LOAD MODULE ADDRESS=000067E0 OFFSET= NAME=CKDPFSPS DATA AT PSW 00057354 - FCA5DAE0 45F7940F DAE3F075 GPR 0-3 083C7D00 083C84A0 083F9028 00000016 GPR 4-7 083F903E 083C7638 0004B24C 083F9028 GPR 8-11 083CB028 083CC028 0004A24C 000570C6 GPR 12-15 0004A1F8 083C79C0 8005727A 00000000 END OF SYMPTOM DUMP IEF450I CL$$0020 STEP0030 JSTEP010 - ABEND=S0C7 U0000 REA ",
  "ANALYSIS": "I QUICKLY DETERMINED THIS WAS NOT GOING TO BE SOMETHING I WAS GOING TO FIGURE OUT IN A FEW HOURS. ",
  "SOLUTION": "9\/21\/1998 WE NEED TO DO POLICY PAGES FOR OTHER POLICIES SO I COPIED THE PRODUCTION FILE CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT. G00XXV00 TO MY TEST FILE TEST.CL.SLJ.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT AND DELETED THE BAD POLICY FROM MY FILE. THEN HAD AN OVERRIDE PUT IN CL$$0020 FOR \/\/STEP0030.SEQUEN DD DSN=TEST.CL.SLJ.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT AND RESTARTED THE JOB AT STEP0030. --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! 4\/13\/2004 S JEFFS JOB CL$T0020 IS SETUP IN TEST.CL.TOOLS TO USE AS A TEST USING PRODUCTION FILES. IT CAN BE USED TO VERIFY THE RUN BEFORE RERUNNING THE PRODUCTION JOB. WE HAD TROUBLE DETERMINING THE BAD POLICY BY LOOKING AT THE IDIREPRT DUMP. WHEN YOU LOOK FOR THE 'SEQUEN' DD, WHICH IS THE INPUT FILE IT WOULD INDICATE A POLICY NUMBER HOWEVER THE TRUE PROBLEM POLICY WAS THE ONE PRIOR TO THE 'PREVIOUS RECORD'. THAT'S WHY IF YOU THINK YOU KNOW THE PROBLEM POLICY, IT'S BEST TO TRY PULLING IT IN A TEST RUN TO BE SURE. LE NAME . . . . . . . . . : SEQUEN DATA SET NAME . . . . . . : CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G2780V00 FILE ATTRIBUTES . . . . . : ORGANIZATION=SEQUENTIAL, ACCESS MODE=N\/A, RECFM=VARIABLE BLOCKED LAST I\/O FUNCTION . . . . : READ OPEN STATUS . . . . . . . : I-O PREVIOUS RECORD . . . . . : RECORD DATA LENGTH 90, VARIABLE RECORD ADDRESS OFFSET HEX EBCDIC -------- --------- ----------------------------------- ---------------- 0041732F E9D6204C 103C00BD 4D9500F2 F0F5F2F2 *ZO.<....(N.2052 0041733F +10 F9F8F0F7 F000BD4D 95C9F6F0 F6E300F5 *98070..(NI606T. 0041734F +20 F6F0F0E0 00000000 00000000 002E0000 *600\\........... 0041735F +30 E2D700F2 F0F5F2F2 F9F8F0F7 F0000000 *SP.2052298070.. SOLUTION: THIS JOB CREATES FILES FOR POLICY PAGES. PUT CL$$0020 ON HOLD ALONG WITH CL$$0845, CL$$0846, CL$$0847. HAD OPERATIONS ALLOW CL$$0030 TO GO AHEAD AND RUN WITH THE REST OF THE CYCLE. THE NEXT DAY, WE DETERMINED WHAT POLICY WENT DOWN. PULLED THE POLICY AND RESTARTED CL$$0020 IN STEP0030 WITH SYMBOLIC GDG01 OVERRIDDEN TO -0 INSTEAD OF +1. --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! OH YEAH, BACKUP THE FILE PRIOR TO DELETING THE BAD POLICY. THIS PROCESS CAN ACTUALLY BE FOLLOWED AT ABEND TIME. THIS WILL NOT HOLD UP OTHER POLICY PAGES. P1DLC FIGURED OUT WHAT WAS CAUSING THE PROBLEM AND PUT IN PROGRAMATIC FIX.....HOPEFULLY.THIS PROBLEM IS GONE. --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0846",
  "PROBLEM": "CONDITION CODE 8 IEC161I 052(009)-084,CL$$0846,EMITTER XICSIL,VSRN02,,, IEC161I XICS.COMPUSET.DCLIB3,XICS.COMPUSET.DCLIB3.DATA,CATALOG.TEC IEC161I 052(009)-084,CL$$0846,EMITTER XICSIL,VSRN02,,, IEC161I XICS.COMPUSET.DCLIB3,XICS.COMPUSET.DCLIB3.DATA,CATALOG.TEC +AFB002I STOP 8 ",
  "SOLUTION": "RAN JOB AGAIN FROM THE TOP. RAN OKAY. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0840",
  "PROBLEM": "THE IDCAMS STEP TO VERIFY THE COMPUSET FILE GOT A CC 12. THEN THE LATER COMPOSE AND EMITTER COMPUSET STEPS FLUSHED. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "OTHER JOBS MAY BE USING THE COMPUSET FILES. AUL1MASST451\/AUL1ABS$0102 BOTH MAKE USE OF THE JOB. THE VERIFY WANTS EXCLUSIVE RIGHTS TO THE FILE WHICH IS CAUSING A CC 12. ",
  "SOLUTION": "TRY RUNNING AGAIN. I CHECKED A 'WHOENQ' ON THE FOLLOWING DSN'S UNTIL THEY WERE FREE. XICS.COMPUSET.DCLIB1 XICS.COMPUSET.DCLIB2 XICS.COMPUSET.DCLIB3 BEFORE RESTARTING THE JOB, I WENT INTO FIRECALL AND DELETED THE CL.CL$$0840.OTAGCON() LATEST GDG AND THE CL.CL$$0840.CONARCH() LATEST GDG, SO THE JOB COULD BE RESTARTED FROM THE TOP WITHOUT OVERRIDES. THOSE STEPS RAN SUCCESSFULLY THAT CREATED THE NEW FILES. ---------------------------------------------------- - CHANGES WERE MADE TO THIS JOB TO MAKE IT RESTARTABLE - FROM THE TOP WITHOUT CLEANUP. WATCH TO MAKE SURE - LAST STEP DID NOT RUN. ----------------------------------------------------- 1 "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "ASRA ABEND ON 3465000670 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "POLICY PRINT WORKED FINE. 60XX WORKED FINE. THIS IMPLIES THE PENDING MASTER FILE IS NOT HAVING A PROBLEM. LOOKED AT OTHER POLICIES IN SIMILAR STATUS UNDER 60D1 AND THEY WERE OKAY. THE DATA ON THIS SCREEN IS AN ACCUMULATION OF NUMBERS FROM SOURCE FILES OTHER THAN THE PENDING FILE. THERE MUST BE SOME PROBLEM WITH ONE OF THE RELATIONSHIP FILES. ",
  "SOLUTION": "NONE FOUND. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0840",
  "PROBLEM": "DOWN WITH A CC12 IDC3302I ACTION ERROR ON CL.CL$$0840.CONARCH.G0003V00 IDC3309I ** RECORD X'F3F4F6F5F0' NOT WRITTEN. LENGTH INV ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOUND INPUT FILES WERE FIXED BLOCK. THE OUTPUT FILE WAS VARIABLE BLOCK. SINCE THIS IS A BACKUP TAPE OF HISTORY, WE SHOULD USE FB. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CHANGE JCL ON THE 'OUTPUT' DDNAME TO BE RECFM=FB. PUT IN OVERRIDE SO OTAGCON DATASET POINTS TO (-0) GENERATION. THEN RESTART IN STEP0006. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0110",
  "PROBLEM": "+IGZ401I A FILE ATTRIBUTE MISMATCH WAS DETECTED. FILE 'OUT-ANS-FILE' IN PROGRAM 'CKCME010' HAD A RECORD LENGTH OF '175' AND THE FILE SPECIFIED IN THE ASSIGN CLAUSE HAD A RECORD LENGTH OF '181'. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "A CHANGE HAD GONE TO PRODUCTION THAT DAY FOR THIS EXPANSION. FOUND THE JCL HAD MIGRATED BUT THE NEW LINK FOR CLCMCALC DID NOT GET MOVED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "THE LINK STILL EXISTED IN 'TEST.CL.SLJ.LOADLIB'. WE PUT IN A STEPLIB TO USE THE LINK OUT OF THIS LIBRARY. ALSO HAD TO CONCATINATE THE PRODUCTION LOADLIBS INTO THE STEPLIB. HAD TO REPRO THE VSAM AGTFIN FILE FROM THE BACKUPS OUT OF CL$$0060. RESTARTED THE JOB FROM THE TOP. THE NEXT DAY, I RESUBMITTED THE FORM TO MIGRATE THE LOADLIB 'CKCMCALC' TO PRODUCTION. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0120",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC-7 IEA995I SYMPTOM DUMP OUTPUT SYSTEM COMPLETION CODE=0C7 REASON CODE=00000007 TIME=19.37.46 SEQ=15202 CPU=0000 ASID=005C PSW AT TIME OF ERROR 478D1000 8800544A ILC 6 INTC 07 ACTIVE LOAD MODULE ADDRESS=08000208 OFFSET=000 NAME=CKBSFMCT DATA AT PSW 08005444 - FA549112 D249940F 9112960F GPR 0-3 0813E9D4 0813EA78 0803F4B8 08149028 GPR 4-7 08141028 00000000 0814A028 00000000 GPR 8-11 0803F640 08140028 080046DC 080048F6 GPR 12-15 080046D0 0813E830 88005342 00000000 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "FOUND A ROUTE AND TRANSIT NUMBER ONLY HAD 8 POSITIONS. I FOUND THIS BY COMPILING CKBSFMCT AND TRACKING THE FIELD WE WENT DOWN ON AND THE LINE OF CODE WE WENT DOWN ON. I COULD SEE THE FIELD WE WENT DOWN ON WAS THE R&T AND HAD A '40' IN THE LAST POSITION. I THEN LOOKED IN THE VSAM BILLINFO. I COULD FIND THE R&T IN THIS FILE AND FOUND WHAT I BELIEVED TO BE THE 9TH POSITION 70-78 IS THE 9 DIGIT R&T. I THEN LOOKED IN CL.BASEB.BILL.EXTRACTS TO FIND THE R&T. IT WILL BE ON THE '7' RECORD(THIS WILL APPEAR A FEW POSITION TO THE LEFT OF THE R&T)...FIND ON THE 8 DIGIT R&T #. THIS WILL CONFIRM THE CORRECT POLICY. MIGHT WANT TO POKE AROUND A LITTLE IN THIS FILE. IF THERE IS ANOTHER ONE, YOU WILL GO DOWN ON IT AT RE-START TIME. POLICY: 3465000040 R&T: 04121381 CORRECT R&T: 041213814 POLICY: 3465000250 R&T: 07400001 CORRECT R&T: 074000010 ",
  "SOLUTION": "FILE FIX CL.BASEB.BILL.EXTRACTS BY ADDING THE 9TH POSITION TO THE R&T NUMBER. RESTART FROM THE TOP. THE ON-LINE MUST BE DOWN TO RUN THIS JOB THE FOLLOWING FILE IS OPENED UPDATEABLE. CL.VSAM.BASEOL.BILLPMNT IF YOU FORGET THIS. YOU WILL GO DOWN IN STEP0130 WITH A U0001. THIS IS OKAY....YOU CAN HAVE THE JOB STARTED FROM THE TOP AGAIN WHEN CICS IS DOWN OR 'FVDLSBD' IS BROUGHT DOWN. 1 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC1 ABEND ",
  "ANALYSIS": "RAN CKAP34V AGAINST PENDING FILE TO DETERMINE IF A PROBLEM WITH THE POLICY RELATED TO THE DATABASE. IF THE PRINT PENDING RUNS GOOD THEN THE DATABASE IS NOT THE PROBLEM. HOWEVER IN THIS CASE THE PROBLEM WAS THERE WAS NO INFO ON CLIENT FOR THE PENDING POLICY. SO THE PRINT PENDING JOB DOES ABEND, AND THERE WAS MORE THAN 1 POLICY. SO YOU HAVE TO KEEP RUNNING THE PRINT PENDING TO FIND ALL THE POLICIES. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DID THE FOLLOWING STEPS IN ORDER TO GET CYCLE GOING: 1- RUN CL$$R010 TO RESTORE FILES ******* NOTE: CL$$RC10 WAS REPLACED WITH CL$$RCL2 ******** 2- RUN CL$$RC10 TO RESTORE DATABASE 3- FM THE PENDING FILE TO DELETE THE BAD POLICIES UNDER FIRECALL 4- FM THE AUXSEG2 FILE TO DELETE THE BAD POLICIES UNDER FIRECALL 5- CREATE ACTIVITY FILE COPY TEST.CL.SLJPDS(REPRO) 6- RUN WAAPD AGAINST ACTIVITY FILE COPY TEST.CL.SLJPDS(DROPREC) 7- RELOAD NEW ACTIVITY FILE UNDER FIRECALL TEST.CL.SLJPDS(REPACT) 8- RUN CKAP34V TO BE SURE NO MORE PROBLEMS 9- RUN CL$$0010 TO CREATE NEW BACKUPS 10- RUN CL$$0030 FROM TOP "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0910",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB GOT CONDITION CODE 12, WITH S0C1 ABEND IN STEP 20. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "REVIEWED IN EXPEDITER AND FOUND POLICY # 5448855110 INVALID CALL FOR THE 89 SEGMENT. INVALID POLICY - 5449025440 03\/25\/05 LAP ",
  "SOLUTION": "COPIED INPUT FILE TO TEST.CL.CL$$0910.MLIR.D0321 AND DELETED POLICY 5448855110 FROM PROD INPUT FILE. RESTARTED IN STEP0020 - JOB COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0600",
  "PROBLEM": "4039 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DB2 ERROR - +IDI0082E DB2 CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQL RETURN CODE -1 FOR SQLALLOCCONNECT TO DB2 SYSTEM DB2P. ",
  "SOLUTION": "DUE TO CYCLE PROBLEMS, CL$$0600 WAS STILL RUNNING AFTER SYSTEM WAS BROUGHT UP. AFTER REVIEWING POLICY, FELT THAT IT WAS PROBABLY BEING UPDATED BY USERS AT SAME TIME (THIS HAS HAPPENED IN SEVERAL JOBS). DETERMINED THAT WE HAD A GOOD PRICE FILE. CREATED EMPTY FILES FOR REST. FORCED JOB COMPLETE WHICH KICKED OFF THE TRANSMISSION JOBS. REQUESTED OVERRIDE IN THE NEXT NIGHT'S CYCLE TO BRING IN THE -1 ACTIVITY FILE INTO STEP0210: \/\/STEP0210.SORTIN DD DSN=CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT(-1), \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) \/\/ DD DSN=CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT(-0), \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0850",
  "PROBLEM": "4039 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DUE TO OPTIMIZATION THE HIGH AMOUT OF DATA WAS CAUSING THE JOB TO GO DOWN WITH A SPACE ERROR. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD OPS UP THE SPACE ON CL.CL$$0850.ABCAUD TO 750. WITH DAVID'S HELP, HE NOTICED WE HAD TO UP THE SPACE ON FILES IN SUBSEQUENT STEPS. WE HAD OPS UP THE FILE SPACE IN STEPS 40, 50 AND 60 TO 400 TRACKS. CLEANED UP FILES THAT GOT CREATED ON PREVIOUS RUN AND RERAN JOB FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0730",
  "PROBLEM": "4039 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "DUE TO OPTIMIZATION THE HIGH AMOUT OF DATA WAS CAUSING THE JOB TO DO DOWN WITH A SPACE ERROR. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAD PCD UP THE SPACE ON FILE CREATED IN STEP0060. RESTARTED IN STEP0060. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0420",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC4 +IDI0082E DB2 CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQL RETURN CODE -1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS JOB WAS RUNNING DURING THE DAY WHILE USERS WERE HITTING CLIENT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "COULD'VE RESTARTED JOB AND HOPE THAT IT DIDN'T HIT A PARTICULAR CLIENT WHILE A USER WAS UPDATING IT. DECIDED TO CONTACT ACTUARY TO SEE IF THEY ABSOLUTELY NEEDED POLICY EXHIBIT. THEY SAID THEY DIDN'T NEED IT THAT DAY BUT DEFINATELY NEEDED IT THE NEXT DAY. WE PUT CL$$0430 AND CL$$0440 ON HOLD SO THEY DON'T KICK OFF, FORCED OKAY CL$$0420 AND THEN REMOVED CL$$0430 AND CL$$0440. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0820",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC4 +IDI0082E DB2 CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQL RETURN CODE -1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS JOB WAS RUNNING DURING THE DAY WHILE USERS WERE HITTING CLIENT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "JOB STARTED WHILE THE PARMDATE WAS STILL THE PRIOR DAY. WAITED UNTIL PARMDATE CHANGED TO TODAY'S DATE AND RERAN JOB FROM TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0820",
  "PROBLEM": "CC40 IN THE SYSOUT: *************************************** * DATE ON INPUT FILE DOES NOT MATCH * * DATE ON PARM CARD - CHECK PARM CARD * * CHECK INPUT FILE TO MAKE SURE * * CORRECT FILE IS BEING USED * * FILE DATE: 062905 % * PARM DATE: 06-30-05 *************************************** ******************************************** * PROCESS WENT DOWN ON THE FOLLOWING RECORD: ******************************************** *062805 % 062905 % ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE INPUT FILE HAD THE PREVIOUS DAY'S DATE. ",
  "SOLUTION": "USING FIRECALL RHONDA WENT IN AND UPDATED THE DATE IN CL.CL$$0100.STEP0450.DACCTING TO TODAY'S DATE. RERAN JOB FROM THE TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0006",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC4 +IDI0082E DB2 CALL LEVEL INTERFACE ERROR: SQL RETURN CODE -1 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THIS JOB WAS RUNNING DURING THE DAY WHILE USERS WERE HITTING CLIENT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "JOB STARTED WHILE THE PARMDATE WAS STILL THE PRIOR DAY. WAITED UNTIL PARMDATE CHANGED TO TODAY'S DATE AND RERAN JOB FROM TOP. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$2060",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "POLICY 2051068507 CAUSING SOC7 BECAUSE WE ARE TRYING TO CALCULATE THE OWNER'S AGE (CURRENT DATE - BIRTH DATE) ON A CORPORATE IDENTITY (THE TRUST) WHICH HAS NO B'DAY. ",
  "SOLUTION": "UPDATED PROGRAM (BRIAN 04-01-05) TO BYPASS THIS POLICY. PCD RAN ONLY STEP0020 (TEST.CL.LAP.JCLLIB(CL$$2060)) SO THAT THE REPORT WOULD BE AVAILABLE IN CNTL-D. CREATED ISSUE 6360. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1180",
  "PROBLEM": "CC 16 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "CL.TIERCOMM.FROMCL.SORTED HAD 9 3465(VUL) RECORDS. ULTIM ABSCOMM1 ONLY EXTRACTS POLICIES THAT BEGIN WITH 2453. ULTIM ABSTIER MATCHES ABS RECORDS TO CL RECORDS. SINCE THE 9 3465 RECORDS DID NOT MATCH, 9 BLANK RECORDS WERE WRITTEN ON CL.TIERCOMM.ABS.EXTRACT AND CREATED THE CC 16 WHEN PROCESSED IN STEP9040 BY ULTIM ABSTIER1. THE JOB FINISHED AND THE 9 3465 RECORDS WERE ON THE FILE SENT TO ABS, BUT THEIR AMOUNTS WERE WRONG. ",
  "SOLUTION": "MONICA MAXWELL IN AGENTS ACCOUNTING CORRECTED THE RECORDS IN ABS. CREATED ISSUE 6423 TO INCLUDE 3465 POLICIES IN THE FILE CREATED BY ULTIM ABSCOMM1. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0007",
  "PROBLEM": "SOC7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "POLICY 0620175870 HAD C35C IN THE TERMINATION DAY IN THE PAYOR 89 SEGMENT (20\/1). CKDCINEX ABENDED. I DIDN'T REALIZE THE JOB WAS USING THE SA FILE AND HAD THE USER DELETE THE PAYOR AND RE-ADD IT. THE RECORD THEN HAD A 20\/2 SEGMENT. THE CKETRGET ABENDED BECAUSE THE SA VSAM RECORD STILL HAD 20\/1 AND CLIENT HAD 20\/2. KATHY HANNAH WORKED ON IT AND REBUILT THE 20\/1 RECORD AND WE GOT THE BAD TERMINATION DATE AGAIN. I MODIFIED D724MAIN TO BYPASS THE POLICY AND IT WENT DOWN ON 2453368990. AT 11:30 AM, I SCRAPPED THE RUN BECAUSE CLIENT WAS OUT SYNC WITH THE SA FILES & IT TAKES ABOUT 2 HOURS TO RUN. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0020",
  "PROBLEM": "VUL POLICY 3465102120 IS ABENDING WITH A S0C7. STILL TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT IS BAD WITH THIS POLICY. POLICY 3465102130 ALSO ABENDED. CKDPPVGC OFFSET 149E LINE 2264 MOVE WS-DURATION(WS-SUB) TO ... WS-SUB IS PROBABLY ZERO ",
  "ANALYSIS": "I COPIED CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G3484V00 TO P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.G3484BKP THEN DELETED 3465102120 FROM THE PRODUCTION FILE USING FIRECALL ID. I HAD PCD SET UP CL$$0020 OVERRIDES: \/\/ RESTART=JSTEP010.STEP0030, AND \/\/JSTEP010 EXEC PROC=CL$$0020,GDG01='0'. --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! THE RERUN WAS GOOD. EMAILED CYBERLIFE IND AND PRINT TEAM NOTIFYING THEM THAT THE POLICIES WERE PULLED AND DID NOT PRINT. 9\/8\/05 ISSUE 6499\/SPR IN8686 0401 RESOLVED THIS "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0700",
  "PROBLEM": "RECEIVED S0C7 ABEND BECAUSE SORTIN (CL.ADJUST.OUTPUT) CONTAINED INVALID DATA: INVALID AGIVA1SELL.37.36... INVALID AIYIVBSELL.86.26... VALID ALBAGRSELL 1251.49 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "UNKNOWN HOW THE DATA WAS CORRUPTED. LINDA KIENTZ ENTERE ENTERED THE DATA HERSELF AND DID IT THE WAY SHE ALWAYS DOES. AFTER TALKING WITH LINDA FURTHER, SHE EXPLAINED THAT THE FILE IS CREATED BY AN ACCESS DATABASE. SHE MANIPULATED IT VIA DOS ON TUESDAY. SHE SAID SHE DID THE SAME THING LAST WEEK TO CORRECT SOMETHING, BUT IT IS NOT THE NORMAL PROCESS AND SHE SAID SHE WON'T DO IT AGAIN. ",
  "SOLUTION": "I COPIED CL.ADJUST.OUTPUT TO CL.ADJUST.OUTPUT.D083005. I THEN DELETED ALL OF THE RECORDS FROM CL.ADJUST.OUTPUT. ASKED THAT CL$$R700 BE RUN AND THEN RESTARTED FROM THE TOP. IT RAN SUCCESSFULLY. IF CL.ADJUST.UPLOAD IS BAD, WE CAN BYPASS IT. SEPARATE ACCOUNTS DOES NOT NEED TO BE NOTIFIED AT NIGHT, WE CAN NOTIFY THEM IN THE MORNING. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0730",
  "PROBLEM": "RECEIVED S0C7 ABEND BECAUSE CL$$0700 HAD NOT COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB WAS RELEASED THE CL$$R700 COMPLETED (THIS HAS BEEN CORRECTED). ",
  "SOLUTION": "AFTER CL$$0700 COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY, HAD JOB RERUN FROM THE TOP. JOB COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$I000",
  "PROBLEM": "VARIES ",
  "ANALYSIS": "VARIES - DEPENDING UPON WHERE THE ERROR OCCURED. WILL NEED TO REVIEW THE SESSION LOG. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CONTACT DOREEN KLOMSTAD OR LINDA PRAED TO FIX PROBLEM AND RESTART THE WORKFLOW "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0600",
  "PROBLEM": "RECEIVED U0046 ABEND BECAUSE CL$$0600 HAD NOT COMPLETED SUCCESSFULLY. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "STEP0050, WHICH IS THE SORT STEP ABENDED WITH U0046. SYSOUT OF STEP0050 SHOWED -- SORT CAPACITY EXCEEDED. ",
  "SOLUTION": "CHECKED WHETHER CL.CL$$0600.AGENT.REL.SORTED IS CATALOGED OR NOT. IF THE FILE IS CATALOGED THEN DELETE IT. ASK PCD TO RESTART THE JOB FROM STEP0050. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0030",
  "PROBLEM": "CL$$0030 ENDED UNSUCCESSFULLY WITH RC=12 IN SEP0192. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JESYSMSG SHOWED SPACE ABEND SB37 FOR QSAM1. ",
  "SOLUTION": "ASKED PCD TO RUN THE RESTORE JOBS CL$$R030 CL$$RCL2 CL$$R017 ASKED PCD TO RUN CL$$0017 FROM THE TOP ASKED PCD TO RUN THE CL$$0030 FROM THE TOP WITH THE FOLLOWING OVERRIDE(INCREASED SPACE OF FILE) \/\/STEP0192.QSAM1 DD DSN=&PREFIX.ACT.BKUP(+1), \/\/ DISP=(NEW,CATLG,DELETE), \/\/ UNIT=&DISK, \/\/ SPACE=(CYL,(500,500),RLSE), \/\/ DCB=(MODELDCB,RECFM=VB,BLKSIZE=23200) "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0040",
  "PROBLEM": "ABEND IN CL$$0030 TOOK LONG TIME TO GET RESOLVED. CL$$0103 WAS IN WAIT CONDITION AND WE WERE ANITICIPATING AN ABEND IN CL$$0040 TOO. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "WE HAD A TALK WITH DAVID AND CL$$0040 WAS FORCE COMPLETED TO KICK OFF THE MV(CL$$0103).JOB CL$$0105 WAS PUT ON HOLD. ONCE CL$$0103 ENDED OK, THEN CL$$0040 WAS RELEASED WITH FOLLOWING OVERRIDE(USING SI FILES FOR PENDING AND AUXSEG2) \/\/STEP0170.VSAM4 DD DSN=CL.SI.VSAM.BASEOL.PENDING \/\/STEP0170.FVDSEG2 DD DSN=CL.SI.VSAM.BASEOL.AUXSEG2 ALSO, ANTICIPATING A SPACE ABEND BECAUSE OF ACTIVITY FILE ADDED FOLLOWING OVERRIDES TO CL$$0040 \/\/STEP0120.SEQUEN3 DD DSN=&&TEMP, \/\/ DISP=(NEW,PASS,KEEP), \/\/ UNIT=SYSDA, \/\/ SPACE=(CYL,(500,300),RLSE), \/\/ DCB=(RECFM=VB,BLKSIZE=9076) \/\/* \/\/STEP0150.SORTOUT DD DSN=&&TEMP2, \/\/ DISP=(NEW,PASS,KEEP), \/\/ UNIT=SYSDA, \/\/ SPACE=(CYL,(500,300),RLSE), \/\/ DCB=(RECFM=VB,BLKSIZE=9076) CL$$0040 AGAIN ABENDED WITH A SPACE PROBLEM IN STEP0160 FOR SEQUEN8 DATASET. ASKED PCD TO ADD ONE MORE OVERRIDE SHOWN AS BELOW - \/\/STEP0160.SEQUEN8 DD DSN=&&STATS, \/\/ DISP=(NEW,PASS,KEEP), \/\/ UNIT=&DISK, \/\/ SPACE=(CYL,(500,100),RLSE,,ROUND), \/\/ DCB=(RECFM=VB,BLKSIZE=9076) FINALLY JOB WENT DOWN IN STEP0380 ABEND=S000 U0999 WE FORCE COMPLETED THE JOB AND MOVED ON IN ORDER TO GET CYCLE COMPLETED AND MAKE TRADES. STEP0380 AND STEP0390 BOTH PRODUCE REPORTS. STEP0380 PGM=CKOA11 TERMINAL USAGE REPORT STEP=STEP0390 PGM=GOMIBUTL PRINT MIB ERROR REPORT ",
  "SOLUTION": "THE PROBLEM IS COMING FROM CKVPMMVC WHICH ISTRYING TO DO A DATE CONVERSION ON EXTRA LIFE(03) SEGMENT CEASE DATE. THERE ARE MULTIPLE 03 SEGMENTS ON THIS POLICY WITHOUT HAVING A CEASE DATE WHICH APPEARS TO BE THE PROBLEM. 03 0058 00000000 00000000 102 6 0 00 1 00\/00\/1900 E .00 .00 .00 00\/00\/1900 00\/00\/1900 03 0058 00000000 00000000 102 5 0 00 1 00\/00\/1900 E .00 .00 .00 00\/00\/1900 00\/00\/1900 03 0058 00000000 10000000 2 5 0 00 1 00\/00\/1900 E .00 .00 .00 00\/00\/1900 08\/20\/2011 03 0058 00000000 10000000 2 6 0 00 1 00\/00\/1900 E .00 .00 .00 00\/00\/1900 08\/20\/2011 03 0058 00000000 00100000 1 6 0 00 1 02\/03\/2032 1 0 E .00 .00 .00 02\/03\/2032 02\/03\/2012 03 0058 00000000 00100000 1 5 0 00 1 02\/03\/2032 1 0 E .00 .00 .00 02\/03\/2032 02\/03\/2012 SOLUTION: SKIP THE POLICY AND RESTART THE JOB. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0103",
  "PROBLEM": "S04C 0356 2 AP0356 - FILE DATES ARE INCONSISTENT >>>> DATECNTL\/PARMDATE IS LAST BATCH CYCLE <<<<< SEVERE ERROR - RUN ABORTED FOR THIS USER ",
  "ANALYSIS": "ALTHOUGH THE FILE DATES WERE CORRECT, THE JOB ABENDED DUE TO FOLLOWING \"IF\" STATEMENT INSIDE PROGRAM CKUBMC0F - CL3739 IF UBRUNDAT-RUN-DATE = FFFLODTE-LAST-OFFLINE-DATE ",
  "SOLUTION": "ON ANALYZING FOUND THAT ABOVE \"IF\" STATEMENT SHOULD CHECK LEAP DAY INDICATOR ALONG WITH THE ACTUAL DATE. DISCUSSED THE PROBLEM WITH BILL AND PROPOSED FOLLOWING CHANGED IN THE PROGRAM - CL3739*TESTIF UBRUNDAT-RUN-DATE = FFFLODTE-LAST-OFFLINE-DATE *TEST IF (UBRUNDAT-RUN-DATE = FFFLODTE-LAST-OFFLINE-DATE) *TEST AND (UBRUNLPD-RUN-DATE-LEAP-IND = *TEST FFFLODLI-LAST-OFFLN-LEAP-IND) (1) THE MODIFIED PROGRAM IS PRESENT AT FOLLOWING LOCATION WITH \"*TEST\" TAG - PAN.CL.DPANLIB(CKUBMC0FAB) (2) COMPILED THE MODIFIED PROGRAM IN - TEST.CL.PROD.OBJLIB (3) LINKED THE MODIFIED PROGRAM WITH CKAP01V LOAD IN - TEST.CL.PROD.LOADLIB (4) GOT THE RESTORE JOBS - CL$$R060 (FILES RESTORE) AND CL$$RCL4 (CLIENT RESTORE) EXECUTED FROM OPS. (5) AS BATCHPAY FILE WAS NOT EMPTY, GOT CL$$0102 JOB RERAN FROM TOP. (6) ASKED OPS TO RERUN CL$$0103 FROM TOP WITH THE LOADLIB OVERRIDE NOTE: THIS PROBLEM WAS BECAUSE OF LEAP YEAR PROCESSING. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "FILE OPEN ERROR ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE JOB IS NOT SET UP CORRECTLY TO RUN IN PRODUCTION. AN IDEA IS BEING SUBMITTED TO REMOVE THE JOB FROM PROD. ",
  "SOLUTION": "HAVE OPERATIONS FORCE JOB COMPLETE - NO FURTHER ACTION NEEDED. "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "IDCPI0837S ENDED NOT OK. MESSAGE IN SYSOUT: UNSUCCESSFUL EXECUTION OF PMCMDSTARTWORKFLOW, RC=3, SEE S:\\INFA\\$SPT\\\\CYBERLIFE\\IDCPI0837S_WF_IDOC_C ANNUITY_SECONDARY_LOAD_XML_20120517112351.LOG FOR MESSAGES ",
  "ANALYSIS": "VIEW INFORMATICA WORKFLOW LOG, HAD FOLLOWING MSG: ERROR: WORKFLOW [WF_IDOC_CL_ANNUITY_SECONDARY_LOAD_XML]: CANNOT RENAME WORKFLOW LOG FILE [S:\\INFA\\WORKFLOWLOGS\\CYBERLIFE\\WF_IDOC_CL_SECONDARY_LOAD_XML.LOG.BI TO ... PLEASE CHECK THE INTEGRATION SERVICE LOG FOR MORE INFORMATION ",
  "SOLUTION": "GENERALLY, WE CAN RERUN THE JOB FROM THE TOP AND IT COMPLETES SUCCESSFULLY. COMPLETED PROJECT FOR PERMANENT SOLUTION, WHICH WAS TO MAKE THE LOG FILE NAME UNIQUE "
 },
 {
  "PROBLEM": "A SYSTEM ABEND 0C7 OCCURRED IN MODULE CKDPFSPS PROGRAM D724DANN AT OFFSETX'E014'. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE PROBLEM POLICY WAS 2650201990.IT HAD AN ISSUE DATE OF 01\/14\/2014 AND THERE WAS NO RATE FOR THE PLAN IN THE INTEREST RATE FILE.THE EARLIEST RATE FOR THE PLAN ON THE FILE IS EFFECTIVE 1\/15\/2012.THE POLICY HAD NO MONEY IN THE FIXED FUND. ",
  "SOLUTION": "1: TAKE BACKUP OF INPUT FILE TEST.CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT(0) & NAME TEST.CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT.D<DATE> [EX. D071211] 2: TO CHECK THE ABENDING POLICY : A) IF POLICY NUMBER PRESENT IN OERROR REPORT IS SAME AS THE CURRENT POLICY NUMBER PRESENT IN IDIREPORT.THEN IT IS THE ABENDING POLICY. B) IF POLICY NUMBER PRESENT IN OERROR REPORT IS DIFFERENT THAN THE CURRENT POLICY NUMBER PRESENT IN IDIREPORT.THEN THE THE ABENDING POLICY IS THE ONE PRESENT IN OERROR REPORT. C) IF POLICY NUMBER IS NOT PRESENT IN OERROR REPORT THEN THE CURRENT POLICY NUMBER PRESENT IN IDIREPORT IS THE ABENDING POLICY. 3: DELETED ALL THE RECORDS OF ABENDING POLICY FROM ORIGINAL FILE TEST.CL.P0020.S0025.SORTOUT(0) 4: REQUESTED OPS TO RESTART THE JOB CL$T0020 FROM STEP0030 WITH FOLLOWING OVERRIDES: UNCOMMENT BELOW LINE \/\/* GDG01='0', AND COMMENT OUT BELOW LINE \/\/ GDG01='+1', --> IMPORTANT NOTE: AS OF 7\/2013 WHEN OVERRIDING 'SEQUEN' IN STEP0030 --> NEED TO ALSO OVERRIDE 'SORTIN' IN STEP0045!! 5: SEND EMAIL TO TRIAGE ABOUT PROBLEM WITH POLICY & ASK THAT POLICY CREATOR FIX POLICY BEFORE RESUBMITTING\/REORDERING. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0103",
  "PROBLEM": "5200504940 SUSPENDED AFTER INT RATE SEGMENT NOT FOUND ERROR. AP0140 - INT RTE SEGMENT FOR REQUESTED PRIOR PRD CODE NOT FOUND ",
  "ANALYSIS": "PAYMENT\/MONEY APPLIED ON THIS POLICY IN APRIL 2015 (04\/07\/15) WITH AN EFFECTIVE DATE (06\/02\/2015) ANNIVERSARY DATE OF THIS POLICY : 06\/02\/2015 WHEN THE POLICY WAS PROCESSED, THE INTEREST RATE FILE WAS HAVING THE LAST\/INT RATE DATE AS 05\/01\/2015. LAST ENTRY IN MAY MONTH INTEREST RATE FILE:- ---------------------- 251101001D99000 1C2C00C0C49C40C ---------------------- X'215C121C' = 05\/01\/2015 AS THE MONEY FOR THIS POLICY WAS APPLIED IN APRIL, THE SEARCH DATE WAS SET AS 04\/01\/2015 ( RATE START DATE FROM 69 SEGMENT). AS PER CKUBINTR PROGRAM LOGIC, THE INTEREST RATE FILE SEGMENT WAS NOT FOUND FOR THE SEARCH DATE 04\/01\/2015, AS IT HAD THE LAST\/LATEST SEGMENT DATE AS 05\/01\/2015, HENCE FAILED WITH INTEREST SEGMENT NOT FOUND ERROR. ",
  "SOLUTION": "SQA TEAM TO REQUEST TO PERFORM FILE MARVEL TO UPDATE THE 69 SEGMENT RATE START DATE FROM 04\/01\/2015 TO 05\/01\/2015, AS THE INTRATES FILES GOT UPDATED AFTER APRIL WITH NEW ENTRY 05\/01\/2015. THE POLICY PROCESSED SUCCESSFULLY WITHOUT ERROR IN NEXT TIME DRIVEN PROCESSING. *******######******** "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0015",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED IN IDIREPRT AND SAW... DATA ITEM . . . . . . . . : BLW=0000+060 AT ADDRESS. . . . . . . : 0E695118 LENGTH. . . . . . . . . : X'1' DATA ITEM STORAGE . . . : 61 *\/* WHEN I SEARCHED FOR THE CURRENT RECORD, I FOUND AS BELOW IN IDIREPRT. CURRENT RECORD. . . . . . : RDW=01930000 RECORD DATA LENGTH 399, HEX EBCDIC ----------------------------------- ------------------ F0F261F1 F161F2F0 F1F64040 404040D7 *02\/11\/2016 P* C5D9E2D6 D5C1D340 40404040 40404040 *ERSONAL * 40C4F5D7 D9E2D6D5 D340F2F0 F1F660F0 * D5PRSONL 2016-0* THE AGENT NUMBER RESIDES RECORDS THAT HAD 02\/11\/2016. THIS OBVIOUSLY WAS INCORRECT. ",
  "SOLUTION": "1.COPIED THE CL.CL$$0015.REPS.SORTED(0) TO TEST FILE. 2. TEST.CL.CL$$0015.REPS.SORTED.D022216, DELETED ALL THE RECORD STARTS WITH 02\/11\/2016 FROM BACKUP TEST FILE. 3. MODIFIED THE JOB IN OVERRIDE LIBRARY TEST.CL.CSC.JCLLIB(CL$$0015) TO HAVE TEST.CL.CL$$0015.REPS.SORTED.D022216 FILE AS INPUT IN THE STEPS STEP0040, STEP0050 AND STEP0060. 4. AS PER RESTART INSTRUCTIONS, EXECUTED THE RESTORE JOB CL$$R015 5. ONCE AFTER COMPLETION OF THE RESTORE JOB , RESTARTED THE ABENDED JOB CL$$0015 FROM STEP0040. 6. THE JOB ENDED OK. THIS IS ALSO NECESSARY FOR JOBS CL$BACF CL$TACF AND CL$MACF AS THEY WENT DOWN ALSO. "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0106",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED IN IDIREPRT AND SAW... DATA ITEM . . . . . . . . : BLW=0000+060 A USER ABEND 0001 OCCURRED IN MODULE D724ANNV CSECT CKABEND AT OFFSET X'116'. THE ABEND WAS CAUSED BY MACHINE INSTRUCTION 0DEF (BRANCH AND SAVE) IN MODULE D724ANNV CSECT CKETRINV AT OFFSET X'B90'. PROBLEM : THE ERROR ENCOUNTERED WITH CL$$0035 WITH A CLIENT CONTENTION. ",
  "SOLUTION": "1.AS THE JOB WAS ABENDED CLOSE TO 8:00AM EST, WAITED FOR THE DATES CARDS PARMDATE AND PARMPREV CHANGE. 2.THEN RESTARTED THE JOB FROM THE ABENDED STEP STEP0440 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$0860",
  "PROBLEM": "S0C7 ",
  "ANALYSIS": "LOOKED IN SYSPDUMP AND SAW... PROGRAM CHECK HAS OCCURRED. TYPE = 0C7 (DECIMAL DATA) AT LOCATION 0061D0 IN ELEMENT CKUBMVVB PSW = 078D0400 8EA92FF6 EPA=0EA8CE20 OFFSET 0061D0 THE REASON OF THE ABEND WAS THAT THE POLICY WAS TRYING TO PROCESS THE COB FUND AND THERE WAS NO COB RIDER ON THE POLICY, THE COB RIDER HAS THE COB PERIOD WHICH WOULD CAUSE A CALCULATION WITH NULL THE POLICY WAS TRYING TO PROCESS COB FUND AS THERE WAS SOME MANUAL ADJUSTMENTS FOR COST BASIS WAS DONE ON COB FUND INSTEAD OF CASH FUND. THIS CAUSED THE POLICY TO ADD 55 AND 65 VALUES SEGMENT. ABENDING POLICY : 5820028990 THERE ARE FEW MORE POLICIES WHICH CAN ABEND WITH THE SAME ISSUE LIST OF ALL THE POLICIES - 5820112410 5820000990 5820041540 5820115730 5820191300 5820359310 5820028990 ",
  "SOLUTION": "1.COPIED CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT TO TEST.CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT.D060917 AND BYPASS THE ABENDING POLICY 2.PROVIDED THE BELOW OVERRIDES IN THE JOB \/\/STEP0020.SORTIN DD DSN=TEST.CL.CL$$0100.STEP0320.AUDIT.D060917, \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) NOTE - THIS IS A KNOWN PROBLEM TO THE LTC TEAM AND WILL BE HANDLED UNDER LTC CLAIMS PROJECT. MORE DETAILS REGARDING THIS PROBLEM CAN BE LOCATED AT FOLLOWING LOCATION (POINT #11) - K:\\IT WORK\\PROJ00010152 - LONG TERM CARE CLAIMS\\ANNUITY CARE\\ANALYSIS\\ PRODUCTION PROBLEMS RELATED WITH ANNUITY CARE 1 AND 2 PRODUCTS "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$DW60",
  "PROBLEM": "JOB CL$$DW60 WAS LOOPING. ",
  "ANALYSIS": "THE FIELD SEQUENCE NUMBER (WS-SEG-SEQ) BEING DEFINED AS S9(3) COMP-3 AND POLICY#5200333470 CONTAINED NEARLY 1540 '75' SEGMENTS. THIS MADE THE JOB TO LOOP. LOOPING ELEMENTS - CKULDBEN (IN CL$$DW60) AND CKDFFRAM (IN ONLINE). ",
  "SOLUTION": "WE HAVE CHANGED THE FIELDS FOR SEQUENCE NUMBER FROM S9(3) COMP-3 TO S9(5) COMP-3 IN CKULDBEN AND FROM PL2 TO PL3 IN CKDFFRAM. FURTHER ANALYSIS: TWO MORE POLICIES FOUND WITH MORE NUMBER OF 75 SEGMENTS. - 1000779612 - 1000782392 "
 },
 {
  "JOB_NAME": "CL$$1400",
  "PROBLEM": "- CL$$1400 FAILED WITH ABEND S2F3 AT STEP0020 AS PER INITIAL ",
  "ANALYSIS": "JOB SEEMS TO BE ABENDED WITH VIRTUAL STORAGE, SO WE CONTACTED COG INFRA TEAM AND THEY TOLD US PUT REGION PARAMETER IN PROC STEP, BUT IT DID NOT WORKED AND JOB ABENDED AGAIN. AFTER THAT WE TRIED TO BYPASS POLICY FROM INPUT FILE OF STEP0020 BUT JOB WENT TO HOLD AND LATER ABENDED WITH SAME REASON. BUT WHEN WE TRIED TO RUN STEP0020 IN UNIT IT RAN SUCCESSFULLY SOMEHOW. ",
  "SOLUTION": "- RAN STEP0020 IN UNIT REGION, IT ENDED FINE. - SAVED OUTPUT SO THAT IT CAN BE USED IN PROD JOB AS INPUT - GIVEN OVERRIDE IN STEP0030 AND RESTART PARAMETER FOR STEP0030 IN PROD.SCHD.IND.CALLOUT \/\/* \/\/STEP0030.SORTIN DD DSN=TEST.CL.PROXY.WEEKLY.EXTRACT.UNSORTED, \/\/ DISP=(SHR,KEEP,KEEP) \/\/* - ASKED OPS TO RERUN THE FAILED FROM THE ABOVE-MENTIONED LIBRARY. JOB EXECUTED SUCCESSFULLY. - RAISED INCIDENTTASK FOR COG INFRA TEAM TO DETEMINE REASON FOR THIS BEHAVIOUR. "
 }
]